Here lives a girl who dreams to become a ringmaster.
Narrator
Omaru Polka
Hello? This is Omaru.
What? You're serious?
I...
made it into Hololive's fifth generation?
Yay!
Good morning.
Good morning!
Are you nervous?
Today's my debut stream, so yeah I'm really nervous.
This'll be my first stage appearance outside of the circus.
What do you have in your hand?
This?
I'm just drinking my afternoon tea first thing in the morning.
Afternoon tea even though it's the morning!
Afternoon tea, even though it's the morning.
So, listen.
Omaru Polka's been tweeting quite a bit in English and Chinese!
But!
In reality,
I've been using Google Translate!
Please forgive me!
So I went and Google Translated how I'd explain this, too.
For those in other countries,
please listen to my Hyper Super English.
(I cannot speak much English.)
私は英語であんまり喋れない
(That is all.)
です。
Come on! Light up! It's showtime!
Time for the Polka Circus!
I brought a lot of instruments for today.
So um, when I was talking with
the other fifth gen girls,
they told me to stop because it was making them anxious.
They told me to stop.
Why?
It's such a nice melody!
They told me to stick to C and D notes, but that's hard...
Oh, this one's wood.
I brought the "I like this" Amazon-chan I drew!
This.
I like this.
I am Omaru Polka!
I'm one-fourths fennec fox, I believe.
I've been told that my grandfather was a fennec, apparently.
Years?
Age?
Why's there a field for age?
Why's there a field for age...?
I guess humans do keep track of their age.
But, well, I can't bring it up here.
It's a secret for now!
I'll let you guys know eventually! Wait.
I'd prefer it if that day never came.
Okay! Dislikes!
Humidity! I hate it when it's muggy!
That rainy season we just had was so awful!
Someone tell the Earth to get its act together!
Also, gravity! This sucks, too!
The Earth is hopeless!
Let's go to the moon.
Also, explaining things.
I suck at it.
Favourite games.
The main thing I want you to know—
The main thing
I want you to know is that
I suck at games.
Wait, but this is a spoiler.
Either way, I'm awful at games.
But I like simulation games and free games—
These are so nice.
I like those games you can finish in one go.
My favourite anime and manga include
Aikatsu! and everything in between Pretty Rhythm and Pri-chan.
Girls of any age like games made for little girls.
Er, I mean anime, not games.
Well, I guess they were originally games anyway.
Yuru Camp!
Why is Yuru Camp so enjoyable?
No matter how many times
one watches it,
Yuru Camp is enjoyable.
So, Hunter × Hunter has
a synapse—
Not synapse. I'm looking for a similar but different word.
Um, it has a character with
a close synergy
to me.
But I read it a long time ago.
I love it, but, how do I say this?
You can't help but forget stuff you've read in the past, right?
It's the same with JoJo, too.
JoJo is—oh, I like JoJo Part 6.
Wait! Stop talking about my age!
Why are you bringing that up while this kid hasn't finished the topic?!
Songs!
I really love idol songs.
Yeah, like Dear☆Stage.
ASMR...
What'll I do here?
What'll I do?
The weird late night me wrote this, I'm sure.
Am I gonna do ASMR?
I-I'm Omaru Polka.
Um, I'm Omaru Polka.
Are you there?
I've come to collect your money.
What shall I do?
Come closer?
What do I do for these?
Someone help!
What do I do?
Super intimate distance? OK, leave it to me.
Snap it! Now!
Kodak Moment! Yeah!
3! 2! 1!
This is my angry face.
And
this one is...
Wait, this one's also my angry face.
Give me a sec.
My troubled face.
Huh? Why not?
And this—
This is my surprised face!
That one expression that everyone says looks as high as a kite!
The one Watame-senpai always uses!
To all the viewers watching from outside of Japan:
Let's see.
(Thank you for your watching!)
見てくれてありがとう！
(T—Like you so much! Thank you!)
あ…君のことすきです！ありがとう！
(You made me so happy! I love you!)
とっても嬉しいです！大好き！
(I will read through your comments.)
コメントはしっかり読みますね。
(Hope you will like me more.)
私のことをもっと好きになって欲しい。
(Welcome to my channel!)
私のチャンネルにようこそ！
(Please make yourself comfortable.)
どうぞお平らに。
(That is all.)
です。
M-Maybe that was a bit too hard for me.
(YAGOO CUTE!)
YAGOOかわいい！
(YAGOO IS BEST GIRL!)
YAGOOは世界一の女！
I'm sure that many of you have mixed feelings
after hearing that Hololive was getting new girls
after such a long time, but...
Whatever has been born has been born,
so please be sure to cherish them.
Subscribe to Omaru Polka if you liked this!
↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓
As a part of Hololive's fifth generation,
please look forward to all of our activities!
Thanks for sticking with me! Thank you!