good morning~
good
good morn
good morning~
Today, you guys have been, like,
"This is gonna be over in a flash,"
"She'll only last a minute,"
And just commenting whatever comes to your head...
"You should read super chats in advance."
Are you making fun of me?!
So like, I haven't practiced for today,
But I'm wholeheartedly going to play with caution today.
Wholeheartedly!
I want to keep at it for an hour.
I want to last an hour, so I'll give it my all.
Well, I have another stream at 1 AM today, too.
So like, uh... Y'know?
Y'know, I've got some waywaylee...
Waywaylee.
Like, even if I end this stream immediately,
even if it's over quickly, it's fine in the long run.
Okay?
With that out of the way...
Gimme a sec.
The usual.
Looking good. How about you guys raise a ruckus while I wait?
Raise a ruckus while you still can.
Gimme a sec, I'll read your comments.
Alright.
Oh, wait, this is...
Oh nononono yo!
Oh it's over here.
Ah nonono.
Select Load and open this one?
It's this one, right?
January 25...yup, this one.
"Good morning, this is rare!"
Let's go!
Wait,
Wait! Wait!
Wait a minute!
Wait!
W-w-wait a minute,
Wait...
Why?
What do I do? (x3)
Stop! Stop!
It's gonna be over!
It'll be over! Hey!
No...
But [gibberish]
Do this...
Wait, I can get past using this. (x3)
Wait for it.
Wait for it. (x4)
No! No! I don't want it to end!
There!
That was close. (x3)
These guys...
Wait! I hate this!
No!
Come on! This is futile!
What do I do? (x3)
Hold up. What do I do? (x7)
What do I do? (x4) Hold up.
There's one over there, too.
Gimme a sec. After it shoots...
After it shoots...
There!
You're kidding me.
Hold on.
How high can I jump...?
Nooooooooo!!!!!!!!