"Pekora's kind at heart, isn't she?"
That's right.
I'm actually very kind.
Which one should I read next...
A ton of elaborate entries sure came in this time...
Let's go with a crazy one.
"Pekello! I heard that I need to look like Pekora-chan
in order to get into Pekoland,
so I put on a school swimsuit and bunny ears,
but they didn't let me through!"
"Whatever was I missing?"
Brain cells!
Alright, next.
Subscribe to Usada Pekora if you liked this!
↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓
"Do you not have any friends?"
Buddy, you just crossed the line.
This dude just crossed the line of what is and is not acceptable to say!
"No friends" dude, you looking for a fight?
I dare you to say that to someone's face.