Subscribe to Murasaki Shion if you liked this!
↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓
Wait, I can't get out.
What's going on?
I can't get out at all.
Can I get out like this? Oh, nope...
I'm totally stuck!
This is hopeless.
It's no use!
Can I ask for help?
Guide/Settings
Add Player
Return to Lab
Guide/Settings
Add Player
Return to Lab
Guide/Settings
Dang, I have no idea how to ask for help.
Thanks!
Wait, not that one.
Over here!
I guess I didn't have to call them.
Huh?! Wait a sec!
Save me! Save me!
Somebody save me!
Someone save me~
Help!
Oh, it's this one!
All I've been doing is asking for help.
Can't even bring out the other Luigi.
It's over for me.
Help!
Nobody's coming to save me!
Come on...
Come on!
Somebody come rescue me!
How'd I get out earlier?
Whoa! Somebody came!
Thank you!
I'm free.
My nose is runny.
Now then.