Sorry, this...
I always just talk about Beyblades when letting myself unwind...
Yeah...
They're just amazing!
I'm telling you!
Like the one that has a loaded spring...
Um..
There's a spring loaded into the collision area
and when it collides, it abruptly shrinks
like BAM! it bursts open.
I really love how they come up with all these mechanisms.
I just ended up chatting away again.
I always just talk about things I like.
But all of you guys...
gladly listen to me, don't you.
How do I put this...
Yeah, I guess we're slowly...
nearing the end of today's stream.
Talked for an hour, after all.
I'd probably keep talking at this rate...
Right?
Seems like a good spot to end the stream...
Well,
Back to the earlier topic—well, not back to, but...
Really, hanging out with everyone like this...
To those who discovered me,
to those who cheer me on
and come to watch me and do lots of things for me,
I am really, truly grateful.
I really...
love all of you.
I guess, if I don't put those feelings into words, then people would have a hard time knowing.
I figured I should today,
since it's been a while since
I've streamed like this, and on a Monday, too.
This gave me a chance to just relax,
take a breather and chat.
So, yeah... I figured I'd just talk about everything I've been thinking.
I love each and every one of you.
And because of that—
and I know this worries many of you—
and because of that,
I've been streaming a lot.
It's really fun hanging out with everyone.
Why'd you bring that up?
Enough with the love-love-forever!
Um...
Thanks as always.
I love you.
I'm really thankful to you.
How'd this conversation end up so glum?
Huh? What's with this gloomy mood?
I wonder why...
Well, with that said.
Let's wrap things up here
and end the stream.
Okay.
Yeah. Please continue to support...
Holostars, HoloPro, and other VTubers...
and really, anyone you're a fan of.
Something like that.
Yeah...
Please keep supporting them.
And with that,
I think it's time for today's chatting stream to come to a close.
Okay, everyone,
Time for our Nail ya later!
Get ready!
Ready, set...
Nail ya later~!
Bye bye.