Soap Opera
Blossoms
Cherry
&
Bread
See You
Next Time
Be sure to subscribe to Inugami Korone and Sakura Miko!
Soap Opera
Cherry
Blossoms
&
Bread
Cast
Manager, his Early Years
Soap Opera
Cherry
Blossoms
&
Bread
Sakuramiya Mikoo
Koromi the Baker
Barako
Soap Opera
Cherry
Blossoms
&
Bread
ACT I
Soap Opera
Cherry
Blossoms
&
Bread
So heavy.
Working at a bakery is so hard.
I'm beat...
Why am I so exhausted?
Why do I have to work this hard?
I don't want to do this anymore.
Korone-chan?
Manager!
Working?
Good morning.
Yes, I'm working my hardest.
You do shine brightest when you give it your all.
Okay. I'll keep doing my best.
This isn't good. None of this is good.
Why am I work—
Ah! I'll keep doing my best.
I'll keep doing my best.
If anything's on your mind, I'm all ears.
Well...
Never mind.
I'll do my best.
Alright, then I'm going back to my papers.
Okay.
Every single day I kee—who was that?
Every single day, I keep going through the same motions
with enjoyment nowhere to be found.
This is the boring life that I, Koromi, live.
Tinkle tinkle.
Welco—
I hope this shop has some decent bread.
I can't believe it...
Excuse me?
Hm?
You're—
I knew it. I'm Koromi, do you remember me?
Oh, I remember you.
Koromi—
Right, I haven't seen you since middle school.
So it really was you.
Wow, so you ended up working here, huh?
Yeah...
But, I keep getting cracked skin all over—
I wash dishes, I bake bread, all while my skin cracks...
Everything's cracked, even the skin on my fingers.
Oh yeah? Show them to me.
Over here, see?
*lick*
W-wait a minute!
Sorry.
The cracks are gone...
This is strange. We haven't seen each other in ages,
yet it feels like we're so close.
Would you like to take this
freshly baked French bread for lunch?
Huh? Can I?
Yes.
T-Thank you.
Oh, but look at the time.
I need to get back to work.
Unfortunately, I can't bring that back into the office.
Why'd you come to this bakery?
Uh...
Why'd you stop by?
My boss said he loves this bakery.
I see, so you just came to check it out...
What's wrong?
Oh, I'm sorry...
Is there something on my face?
I was just thinking your face was a bit big...
What?
Don't worry about it.
Will I see you again?
I'm not sure. It sure would be nice to, though...
That face sure was something.
He really is as nice as I thought.
And to top it off,
he's way more attractive now than he was in middle school.
So handsome...
But I'm just an obscu—
I'm just an ordinary person working at an ordinary bakery.
He's beyond my league.
Tinkle tinkle tinkle.
Welcome!
I tried so hard to get here quickly...
Huh?
Hello.
Mikoo-san isn't here!
Mikoo-san?
Do you know him?
What's with you?
Um, I mean, he just stopped by a moment ago
but had to rush back to the office.
Is there something between you and Mikoo?
Oh, no! He just licked my finger earl—
Wait, that's not—
What?
That's not what—
That's not it!
"Licked my finger"?
No! Um...
What?
He was like, "That bread looks tasty."
But then he licked my finger and...
What?!
He just licked it by accident.
We hardly know each other.
I think he just mixed up my finger and the French bread,
I see...
and licked it.
I suppose he does have a habit of doing things like that.
Right...
I'm married to him.
Huh?
Oh! The finger on that ring finger. Rin—
The finger...
The ring on your ring finger...
See this?
I can.
This.
Yes.
Of course...
Do you see this?
Don't worry, I see it.
Of course.
So, don't think of doing anything fishy with him.
I'm not thinking like that!
Really?
Gimme a sec.
Um...
Really?
Would you like to take this French bread
back for lunch?
I don't eat such cheap bread.
It's for free, so please try taking it home to have a taste.
You can share it with your husband, too.
I'm sure the bread someone like you makes is delicious.
But it's not the kind of bread that's meant for our mouths.
We're part of the upper class.
So you're rich?
Correct.
In that case, this bread is ten thousand yen.
Ten thousand yen?
This bread actually costs ten thousand yen. Will you buy it?
Really?
It's high quality.
The wheat flour used is some of the best.
Oh? Tell me more.
So wheat flour is usually made from wheat, right?
Sure.
But this...this is made from breadcrumbs.
What?
Breadcrumbs come from bread, right?
Wait, don't you make bread from breadcrumbs?
Bread...Bread is usually made from wheat.
I see.
Right.
But this was made by collecting breadcrumbs from bread
to bake into bread.
It's as bread as you can get.
Alright, if you're willing to say that much...
You want money, right?
I'm sure someone as poor as you wants money.
That's—
I'll give you some. Here.
Here! Here, here!
That's not the point!
Why thank you.
Anyway, I'm a busy woman. I'm leaving, okay?
Thank you.
Wait, what about the bread?
Won't you take it with you?
I don't want bread baked by your hands.
I'll see myself out.
I wonder where Mikoo-san went?
How did someone like her
get to marry Mikoo-san?
A Q&A session played itself out in Koromi's inner thoughts.
She pondered that question endlessly.