[35P actually show in the back for a few seconds at 00:02:09]
What do you think?
Am i cute?
How's this?
Or this?
Is this good?
How is it?
Mmh?
I...
really don't know what poses could be good.
Here's me imitating a crying person.
Here I go.
I'm so sorry!
I'll compensate you with my whole life!
Ok, that's the usual deal.
I use that to make people not get mad at me.
What kind of face should I go for?
Oh? You want some, huh???
Hey, you. Yeah, you. Come on.
Get your face over here!
F*ck you!!!
Is this ok to say?
Sh*t!
You are die!
You die!
Me? Me? Me?
Oh, Me [is] lovely, Elite Miko!
Thank you!!!
Thank you, World 35P!!!
Ok, and with that!
I believe you guys already took a lot of screenshots so,
I want to go to the next corner
Next corner is!
The one you've been looking forward to!
The guests!
I'm really looking forward to it too so!
Shall I go to that place?
Ok. Let's change places to!
Hololive's office!
And so!
This is Hololive.
This is Hololive's office.
And uhhh...
That!
So many of those boxes came to my house!!!
So many!!!
Thank you so much for all your gifts!!!
And this is the place where me and the other members spend our days.
This is the place~
And so...
[The place that keeps blowing up!]
Yeah a lot of accidents happen over there but...
Well if I were to say,
This is where our managers and Yagoo work until their eyes turn white to clean up our messes.
Yeah.
[Accident scene]
Yeah, this is the crime scene.
So...
I'll explain the what this next corner is about.
The next corner is...!
"I'm today's protagonist~! Now waiting for praise callers"
Yeah!
You know... This time...
Well, to just ask people directly to compliment me...
That's something I usually can't bring myself to do, to be honest.
So now I called the members that also won't say it directly.
Umm...
Well, maybe you could call them Hololive's wildcards...
Maybe "the trouble makers"...
Or just girls who can't be honest.
Like...
Let's say, someone who keeps saying she'll beat me up...
Or one that always uses her butt hook on me...
Well, I gathered these very well known personalities from Hololive and...
They are here today so...
We are going to get into a call and really just...
Maybe they'll say things they like about me,
Or maybe my good points...
Wonder if they'll really praise me.
But of course they will.
I'm today's protagonist after all.
Because today's my birthday.
I'm the king.
So, We shall start now!!!
So, there'll be 6 people in total, I think.
I called 6 people so I should call the first one.
Wonder who will be first~
Who do you think?
First is...
Someone among Hololive that really has this...
This...
BANG aura to her.
Like that...
Goes, "Good morning!!!"...
Will, she call~?
Will she~?
I'll wait.
Wait, the calendar there is still December’s...
What happened with-
+Paisen!!!
Oh?! Chairman!!!
+Pa- Pa- Pa- Pa- Pa- Pa- Pa- Pa- Pa- Pa- Pa- Paisen!!!
Cha- Cha- Cha- Cha- Cha- Cha- Cha- Cha- Cha- Cha- Chairman!!!
And so, the first caller is, Kiryu Coco, Chairman!
+Kiryu Coco's here! Yay!!!
Chairman! Thank you for always helping me in Ark, really.
+Miko-paisen, who would've even imagined, you out of everyone, would get suck this damn hard into the addiction path...
Yeah, I wasn't expecting it either but...
Just, at some point, it turned into my daily routine... it basically became my life. I'm really thankful.
+"Turned into my daily routine and then my life"?! Wise words have been spoken!
Yeah.
Thank you so much!
And with that, she's 4th's gen bigger trouble maker, Coco Chairman.
So...
Umm, did you know today's my birthday?
+Oh, But of course I know!
Really?
+Happy birthday, Miko-paisen!!!
Thank you so much! It really made me happy that you even talked about it in Asacoco! Thank you so much!
And so...
+Yes?
Is there any good points, or anything that you like about me that you would like to... you could tell me?
+Good points?
Yeah
+If we talk about you, I'm always... Uh, I think you call your late night streams mikodrones, right?
TL note: Play on words that originated from Shachiku (corporate drone) and became Mikochiku (mikodrones)
I'm always monitoring them and...
Huh? You're monitoring me?
+No matter when I get on there's always such great news material.
+Really helps a lot!
Does it... really? Now that I think about it, as soon as I have trouble in game
you always show up in the comments... so that was the reason?
+Exactly!
+I can always watch you in the middle of the night while spacing out and I won't have a clue of anything you are saying. It's the best!
Not a clu- Is... is that a compliment? Is that...
+I say it with love.
Oh, I see! With love! Love, right! Right!
I'm really happy! ...really happy.
I'm always listening, and it feels like
+"Ahh, I have no idea what she's saying but it kinda seems like it's so calming, I think!"
+That's how I always feel while watching!
Uh... you're complimenting me, right?
+Sure I am~!
Ah! uhh... Tha- thank you so much! I also always watch your show! Asacoco! I watch it daily!
+Thanks! Makes me happy!
I'm always amazed at how you do it! Thank you so much for that!
+Thank you for always letting me use the jokes about you!
Oh, yeah.
Uhh, Right... you are always like "Oh, Miko-senpai is ok, she's won't mind this"
+I also do think of you as Free Material.
Yeah, you said that! You said that before! You said that while we were in a call!
That made me go "Uhh... uhh... o- ok..." That's all I could say!
But, still. But, still! Thank you so much for always making fun streams.
Glad to be part of them!
+That's how it is. And Is it... is it really ok for me to praise you this badly on your birthday?
It's ok! I have thick skin!
So! How about next time, what do you say we play Yakuza or Ark together!!!
+Oh! Can I go to your place?
Sure, you can. But my place is a bit... you know... you won't mind?
Somethings are just, you know... It's basically an Otaku room so...
+Don't mind at all!
If that's the case, then come whenever you want!
+Nice! I'll be waiting for our collab!
Let's do it!
+And with that I'll be leaving for now!
Thank you!
And so that was Chairman.
She praised me... right... I think... she did, right?
Did... she?
Yeah, she did. She praised me so let's go right to the next one.
Next is!
Well, someone I have a connection to...
Someone who's become more popular lately, right.
And personally, I want to beat her, I TRULY want to beat her.
She basically makes me feel that way every time...
Now then-!
^Dododododo
Ah-
Dododododo
^Happy...
Good eve-dododo!!!
^Birthday!!!
Thank you!!!
And so, the second guest is Watame!
^Butt hook! Tsunomaki Watame, here!
You...
Don't you "But hook!" in here!
You don't know how scared I was that time!
^[00:24:12]
Seriously my mind just went "Is this a bug? Is this a b- Oh no, the lava! Ah, so this is how I die..."
I really thought that! I was already prepared to die...
^I just thought "Oh, I caught something..."
What do you mean "Caught"! Do you even know what I was feeling in that moment!
You better watch your back on the 7th! I'll use the butt hook on you!
[Date of the Ark Lava cave raid]
^I'm practicing to get better with it too.
She really is! She's gotten better at using it as a butt hook!
For those of you that don't know, every morning starting at 5:45,
Watame premiers a new a 10 minute video called Watame's Song Corner.(Watame no Uta)
It's her morning show where you will always get to listen to her singing,
play Rock-Paper-Scissors against her and hear a special comment of the day.
And so, since I'm always doing late night streams, at the end of my streams
I'll always do a live reaction of them and play janken Rock-Paper-Scissors against her but...
The thing is... you know, for some strange reason... I can never win...
^You suck at Rock-Paper-Scissors so much
Hey! Remember I'm today's protagonist!
Very well, so today...
Specially for that Watame-chan that loves to use her butt hook on me or to taunt me on Rock-Paper-Scissors,
I prepared this! "Praise caller"!
Where you can tell me all the things you like about me or the good points you see in me.
An opportunity I give to leave the past conflicts in the past.
^I see! But instead of that how about we play Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Oh, you want go? Nice!
I'm all for it
You want to go?!
I'm ready! I'm always ready! I'm...
I was already getting anxious just talking to you like this.
^I'll praise you if you win.
^Let's go
OK.
Hold on, let me just...
Ok, I see.
I see, ok.
I'm ready.
Here I go!
^Let's go
Tsunomaki Tsunomaki
Tsunomaki Rock-Paper-Scissors
^Rock!
Hold on, I ripped my earphone off.
Hold on...
What was it? What did she use? Did I win?
^I used paper.
I lost?
Did I lose?!
Did I really lose?!
You serious?!
^You suck!!!
Nooo! Why does this have to happen even on my birthday!?
^You should've won... I had even planned to say "I let you win this time, since today's your Birthday "
You should've let me! This was supposed to be for that!
Why did you win?!
Why?!
^We can leave it at "you just simply suck in Rock-Paper-Scissors"
Basically it...
But, I'll definitely win next time!
That way Watame's Song Corner can keep going on forever!
^It will!
And so that was Wata... Watame...
Wait, did she praise me?
^Wait...
^I didn't...
^Let's collab soon!
Well, you'll praise me when I beat you, right!
Yeah!
^Yeah!
Let's do it!
See you!!!
^See you!!!
Umm... I was supposed to wait for praise callers, right?
We just played Rock-Paper-Scissors.
We played and I lost...
This is weird...
Why?
Very well, I want to call the third one!
The third person is... basically a little brat.
Whenever we meet in collabs she is just a little brat.
Makes fun of me or just laughs with that smug smile.
She's cute though... She is...
And because of that I'm really looking forward to see if that little brat will praise me
So! Here's the third caller!
Is this...
[It'll be fine!]
Really?
Who are you talking about?
Who are you talking about, guys!
Who-
Why? What? Who are talking about?
I never said anything...
Never said anything so I don't know what you are talking about.
Oh?
It seems they didn't had the time to get the
It seems like they couldn't get their feelings on line so
For now, let's uh... let's, let's go call the unparalleled-
Hololive's-
I'm calling the woman who's known as Hololive's TNT.
So...
Wonder if she'll pick up?
Will she...?
Uh, Hololive's TNT and... what else could she be known for?
When I think about her I can only see her blowing stuff up with TNT.
Oh, right but ARK as well.
She's the same as me!
She's caused a pandemic in ARK just like me, right!
Yeah!
And on top of that!
Well the 7th I actually became the leader of the 4th squad but...!
before we have fought together so you could say we are "sisters in arms"
She's really cool.
I actually look up to her.
Before, when she was waiting for call-
When she was waiting for callers...
It was sad that she didn't get any callers but...
I was actually planning go be there.
I was properly waiting for her in ARK
I was but... for some reason she never came...
["Waiting for callers", 0 participants]
But I didn't end up with 0 callers!
I learned that If you properly kneel down and prostrate yourself on the ground to ask politely, everyone will come.
I'd love to say it to everyone. Like to Kanatan, and Kanatan, and Kanatan too.
Yeah, I can always go that far.
Just "Please. Sorry for the trouble!"
"??? please?"
I'll never do that live though. Prostrating I mean.
[Sure they really coming?]
She's coming!
Of course she's coming!
She's definitely going to come!
There's just a lot of troubles going on
Don't make me say it.
Really.
People are doing their best to connect the call.
Just some minor troubles
Yeah
[That an excuse?]
Then should we do something while we wait? Don't want to though
Then...
Oh! Got it!
Then let's do gesture games!
Ark gesture game! Try to guess what am I imitating right now?
What was that?
You got it?
Did you?
WOW, Someone got it!
Right answer, Right answer!
Wow! That's amazing!
I can tell you watch me.
Oh, but seems the call connected so I'll call them here.
Hello!
weird...
Hello!!!
Hey, don't get my hopes up, staff!
Don't mess with me!
Made me think they were here!
I thought I could stop doing that!
Come on!
Staff!
...?
Weird...
The- then, should I do another one?
Let's go for one more.
What should I do...
Ok, here I go!
ARK, gestures game!
2 round!
You should know this one.
Can you please not stop the music...
This is embarrassing...
Oh, thank you.
You got it? You got it?
Ahh, you got the flying creature part.
Now pay attention to how it flaps.
It's all on how it does it.
Oh, there's one that got it!
Good answer!
A Quetzal!
By the way, an Argentavis is actually like this.
And a Pteranodon is like this.
It's all in the speed, you see.
You have a long way to go, guys.
That means-
You're not taking your flying creatures seriously.
You have a long way to go, guys.
[Then how about a Griffin?]
Oh, a Griffin is...
Can I do it right?
Here I go.
Just like this.
It's all in the hands, you see.
That's it!
That's how it is~
Now then, let's call the next person.
Hello? Help me.
°Happy-
°Happy Birthday to you~!
To you~
°Chan, chan chan, chan you dummy! ◄
Huh?
°Chan, chan chan, chan you dummy!
°Chan, chan chan, chan Elite dummy!
Huh?
That's not the right one...
°Eh?
Not the right one...
It's not the right one...
°Was that not it? Eh?
It should end with "...Sakura Miko!"
°Oh! Chan, chan chan, chan you dummy!
I told you that's wrong!
°Congratulations!
That's not how it goes!
It doesn't go like that!
°Eh?
"Miko-senpai~"
°Today's your birthday, right?
Yeah, it is! Thank you!
You really helped me there!
°Congratulations-peko! Wait, What do you mean?
I was making time playing ARK gestures game... My heart was about to break...
°You know...
°I would've love to actually let that go on for an hour...
Don't make fun of me!
°Was telling to myself "Let's not go! Let's not go!"
I would've died. I really would've...
°Wondering just, "I can really break her with a full hour of ARK Gestures game, huh."
I won't break!
But let's just leave it at you helped me by just coming here. Thank you...
°No, please. Congratulations! Today you are the protagonist!
°Congratulations!
Thank you, makes me so happy! Thank you!
That's makes blush...
°By the way why are you waiting for callers?
Well, today~
°Should we belittle you?
No- No, no, no! The complete opposite.
°Oh, that's not it-peko? I see...
Today I’d like you to...
°Yes?
Well, you know how we have collabed so many times as PekoMiko...
°Of course-peko!
Right!
°Yeah.
...so could you praise me today?
°Pra- praise you?
°Eh?
I thought maybe you could-
°Oh, So I... I should praise your right? That's how this call works?
Yeah! You should have a lot of good things you see in me or things you like about me, right?
°Come on-Peko, guys. Have you seen for how many months we have been paying together-peko?
Yeah!!! You’ve seen so many good things about me in that time, right!
But of course you have!
°Can I list them all-peko?
Yes! Yes!
Of course you can! Yeah.
°Things Miko-senpai can be praised for:
Yes?
°She has big boobs!
°Yaaay!
That’s not it, right?
°Eh?
That’s just my body..
See, lets say for instance someone goes: “What I like about Pekora are her small boobs! Yaaaaay!”
Then what would you do?
°I'd punch them on the face with my fist-peko.
Well that’s the same with me!!!
It’s exactly the same!
Exactly the same!
There must be something right?
Something more internal...
Something like that.
°Internal...
Right.
°Ah, got one! Sorry for that, senpai!
It's fine, it's fine! Tell me.
°That's right. Today we are supposed to motivate you-peko, right?
Exactly, because I'm the protagonist!
°Protagonist-peko, yeah.
°Right
Yeah, today it's fine if you are honest. / today you can be honest for once.
°I...
Y-yes?
°Ok, I'll be honest-peko.
Ok
°The thing I want to praise you on is!
°Your dumb side!
°Yaaay!
Still not it...
Just not it...
Are you bad-
Badmouthing me?
Badmouthing...
°Is that-?
°But isn't my "dumb" a compliment-peko?
Then you've been praising me all this time?
°Yeah-peko! All the times I went "What a dummy-peko~" "Wow, she's dumb-peko~"
°Those were all compliments-peko.
Is "dumb" even a compliment?
°It is-peko!
Like, "So nice that you are dumb"?
°Yeah, like that's what made you cute-peko.
Oh, So you're saying I'm cute?
°Exactly-peko!
°But seriously!
°Since today is an important day...
Yeah?
°And to be honest seeing the other calls it made me feel a little bad-peko so.
Oh, yes?
°I want to say how I actually feel after spending these past few months with you.
Oh, what will it be!
Yeah?
°You have a dumb side to you-peko, but then you are also actually really reliable.
°So, you know... I feel like being together is always really fun too.
°When the situation calls for it you become really a reliable senior-peko.
°It was like that for the collab we did not too long ago too.
Yeah.
°Like the raid- the desert raid was the same.
°You prepared a lot of things for us.
°And then...
Well I did somethings.
°the moment you went "Pekora! Don't! That's bad!" and a wall comes crashing to the ground. You saved me there-peko!
°Oh, well, yeah. You know, and the timing was amazing, huh.
°Makes you see that PekoMiko are kinda close in its own way.
I see~
°Oh, look! Is- Isn't the next person connecting?
Mmmmh, I see. So you have a cute side too! I see, so that's how you see me.
Makes me really happy! Thank you!
°I really wish you a happy birthday-peko!
°Let's...
°you know, continue the war from time to time!
From time to time is good, let's do it.
°Because I'll beat you to dust.
Ummh... I'll beat you to the ground too!
I've already lost a few times though, [...] you...
°Uh, Yeah! Congrats-peko! See you!
Thanks-peko!
So yeah! That was uh...
We saw that she, uh... that she can also kinda be like that, uh... too. Yeah...
Ok, let's go onto the next one!
Next one!
Next is, the *TNT* from before.
T-T-*TNT*
I'll call her.
Hello?
<Hello?
<You can hear me?
Akutan! Yeah, I can!
<Oh, you can!
Yay!
Miko-Miko-Miko!
Akutan!
<Glad I made it! ...There were a lot of troubles though.
<Is everything ok?
All good! I can hear you!
<Ok!
Yay!
<I was wondering if it was really ok for me to come but,
<Is- is it going ok?
It’s ok, it’s ok.
<Oh, really?
And You know, Akutan, how we...
<wha- wha- what is it?
<What?
You know, how in were in the same squad in Ark.
<Yeah.
<We did.
And lately we have been interacting more too.
<Yeah.
So today, could you- I was wondering if you had any things you like about me or good things you see on me...
<Right, that was what this stream was about, right.
Yeah!!!
Yeah, I was just thinking to myself that you maybe had some.
<Oh, of course, of course, but of course!
<Of course I have some, but... Before that, can I complain about one little thing?
Yeah?
<You see... a few days ago I was waiting for callers to celebrate my 300k subscribers.
Oh, yeah. I... watched that.
<And you are aware that no caller ever came, right?
Well that... I’d like to explain myself here but uh... it’s not what it seems.
<What was it then, you can tell me?
I was actually waiting for you in ARK, you see.
<Oh, yeah, yeah. In ark, Right. So it was just mistake, you say.
I was watching but then you never came so...
Exactly, I was like "Ah... Maybe I got this wrong..."
<I see.
I was even holding a sign saying “I’m waiting for you”
I was hoping you'd come.
<Well, I see. So you are aware there's a victim here of getting no callers at the time, right.
Yeah, you're right. There's one.
<And knowing that, you come up with a "waiting for praise callers" corner,
<but you then call around 6 people before hand and have them be on hold...
<and to top it off you called said victim among them.
<Like, I don't really know about that...
<Are you running away?
<Are you?!
It's just that I- I don't think I could've bear that!
Like, come on, think about it!
There're 2 victims in Hololive already!
After witnessing that hell, I just couldn't... you know!
To be in a celebration stream, in 3D in front of staff, and get 0 callers.
That's just...
It- it's not like I'm scared...
You know, there's that.
I'd be bad for the adults working here, you know.
That's it!
<You go and use that excuse!
<You go and use that! You...!
That's not it!
Hey, wait, this wasn't a call to take complaints!
[Incomprehensible screaming]
<You bastard!
She's scary...
But there's still that!
The ARK cave raid is still happening and..!
We ended up in different squads but... I'm still really counting on you!
I actually really respect you! Really.
<Well I too... And you always stream ARK in the middle of the night, right?
Yes, I do.
<To be honest, I get lonely when I play ARK alone so use your streams for company.
Oh, really?
<So, I hope you keep doing your best.
Oh, then... how about, let's do our best together.
<Let's do it.
Yeah! Let's do our best in ARK!
<BUT I WON'T FORGIVE YOU FOR CALLING ME WHEN I DIDN'T GET ANY CALLER, YOU JERK!!!
HANG UP!!! HANG UP NOW!!!
<HAPPY BIRTHDAY!!! [I had to lower the speed of the video to get this line]
SHE'S GOING CRAZY! SHE'LL BLOW ME UP WITH TNT!
I CAN SEE A ROCKET LAUNCHER! HANG UP ALREADY!
<YOU IDIOT!!! YOU IDIOT!!! YOU ID-
That was a close one...
Got me scared...
Well, uh...
Seems I did mess up, huh.
That was close...
These things can happen too when you take people's praising calls, huh...
That scared me to a different level...
We should treat kindly those people with 0 callers, Ok?
Let's be sure to do it.
And with that, I think probably due to some trouble the last person couldn't connect,
so that will be it for this corner!
That was "Waiting for Praise Callers"!
Thank you everyone! It made me really happy!
Thank you!!!
Now, then...
I'd like to go onto the next corner but...
You guys will probably be really surprised.
Very well. Let's do it.
Let's go to the next corner!
*Where... am I...?
*Just a now I was watching Sakura Miko's Birthday stream, wasn't I...?
*But when I open my eyes all I can see is an open sky...
*Right, this place is...
*This place is ARK...!!!
Miko: Huh? Are you another survivor? Hey! You ok?
Are you ok?
Look, this thing.
Miko: Good thing you respawned here! There aren't many dangerous dinosaurs in this area
so you got real lucky!
Great, right!
*MikoP: OOOOOOOH, MIKO-CHAN IN THE FLESH!!!!!! OH MY GOD, SHE'S SO CUUUUUUUUUUUTE!!!!!!
Eh? Wha- what is this person saying...? Does they know me? And they are naked for some reason...
*Tame her *Introduce yourself
Is this person all right?
Huh?
Did I decided to talk to some crazy person...
Wai- what is it?
Huh?
Hold- why are you looking at me like that?
What is it with those eyes...!?
Are you all right?!
What- What do you want?
Miko: Ouch!!! It hurts!!! What are you doing?! Why are you punching me?! This server is not PVP!!!
Wait!!! It really hurts!!! It hurts!!! Stop!!! Stop it already!
It hurts!!! It hurts!!! It hurts so much!!!
Uwaaaaah!!! HEY! YOU REALLY WANT SOME! HUH?! TAKE THIS!!!
HAVE THIS!!! WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU ARE DOING?! YOU WANT TO FIGHT?!
I HAVE OVER 300 HOURS IN ARK!!! DON'T YOU LOOK DOWN ON ME, NOOB!!!
HAVE THIS!!! AND THAT!!!
*MikoP: Ah-, Sorry...
Oh... O- Ok... It's fine... Don't worry.
I'm sorry too.
*MikoP: So no knock out tame, huh... Then how about an offering to tame her?
Mmh? Something wrong?
*MikoP: Um, Miko-chi, today is your birthday, right? Here have this.
Oh? Yeah, it is!
Oh? What happened?
This is...!
The latest entry from my favorite Eroge series! Thank you! I'm so happy!
Thank you.
*Name the Elite Beautiful Girl:
I'm really happy, you know.
Master?
I'll never leave your side!
It must have been really expensive. It's even the premium edition.
I really love you! You made me so happy!
Oh, what is it?
Something on your mind?
Are you having trouble deciding on something?
*Name the Elite Beautiful Girl: Easy.
*Name the Elite Beautiful Girl:
What happened? can't decide on something?
Can't decide?
But really... and it comes with special content too
Really, I can never get enough tapestries. I'll hang it in my room.
Can I even hang it in this world...
Can I?
*Name the Elite Beautiful Girl: Dumb Elite.
I'm so happy. This was a great birthday.
Dumb Elite: Huh?! Just now we were in ARK but... huh? Are we back in the real world?!
Huh? This is weird...
*Thank god! Had I not changed it to "Official ARK Junkie, Elite Miko",
*I don't think we could've ever logged out from there...
"Oficial ARK Junkie, Elite Miko"?
Wha- "Log out"? What are you talking about...
Oh, by the way, Is there something special you want to say to me today~?
You didn't forget, did you?
*Happy Birthday!
*I love you.
Is there?
Is there not?
What is it?
Well?
You can't decide?
You can't decide what to say?
You are really having a hard time...
Huh? I- I love you too but... That should've been a "Happy birthday!", right!
But... well... I love you too. Thank you!
Where am I?!
Nyahello~!
How was that?
Were you surprised?
I sure was...
That was amazing!
You were really picking the options.
Ok.
Let me take a sip of water.
And so, thank you so much for coming to my birthday stream and thank you everyone for celebrating me!
Now then, I, Sakura Miko, want to sing you a song.
With all the memories in my heart and that view in my mind, I want to sing this for you.
Please listen to, Kirameki Rider(Shine Rider).
Let's make our newborn excitement resonate,
We can have the best time, if we are with our best friends
So come on and ride your shine☆ (Yay!)
Do you still remember how was my first song?
You see, my voice was trembling.
But the future that started from that day,
Is the present we built together.
Faster, faster, and much faster, our hearts start racing,
We'll go wherever it takes.
Everything Ok?
Open up the door to your dreams! (1, 2, 3)
We are Shine Riders☆
Let's make our newborn excitement resonate,
We can have the best time, if we are with our best friends
We're right here, because you found us.
And we came because we wanted to meet you, so let's all sing together
An everlasting melody.
So come on and ride your shine☆ (Yay!)
I wonder, is my voice reaching you?
All I want to give you is a smile.
Bothered by the remoteness of our ideal,
We smiled between tears.
Tighter, tighter, and much tighter, we embraced it all.
We'll go wherever it takes.
Everything Ok?
Continue the path to your wishes!(1, 2, 3)
We are Shine Riders☆
Let's put our feelings into a colorful song,
This will be the best place ever, filled with the best people
We are here, we assure you this is not an illusion.
So that your heart gets filled with happiness.
Our harmony will go on,
so come on and gather your shine☆
I want to keep singing, I want to keep dancing,
It's ok to be selfish and ask for that, right?
It's just that it's so fun I can't stop anymore.
I want to stay in this dazzling stage for longer
Even for forever!
Guys! Thank you! I am so happy to be supported by so many people.
Truly, thank you!
I can't just talk about happiness, fun and love,
If I'm honest I still have my doubts,
I'm right here, standing in front of you.
Looking at the same world you see,
Let's go! We are Shine Riders☆
Let's make our newborn excitement resonate,
We can have the best time, if we are with our best friends
We're right here because you found us.
And we came because we wanted to meet you, so let's all sing together(One, two!)
An everlasting melody.
Come on and ride your shine☆
Come on and gather your shine☆
(Yay!)
---------------------------------------
Umaretate no doki doki wo hibikaseyou,
Saikou no jikan saikou no nakama to
Kirameki ni notte☆ (Yay!)
Oboeteru ka na? Saishou no uta,
Watashi koe ga furueteita.
Ano hi kara sutzuku mirai wa
minna to tsukutta kyou da yo.
Motto motto motto motto Kasoku suru Haato,
Iku yo doko made mo.
Junbi wa OK?
Hirake yume no tobira wo!!! (1 2 3)
(Kirameki rider☆)
Umaretate no doki doki wo hibikaseyou,
Saikou no jikan saikou no nakama to.
koko ni iru yo mitsuketekureta kara.
Kimi ni aitakute yattekitanda minna de utaou
Owaranai merody Kirameki ni notte☆ (Yay!)
Todoiteru ka na? Watashi no koe
Todoketai no wa kimi ni egao
Risou no toosa ni kuyashikute
Minna to naki waratta ne.
Gyutto Gyutto Gyutto Gyutto Subete dakishimete
Ikou, doko made mo
Junbi wa OK?
Susume! Kibou no michi wo! (1 2 3)
(Kirameki rider☆)
Sukina kimochi karafuru ni kanadetainda
Saikou no basho saikou no minna to
koko ni iru yo maboroshi nanka ja nai
Kimi no kokoro ga shiawase ni somaru you ni
Kasaneteku haamonii Kirameki matotte☆
Utai tsutzuketai na, odori tsutzuketai na
Sonna negai ya wagamama mo ii deshou?
Datte tanoshisugite mou tomaranai
Kagayaku suteeji de motto motto
zutto!
Ureshii, Tanoshii, Aishi dake ya katarenai
Ima mo ima mo nayami wa aru kedo
koko ni iru yo watashi koko ni iru yo
Kimi to onaji sekai wo mitsumete
Iku yo!
(Kirameki raidaa☆)
Umaretate no doki doki wo hibikaseyou
Saikou no jikan saikou no nakama to
koko ni iru yo mitsuketekureta kara
Kimi ni aitakute yattekitanda minna de utaou
(Se no!)Owaranai memory
Kirameki ni notte☆
Kirameki matotte☆
(Yay!)
Ok, that was Kirameki Raidaa.
I was really nervous.
That didn't go well at all...
But, I'll do better next time... I actually did better on the rehearsal...
Getting nervous is bad, huh.
And so! Thank you so much for coming to celebrate me today!
There's a few things I've come to see.
You see, Last night I was doing a lot of ego searching and looking at all of your congratulation comments and tweets.
And looking back on things, you know.
And, Also 35P... 35P from all Japan and from all over the world-
The World 35P made a video for me.
And that moment...
Well, I always do this in front of a screen, right?
So I can't see your faces and if I think about it I'm basically always looking at myself when I stream.
But seeing so many comments and thinking that each and everyone of them is a unique person that watches us
It felt really reassuring
And to be able to personally see the faces of those people through that video was really touching.
Like "Oh, everyone is actually there and alive"
You are all alive and, while you leave your comments, each and everyone of you
also have their own thoughts and reasons to show support.
It genuinely made me happy.
Thank you. Really.
And it's that, turning 18.2 years old I want to embrace your thoughts on me
and grow more as a person.
Right now I'm still not good with preparing stuff
I have a long way to go. And, yeah I do have a dummy side to me...
So, I want to mature a bit more and then one day...
Well, I'd like to create an event where all 35P, all the fans that really support me
and have me as as their favorite can get together.
That's something I've been really thinking about from the bottom of my heart since yesterday
So, I'll do my best to get a solo event!
I still don't know if I'll be able to, neither if the grown ups will give me an ok,
but I'll do my best to make them give it to me.
And now, there's something I'd like to announce to everyone.
Umm...
I think it's something you'll really like.
Can I?
Now then,
Here's my announcement.
Take a look.
My 2nd Original song's release date has been set to the 27th of March, cherry blossom’s day!
Let's see.
Hearing everyone sing so passionately the interjection to my song My Name Is Elite at Toyosu Pitt
became a really treasured memory of mine.
So the next time there's a live, I'd like to have one more song to-
I'd like to have 2, or 3, or 4, or 5 more songs! I want to have way more so
this time I asked Hamu for it.
And the BGM you are listening to right now was made by them too.
Thank for always letting me use your BGMs.
And let me tell you, it's such a great song!
This time,
Well, just like you saw in the visual...
It'll be like my really loved Eroge Openings. Galgame, right.
It seems like it'll be like an Opening. A song like Sakura Miko, like cherry blossoms and like us.
That was the aim of the song.
The song was made for me but I was able to freely ask for things like phrases I wanted to have in the song
It's a song that was made by me telling them the feelings I wanted to convey in it.
So it's a song full of my feelings.
I'd be really happy if you look forward to it
It'll be released the 27th of march, the Cherry blossoms say so
Be sure to look forward to it!
That's about it.
But there's one more thing.
This one I've already talked about but here you go
Sakura Miko Birthday Voice is now on sale.
This one started sales today at 22:00 so I think it should be up already.
For those of you who buy this one before the 6th of April at 12:oo you get the following special gifts.
A postcard with Sakura Miko’s autograph and an acrylic panel with a new art drawn
by Narumi Nanami-sensei.
That is, the same art that I'm using for my new original song
Will be made into a really good quality acrylic panel.
I am really thankful to everyone that was involved in the making of this.
And this one was also taken at studio I mentioned last time and with majority of ASMR content,
though it's not the super romantic type it's full of ones that will make you skip a beat
Well yeah, there's also that... *something* report. [TL note: poop report. Check her ark streams for more context]
So for more information I'd be happy if you could check booth's page
And so, that all the information for now.
Truly thank you guys.
I don't know what may
A lot of things may lay ahead but,
I'd like it if you could keep on supporting and having fun with everyone in Hololive, same as ever.
Everyone is doing their best, they deserve it.
I am doing my best.
Let's live our days with the biggest smile we have.
And like that, let's do our best together!
Everything is non-stop from here on!
And my Sakura Story is also non-stop from here on!
But for no, I think that'll be all for now.
Thank you so much for watching.
If you enjoyed please like, subscribe, follow me on twitter,
fall in love with me, and become a 35P!
Impressions and screenshots can go on this hashtag, forgot to say that...
Thank you, everyone.
Yesterday I was fully made aware that people all around the world support me...
Really, I was just on top of my bed seriously crying my heart out...
Even I was surprised about that.
Thank you,
Thanks for lovin' me.
Now everyone, I'll see you in my next stream.
That's all from Sakura Miko.
Bye bye!
I love you, guys!
Mmmh?
Ohh?
Uhh?
Nyahello!!!
Nyahello~! Nyahello~!
Mi-kochi, Mikochi, Mi-kochi is recruiting!
Miko-chi, Miko-chi, Elite Sakura Shrine!
Ok, Everyone!
Can you see me?
Yaaay! yay! ya- ohh, thank you!
Fubu-chan was also going "Miko-chi! Miko-chi!" just now,
Made me happy! Thank you everyone!
Thank you so much!
So!
Today...
Today's birthday girl
Is yours truly, Elite shrine maiden, Sakura Miko!
Today we celebrate that so... basically that's what this stream is for.
Thank you for coming to my Birthday stre-
This is crazy!
It's crazy!
Your donations-
They are here!
They are so full but are falling to the ground!
What a waste!
I'll catch them! I'll catch them all!
I'll make sure to!
Thank you!!
Was that...
Will it come?
My offering box!!!
Here it is!
Look, look everyone--
My offering bo-
Thank you, guys!!
I'm so happy-
I'm so happy! Thank you! This is crazy! Makes me really happy! Wow, so many!
I'll make sure to take them all!
Wow! Thank you!!
Got 'em, nice.
Thank you, guys!!! Thank you!!! Thank you!!!
Wait..., this is really hard...
Oh! it went to-
Hey don't run off to the back!
My offering box-! Oh, it's back!
Thank you, guys!!! Thank you!
Ohh, thank you! Really, thank you!
So yeah, today-
Ohh, thank you!!! Thank you!!!
You see...
Tha- Than- Thank you, guys!!!
Don't worry, it's all going inside here so...
Oh, I'm getting the hang of this!
Wow, guys! You're donating so much!
Thank you!!
Ok.
That's all the commentary I can do...
This... is... all I can do now...
Ok!
So, I want to truly thank you for coming to celebrate me today!
Thank so much you!
Now then...
We are just starting and I already used quite a bit of stamina but...
Today I have prepared some really fun activities. Things I'd like to do-
I need some water... let me take just take a sip...
The beginning... The beginning is always nerve wracking, isn't it?
I get so nervous I run out of breath...
Ever since I see the countdown before start is just breath heavily...
Thank you, guys!
Now then.
Today I have a lot of fun activities prepared so please enjoy!!!
Let's get things donezo!
And so,
I'd like to go to my room right away...
Today 35P might be waiting in there!
They could be there. Probably...
So, let's change places!
To my room!
Uh... There's no one here, this is weird...
There's no one here...
Not a single one is here...
Ah, they're probably just late.
Probably just in a traffic jam.
Ok, so.
Getting right into it. Today...
Well, first is that. I was thinking I could have some cake.
And maybe you can take some screen shots.
Please look forward to that.
And after that,
Well, I've called a few guests... yeah, I called them...
So, please look forward to that too...
And that's the plan...
So...
Will 35P come?
Will they come?
Oh, they won't.
Oh, it seems they might be in the middle of logging in at home. So let me tell you about today...
Just now you donated so much, right?
Thank you for that!!!
You know what, using all that money I'm thinking in going into virtual -something or other- amazon,
and getting a huge cake ready.
A family sized one!
One a whole family could eat.
I'm looking forward to it.
Then, do you think I can order my cake now?
Can I? Can I?
Oh, it seems I can! Nice!
Then! With all of your...
Everything you gave me will go directly into the bill.
So...!
Come to me, my cake!!!
Huh?
So huge!
It's way too huge!
Way too huge!
Like...
Oh, but this might work
What do you think?
How is it?
And the candle...
Doesn't it look like a hat?
What do you think?
[You are really in it!]
Well I am the protagonist so I get a protagonist cake, right
Yaaay! Yaay!
And I can eat it like this
Oh, but first let's take some photos!
You could take some pictures like this.
Hey, Mr. Camera man!
Mr. Camera man, are you here?
Oh, nice!
What do you think?
How's this? How's this?
Is this good? Am I cute?
Am I?
mmh? Am I cute?
It says "Happy Birthday"
And I have finally become a cake, huh!
What do you think?
[Even the fork is huge!]
Yeah!
Got it!!!
I can eat it like this-
How's... How's this?
Today's protagonist. I, Sakura Miko, just turned 18.2 years old!
What do you think? Is this good?
[Can I eat you?]
Fubu-chan?!
I'm the one on the... eating side.
I spend my days in the world of the survival of the... ones that.. eat...
Umm, Survival of the fittest. Yeah, Survival of the fittest!
I'm always the one being eaten-
I mean, I'm always the one that eats others!
A certain sheep and a rabbit you may know are my meals!
*Smug face*
Ok! Let me try it!
Here I go
Woow, so cool!!!
How's this?
Look everyone, look!
I got it!!!
Look! This cake is huge!
This is crazy... it really is.
Bon Appetit!
Ok, I'll try it.
Here I go!
It's so good!
It tastes so good!
Oh.
Hi.
Sakura Miko, here.
Ok! Let's have some more!
Woow, so cool!
Oh Ok, ok, ok.
You want to take pictures?
There!
You can take pictures.
Yay!
Oh, Is that a camera?
Let's bring a camera here
Come on~
Oh?
Can we?
I'm gonna eat this.
This looks so real...
Bon Ap-
Eh?
It shrunk!!!
Why?!
It's tiny now!
It shouldn't be like this.
Was I just dreaming?!
It became ti-
Oh, it's big again!
It's big again!
Bon Appetit!
It's so, so good!
It tastes soo good! It's great!
Birthdays are great, aren't they!
This is really tasty guys!
Do you want some too?
You do?
Ok.
Oh, seems you don't get any.
Hold on.
Seems your part is gone, sorry!
Give me a sec.
Sorry.
Seems you don't get any. I'm not doing this on purpose.
Oh... Ok, I might give it one more shot.
Oh? Seems... Seems a camera is here!
A camera- Oh, seem it won't.
And neither will the cake...
'Kay, now a stylish pose.
Ok... How's this?
Fork and I.
Mmh, a pose...
Oh, like this?
Go ahead.
You can eat
You can eat me.
Or something like that.
How was that? How was that?
That famous scene! ...It isn't famous though.
And I still can't take more!!!
Oh, got it!
There guys, this is for you!
There, you can have some.
"nom"
Ohhh, you ate it!
That means everyone watching just ate some of my cake.
Good for you, isn't it!
There, there.
Now I'll have some~
Oh, really ate it.
But I'm feeling really full now.
But I have a different stomach for sweets,
and I still have so much left so I can keep going until it ends.
Here I go!
Tasty.
Oh, does this cake have infinite slices?!
What do you think? Am I cute?
Do I look good?
Does this looks good?
Bon Appetit!
Ate it all!
Feast's over.
[Cute!]
Aww, makes me happy!
And with that, thanks for the meal.
Ate quite a bit. Really.
Thanks for the meal.
And so.
Well I finished eating my cake and... Did you take pictures?
Did you?
Mmh, feels like...
Like for a birthday...
A birth-
Ah...
Here!
Mmh, but I always go for peace signs...
Maybe like this.
What do you think?
Will you buy me an eroge? Please?
YO YO, Check it out!
What's the contrary of DESU YO
Nothing but fun!
YO YO, Check it out!
<Before that, can I complain about one little thing.
...
Nyan~ nyan~
_Hello?
Hello!
_Don't call me a little brat!!!
But you are one!!!
_Don't call me that!
And you're a loli, come on.
No matter how you look at it you are a loli.
_Miko!
Yeah?
_Happy birthday!
Thank you!!! That makes me happy!!!
_Congratulations!!!
Oh, you're suck a good kid. Suck a good girl who praises me.
_Sure, sure. Congrats'
Sh- shit... No. Calm down. Calm down.
Right. Today...
_Sure, I'm a good girl so I'm here to congratulate you~
She's making fun of me! I can tell by how she talks to me.
Every time we talk she makes fun of me!
_I do not! Miko-chan, you are really cute today!
Really?
Oh... well, thank you.
Then... today I'm waiting for praise callers so,
Would you tell me some things you like about me, or good points about me?
_Miko- Oh, got it. Here's the first one.
"First one"? There's more?!
_No, there aren't. No.
Hey! You are the worst at this!!!
_Well, It always seems like you would suck at everything...
Ah, "like I would suck" right...
_But it's really cute to see you... you know, try your best
"Trying my best"?
Are you... making fun of me?
_Like, she- she's really doing her best today too. Makes me feel proud.
_That's how you make me feel.
Uhh... yeah. Thank you! Then how about the second one?
_Sure
What's the second one? Tell me. There is one right?
_Second one?
This one is for real
_The second one is...
Can't you just spit it out?
You said "first one", so there should be more, right?
_There are just so many!
Oh, so many? So that's why! That's really cute! You do have a cute side to you!
So, what is it? There's something, right??
_Is there anything?
Eh? There's nothing else?
No- nothing...?
_You are just so cute!!! Congrats on your birthday!
Yay! Thank you! Thank you!
_You are really cute!
You better remember this!
You better do!
You are really a little brat after all...
_You want some of this?
_You want some, Miko-chan?
Oh, you want to fight?
You think you can win?
_You want some?
You think you can beat me with that body!
Let me tell you but I'm taller than you.
You ready?
I can chill your tummy, y'know.
I have protection against that.
_She wants to put something cold on me!
I'm all for it. I can take some ice from the fridge and press it against your tummy.
_You really want to do that?
Let's see how you feel after that.
_Do you really?
_Then, Imma grope your breasts!
"Grope my breasts"?! Stop that! That's lewd!
Stop that! That's not something a little brat should be doing!
Seriously.
Ok, and so... well I don't really like how this went but thank you Shion-chan.
_Congratulations, let's do something together again.
Yeah, let's!
Thank you!
_Yeah! Bye bye, Miko-chan. Enjoy your birthday~
_Bye bye!
I just can't hate her...
Shion-chan is a little brat and that won't change but I really hate the fact that you
can't just hate her. She's too cute.
Like...
This won't work, huh...
That is definitely my loss.
But the next person will surely praise me.
But it's been a long time since we've talked... Will it be fine?
I'm... I'm a little nervous right now...
Can you guys help me relax just one bit?
Oh, it's getting better.
Can you keep going?
Can you?
Well?
Will... you?
Will you?
Oh, no.
Now I'm thinking about it again!
I'm feeling it more and more!
Will it be ok...
Like...
It's...
How to say it...
Well a lot of things..
Did I miss the timing- does she not like me anymore?
Will this be ok?
Will she pick up?
Is this ok?
She coming?
Is it maybe that she's feeling too nervous to pick up?