So heavy...
Working at a bakery is hard...
I'm beat...
Why is this so tiring?
Why am I working so much?
Korone-chan?
Manager!
Working?
Good morning.
Yes, as you can tell I'm working my hardest.
You do shine the brightest while working hard.
Understood. I'll keep doing my best.
This isn't good. None of this is good.
Why am I work-
! I'll keep doing my best.
I'll keep doing my best.
If anything's on your mind, I'm all ears.
Well...
Never mind.
I'll do my best.
Alright, I'm heading back to my work area.
Okay.
Every single day I kee-who is it?
Every single day, I keep living this life again and again,
with enjoyment nowhere to be found.
This is the boring life that I, Koromi, live.
Tinkle tinkle.
Welco-
You're...
My boss said he loves this bakery.
Ah, I'm sorry...
What?
"Licked my finger"?
What?!
Huh?