Oh no, oh no, oh no, oh noparapappappa!
I totally meant for that to be a Kirby song, but I guess I ended up humming Tetris.
Close one!
I was trying to hum something from Kirby.
oh crap, oh crap, oh crap
Okay!
There!
Alright,
everything went as planned.
Riiiise and shine!
Morning, everybody!
Good morning!
Morning!
Oh, it's been a while! How've you been?
That's nice to hear! He's doing good!
Whoa!
You look different today.
Rocking a Vegeta hairstyle, huh?
Nice! Looks pretty good on you!
Hold up.
Hey.
What are you doing there? Hey!
Crap, they're gonna scold me!
They're gonna scold me!
They're gonna be mad!
They're gonna be really mad if you do that!
Wait. No, wait! Wait! Don't!
Please don—
Please don't do that! I'm sorry!
The keyboard did this.
It was the keyboard's fault!
Shit!
I gotta cover this up.
Crap.