What's this?
What is this? It won't open!
It won't let me open it at all.
Poor thing.
Huh? Who'd do th―poor thing!
Are they psychotic?
The Sweets Shack.
Halloween Exclusive.
You can have the sweets inside.
There are sweets?!
Oh, this is cute! I guess it's supposed to be a cake?
Yeah, this is probably a cake.
Give me candy, or I'll play a trick on you!
How do I get out?
That gave me a heart attack.
H-How do I...
How do I get out?
You're all in the way!
There's a few missing their face!
The uggos, they're mingling!
The uggos are mingling with you guys! Hey!
Where's the exit?
Is this the exit?
There's a door!
I can't get out.
Man, that really spooked me.
I'm finally out!
You know, for a split second,
I thought I was gonna lose all my experience points when I fell.
I thought I was a definite goner.
That sure was something.
That spooked me, like super spooked, seriously.
I thought my heart was gonna stop.
I'm not really into jumpscares and stuff.
Whoa! It's trapped?
The girls sure do some crazy things.
There's even a diamond block here.
Only a psychopath would do this.
Those snowmen, they're all imprisoned...