Subscribe to Murasaki Shion if you liked this!
↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓
I'm so lonely.
"This'll make their heart skip a beat!"
I thought while saying that.
I'm absolutely trash.
Which way was home again?
It's so dark!
Oh! Isn't it that way?
Wait, is it?
Hm, maybe it is.
That means I need to get up there, huh?
Let's go up.
Oh, I know what to do.
This spot works.
I hear it wailing.
Oh! It's this way-ay-ay-ay-ay!
My stones went whoosh back there.
I could've sworn I was done for.
Whooshing stones...!
They're gone! Those things girls don't have.
That sure spooked me.
Where's the entrance...
you don't have balls!
Is that the entrance?
"soul" stones went whoosh lol
This is spine-chilling.
Where's the ghast?
Yeah, my soul stones went whoosh.
Man, that seriously surprised me.
Thought I was done for.
Absolutely dooooone.
Thank goodness I survived.