Subscribe to Murasaki Shion if you liked this!
↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓
My gramps picked up an acorn
and showed it to me and was like,
"Did you know acorns are edible?"
I still won't eat them, though.
Today's dessert was a fruity one.
I've been getting nice food as of late.
Am I being domesticated?
I'm being domesticated, aren't I?
Now!
There!
What now?
Something cam—what?
Do I kill this guy?
Whoa, I'm on like a hidden path.
Wait, shouldn't I be below?! I messed up!
What am I supposed to do about this now?
I'm totally supposed to take that sword and beat him.
This sucks!
That damn robot...!
Huh?
What.
GAME CLEAR
THANK YOU FOR PLAYING
Huh?!
It's a melon.
Oh! This is by the guy who made Eryi—
Wait, the game's over!
This is by the same guy who made Eryi's Action, isn't it?
You sure love melons, don't you?!
You're just like me, then.
There was a melon in the last stage in Eryi's Action, too.
Is the game really over?
You guys should applaud me.
Congratulate me! Say congratulations!
Applaud me! You're supposed to applaud me here, right?
Probably.
I totally thought I messed up there, though.
I'm a genius.
Thanks for keeping me company.
Thank you!
"Congrats on beating the game!"—
thank you so much!
Thank you!
Now then...
Is this really the end?
Of course I'm elated.
I thought I'd keep messing up.
Hm, it stopped moving.
Oh, it started scrolling again.
THANK YOU FOR PLAYING THIS GAME.
What am I supposed to do for the rest of today's stream?
Huh, it really is ending, isn't it?
THANK YOU FOR PLAYING THIS GAME.
It sure is.
I didn't plan to beat you in three days. Hey.
Seriously?
It's over.