Hi, let's have a nice game.
Let's have a nice game.
Alright, let's go!
I'll finish him.
I'll definitely finish him.
Wait.
I'm gonna finish him.
Stop it. Stop it.
Hey wait,
Hey wait, wait,
Hey wait, wait, wait,
Hey wait, wait, wait, wait,
Hey wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
Hey wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
Hey wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
Hey wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
Hey wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
Hey wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
Hey wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Waitwaitwait
Ground, ground!
Wait until I'm on the ground!
I'll definitely finish you off.
That was close.
This guy! This damn guy!
pitto?
Heeeeeeeeey
This guy isn't gentle.
You're not gentle at all.
Not gentle at all!
Gentle not one bit!
Totally not gentle.
So not gentle...
You're not gonna get a girlfriend if you're not more gentle, you know.
You won't get a girlfriend!
H-H-Hey if you keep doing that you won't get a girlfriend!
Oh he died.
All good, all good.
Was that you being gentle?
I guess that means you wanted a girlfriend.
Yeah, I guess you wanted a girlfriend. Probably.
Gimme some room!
"He might have one already"
That's not
*hiss*