Friday, November 29th
HoloWeather
What's my HoloFortune?
/Morning\
HoloWeather
Friday, November 29th
/Morning\
What's my HoloFortune?
Friday, November 29th
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
Good morning, everyone!
Natsuiro Matsuri
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
Good morning, everyone!
Natsuiro Matsuri
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
Good morning, everyone!
Natsuiro Matsuri
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
Good morning, everyone!
Natsuiro Matsuri
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
Good morning, everyone!
Natsuiro Matsuri
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
Good morning, everyone!
Natsuiro Matsuri
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
Good morning, everyone!
Natsuiro Matsuri
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
Good morning, everyone!
Natsuiro Matsuri
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
HoloWeather
Natsuiro Matsuri
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
HoloWeather
Natsuiro Matsuri
Natsuiro Matsuri, here!
Not sure how long I can hold this!
It's Friday, November 29th,
and I'm here with the weather and horoscopes!
Now, on to today's forecast.
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
Did you know hamsters
can dislocate their jaws?
HoloWeather
That's why they can fit
so much in their mouths!
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
HoloWeather
What's my HoloFortune?
Now for what you've all been
waiting for: the horoscopes!
What's my HoloFortune?
Today's luckiest sign is this one!
Lucky Hololiver: Natsuiro Matsuri
What's my HoloFortune?
It's you, Virgo! Congratulations.
Lucky Hololiver: Natsuiro Matsuri
You'll grow by actively challenging yourself!
Your lucky Hololiver is me, Ma~tsuri~!
In fourth place, Cancer:
Splendid encounters today!
Go with the flow.
Your lucky Hololiver is Miko-Miko!
In eighth place, Taurus:
Broaden the range of your activities and luck will follow.
Your lucky Hololiver is Roboco-senpai!
In tenth place, Leo:
Affection from romantic interests. Trust your charms!
Your lucky Hololiver is Haato-chan!
And today's
unluckiest sign is...
Lucky Hololiver: Nekomata Okayu
Sorry, Aquarius. It's you!
Identify your wasteful expenses and tighten up your budget!
Your lucky Hololiver is Okayun!
Thanks again
for watching today!
Have a nice day!
Bye-bye!
Hololive's first full-group event!!
-NON-STOP STORY-
January 24, 2020     @ Toyosu PIT