Friday, November 22th
HoloWeather
What's my HoloFortune?
/Morning\
HoloWeather
Friday, November 22th
/Morning\
What's my HoloFortune?
Friday, November 22th
Use "euphoriphones" to listen to Commander today!
Good muscling, everyone!
HoloWeather
Use "euphoriphones" to listen to Commander today!
Shirogane Noel here.
Good on you for waking up~
It's Friday, November 22nd, and Shirogane Noel's here with the weather and horoscopes!
Now, on to today's forecast.
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
Today's weather sure is something else!
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
HoloWeather
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
HoloWeather
Now for what you've all been
waiting for: the horoscopes!
What's my HoloFortune?
Today's luckiest sign is...
Over here!
Lucky Hololiver: Yuzuki Choco
What's my HoloFortune?
It's you, Leo! Congratulations!
Romantic luck up!
Be confident and put yourself out there!
Your lucky Hololiver is Choco-senpai!
In fifth place, Taurus:
What's my HoloFortune?
Time to get aggressive!
A confident posture will go a long way!
Your lucky Hololiver is Marine!
What's my HoloFortune?
In sixth place, Cancer:
You can discard your biases.
You'll find luck in listening to others.
Your lucky Hololiver is Akai Haato-senpai!
In eleventh place, Aquarius:
Flexible planning is the key to greater fun!
Your lucky Hololiver is Miko-senpai!
What's my HoloFortune?
And today's unluckiest sign is...
Sorry, Aries! It's you!
What's my HoloFortune?
Be careful not to act impulsively. Take a breather, first.
Your lucky Hololiver is Mel-senpai!
Thanks for watching again today!
It may be Friday, but keep at it!
Have a nice day!
Hololive's first full-group event!!
-NON-STOP STORY-
January 24, 2020       @ Toyosu PIT
Second Batch of Tickets (lottery via e-plus)