Saturday, February 1st
HoloWeather
What's my HoloFortune?
/Morning\
HoloWeather
Saturday, February 1st
/Morning\
What's my HoloFortune?
Saturday, February 1st
Good "cornMio"rning everyone!
HoloWeather
Good "cornMio"rning!
It's Shirakami Fubuki and...
Okami Mio!
The last day of January
got us in a really weird mood
but with February
we want to make a comeback!
We're shifting gears, yup!
Hurray!
It's Saturday, February 1st, and the two of us are here for the weather and horoscopes.
Yay!
HoloWeather
Now, on to today's forecast. Let's go!
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
The MioFas' Forest is probably growing strong today.
Nice, that means it must be pretty sunny, right?
Yup! All nice and good!
It's nice and good to be nice and good!
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
HoloWeather
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
HoloWeather
Now for what you have all been
waiting for: the horoscopes!
What's my HoloFortune?
Hurray!
Today's luckiest sign is... YOU!
It's you!
Lucky Hololiver: Okami Mio
It's you, Aries. Congratulations!
Congratulations!
Treat yourself with income
that's not from your main job!
From here and there.
Your lucky Hololiver is...
Wah! It's Miooo~
It's meeee~
Go and worship her!
In fourth place, Leo:
Virgo: Listen when relied upon. Your reuptation will improve
Lucky Hololiver: Shirogane Noel
Taurus: Thorough groundwork is the key to success!
Lucky Hololiver: Minato Aqua
Leo: Usually difficult work will seem easy today?!
Lucky Hololiver: Sakura Miko
Capricorn: Time to get aggressive. Make that early investment
Lucky Hololiver: Nekomata Okayu
Usually difficult work might actually seem easy today!
Great!
Your lucky Hololiver is...
Nyahello! Sakura Miko!
In sixth place, Pisces:♪
Pisces: You can discard preconceptions. Luck in listening to others
Lucky Hololiver: Tsunomaki Watame
Scorpio: You're sharp today! What you do will go smoothly
Lucky Hololiver: Murasaki Shion
Aquarius: Grow through interesting, albeit ill-compensated work
Lucky Hololiver: Hoshimachi Suisei
You're sharp today! What you do will go smoothly.
Your lucky Hololiver is Shion-chan!
It's Shion-chan!
In tenth place, Gemini:
Cancer: You may get carried away and spend unnecessarily
Lucky Hololiver: Usada Pekora
Gemini: Careful not to be taken in by a shady scheme!
Lucky Hololiver: Amane Kanata
Libra: Listen to your superiors' advice
Lucky Hololiver: Himemori Luna
Careful not to be taken in by a shady scheme!
Say what?!
Your lucky Hololiver is the PP angel, Kanata-chan!
Keep faith in the PP!
And today's unluckiest sign is...
Lucky Hololiver: Shirakami Fubuki
Sorry! It's you, Sagittarius.
Being yourself will be important today. Put enjoyment first!
Your lucky Hololiver is...
Guess what! It's Shirakami!
"Kon-kon" goes the fox!
Goes the fox!
That means if you whale today
something good might come out!
Great! Let's whale!
You're doing it too?!
Thank you for watching again today!
Thanks!
It's already February! How the time flies~
Keep doing your best this month, too!
Do your best, ok?
/Morning\