Friday, March 6th
HoloWeather
What's my HoloFortune?
/Morning\
HoloWeather
Friday, March 6th
/Morning\
What's my HoloFortune?
Friday, March 6th
Hoshimachi Suisei
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
HoloWeather
Hoshimachi Suisei
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
HoloWeather
Hoshimachi Suisei
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
HoloWeather
Hoshimachi Suisei
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
HoloWeather
Good morning, everyone.
I thought I'd get super
up-close and intimate today.
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
Well? Do you think I'm cute?
You do, don't you?
Don't forget to subscribe on YouTube as well!
That cute girl before you
is named Hoshimachi Suisei.
Hoshimachi Suisei is here with the weather and horoscopes for Friday, March 6th.
Now, on to today's forecast.
So cute. My makeup
looks perfect as usual today.
Gosh, I'm cute.
HoloWeather
Now on to what you've all been waiting for: the horoscopes!
Today's luckiest sign is... this!
What's my HoloFortune?
That's right, Gemini! Congratulations!
You'll have a fulfilling day,
alone or with others.
Your lucky Hololiver is Shirakami Fubuki-chan!
Good corn-ing!
In fourth place, Libra:
Buy only what you absolutely need.
Your lucky Hololiver is me, Sui-chan!
Sui-chan buys all the clothes she wants.
All of them.
In seventh place, Capricorn:
Spend wisely to further boost your financial luck!
Your lucky Hololiver is Shiranui Flare!
Good morn-nui~
In ninth place, Virgo:
You'll be prone to wasteful
spending today. Shop carefully.
Your lucky Hololiver is Shirogane Noel!
Good muscling!
And today's unluckiest sign is...
Sorry, Aquarius. It's you!
It's important to know
when to give up gracefully.
Your lucky Hololiver is Akai Haato-chan!
Rouge and shine! Akai Haato, here!
Was that spot-on or what?
Thanks for watching again today!
Was I close enough to make your heart race?
I'm pretty cute, aren't I?
Well, look forward to tomorrow's episode!
Have a nice day!
/Sui-chan is~?\