Friday, January 31st
HoloWeather
What's my HoloFortune?
/Morning\
HoloWeather
Friday, January 31st
/Morning\
What's my HoloFortune?
Friday, January 31st
Good morning everyone!
HoloWeather
Good morning!
It's Okami Mio...
Shirakami Fubuki!
Yeah!
Is everyone up?
If they're not that's no good! No good at all!
Wake up! Wake up!
Yeah.
It's Friday, January 31st, and we're here for the weather and horoscopes.
HoloWeather
Black and white sisters!
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
HoloWeather
Now for what you have all been
waiting for: the horoscopes!
What's my HoloFortune?
Check it out!
Today's luckiest sign is this dude!
It's you!
Lucky Hololiver: Yozora Mel
It's you, Aquarius. Congratulations!
Congratulations!
Let's grow closer to another's heart.
Snug up close.
It's good to reach out!
It is.
Your lucky Hololiver is Mel-chan.
Mel-chan, Mel-chan.
In fourth place, Virgo:
Libra: Invest money in fashion
Lucky Hololiver: Natsuiro Matsuri
Aries: You'll join forces with others to accomplish great things
Lucky Hololiver: Tokino Sora
Virgo: Treat yourself to some sweets
Lucky Hololiver: Houshou Marine
Scorpio: Your skills will improve the busier you are at work!
Lucky Hololiver: Minato Aqua
Treat yourself to some sweets.
Sweets.
Your lucky Hololiver is Houshou Marine!
Houshou Marine!
In sixth place, Pisces:
Pisces: Your processing power's improving steadily!
Lucky Hololiver: Uruha Rushia
Leo: No mistakes at work! Good day for language study
Lucky Hololiver: Shiranui Flare
Cancer: Be optimistic and discard preconceived notions
Lucky Hololiver: Akai Haato
Fishy~
Your processing power's going up, up, up!
Up!
It's improving steadily!
Your lucky Hololiver is Rushia.
It's Rushia~
In ninth place, Gemini:
Gemini: Good luck in gifts, both giving and receiving
Lucky Hololiver: AkiRose
Taurus: Money luck in surprising places. Don't think too hard
Lucky Hololiver: Shirogane Noel
Capricorn: It may be hard to let go when a move or transfer comes
Lucky Hololiver: Roboco-san
Good luck in gifts, both giving and receiving.
Presents!
Your lucky Hololiver is Aki Rosenthal.
Aki-chwan.
And today's the most BAD sign is...
Bad, bad you!
Lucky Hololiver: Nakiri Ayame
Sorry! It's you, Sagittarius.
I'm sorry!
You'll get lots of attention today.
Do your best to maintain harmony. Yup.
Oh?
Harmony.
Your lucky Hololiver is Nakiri Ayame.
Oh, Japanese Ogre!
Ogre!
Thanks for watching again today!
Check it out!
Any comments, Shirakami?
Mysterious characters!
Once we get into it there's no stopping this mess!
Don't stop us now!
Y'all better not be stopping today either!
Don't stop and have a nice day!
Go~!
/Morning\