Monday, January 27th
HoloWeather
What's my HoloFortune?
/Morning\
HoloWeather
Monday, January 27th
/Morning\
What's my HoloFortune?
Monday, January 27th
Everyone! Good "cornMio"ning!
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
Everyone! Good "cornMio"ning!
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
Everyone! Good "cornMio"ning!
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
Everyone! Good "cornMio"ning!
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
Everyone! Good "cornMio"ning!
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
Everyone! Good "cornMio"ning!
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
Everyone! Good "cornMio"ning!
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
Everyone! Good "cornMio"ning!
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
Everyone! Good "cornMio"ning!
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
HoloWeather
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
HoloWeather
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
HoloWeather
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
HoloWeather
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
HoloWeather
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
HoloWeather
Shirakami Fubuki
Okami Mio
HoloWeather
It's Shirakami Fubuki and Okami Mio!
Hmm? Did you really wake up?
I wonder if they did~
If they're still asleep then...
Poke, poke!
Slap!
It's Monday, January 27th, and we're here with the weather and horoscopes.
HoloWeather
Now, on to today's forecast.
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
There's some sun and there's some clouds, I know that, oh I know~♪
But I wonder if there's any snow?
Doesn't look like there is.
Bummer, I want to play with it...
Let's make a snowman!
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
HoloWeather
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
HoloWeather
Now for what you've all been
waiting for: the horoscopes.
What's my HoloFortune?
Today's luckiest sign is this one!
You, Scorpio. Congratulations!
Congratulations!
Grow by challenging yourself with a new job!
Your lucky Hololiver is commander Noel.
Commander Noel?
Yup.
Commander!
In fifth place, Capricorn:
Give in to your curiosity. Your world will expand.
Your lucky Hololiver is Ozyora Chubaru-chama!
Aji, aji. Aji, aji.
In seventh place, Pisces:
Don't start your day off carrying lots of cash!
Sorry!
Your lucky Hololiver is chairman Coco.
Chairman Coco!
In tenth place, Libra:
Sway, sway~
Start studying to improve your abilities even further.
Whoa, whoa!
Your lucky Hololiver is Towa-chan.
Towa-chan!
And today's unluckiest sign is... Oh no!
Sorry. It's you, Aries.
Nooo!
So sad...
Your new idea might get a better reception than you expected!
Oh?
Say what?!
It doesn't really feel like last place.
That's right. Yup!
Your lucky Hololiver is AZKi-chan.
Let's listen to her songs! That will cheer us up!
Good idea!
Thank you very much for watching again today!
Thanks!
This time we're doing Morning hololive in our idol outfits!
It's the first time two people are doing it, right?
It really is! Yay!
Hurray!!!
Well then everyone, have a nice day!
Have a nice day!
/Morning\