Sunday, January 19th
HoloWeather
What's my HoloFortune?
/Morning\
HoloWeather
Sunday, January 19th
/Morning\
What's my HoloFortune?
Sunday, January 19th
Mornin', everyone!
HoloWeather
Ozora Subaru, here!
Good job gettin' outta bed!
It's cold out, but don't let that getcha down!
It's Sunday, January 19th, and I'm here with the weather and horoscopes!
Now, on to today's forecast.
HoloWeather
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
It's Sunday, so I bet it's sunny out!
Just guessin'.
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
HoloWeather
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
HoloWeather
Provided by
WeatherNews Inc.
HoloWeather
Now for what you've all been
waiting for: the horoscopes!
Today's luckiest sign is... this one!
It's you, Virgo! Congratulations!
You'll have good luck at work!
Strike up a conversation with those around you.
Your lucky Hololiver is me, Subaaaaaru!
In third place, Scorpio:
That purchase may be costly, but trust your instincts!
Your lucky Hololiver is Fubuki-senpai!
In eighth place, Aquarius:
Train your appraisal skills to
boost, boost, boost your money luck!
Your lucky Hololiver is Watame-chan.
That's not to say your money luck will actually improve.
In eleventh place, Leo:
It may be hard to let go when a move or transfer comes!
Your lucky Hololiver is Ayame-chan!
And today's unluckiest sign is...
Sorry, Cancer! It's you.
Good intrerpersonal relationships
will have a positive effect on your work.
Your lucky Hololiver is everyone's mom, Mio-chan!
Hi, Mio-chan! Are you watching?
Thanks for watching again t'day.
How'd ya like seeing me in super-close-up?
Fall for me already!
'Kay, see ya later, guys!
Bye-bye!
/Morning\