Friday, January 24th
HoloWeather
What's my HoloFortune?
/Morning\
HoloWeather
Friday, January 24th
/Morning\
What's my HoloFortune?
Friday, January 24th
Hello everyone, good Aqua!
It's Minato Aqua!
Huh? Is it just my imagination or am I big today?
It's Friday, January 24th, and I'm here with the weather and horoscopes!
Now, on to today's forecast.
Are you able to tell the weather? Can you see?
Well, whatever.
Now for what you've all been
waiting for: the horoscooooopes!
Today's luckiest sign is...
You, Sagittarius! Congratulations!
You might land some side money today!
Your lucky Hololiver is...
Jump! Sakura Miko!
In fourth place, Aries:
Difficult work should be a breeze today!
Your lucky Hololiver is Flare-chan!
Jump.
In eighth place, Libra:
A side job with great terms may be in store for you!
Your lucky Hololiver is Watame-chan!
Jump!
In ninth place, Pisces:
Wasteful spending likely. Keep your wits about you!
Your lucky Hololiver is Subaruuuuuuuu!
Jump!
And today's unluckiest sign is...
Sorry. It's you, Leo.
You'll be able to overcome stressful situations!
Your lucky Hololiver is Aki-chan!
Jump! Jump! A jumpy jump!
Thank you for watching again today.
It may be Friday, but roll up your sleeves and do your best today!
/Morning\