My name is Shishiro Botan.
I was born in and grew up in a place
one could hardly call clean on any scale.
But I've managed to live in tranquility, spending my days away just killing time.
Sigh.
Same old day, in and out.
I can't even manage to hold on to any hopes and dreams.
I want to do something fun.
Something, something fun...
I'm so sleepy...
Lazing away really makes your body more prone to tiredness...
Hm? What's this website?
Hololive...
"makes fans go wild, the world over..."
"We're accepting applications, send yours in..."
Wow, this sounds super fun...!
This just might be the fun I was looking for.
With that out of the way, hello!
Good evening!
Um... From Hololive's 5th generation,
I'm Shishiro Botan!
Yeah!
◾ Profile
The mind of a lazy house cat in the body of a
fearsome white lion. She’s conscientious and
will finish what she has started, but good luck
getting her to start. Her favorite phrase is,
“Go big or go home!”
Height: 166cm
Birthday: September 8th
Here's my profile.
The mind of a lazy house cat in the body of a fearsome white lion.
She’s conscientious and will finish what she's started, but good luck getting her to start.
Her favorite phrase is, "Go big or go home!"
My birthday is September 8.
It's pretty soon.
Today's the 14th of August,
so it's less than a month away.
So start prepping! I'll be waiting.
Yeah, I'm pretty tall.
Oh! This is confidential,
but I'm the same height as Honda Tsubasa.
◾ Likes
Games (Too long to list, more deets later)
Video Editing (making random edits)
PC Building (casual)
Fun things (Interesting things)
Udon/Horumon restaurants under overpasses
Orange juice
◾ Favourite Manga
Parasyte
Naniwa Kin'yudo
Subaru
NARUTO
◾ Dislikes
Spicy food
Alcohol
Homework
By the way, I built my current PC myself.
I'm not an old man, I'm a white lion.
And last, I like orange juice.
Also, this is listed further down,
but I can't handle drinking alcohol.
So whenever it's time for me to toast Lamy-chan,
Lamy'll have alcohol and I'll have orange juice.
I'm learning Chinese, actually.
And
I get homework for that.
I-I guess I'm like an elementary schooler who hates homework. Yeah.
How about I read around page 5?
Gimme a sec. Page 5...
Hello.
H-Hello.
Thank you.
There.
That was page 5.
I'm still learning but I hope to become fluent someday.
I saw my friend cultivating on her veranda
and thought I could copy her.
A friend's been growing perilla—
uh, herbs on her veranda.
And I kinda want...
How do I say this?
Well, since it's legal, I was thinking I could consume it.
Maybe even grow it, since it seems really simple.
I was thinking that
maybe I could share with everyone in the fifth gen
since it seems like it gets you pretty high.
Let me give an explanation as to why I tweeted "Pawoo".
Explanation? It's an excuse, I guess.
So I was actually trying to test my Twitter,
but I got a bit jumpy
and ended up tweeting just "Pawoo".
And then
people reacted quite a bit to it on Twitter
and I couldn't bring myself to say it was a mistake.
I figured I could keep it
as a part of me, now.
Also, the herb thing is legal so don't worry about it.
I also have permission from
my manager to show that on stream.
It's fine.
Ah! An ambulance is here!
Wait! Don't take me!
Stop!
Okay, hurry up!
You'll make it on time!
You'll be fine!
You'll make it on tiiime!
Subscribe to Shishiro Botan if you liked this!
↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓↓↓↓↓ ↓↓↓↓
Are we good?
Did you screenshot me?
We're good, right?