I want an orc.
Muscle-Brained Female Knight
Shirogane Noel
Necromancer Girl
Uruha Rushia
Are we into fictional pets now?
Hello!
"Can't escape this room
unless you win at Othello"?
There has to be a way
for both of us to escape.
Let's just give it a shot.
I'd rather play black!
I'll take white.
Yikes, yikes, yikes!
I'm going to lose!
Going good.
Whoa, that orc is really detailed!
I can't lose like this...
Not now,
not ever!
My turn.
Wow, you're so good at this!
What a comeback!
How did that happen?
Anyway, I see my path to victory now.
I win!
Man, I lost.
You really are good, Rushia.
N-Now you see what I'm capable of!
Cheat DQ... Sentenced to Othello?
What? Why?
Was it because I slammed the table?
No!
Rushia-chan, you okay?
Huh?
Fubuki-senpai and Mio-senpai?
TL;DR: This game of Othello
was actually Fubuki and Mio,
who'd been transformed by the same strange power.
Were we playing with you as our pieces?
Sorry! I'm so sorry!
She turned into an Othello board.
We really are in space.
Anyway, let's first get the office back to Earth.
And so, we landed on Mars
and discovered a mysterious lifeform.
NASA bought those specimens
for an unbelievable ten billion!
Now loaded, hololive decided to sell
an original version of Othello.
hololive Othello will be available
in mid-December, 7890 A.D.!
We have third-gens, too!
Want!
And 5,870 years later...
Tweet your comments and thoughts using #ホロぐら!