Nerve synchronization enabled
Yomemi is sharing your sense of smell
Gah
Uuugh!
Nerve synchronization enabled
Yomemi is sharing your sense of smell
Waaahaha!
Nerve synchronization enabled
Yomemi is sharing your sense of smell
Oh wow!
Oh no! This is really bad.
Huh? What happened?
Who's there?!
Yomemi-chan?!
What? Fubuki-chan?
Wow! I finally get to meet you in person!
Ehehe, you're making me blush.
But how'd you end up here at hololive?
I made a Hi Potion and it blew up.
And next thing you knew...?
I need to get back somehow!
Or else Étra-chan will...
Hmm... Then why don't I help you look for a way back?
Where would we even start?
In our office, there's no telling what you might find.
No!
What the?!
Wh-What happened here?!
I haven't played Splatoon lately,
so its desire for my attention took physical form.
Wait, that's Yomemi-chan!
Hey, it's Roboco-chan.
Whoa!
Yomemi-chan?!
Why's it doing this?
Thanks.
You really saved me there, Yomemi-chan.
I'm amazing, aren't I.
The best!
We should probably get out of here
before that thing wakes up.
Plus, we might find a way home for you outside.
Then let's go out and have some fun together!
Yeah!
Bubble tea!
This has my seal of approval.
I wanna go to the arcade!
You won't beat me at shooting games.
Is- Is this...
...what the cool kids eat?
Everybody eats crepes.
I can't hold it any longer!
Oh yeah, we don't have restrooms in the office.
Why? Because idols don't need to go.
Augh...
Whoa!
That shock almost made me lose it...
Ooh... It's already so murky... No choice!
We're so lucky they were selling
Anywhere Doors in Virtual Akihabara!
I can go back home then.
You're leaving already?
Eilene-san is probably worried... and stuff.
I see...
But I had a lot of fun today with the two of you!
Thanks!
It was our pleasure! I enjoyed myself, too.
Me, too!
Be seeing you!
Eilene-san! You must be tired from all that work.
Here, have this!
Oooooooooooh!
Delicious!