Yeah, the dark matter went...
Heya!
Looks like we've got the wrong floor.
The office bugged out!
Why's it stretched out so far ahead?
This has to be M*rio!
Hello there.
Help! I'm gonna be molested!
Hold up! I'm not going to do that!
We must go save her!
I don't know. She'll be fine, probably.
Let's just go!
You don't mind if I take this thing out, right?
I don't think it's a good idea
to eat flowers you picked up.
We can't let her sacrifice be in vain.
We must keep going!
Someone's pumped up about this.
Oh, MikoMiko!
I'm not handing Miko-sama over.
But we beat the game! Give Miko-chan back!
You only beat Level 1-1.
Keep going until 8-8.
She worked hard and beat it.
Tweet your comments and thoughts using #ホロぐら!