Extra Edition
Matsuri Natsuiro fluffing her lines
This program is about Gusto(family restaurant) around Japan, which is
fo- holdi......
At the beginning of the program is a short movie named "Introduction to Gust with *blank move",
a special video where we introduce Gusto to you!
Be sure to chuck...
Matsuri-chaaan!
Matsuri-senpaaai!
So clumsy~
Fluffin!
Fluffin-Matsuri!
Let me say it again from "At the beginning of the program"
OK.
At the beginning of the program is the short movie called
"Introduction to Gusto with *blank bo......
*blank boom!
Help meeee!
*blank moove!
With a body language
*blank MOO-VE!
OK.
You'll be OK this time.
Every Friday, switching the host and the revieur...
Every Friday, switching the host and the re...viewer...
OK. Redo.
Every Friday, switching the host and the reviewer... in turn,
the show is published, so make sure
......
MAKE SURE! YAAAAAAY!
MAKE SURE SURE! YAY YAY!
MAKE SURE!
OK.
Every Friday, switching the host and the reviewer in turn,
the show is published, so make sure to watch all of them!
Please watch them~!
This time, the host is me! Matsuri Natsuiro!
Yaaaay!
Good luck!
I'm sorry~!
It's alright
That was super funny
My tongue is destroyed.
MAKE SURE!
"Japan Gourmet Tour" allows you to enjoy featured meals from all over Japan
without getting out of Gusto!
Perfect fair for gourmets hunting for delicious autemn food!
Here's what we introduce this time!
You said "autemn food", didn't you?