August is getting closer...
Dwa-!
Gyaa!!
W-What's the matter!?
That voice...
Ayame-chan!?
Obviously-
It's "me"!
What happened to you!?
Hehe, guess I got tanned a bit.
Well, more like"charred" for you!
The sun could be unstable in the underworld...
How would you explain for your clothes...?
It's a pity they were "bleached"...!
They were my best outfit too...
But!
Being tanned isn’t that bad you know?
You see...
Tada! A "Puppeteer"!
Those cows looked “Croaked”…
Now you’ll even get a free cow puppet too!
-If you win me in a “Cow-Battle” that is.
Most, unwanted.
Gone, choose a cow!
You pick one too...
Well,
I'll choose this one.
Victory looks like mine.
Oh, You're thinking you can’t read the mighty Ayame Nakiri’s mind,
-don't you?
But your "mind" is outrageous todaaaaaaaayyy!
Oww...
Where am I?
A Coffee shop chain that resembles capitalism by its existence, in such place!?
Whew, ain't easy being an elite.
Slapping up tasks and benefits by pandemics!!
It's a mess all over!
Now that you know my secret,
Looks like I cannot let you leave alive...
You can’t just babble out loud your “secrets”!
Heey!
I've come to rescue you!
Let's get out of this pitch black world!
EEk!
An unmanned bike running towards me!?
It's "me"!
Keep in mind of your background!!
Just hop on the bike, pronto!
Alley..oop!
Hey, beastie ears!!
Stop it right there!!
You’re going over the limit!!
Ee!?
Ayame-chan, you’ve got to slow down!
I’d like to do that,
but I don’t know the brakes!!
I’m surprised you’re still going.
Enough small talk!
Exit ahead! We’re going rough!
Yeaaargh! Let me off!!
"Virtual Driving school"
As you can see,
Driving with "vibes" can result in accidents.
Always, be aware of the unexpected. Drive safely!
Now that's "Content"!
"The tan wore off in two minutes."
"Share your thoughts with #ホロぐら"