The office was razed again.
Gotta rebuild it. It's cold out.
I hear ya.
No! My rice ball!
I'm an Undergrounder.
What's up?
Was it a rice ball you lost?
Or was it Oozora Subaru?
Rice ball.
Help me out here!
You get a prize for your honesty.
What is this?
An office sapling.
How can we grow this into an office?
Try watering it.
Fertilizer?
Look, any second now.
The joy of dancing helps people grow.
You must feel the cosmos.
You know, sunlight's gotta be
the most important thing, right?
Koro-san, it's gotten warmer now.
Yeah, so warm!
There's still no office!
Let's start over!
What can we do to make it grow?
It says here that
an Undergrounder's fluids will help.
Didn't work.
You need to be the fertilizer.
Koro-san?
The Korone Company is born!
Yay!
Koro-san's grown so big...