Last time, on Hololive!
I'd just hit the age where even a rolling chopstick seems funny,
Entrance
Ceremony
Holo
Elementary
Junior High
Holo
when I developed a condition that made me laugh at literally anything!
High
Holo
The only cure was to put my adolescence behind me!
By swearing Vows and Restrictions, I attained a rapid growth spurt!
However...
The real world doesn't work like manga.
I must say, this is amusing to watch.
But I had to do something about my condition!
I just couldn't let go!
I had to do it!
Last time, on Hololive!
Despite being a robot, I'd come down with out-of-season hay fever.
What's more, my nose was spewing oil instead of snot!
Tissue
Roboco's oil is everywhere!
I wish I could erase all pollen, from the past, present, future, and every universe, before it was born!
Wow, the floor's slippery
Ow!
Aqua hit her head and lost her memory!
If only I could become a magical girl and erase all pollen!
Last time, on Hololive!
I'm Yamada, and this is all kinda new to me.
See, I lost my memory, but the nice people at the office have filled me in!
Apparently, I owe everyone here a huge debt, so I've been working hard to repay it!
I thought I told you to buy me pork buns?
Right-o! Time to go buy lunch and drinks for these lovely people!
Last time, on Hololive!
The others have been acting strangely lately.
So my name is really Yamada Hermione?
We thought that, by working together, we could overcome our troubles.
We gotta do something about the oil level!
Oil levels?
The amount of oil that's accumulated from Roboco's nose.
Our efforts finally produced an enormous absorbent sheet!
It's clean-up time!
Last time, on Hololive!
One enormous absorbent sheet didn't do a thing to the oil level, and soon the office was flooded!
At last, we decided to relocate our office!
Last time, on Hololive!
It's lunchtime, and Yamada's nowhere to be found.
Perhaps I shall cook for the others today.
They're trying awful hard to tell me something.
But I haven't a clue what!
No matter. I think I shall make vegetable stir-fry.
Brought to you by
Hololive