I smell Winter Comiket.
Where?
Carrot-Lover
Usada Pekora
I feel it in my throat.
Ow.
There.
But that's pek ol' wall.
Anybody home?
Why are you stuck in the wall?
Well, I was practicing teleportation,
and I messed up.
So pekoolish.
Hey, you've got carrots stuck in your hair too!
Unlike you, Shion-senpai,
these come pekout easily!
Huh?
Where are we?
I smell Pekora-chan.
We got stuck in Pekora's hair
in place of that carrot.
How silky.
Like smooth rice!
Listen to me.
Now I'm hungry.
There's gotta be carrots stuck somewhere.
I'll go look for some.
Whoa!
Dear oh dear.
Huh?
We gotta rescue her!
Any ideas?
All I have right now
is some Winter Comiket merch.
That will do!
Huh?
Wait, Shion-chan,
didn't you practice how to teleport?
Ah!
Dear oh dear oh dear.
We made it back!
Wait, where's Pekora-chan?
Huh?
That was the final hologra of 2019!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!