Flare, Marine
Please, muscles
Matsuri, Shion
I really wanna be popular!
Roboco, Rushia
Please, muscles
Matsuri, Shion
I really wanna lose weight! YES!
Mel, AkiRose
Please, muscles
Matsuri, Shion
Because I really wanna be popular
Oh
Pekora, Noel
You've got this!
Matsuri, Shion
Ha
Aqua, Fubuki
You've got this!
Matsuri, Shion
I make a wish to my muscles!
AkiRose , Shion
Hip raise! Side bend!
Flare, Miko
Your abs have a gorgeous six pack!
Subaru, Ayame
Dumbbell curl! Hammer curl!
Mel, Matsuri
Your biceps are like Mount Everest!
Roboco, Rushia
Push-up! Bench press!
Fubuki, Okayu
Your pecs are making strides!
Pekora, Marine
You're almost there! Almost there!
You're a Muscle Man! Yeah, BAM!
Aqua
Once you picture your ideal self
Start training right away!
Shion
Yes, muscles!
Matsuri
If you wanna make it a reality
Do some free weights with a dumbbell in each hand!
Fubuki
Nice macho!
Mio
Don't be impatient, forcing it will sink you
Just focus on weight control
Miko
Yeah, muscles!
Subaru
Go 10 reps at full strength, push it to the limit
You'll be done after three sets
Ayame
Nice form!
Marine
The road is painful to get strong muscles
Strong muscles
Rushia
But I really, really want a hot body
Aqua
To transform myself into a hottie
A hottie
AkiRose
Check out this side!
Mel, Aqua, Okayu, Roboco
Side?
Miko, Fubuki
Side!
Pekora, Marine, Rushia, Noel, Flare, Shion, Mio
Side?
Yeah! Side chest!
Matsuri, Shion
Please, muscles
Mel, Roboco
I really wanna be popular!
Mio, Subaru
Please, muscles
Mel, Roboco
I really wanna lose weight! YES!
Ayame, Aqua
Please, muscles
Mel, Roboco
Because I really wanna be popular
Oh
Fubuki, Okayu
You've got this!
Mel, Roboco
Ha
Rushia, Marine
You've got this!
Mel, Roboco
I want muscles!
AkiRose, Shion
Leg curl! Hacklift!
Matsuri, Fubuki
Those are such intimidating thighs!
Marine, Aqua
Back press! Side raise!
Pekora, Noel
Those machine-line shoulders!
Mio, Mel
Bend over! Lat pulldown!
Ayame, Subaru
A trapezius that houses demons!
You're almost there! Almost there!
You're beautiful when you give it your all!