Poster Dog for a Tokyo Bakery
Inugami Korone
Hope I catch something.
We're in Electric Town, so I don't think you will.
Woof!
But I'm getting a ton of bites.
How?!
Whoa, it's a big one!
I have a bad feeling about this.
Korone!
Oh no! I need to go help her!
I'm back.
Whoa! You're okay?!
Yeah.
By the way, what did you catch?
Not sure, actually.
Human Malice
Uh, it says "human malice" right there.
Huh...
Woof, woof!
Eating the human malice
turned me into a dog-human.
That's my role. Stay out of my lane.
Uh, sorry about that.
Hello? Is this the pound?
There's a stray dog-human you need to take in.
Oh, hey there.
Ookami Mio adopted it.
Tweet your comments and thoughts using #ホロぐら!