This isn't chilled...
Ah, so you can't handle hot stuff
because you're a vampire?
I don't really have any conditions like that, but...
But?
It's weird that we don't have curtains,
don't you think?
Yeah... You've got a point.
Ah, the floor feels so nice and cool.
Wow, she's not doing great.
It's bad news when Mel-sama gets like this.
You were here, Choco-sensei?
If nothing's done,
she'll melt off and shrink in size.
Oh, please...
She melted and shrank in size!
Cute... Too cute!
She's dancing in the palm of my hand.
Phrasing!
Why do we have a beetle in the office?
Beetles are the rules of the tiny animal kingdom.
It must've detected a new challenger
and come to take her down.
Hang in there, Mel-sama.
Looks like our horned beetle
was a horny beetle too.
So pure.
The next attacker's here.
Attacker?!
It's a soot gremlin.
We had one in the office?
Yeah, that's the right way to beat 'em!
Keep at it!
Now we have a soot greMelin.
What now?
We pray to the stars.
I was so distracted by this,
I didn't realize the sun had set.
$%&#
Say what?
I chanted, "May Mel-sama go back to normal"
three times in quick succession.
That's how you time it to a shooting star.
She really is back to normal!
Thanks for helping me turn back,
Choco-sensei, Matsuri-chan.
Nah, I didn't really do anything...
Just having you by my side, watching over me,
gave me immense strength.
Really?
Feel free to ask if you need my help again.
Well, if you say so,
I need some help right now.
Huh?
Looks like the beetles can't get enough of me.
Could you do something about them?
Sensei, what can we do?
"To tell you the truth, I can't stand bugs."
Leave this to me!
Tweet your comments and thoughts using #ホロぐら!