I wanna do this too!
I dd it!
But wait!
I don't know how to stop!
How do I go back!?
Huh!?  Fubuki-chan!?
Fubuki-chan?
Pardon, I'm Altair!
Oh, wrong person then.
Today’s the day of Tanabata,
but because of the sudden rainstorm, the milkyway has flooded...
-and I can no longer meet with my lover, Vega….
... Sooo you’re that kind of person.
But worry no more!
I’ll create a wormhole so that you could meet her!
What are you saying!
That will mean you’ll lose your Twin-pigtail to the nether,
it will disappear from existence!
You will lose your flying capabilities,
-making you plummet down to Earth!
Such thing,
...doesn't matter!
I am the "Virtual Maid"!
My reason is to make everyone in the world smile, and-
...That's my DESTINY!
Aqua-chaaaaaaan!!!
*rain pouring*
Such a pity that it’s raining on Tanabata-day…
Sure is...
Do you think Vega and Altair were able to meet?
... Hah, funny me-
They were.
I know it.
Fubuki...?
TV: " Breaking News"
(Why in the Amazon river?)
"Authority has announced-"
(Suspect Aqua 17 yrs-self claimed)
"-to have caught an illegal traveler..."
Well, at least those lovebirds were happy...
-All OK with me!