Wha!?
Shijimin: Eat rice
Oendancho: Strong roots make strong spirit
Choco: Nailed it.
Hrmm...
Sleep!
Snore...
Tapioca Challenge!!
Having fun borrowing somebody's chest?
It'll spill if I used mine!
That tone...You tried, didn't you
That's stable...
You think it can take more?
Soda bottle!
Too easy!!
An Altlas?
It holds!
PC!
Whoooaa...
A desk!
Really...?
Huh?
Where's that Bubble tea?
Uh, that's supposed to be ther-
It's gone...?
*Heavy rumbling*
It's Katamari Damacy,
...but with Boobs!!!
We're gonna get crushed at this rate!
Don’t you have spells like shrinking breasts!?
Why would I for such pinpoint purpose!
Yeeeaaargh!!!
And so,
The galaxy has been swallowed by Ms.Choco's breasts..
-And that was my dream.
Roboco-sama,
What do you mean by that?
Ah ha ha,
Yar yar!
Ms.Choco, that tickles! heehee
That's it!
Our breasts...
Shion-sama's breasts...
...Has switched places!?
Give me back my boobs!!
Eeeeh?
Mine also became flat as a board…
Yep
Isn't that a bit small for two?
Yeahh?
It means Shion-sama's,
- and my breasts has switched right?
Definitely!
Then,
Where's mine now...?
Where...?
-And that was the dream I saw!
Heeey!
I won't do such thing!?
But,
It's the same three of us here..?
I wonder if this also could be a dream...
"Congrats! Guinenn record: Hololive being the most famous Idol production"
Shion with Breasts?
You get it only on #ホロぐら