This one time,
I was playing the piano
in my high school's music room.
That's when I heard this scream out of nowhere!
It scared me out of my boots.
So I looked in that direction,
but I couldn't see anything clearly.
It remains a mystery to this day.
Thanks for listening.
Oh, there's one left still.
If you blow out the last candle during
ghost stories, one really appears.
What?
I'm going to be too scared
to go to the washroom alone.
I'll go turn on the lights.
Th-Thank you.
That went on for ages.
I was so scared.
But I had fun hanging out with Sora-senpai,
since it's been a while.
Man, I'm starving now.
Wanna cook something?
That sounds good and all,
but didn't Miko-chan and someone
go out on snack run?
I bet they got scared and ran away!
Maybe, yeah.
The lights aren't coming on.
Aren't the switches right there?
Sora-senpai!
Whoa!
You blew it out!
You blew out the last candle!
You're too afraid of this.
I'm more worried about Sora-senpai, really.
The lights aren't coming on,
and she isn't coming back.
Shall we go look for her?
I don't wanna.
C'mon, or we'll leave you behind.
I want that even less!
S-Sora-senpai? Are you there?
Sorry, did I scare you too badly?
The lights just wouldn't come on.
A blackout?
Yeah, so I went looking for this flashlight.
Oh.
Eek!
Y-You okay?
Sora-senpai?
We're back!
And we brought snacks!
Uh, what are you doing?
Huh?
Well, Sora-senpai just...
What's this about me?
When did you get outside?
She was with me, shopping the entire time.
Tweet your comments and thoughts using #ホロぐら!