Comiiing!
Here’s the signature and…Thank you!!
Heavy…
Gnnn…Hrnn
Fubuki!
Some big package there.
Sending address…
None. Let’s see who it’s for…
Morni-Whoa!
Are you okay?
… Well it sure is dangerous here. And a big obstacle too.
I’ll move it on the table just for now.
Awesome!! Nothings impossible to a Hyper-robot like you, Roboko-sempai!
Alley- Oop
Roboko Sempai’s (Shempai’s)(San’s)(My) Armm!!!
Matsuri-chan?
Does this mean I can’t play Fortnite anymore?
You’re worried about THAT!?
Does it not hurt?
Nada.
We’ve gotta catch that arm!!
Not here…
Not there…
Nowhere
To be seen……
It sure is not in this office.
Wheeeeeeree can it beeeee my arrrrrrmm
The very person missing an arm is like this,
seriousness just fades away.
It’s just so tiring looking for it.
Where can it be else…
Speaking of which, I wonder what that package was all about.
It doesn’t say who sent it.
Who is it for?
……Oh, I forgot about that.
It says it’s for you, Roboko-Sempai
Eh?
Isn’t this-
Its Robopko-sempai’s…
My arm!!!
Here..It goes.
I- it attaches just like that…
There’s a letter inside.
Lemme see!
Dear Roboko
How have you been doing?
I only hope that you are living the fullest of your time. Likewise, I have worried your parts had worn out since you play games all the time.
Especially your dominant right arm.
Given that your parts tend to loosen through time,
I advise you to replace yours with the arm included.
Best wishes.
So that’s what happened to Roboko-Sempai
I wonder who sent it after all.
Fufu- I wonder who.
Ah, but you can play games again Roboko-chan! Good for you!
Nnnnn! Of course!
Hey, let’s play Fortnite together this time!
B-but I don’t know how to play-
That’s alright! I’ll teach you how!!
Hmm, I still feel something’s missing…