Hah, the humans are like a—
Huh? What's that?
Time to go pick it up.
I was getting a little peckish, anyway.
I think it was around here...
Wh-What is this?
I've heard of this before.
Some humans take in a Pon ** Ring on a whim,
but can't take care of it as it grows bigger.
In the end, they dump it in an empty lot.
But it grew so plump just
to sate its owner's hunger!
I feel so sorry for this Pon ** Ring!
Hello! Thank you for finding me!
The Pon ** Ring talked?
You're right. I am a pitiful donut
that was abandoned by its owner.
At this rate,
the windows across the street will act
as burning glass and burn me to a crisp.
Before my body turns to ash,
I want revenge on the person
who abandoned me!
Don't! Revenge will only
chip away at your own heart!
I don't care.
As soon as I find that heartless wench,
I'm going to rip her apart.
Help me find her.
Or else I'll rip her apart instead.
I got lost...
Matsuri?!
Were you planning to threaten me all along?
This is the first time I've been glad
that I was born a Pon ** Ring!
Huh? These walls seem kinda appetizing.
It was eaten as its heart desired,
so it can pass on.
Hey, this Pon ** Ring is good.
Let's eat it together.
Yes, let's.
I-I overate...
Her craving was sated, so all's well that ends well.
Tweet your comments and thoughts using #ホロぐら!