*sigh*
I wanna go to the sea...
Both: Agreed
My swimsuit is crying out loud!
Craving to be worn!
So that's why you're wearing it now...
Why don't we "create" one then?
Done!!
Whew, that was a fast.
This isn't what I imagined...
Good enough for me though?
Great fun doing stuff with everyone after a while.
Everyone's suit...
Cuteness...hurts...
No time to lose-
Hn?
What's that!?
I’ve heard about this before…
The ocean, seashore,
-and beauties in swimsuits, all combined...
A cliché scenario for...Sharks!
In conclusion,
It's a Hololive Shark!!
"Hololive Shark"!?
Isn’t "Office Shark" cooler for a name?
*MUNCH*
AAAAAAAAAAAGH!
Ayame-chan!
Huh… This shark is barely nibbling me!?
Shark: I have a JAW problem...
You okay bud?
I've changed my diet to Jellyfish too...
Just a thought...
-Don’t I look a bit like a mermaid?
Huh?
*Everybody screams*
SHARKNADO
Share thoughts by #ホロぐら