[Oo,]
Alas...
[Shinde shimau to wa...]
Death...
[nasakenai!]
should not have taken thee!
[San, ni, ichi...]
Three, two, one...
OH!
[Shinde Shimau to wa Nasakenai!]
Death Should Not Have Taken Thee!
Lyrics, music: Jesus-P
Vocal: Natsuiro Matsuri & Nakiri Ayame
MIX, Inst: Kijibato
[Ou!]
Majesty!
[Nani?]
What?
HELP!
[Nanigoto ja?]
With what?
[Suu!]
Su-...
[Subaru ga sarawaremashitaa]
Subaru has been kidnapped!
[Yuusha wa?]
What of the hero?
[Imasen]
There isn't one.
[Uun, sou da!]
Hmm, okay!
[Kakunaru ue wa omae ga yuusha da]
If it's come to that, you're the hero!
[Settei houkai..!!]
There goes the setting...!!
[Saa, sono takarabako no nakami to kono nakenashi no kane de tabidatte]
Take now the contents of those treasure chests and this paltry sum, set out,
[nakama wo sagashite bakemon taoshite...]
find a party, defeat the monsters...
[..Tekitou janee ka]
...Not taking this seriously, are you?
[Tonikaku komattara machi no hitobito ni hanashi kakeyou ze?]
Oh, and if you're ever troubled, talk to the townspeople, 'kay?
[Bosu toka zenzen taoseru! Taoseru!]
Defeat all those bosses good! Knock 'em down!
[Ma・ji・de!]
For real?!
[Ibatte ibatte ibatte touzen]
Be proud, be proud, be proud, of course!
[Datte jissai ni ichiban erai kara!]
Because you truly are the greatest!
[Hitogoto mitaku itte kureru ze]
Yeah, that's easy for you to say!
[Mattaku motte ue kara mesen sugiru ze]
Geez, you're really on a high perch...
[Keikenchi keikenchi keikenchi tsunde]
Experience, experience, experience, pile it up!
[Motto kukkyou na nakama sagashitamae!]
And find stronger party members!
[Teyuu ka watashi wa ippeisotsu desu]
So you say, but I'm just a soldier.
[Yuukyuukyuuka ga]
Paid vacation?
[DERIITO! DERIITO!]
Deleted! Deleted!
[Sonata ga rasubosu wo taoshite kuru hi wo tanoshimi ni matte oru zoi]
Verily, I wait with bated breath for the day you defeat the last boss!
[Sekai heiwa wo torimodosu tame]
To restore peace to the world,
[Okuni no heiwa wo mamoru tame]
To protect the peace of the land,
[Ichiban ushiro de shiki wo torimasu]
I direct from all the way in back;
[Sonata no keikenchi wo tsutaemashou]
I shall tell you thy experience points!
[Anata no tame ni sekai no tame ni]
Fighting for you, for the world,
[Tatakau bokura no aikokushin]
Recognize our patriotism!
[Nakama mo shinde zetsumetsu sunzen]
We're on the brink of destruction, party fallen;
[Yappari REBERU ga tarinee..]
I knew my levels weren't enough...
[Anata no PAATII wa]
Your party has been...
[zenmetsu shimashita.]
annihilated.
[Oo, kamisama yo!]
Oh, God!
Amen.
[Oo! Shinde shimau to wa nasakenai!]
Alas! Death should not have taken thee!
[Sasureba sonata ni mou ichido]
I will give thee...
[kikai wo ataeyou!]
a second chance!
[Ousama]
Your majesty!
[Nan desu ka]
What is it?
[Mou!]
This is...!
[..Mou muri desu.]
This is impossible.
Eeeh?!
[Wowane wo haku to wa motto nasakenaaaaai!]
More shameful than thy death is thy SAAAAASS!
[Keizairyoku, gunjiryoku tomo ni moushibunnai waga kuni wa touzen]
With the economic and military power of our unobjectionable land,
[Yuushuu na jinzai mo juntaku]
Of course we have people of talent too!
[Jinbou atsui ne]
Such popularity!
[Tada, hitotsu manseiteki na mondai wa kokka genshu no honpou sa]
But the one chronic problem is the uninhibited ruler;
[Yoku ieba muku, waruku ieba..]
"Pure" to put it nicely, to put it badly...
[O・BA・KA]
A MORON.
[Shoushinshoumei]
It's genuine,
[zenjinrui wa]
all humanity is...
[sentou minzoku]
a warring species.
[Iwazu mo ga na (OK?)]
But I won't say it... (OK?)
[Kyouchousei ya]
You're saying...
[junnousei ga]
they need...
[juuyou nante]
cooperative personalities and adaptability?
[(Ukiyo wa kusogee ka?!)]
(Is this world a crap game?!)
[Tsugi no reberu ni naru ni wa]
To reach the next level,
[Ato sen pointo no keiken ga]
Thy experience points must increase by 1000,
[Sara ni wa motto jikoshuchou ga]
But thy also needs...
[hitsuyou ja na]
to be more assertive!
[Kujikeru na]
Don't give in.
OK?
[Terissa Borosso Zanji Paronto]
Telissa, Boroso, Zanshi, Palante,
[Mahoutsukai mo tsukai-mon ni natte kita ga]
Mages sure are maging themselves useful...
[Yoyuu shakushaku usura warai de]
With a calm composure and wry smile,
[Gotaku bakka narabete shaku ni sawaru ze..]
Talking impertinently, I hold my scepter...
[Horitto horitto horitto bakka]
Holit, Holit, Holit, always the same;
[Souro wa horitto bakka de baka nano?]
Monks keep using Holit, are they Holidiots?
[Ou no atashi wo nemurasu nante]
It puts I, the sovereign, to sleep;
[Antara ittai nanisama? Sate wa muhon ka?]
Who do you think you are? Is this a rebellion?
[Boku wa yuusha ja arimasen.]
I am no hero.
[Mushiro ou ga yuusha dato omoimaasu!]
Rather, majesty, I believe you are the hero!
[Sekai heiwa wo torimodosu tame]
To restore peace to the world,
[Okuni no heiwa wo mamoru tame]
To protect the peace of the land,
[Saizensen ni mi wo toujimase]
I throw myself to the front line;
[Shijiritsu appu wa me ni mieta! (Oi kora)]
I can see my approval rating going up! (Hey!)
[Ken'eki no tame okane no tame ni]
Fighting for interests, for money,
[Tatakau ousama nani wo miru]
What does our ruler see?
[Konoe mo hinshi zetsumetsu sunzen]
On the brink of destruction, guards dying;
[Shinde shimau to wa nasakenaaaaaaai!]
Death should not take theeeeeEEEEE!
[Sekai heiwa wo torimodosu tame]
To restore peace to the world,
[Anata no egao wo mamoru tame]
To protect your smile,
[Maougun kanren jouhou wo]
We barely manage to scrape up...
[Inochi karagara ni kaki atsume]
info on the dark lord's forces...
[Kyou mo kyou tote chinza shiteiru]
So today, I just sit here in safety...
[Makoto no yuusha wo matteiru]
as we await the true hero.
[Tarikihongan dewa arimasen]
I'm not getting others to do my work;
[Washira ja yatsura nya kanawanee :;]
It's just I'm no match for those guys... :;
Death Should Not Have Taken Thee!
covered by Natsurio Matsuri & Nakiri Ayame
Lyrics, music: Jesus-P
Original movie: Glider
MIX, Inst: Kijibato
Movie: Rinjin Λ (Lambda)