Lost at this casino
Go to h*ll!
Come on!
3rd Gen: Uruha Rushia
Good evening.
I'm very pleased to meet you.
All of you!
I'm Uruha Rushia!
All of you Fandead
will protect me, right?
First time watcher?
Log in already, will you?!
Come on!
*banging table*
Hurry up and log in!
Will you?!
Oh, crap...
Hololog!
And my dream is...
Sakura Miko
...to become an idol!
I discovered anime and games...
It was the first time I felt, "That's what I want to do!"
Man, I need a frikkin' drink...
I'm done with this crap! Seriously...
Hey, lady!
Change these chips back! My money!
Do it!
Lost at this casino
Go to h*ll!
Stupid casino! You're going down!
Frikkin' casino!
Hololog!
As for what I'm planning to do...
1st Gen: Akai Haato
I'll upload an introduction video
and other themed videos.
I also want to stream video games.
That's good enough, right?
I'm gonna take a sec
to sniff my feet right now.
*lol*
Sniff, sniff...
Gahh... *lol*
They
stink!
This is why...
(Why what?)
Hololog!
Right now, I'm...
1st Gen: Aki Rosenthal
watching you,
you know?
Oh...
Hold on-
I'm getting embarrassed. Let me go back.
Haha...
I'm getting kind of embarrassed.
Kind of embarrassed! *blush*
Ah!
Well,
I mean, it's just Coco-chan.
She can see my butt.
*lololololol*
Ahhh!
Hey!
What are you doing?! *lol*
Natsuiro Matsuri
Quit staring straight up the hole!
Hey!
She wants to poop in my face!
Look at this!
Who's going to poop first?
That is the question.
I could beat her to it
and poop first, after all.
Hololog!
If it's your first time meeting me, nice to meet you!
Tokino Sora
I'm Tokino Sora!
I'm 17 years old and in high school!
From now on, I'm going to be uploading videos
to YouTube as a virtual high school girl!
Yay!
Oh!
Oh, what? Senpai!
Ah! There!
Ooh!
Oh, please.
Enough out of you. *eyeroll*
Okay.
Hololog!
(Creepy BGM)
Gamers: Inugami Korone
There! There! There! There!
Finally.
(The BGM) Oh, sounds good.
Well?
No, no, no! It's freaky!
*lolololololol*
Huh? Don't you think so?
It's not freaky!
Rock-paper-scissors, shout it!
Rock, paper, scissors
Go!
Paper!
Paper! Paper!
Yay!
Hololog!
Oh, people...
1st Gen: Shirakami Fubuki
So many of them...
So many people...
Actually, I've started a Twitter.
It's @shirakamifubuki.
Um...
Shearch-
Search for it, please.
There's a tweet-
※〇÷×
Leeb-
Leabe!
Leabe that... (Slipped again)
Please leave the tongue slipping parts out.
Should I tell you guys about my favorite character?
Stefano Valentini.
Lovely name, isn't it?
This guy→
His birthday is December 22.
That's his birthday.
Shirakami rambles on and on about her love
He's 32 years old.
Yes, he is. His height is 178 cm, if I remember correctly.
Actually, he used to be a war photographer,
so he always carries a camera with him.
Don't worry.
He's Italian. Yes. He's Italian.
It's quiet and peaceful.
Hololog!
From Hoshimachi Suisei's new costume stream
Thanks!
Thank you so much, old costume.
Hoshimachi Suisei
Thank you so much, old costume!
GIRLS in the FRONTIER
Composer: Shitara Tetsuya
Lyricist: Yuta Yashiro
Arranger: Shitara Tetsuya
Matsuri-chan!
Matsuri-cha-
Ahahaha! *lololololol*
Ahaha! *lololololol*
Suisei disguised
as Shirakami Fubuki
Matsuri-chan?
Forgive me!
I'll join your side!
For real?
I'll join you!
I'll do anything!
Really?
Anything!
Anything you want!
You'll join my side?
Sorry,
but your friend Shirakami just
doesn't believe you.
You wanna be revived? Do you? Do you?
Urghhh!
I'm gonna die!