᠎I love you always. Take me in your arms and kiss me
itsudemo I love you. kimi ni Take kiss me.
I cannot forget this precious memory of mine
wasurerarenai kara boku no daijina memorii
If dorayaki cannot become my main diet,
dorayaki wa shushoku ni narenai
I'll just have to overwrite it my way
naraba uwagaki shichaeba boku no omoidoori
I'm always watching by your side,
zutto soba de miteru yo
so leave the backup to me
bakkuappu wa makasete
From left to right, events pop up
hidari kara migi e to dekigoto ga
Here, there, and everywhere
acchi kocchi docchi
Where are you right now?
kimi wa koko ni iru no?
Isn't your birthday still some time away?
baasudei mada saki desho?
I'm reasonable enough not to believe
iikagen ni koyubi kara
in the invisible string of fate
mienai ito shuchou shinai
The sound of a parched heart and the shallow mutterings
kawaita shinzou no oto awai uwagoto
are getting on my nerves precisely because they bother me
shaku ni sawaru nante ki ni shiteru kara ni kimatten jan
Still, we need to have faith, be mannerly and polite to become happy
soredemo shinjite shiawase ni naru youni reigitadashiku
For starters, how about some small greetings?
mazu wa sasaina aisatsu toko kara
Are you ready?
I love you always. Take me in your arms and kiss me
itsudemo I love you. kimi ni Take kiss me.
I cannot forget this precious memory of mine
wasurerarenai kara boku no daijina memorii
If dorayaki cannot become my main diet,
dorayaki wa shushoku ni narenai
I'll just have to overwrite it my way
naraba uwagaki shichaeba boku no omoidoori
I don't want to wake up from this dream
yume kara pipipi samenai de samenai de
This warmth, please don't go away
nukumori nigenaide
The morning is still young, so please
mada asa wa tappuri aru kara
give me five... no, ten more minutes
ato gofun iya juppun matasete
If this goes on for a hundred years,
hyakunengo tsuzuku nara
then let's compress our promise
yakusoku asshuku shite
To the text I sent to the wrong person
machigatta meeru kara
comes a quick and mistaken reply
kanchigai no tekipakiteki
Aren't the ways we drink
sutoroo no kuwaekata
from our straws slightly different?
sukoshi wa chigau desho?
If everyone pretends not to notice,
mite minufuri sareta
then the world will explode!!
sekai ga bakuhatsu shichau!!
I get carried away, but then immediately get shot down
choushi ni noridasu demo sugu ni hekomidasu
Who will put a stop to my magnificent rampage for me, baby?
kareina bousou dare ga tomete kuremasu ka beibee
When I bump into something, I discover some new knowledge as well
butsukareba mata atarashii chishiki hakkutsu
However, I'll only go as far as my stamina can hold out
demo chikaratsukite shimaeba soko made
Oh my god!
I love you always. Take me in your arms and kiss me
itsudemo I love you. kimi ni Take kiss me.
Will the stars grant my wishes for me?
ohoshisama ni negaigoto kanaete kuremasu ka
Carry me to the other side of Earth,
chikyuu no uragawa made boku o hakonde
and let's go on a search for the most beautiful flower
ichiban kireina hana o sagashi ni iku nda
Your burning passion turns into tears on your cheeks
mada kimi no atsui omoi wa omoi wa hoho ni tsutau namida
I will hold your tear drops in my bosom
shizuku wa mune ni tsutsunde
and send them into the sky
todokeru yo sora ni
Ahh
GojimajiP feat. Kasane Teto - Ochame Kinou
(covered by hololive)
Lyrics, Composition: GojimajiP
Arrange & MIX: kijibato
I love you always. Take me in your arms and kiss me
itsudemo I love you. kimi ni Take kiss me.
Will the stars grant my wishes for me?
ohoshisama ni negaigoto kanaete kuremasu ka
Carry me to the other side of Earth,
chikyuu no uragawa made boku o hakonde
and let's go on a search for the most beautiful flower
ichiban kireina hana o sagashi ni iku nda
Your burning passion turns into tears on your cheeks
mada kimi no atsui omoi wa omoi wa hoho ni tsutau namida
I will hold your tear drops in my bosom
shizuku wa mune ni tsutsunde
and send them into the sky
todokeru yo sora ni
I love you always. Take me in your arms and kiss me
itsudemo I love you. kimi ni Take kiss me.
I cannot forget this precious memory of mine
wasurerarenai kara boku no daijina memorii
If dorayaki cannot become my main diet,
dorayaki wa shushoku ni narenai
I'll just have to overwrite it my way
naraba uwagaki shichaeba boku no omoidoori
I don't want to wake up from this dream
yume kara pipipi samenaide samenaide
This warmth, please don't go away
nukumori nigenaide
The morning is still young, so please
mada asa wa tappuri aru kara
give me five... no, ten more minutes
ato gofun iya juppun matasete