I art the king!
King
Sire!
What's going on here?
Korone said she wanted to be a king
out of nowhere.
What?
Your Majesty.
Yesterday's thunderstorms ruined all our farmers' crops.
What shall we do?
Then let them eat shabu-shabu.
That's not a solution!
Your Majesty.
I'm hungry.
Very well. We shall all eat together
after the meeting.
That's one magnanimous monarch.
Noel and Okayu are one thing,
but I'm surprised Choco-sensei's
getting in on the act.
Does she like playing with Korone?
Uh, I don't think
it's playing with Korone that she likes.
Your Majesty, if I may.
What is it, Minister?
The proletariat is rioting against taxation.
They're saying, "Quit taxing us
and tax the fat nobles instead!"
Whatever shall we do?
She just likes messing with Korone.
I can see the question marks on her face!
I'm a spy from across the border.
←Or so the story goes
I'm here to lead the king astray
and make it easier for us to invade.
'Tis only a matter of time before this once great nation falls.
...ter? Minister?
S-Sire!
How may I help you?
You're a spy, so to the gaol with ye.
What?!
Uh, the spy got busted.
Korone's intuition is scary.
Green... Far too green.
She should've taken her time
getting in the king's good graces, like us.
You two also seem like spies,
so it's off to the gaol with ye.
What?!
She's exposing one spy after another
through sheer intuition.
That's three too many spies!
What's wrong with the law and order here?!
Hear me, subjects of the Korone Kingdom!
She started giving a speech
to nobody in particular.
My kingdom has but one rule:
"Be nice to each other, and no fighting."
That is all.
Sounds more like the Korone Kindergarten.
Also, we're having a pizza party starting now!
Your wish is our command!
What?!
Oh, but the spies aren't invited.
No pizza for bad men.
Have mercy!