A long, long time ago,
some kids of a poor woodcutter
were abandoned in the woods.
When will we make it back home?
Don't worry.
I left a bread trail on our way here.
It'll show us the way back.
Gah! What do you think you're doing?!
Don't go off-script!
But I was hungry!
Wait, stop... Stop shaking me. I'll choke.
Hmm... What now?
My, do I spot three delicious-looking children?
I think I'll ensnare them in a trap and devour them.
There!
A gingerbread house!
A food source!
Living with Okayu!
Ah, yikes.
Pardon us.
Huh? The door's open.
You're up, Rushia-chan.
H-Huh?
Humans? Why?
But I'm an Oni.
And I'm an all-powerful necromancer.
It's not a competition!
Why are you here, anyway?
Ahem.
I found this yummy-looking house,
so I figured I could stop by for teatime.
What? The door's not opening!
We've been locked in?
Okay. Got 'em.
I made that door to never reopen once shut.
Oh...
We can't get out.
Hey, humans!
Eek! A ghost!
Rude! I'm a witch!
Hear me! I'm going to, uh,
do something or the other and eat you all up!
Forget your line?
Huh? Okayu?
You're standing up for me?
I'm so happy!
Let us leave, and you'll have a slave for life.
What? No, Okayu!
It'll be Aqua-chan.
What?
Why me? I'm not doing it!
I guess that works for me.
Hold up! You're forgetting to
ask someone for consent!
Oh, I know. I can erase this window with magic.
There!
Ah...
Okay, cut!
That's a wrap!
That was our Han*el and Gr*tel skit.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!