I've been put through hell every time
I've stepped into the office.
I'm dead sure something's gonna happen again!
Okay, whoever loses this game
has to do what the other says!
Bwing it on!
Aight, let's do this!
Wow, I wasn't ready for how normal that was!
I mean, it's for the best.
Great! Looks like I'm gonna have
a perfectly calm, peaceful day.
Awwight. You're eating this.
Don't go wasting food, now.
I knew it! I saw that coming!
Hello there!
Huh? Why aren't you opening the door?
You're on your own here.
Go, go, Su-ba-ru!
Fight, fight, Su-ba-ru!
There's more Dark Matter now!
Ah...
Stop making that face. It's scary.
Shall we go stop them?
Nah, that sounds like a pain.
Let's leave them be.
Luna-chan, do you like Rushia?
What? Quit having these stereotypical
school trip conversations!
Hmm... I don't feel stwongly either way.
No! Luna-chan!
Scary, Rushia-senpai! Too scary!
Just kidding!
Luna-chan!
I wuv you... 'cause you'll eat
this Dark Matter for me.
Ah...
I finally did it! My black sesame-seaweed
Hamburg steak is complete!
Oh, the feels!
I should take a pic.
Ka-shunk!
It may look awful,
but it tastes surprisingly...?
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!