A bomb in the office?
That's right.
Apparently, people saw a roach here
and set it up in a panic.
Talk about going all-out to kill a roach.
Ooh, what's going on here?
A bomb?
Who the hell brought in an explosive?
PowerPoint and Mimicry Expert
Amane Kanata
Hmm? Is that what you're talking about?
Wow, fancy finding a nice bench here.
Crap, it's Andy!
Make like a toy!
We need to disarm the bomb now!
Bomb Disposal Squad, assemble!
Yes, sir!
T-minus three minutes to detonation.
Get to work at once.
We can make instant ra-
If you dare say we can make ramen,
this will be you next time, Kanatan.
It's like we're in Ultr...
And if you say it's like we're in Ultr*man,
this will be you next time, PPT.
How are we looking? Over.
This is the Bomb Disposal Squad.
The mood in here is ice cold! Over!
I see how it is.
The Tale of the Bomb Disposal!
She hung up on me!
Hey, we found some wires.
Oh, C*nan taught me all about these!
Uh, which one are we supposed to cut?
I wonder if those two will be all right...
What are you doing, hiding in there?
The cursed toys passed down generations
of my clan both got destroyed...
Only the bomb remains!
What are you talking about?
Andy!
Hey! Keep it down!
What? Why'd you snip that?!
Why did you snip it?!
Kanatan... Have you never heard of
the "sweet release of death"?
You're totally panicking!
You snipped that out of panic!
It didn't stop!
What do we do now?!
Relax!
Cutting the right cord disarms the bomb,
but doesn't disable the clock!
Really?!
Yeah, I saw it on Yaboo! Answers!
So, this bomb is safe now?
Let's stick it in the freezer, just to be sure!
I'm so sorryacinth.
You are absoraned!
Fin
Next Kanata's Hint:
"Throwdown Challenge"!