Good morning!
Morning.
Good... morning?
In Japan, you greet people with "good morning"
whenever you start work, regardless of the time.
Yeah, the staff said the same thing.
That's how it works.
Uh-huh... But it feels weird.
That's just how it works!
Think up a different greeting, then?
I'm in!
Good afternoon, my little lambs.
Is the good afternoon necessary?
I don't think the "little lambs" part is, either.
Magical Banana!
Bananas remind me of yellow!
Yellow reminds me of bananas!
Hark! A ghastly underbelly!
Rend the ghouls! Rend the ghouls!
Revive the dead! Revive the dead!
I told you, that's just how it works!
C'mere, Little Lom.
I've got a banana for you.
You can't get my little lambs to move out that way.
Listen to me!
It's your shooting star, your diamond in the rough!
That's a rip-off!
Ahoy!
And so is that!
Garchomp!
How very original, Rushia. Attagirl.
Hypno!
You just rehashed her idea.
Nothing feels right.
How about "right-o," then?
Doesn't feel right-o.
Shaddup!
Get 'er, Hypno!
🥺
What? It's morning!
What were we doing?
Trying to come up with ideas for something...
Huh?
Morning.
Good morning.
All of you fall prey to Ayame's hypnosis too!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!