Let's have a nagashi somen party!
In.
I'll handle the eating part.
Same.
I saw this coming and made arrangements.
Can always count on you!
Good luck, Shrimperton!
Go, Shrimpy!
Schwing!
Stare...
Shrimperton wins!
Yay!
Shrimpy... You did your best,
and that's what matters.
Let's release the shrimp back into the sea.
...later!
See you...
Don't play with food!
Shrimpy is Shrimpy, not food or anything.
Don't launch her, then!
And so the Shrimp Family reunited
and lived happily ever after.
While we're here anyway, let's have
a nagashi somen party at the beach.
Good idea.
Let's do it.
Somen! Somen!
My jaws can't wait!
What's wrong?
I forgot the actual noodles!
Yikes.
Get yer somen here!
Haachama-chama!
We'll take all the somen you've got!
You got it! A stack is 200 y—
↓Nagashi Somen Equipment
←Bowl in Hand
↑Empty cooler
↑People in need↗
Obviously a nagashi somen party
10,000 yen!
Daylight robbery!
It's called surge pricing, my dear.
I don't have that much money.
I didn't bring much, either.
Same.
Also same.
Th-Then 5,000 yen will do!
Still too much.
2,000!
Nope.
Ugh... 1,000!
Too pricey.
500!
Almost there!
100 yen!
Yummy!
Huh?
Avoid buying stuff from resellers
and scalpers at exorbitant rates, like so.
Be smart with your finances!
That was one forced analogy.
And another summer memory was made.
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!