I wanna play Tetris
with the girls as the blocks!
Vocalist and Tetris Queen
Hoshimachi Suisei
I-I don't want to die!
We must prevent this!
Hello!
It's your diamond in the rough,
your shooting star,
Hoshimachi Suisei, in the flesh!
Wait...
What happened here?!
I found the office like this
when I came in this morning.
We brought in human-sized blocks to distract her.
Time to stack them!
I'll play a game while I wait.
Heavy...
We filled the blocks with blahblah
to make them super-heavy!
This way, we won't ever
be turned into Tetris blocks.
What are you putting in?
Yaddayadda.
Uh, what? I didn't quite get that.
Let me go grab Noel.
She's got the muscle for this.
I'll play a game while I wait.
Th-This is bad news!
Nah, we should be fine.
Noel's a girl too, you know?
You've come to the right person.
There's some empty space.
Let's go look for more blocks!
I'll play a game while I wait.
We need to do something!
Maybe we should get down from here.
Her arms must be killing her.
Ow!
Gah!
Y-You two all right?
We're fin—
Tetris sure is fun!
This is hololive, where dreams come true.
If you liked this, please subscribe for more!