What's the matter, Fubuki-senpai?
What's wrong, Fubuki-chan?
Houshou Marine
Dressed as a Pirate
A snake!
There's a snake in the office!
There were reports that someone
found a snake on the nearby mountain...
Who was it?!
Who went up the mountain recently?!
B-But anyone would flee the moment
they ran into a snake, right?
R-Right!
Nobody in their right mind would bring
a snake they found back to the office...
Later! Snake it easy!
Hold up!
I apologize!
Let's talk this out!
Untie me and let's talk this out!
Why the heck did you bring a snake here?!
I guess you could call it a mountain high...
Why was a pirate up on a mountain?
Surely you've got a plan, Captain!
Wait, wait! My head's gonna roll!
All I have right now
is the Pop-Up Blackbeard
Matsuri-senpai and I stayed up all night to make.
How is that gonna help?
W-We can use it as a gun?
Blackbeard can be the bullet.
Heh...
Who here can handle grabbing a snake?
Ignored...
Roboco-chan! She should be fine with it!
Good idea! Let me go get her!
5 Minutes Later
I-I couldn't find Roboco-san,
so I grabbed a replacement.
That is the worst possible replacement!
Pekora-chan...
You okay with that?
Look, she fainted!
Get her out of this room!
In this moment, the captain thought...
"Everyone's afraid of the snake.
Only I can save them now!"
<- The Root Cause
Out of the way, Fubuki-senpai!
What is that?!
I'm gonna use this Super Blackbeard
to launch the snake into outer space!
Say what?!
No time to waste!
I'm takin' ye up with me!
Captain!
If she could grab the snake,
why didn't she just take it back to the mountain?
And this is how the serpens constellation came to be.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!