I wanna try doing a raid!
Dragon Maintaining Humanoid Form
with Sheer Willpower
Kiryu Coco
Aw, you're such a handful.
Go for it.
Tch.
Huh? Did you just click your tongue at me?
Okay, we'll play the hololive Clan.
You be the raider.
You've got raid!
What're you, the mailman?!
Kick the door down or something!
Say no to violence.
Says the girl who wanted to go raiding!
Take this seriously!
Fun fact: here at hololive,
we get mail basically every day.
Try again when it's Friday!
It's hard to breathe in this thing.
I said, take this seriously!
Fun fact: the 13th dude has never
used a chainsaw in any of his attacks.
Remember when I promised to kill you last?
I lied.
Ah, it's the one gigantic motherf*cker.
I've never actually seen the movie.
Take this seriously. Over and out.
Fun fact:
in the original, when the baddie goes, "If you want
your kid back, then you gotta co-operate, right?"
he replies with "Wrong,"
but in the Japanese dub, he says "OK!"
TIL.
We're going Jurassic.
And your ad-libbing skill needs work.
How was I supposed to expect
a frickin' dino to show up?!
Wow! Is this thing real?
No fun fact this time?!
Fun fact: the ultimate objective of a raid
is not to annihilate the enemy gang.
It's to break the glass window
that has their crest on it.
It's raidin' time!
Ya little punks!
Yer asses gon' pay for this big time, ya hear me?!
We're terribly sorry, milady!
Scoldings can't dampen her spirits!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!