Oh, but it tasted great.
I know that!
Will she notice?
She didn't!
I wanted to eat the blueberry one more.
Log 004: Prankster Cat's Greatest Hits
*lol*
You've got a nice house,
hololive Gamers: Nekomata Okayu
2nd Gen: Murasaki Shion
Shion-chan.
"Shion's House".
Let me fix that for you.
What should I put?
"Murachaki Shion-sama's Castle".
Oh, she didn't see me.
Murasaki Shion
She's focused on making the house.
See you.
"Show us the sign for the house"?
What the?!
Huh?
How?!
Huh?!
Oh, Okayu-chan...
*lol*
I knew it!
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
Like,
"Let's sleep together",
she said.
She...
When she said "Let's sleep together",
this is what she was up to!
I'll allow it.
I'll throw apples from back here.
Shirogane Noel
Let's see if Noel-chan notices.
Will she notice?
Hm?
She didn't!
Wow, she just picks it up.
She didn't notice!
*lololol*
2nd Gen: Oozora Subaru
Y'know, if I go to Subaru-chan's house...
and put a bunch of pressure plates down,
I'm pretty sure she won't notice.
Pressure Plates: Switches of sorts that react to weight
"Where'd all these pressure plates come from?!"
I want to see her react like that.
Where should I put them?
Ooh!
It blends right in!
Here, and...
here, and...
here.
Perfect.
In Subaru's house
"In Subaru's house"...
What?
I'm trying to finish my house tonight.
Note: Due to keeping her voice down for the late-night stream,
Oozora Subaru ends up sounding like a stud.
What?
You've got all those pressure plates, right?
Huh?
Hold up.
I don't remember putting any pressure plates down.
Huh?
Wait, wait, wait...
Did she do it?
Okayu... Did that girl put some down?
Did that girl do it?
"You probably forgot"—
*click*
Wait, wait, wait... Hold up.
I totally stepped on one!
What do I do now?
Is this gonna blow up?
Hey, I stepped on it. Well?
"Nothing's gonna happen if you step"...
Nothing's gonna happen if you step on them
They don't do anything
Shoot...
*dying noises*
Nrggh...
Nrgh...
Ur...
gh...
hh...
Dammit...
Hololog!
So like...
1st Gen: Shirakami Fubuki
hololive Gamers: Ookami Mio
2nd Gen: Nakiri Ayame
This is totally derailing the conversation,
but before starting recording this Holoradi,
during the pre-recording meeting...
This is really funny!
So, like,
I thought I might get hungry,
so I'd bought a rice ball.
But I forgot to eat it.
I was talking to a bunch of people, and then, like,
these three just started laughing for some reason.
Laughing, like, "Fubuki-chan didn't notice!"
*lol*
I didn't know why,
so I thought they did something to me.
Okayu's always playing tricks all the time,
like putting a Tree of Courage strap on me.
Right, I put a Tree of Courage key holder on Fubuki-chan's bag.
Yeah, she put a key holder on it.
At first, I thought that was it,
but then I'd already noticed that,
so I didn't know what it was.
Then Okayu was like,
"Fubuki-chan, it's in my stomach."
The second she said it,
"My rice ball!"
*lol*
My pollack roe rice ball! She just went and ate it!
Oh, but it tasted great.
I know that!
I bought one because they're good!
On a trip, Inugami Korone bought
dessert sandwiches for the girls...
So there were two more sandwiches left,
and she asked, "Who hasn't had one?"
And I said, "I haven't had one!"
And Korone asked,
"Do you want the banana or the blueberry sandwich?"
"Banana!"
I tried to take the wrapper off the sandwich,
but the wrapper wouldn't come off,
so Okayu-chan was like,
"Subaru-chan, I'll take that for you."
And I was like, "You'll take it off? Oh, thanks."
So I was talking to someone else,
and then I looked at Okayu.
The wrapper was off,
and she was eating it.
*lolol*
*lol*
Ahaha *lol*
Oh, and like,
Okayun was sitting across from me,
and I saw her quietly taking the wrapper off.
Subaru was talking to someone...
I think she was talking to Mio-chan?
Yeah, we were talking.
Like, "Yeah, yeah!"
She wasn't watching Okayun,
so I was like, "Okayu's definitely eating that."
And then she did...
Stop her, Ayame!
Why didn't you stop her?!
Yeah, like,
before I ate it, Ayame-chan's eyes met mine, and we were like...
Smirk.
*lolololol*
Like, "Do it! Do it!"
*lolol*
Just like she did with my pollack roe rice ball!
And what did she say while she was eating the banana sandwich?
I wanted to eat the blueberry one more.
Log 004: Nekomata Okayu Prefers Blueberries
Prankster: Nekomata Okayu
Victims:
Murasaki Shion
Shirogane Noel
Oozora Subaru
Shirakami Fubuki
If anyone caught your attention, come join their streams!
Extra
Ladies and gentlemen of the court,
I present this video for your examination.
'Kay.
Despite taking Shion's first kiss,
you then flirted and led on other girls.
This is unforgivable.
I am suing you for infidelity.
She did flirt and led everyone on.
Minato Aqua thought she was number one
And like, like, like,
what's this about a kiss?!
Hey. Hey!
What's this about a kiss? Well?
Well?
What's this about? Well?
Well...
I did kiss Shion-chan.
*lolol*
You told me that you loved me!
But I do love you, Aqua-chan.
See?! Just like that!
Nekomata Okayu...
Guilty as charged!
Thank you very much.
Prankster: Nekomata Okayu
Victims:
Murasaki Shion
Shirogane Noel
Oozora Subaru
Shirakami Fubuki
Minato Aqua
If anyone caught your attention, come join their streams!