Zzz...
R... Ramen...
What the...
So you've awakened.
Haato-chan? What're you doing here?
I moved the sofa.
Is all this stuff on the floor... caltrops?
Mm...
Bingo!
I was having so much fun,
I strewed them all over!
FYI, I'm stuck here with you.
Not something to be smug about!
Wait, is this one of those lamps
that can grant your wishes?
Hoshimachi!
Oh, it's just Sui-chan.
Need help?
Do you need help?
Yes
No
Don't know
Probably
Probably not
No, it's Ak*nator!
I'm stuck here! This sucks!
I shall grant one of your wishes for you.
Awesome! Now we can get out of here!
...
Matsuri-chan?
Haato-chan, you see...
What?
I really want some ramen right now.
Can't you move that down the priority list?
Sui-chan, I want ra...
She wants a ravishing lion!
My ramen!
I'm so sorry! I didn't know what to do!
Hey, Lion, can you get me some ramen?
Comin' right up!
Ramen!
Hmm? No, wait...
It's Sui-chan!
Hoshimachi!
Need help?
Do you need help?
Yes
No
Don't know
Probably
Probably not
No, it's Ak*nator!
Yay! Get rid of these caltrops!
Take me to a ramen place!
What am I supposed to do now?!
Hmm?
That's not a caltrop! It's a soot monster!
Mm... Bingo!
You win a trip to an island to the south!
Hooray!
Haachama-chama...
Brr...
Welcome to the South Pole!
Nothing beats ramen over the Bon holidays!
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!