Aqua VS Shion
Neighbor Wars:
Sunshine Dispute Arc
I -
Eh?
-> Aqua's House (on the left side)
<- Shion's House (on the right side)
This isn't good, is it?
Because the sunlight is coming from this side,
my house on the other side became darker.
Look!
My right to sunshine is being infringed!
Oi!
This is a lawsuit!
I'm going to sue!
I'm going to give her a notice!
I'm suing!
I will sue!
"Because you have violated my right to sunshine...
...I'm going to sue!"
Let's write an alias.
Neighbor A sounds good!
Alright...
Looks good.
Wait, how much should I get for compensation?
I should ask for some diamonds.
2 diamonds.
2 diamonds as compensation!
I'll sue her for that!
I'll ask for 2 diamonds.
I'll sue!
I heard
that whoever lives next to me is angry.
Seems like she's angry.
Look at this!
Can you read it?
"I'm suing you for violating my right to sunshine.
The reason should be obvious.
Your beautiful house right beside A's house is preventing the sunlight from reaching it!"
Let's place a lot of torches.
Here, there's your light.
fuhahaha
I'll say to her, "This is what you wanted, right?"
Let's make it brighter.
*poke*
Ow
Ah!
Let's do that!
"I have been injured by your berries"
"I made your house brighter,
but I was injured by your berries!"
I request compensation!
It's a little bit dark.
It's still dark, huh.
It hurts!
It hurts! Ah, compensation, compensation!
It's still dark even though I placed some torches.
Maybe my house is really...
But still!
It's still bright.
On the first look, they are shining brightly.
Aren't they?
I think it's decent.
"I made it brighter.
I was injured by the sweet berries in front of your house.
I demand a trident as compensation.
Your neighbor M"
Hmm...
I see.
I just remembered.
Come to think of it, I haven't solved the neighborhood issues.
I have trouble with someone in the neighborhood!
Wait a second, this is a problem!
Wait, what should I do now?
Hey you guys, what should I do? This is a problem!
She got me!
When you say trident, I don't think it means only one thing.
For example,
It's just an example here,
Can I name it?
If you name this "trident", it's still a "trident".
How about this?
Oh, this can also become a "trident" by just naming it.
Now I found something!
Do I use a wooden sword for compromise,
or use sweet berries because she got me with it,
and then make it her trauma?
I think I'm going to give her a full stack of sweat berries.
These.
Ow.
Ow, ow, ow.
...and wait for some recovery...
then go like this...
Wait, I'm going to die at this rate!
I can't pick up the inner ones.
Owowow
This berry field has a design fault!
What in the world?
Even the householder is getting hurt from this.
Just pick them up for now,
now I got a full stack.
This is good!
They kind of look like tridents now.
This is the real trident. Good.
I'm done with the preparation.
Here...
Bop
"I brought the goods you demanded.
Please forgive me!
Influenza Type A"
Tridents?!
Let's check what's inside.
"Trident"
Aren't there more berries
around my house?
Like, we didn't have berries here, right?
Here and here.
Hey, who did it?
My neighbor's house? Hey, damn you!
Oi!
Ouch, ouch!
Excuse me!!
Hey, excuse me!!
Hey you! Let me in!
You did something, huh?! Let me in!
Let's just get in.
Eat this cake a bit.
A prank where you take just two bites of a cake.
I don't think I can ever get along with my neighbor.
Aqua VS Shion
Neighbor Wars:
The House Explosion Arc
I have made a berry road underneath Shion's house with the underground gateway.
Also with a perfect camouflage, like this.
Look!
Not suspicious at all!
And also...
(Chat: ) It has been widened.
Yeah, I have widened it for today's stream.
I've made it this far.
Well, on the other side, I mean the neighbor would think:
"It worked! Now Aqua can do absolutely nothing to my house."
Except that's not the case!
I actually made a berry road on this side,
and a secret path to it inside the neighbor's house.
Isn't this really dope?
Finally. It is complete!
Minato Aqua's Underground Aqua Line.
Where are my bees?!
Where is my honey?
Because it IS honey.
*applause*
I see a hole there.
Huh?
Wow.
(Chat: ) That hole is called the main entrance.
"Main Entrance"
Hey, how dare you do this to someone else's house?!
Wait, does that mean...
she comes out here like this, and...
she regularly comes to my house?
Ooooi!
Mysterious
*ultra scream*
Wait, this is amazing!
Oh no!
This is...
I might have saw something that i should never see
Amazing!
Isn't this amazing?
Is it okay to see this?
amazing!
Should i keep that secret?
Should i place a sign that says "our shared home"
or is it better to keep it secret?
"A trespasser then"
A trespasser
"She frequently sleeps on your bed!"
*maniacal laugh*
She slept here?
Nice
* something about smell *
O. K.
That was fun!
I think this entrance was compromised
Rumors said that this entrance was found out
Minato Aqua Line Corp
is going to take actions
Right,
in here
umm...
i want to make some kind of traps
that looks deadly when you enter it
What's going to happen if i do this?
It's done!!
How's that!
Like this?
It's doneeee!
"As of today, Aqua line is closed.
Let's write "Aqua line is closed, goodbye." instead
My neighbor is definitely going to be sad
She might feel annoyed when this exists,
but when it's gone, she'll feel lonely
I want to visit the resource server today
since i've got some treasure maps, i'll take them with me
I think this is it
Hang on, let's play around in here again
Has it changed, i wonder.
Ehh!!?
Wait, it's closed!?
Whe-
Ah...
Wait, i can't get out!
Wow amazing!
minatoaqua joined the game
Oh no, this is bad!
oh no x6
oh no x7
She's here!
*Volume warning*
I'm going to eat the cake since i'm hungry
O. K.
Right
this isn't good x5
Oh no!
Oh no!!!
Wait
This is bad!
This is bad!!
That scared me
Scary x3
Where is the resource server?
Right here?
*kon-aqua~!!!* (Helloqua)
Let's send this!
It is important to say the usual greetings
Where am i?
This is the place?
Ah! this is it! Wow!
Alright! With this,
i can say something like, "What's up? I'm currently in the resource server"
Honestly.
that was a flight or fight situation
What's going on?
"Shion-chan, i'm really sorry"
scary
Scary! What happened?
"I honestly didn't want to do this"
minatoaqua: "I'm really sorry"
Shion: Stop it! What happened?
What is going on?
minatoaqua: "Your house is..."
minatoaqua: "Something bad happened to your house"
EH!?
Ohh
It's tough to enter from here
She looks like a scolded cat
I'm going to scold her
I'm scolding her!
I'm really sorry!
I'm sorry!
Shion-
Shion-chan
I'm sorry!
I was trying to place a bunch of TNT in your house before you come back
So you'd be surprised
That was the plan
But it exploded when i placed a redstone
I'm really- I'm really sorry!
I'm going to fix your house!!
Actually, there is a place where i want to move in
I want a house in here
Eh!?
Well, uh
I can't make it any bigger than a dog's house though
Even so,
If that's okay for you,
i'll reflect on my self!
I want my house fashionable
Fashionable?
alright, then...
I'm going to make it fashionable
i'm looking forw-
Tell me when you're done
I'm looking forward to it
What are you laughing at?
Aqua: It is done!
Shion: Hold on...
I have built your house!
Please enter the house
These are my offerings
It's sliding
Aqua: Here's my offerings
Shion: It's sliding
Shion: The carrots are sliding
Aqua: Please eat properly!
I will fix your house too
Ah, really? Thank you~
I am done!
It's done?
It's done!
I'm going to take a look
I sure hope it looks pretty
It's hard to enter from here
What is this?
This is umm...
I'm matching the style with the 2nd floor!
It does looks fashionable
What do you think??
Shion: I see...
Aqua: thank you
I see
Thanks
I would like to sue
Aqua: *Panics*
Please!
Please let me off the hook!
Aqua: Please...
Shion: don't eat your bread right in my face
Aqua: *intense nom nom nom*
Aqua: Please let me off the hook!
Shion: don't eat your bread right in my face!
Aqua: It hurts!
Please forgive me!
I have a pressure plate
What is that?
Eh?
This is dangerous, isn't it?
Aqua: This is dangerous
Shion: This is dangerous
No-
eh?
Let's go with this
As compensation
"[Shion's cat] was caught in an explosion"
"minatoaqua was blown up by murasakishion"
Being blown up is a terrible way to go
Bonus Meme
She me to play with her?
Cute~
This is aqua's grave
This is her grave
Alright
Eh... Isn't this like...
It's just the two of us here
Ow! Eh!?
Eh!?
"minatoaqua was slain by murasakishion"
"murasakishion has just earned the achievement [DIAMONDS!]
"murasakishion has just earned the achievement [Acquire Hardware]
"⚓️Minato Aqua"
"RIP"