Passions burn but for a moment,
irozuku omohi wa setsuna hyakka ryouran hanafubuki
filling the air with blooming blossoms
hololive IDOL PROJECT
Hyakka Ryoran
Hanafubuki
Blooming Blossoms Fill the Air
Vocals: Shirakami Fubuki, Nakiri Ayame, Ookami Mio
Lyrics, Composition: Takeda Masahiro (Dream Monster)
Arrangement: Takagi Ryuichi (Dream Monster),
Takeda Masahiro (Dream Monster)
Pop, they bloom and scatter,
pa to saite chitta hana wa owari mi o tsuketeku
setting their hips as the season ends
Lying in wait for your time patiently
sono toki o matedo kurasedo koto wa susumazu
will give no ground gained
Softly, my hand I placed there,
sotto furete shitta mune no uchi no atatakasa o
finding a warmth grow within my breast
Experiencing this feeling the first time,
hajimete no kono kimochi dake dakishimeteitai
I wish to hold it near
The promise that we made at the dawn was
akatsuki kawashita yakusoku wa
“real,” that is certain
“honmono” datte kitto
So I will believe
shinjiteru
The blossoming colors are fragrant,
iro ha nihoheto no hana ni miserareta shoujotachi
but the girls that they have charmed
Oh, they flutter, flutter, flutter,
aa harari harari harari ochiru hana to maiodore
dancing with the flowers as they fall
Though all in this world is destined to change,
wa ka yo tare so demo omoi kotonoha ni kometemita
we still put our passions in words
All that lives longs for it,
dare mo mina kogareru gense no kotowari yo
that is the law of this world
Passions burn but for a moment,
irozuku omohi wa setsuna hyakka ryouran hanafubuki
filling the air with blooming blossoms