Hmm?
Whoa! What's gotten into Roboco-san?
Apparently, the seasonal humidity can make her rust,
so she's maintaining her most relaxed posture.
Eek?!
What was that noise?
R-Relax! It was nothing!
Just a stray breeze...
What is that liquid?!
What kind of bodily fluid is that?!
I-It's just curry!
She took a dip in curry in yesterday's stream and all...
You're not fooling anyone!
It's definitely oil!
Hurry up and wipe it!
What now?
It all spilled out...
Let's just keep this between the two of us...
'ello!
Korone!
Help!
Huh?!
I see...
She had an oil spill.
What do we do?
Gotta give yourself up.
Here, a cross and stake.
Crucification?!
Haato-chan...
You'll drive stakes into my hands?
I won't!
Settle down, Shion-chan!
Listen up! If she's just lost her oil,
we can fix that with a refill!
Makes sense.
Why am I being lectured too?
I found some in the kitchen earlier!
What's that?
Olive oil?
Mind if I leave?
We fill 'er up...
Perfect!
It's all over!
All three of us are going to jail!
Wait, I'm an accomplice?!
'kay. Time to bounce.
Absolutely not!
You're staying right here with us!
Hey, you started it all!
I tried my hardest to help, okay?
I'm back!
Huh?
Roboco-san?
But Roboco-san's right here...
Oh, how'd you like that?
I got a new canteen.
It can store a bunch of curry!
Misleading as hell!
No! My canteen!
Curry is a drink!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!