I wanna get over my shyness.
Demon Who Loves Her Silly Pranks
Tokoyami Towa
Okay, I'll play the shy one.
You be the extrovert.
G-Got it!
Why the role reversal? This your first time?!
Doing what?
Why say "knock your socks off"
when the shoes go off first?
Who cares?!
Focus on interacting with me!
I'm too shy for this.
Can I pretend I'm asleep?
Too late for that!
Look at me.
My eyes!
Yay!
Prank successful!
That wasn't a prank! Just wack!
By the way, why were you in that locker?
I lost consciousness as soon as I came in,
and when I woke up I was in there.
It was me. I did it.
Prank successful!
Yay!
Look up "prank" in the dictionary!
I had to do it! I'm too shy
to hold a proper conversation!
Help! Serial killer!
Look! Tiny Kanata!
The brain's adult-size!
Tell me this is a bad dream.
Prank successful!
Yay!
You guys have gotten "prank"
and "wack" all mixed up!
I smell a case, so I'm going to go look for it.
Edogawa!
Don't say that like you're saying "Laters!"
What kinda case?
Putting an idol to sleep
and stashing her in a locker.
The culprit already confessed! Case closed!
Huh? Where's Towa?
She's pretending to be asleep.
Now that's a case!
I don't think she's pretending!
I smell a case in the air somewhere...
It's right there!
Look, she left a dying message!
Worst handwriting ever!
It says, "Why say 'knock your socks off'
when the shoes go off first?"
You're alive?!
You've been prank'd!
Yay!
Like I keep saying...
Wait, I guess that was a prank.
And that completes five straight weeks of debuts!
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!