hololive 4th Gen and idol otaku,
Amane Kanata here!
You can get your hands on your own copy of
hololive 1st Fes. Nonstop Story,
held on Jan. 24 at Toyosu Pit.
To think I'll be able to re-watch the concert
we saw that day as much as I want in HD!
I wasn't able to see my senpai's
shining moments through the tears,
but now I can return to, rewind, and even pause
every moment to my heart's content!
hololive 1st Fes. Nonstop Story Live Blu-ray
will be available at BOOTH from July 24!
I'll buy copies to watch, keep, give away,
and add to the shuriken on my head!
Hey-yappi!
It's hololive 4th Gen's Tokoyami Towa-sama!
hololive 1st Fes. Nonstop Story's
Blu-ray is finally going on sale!
Whether you were at the concert itself,
or were watching it online like us,
or weren't able to watch it at all,
if you buy this, you would―
Yeah.
Yeah, that kind―
You'll, umm―
―have the best time―
Yay!
―of your life.
hololive 1st Fes, Nonstop Story Live Blu-ray,
will be available at BOOTH from July 24!
All of us 4th Gens want to stand
on that stage someday, too.
Do do do do do!
Just a hololive fan passing by―
hololive 4th Gen's Tsunomaki Watame!
Performed on Jan. 24 at Toyosu Pit,
hololive 1st Fes. Nonstop Story
makes its disc debut?!
You'll see all my senpai singing, dancing,
and talking in 3D?!
You get to watch the performances that
brought me to tears as many times as you please.
This deal is so good, it's practically free!
hololive 1st Fes. Nonstop Story Live Blu-ray
will be available at BOOTH from July 24!
I wanna sing on that stage too, someday...
hololive 4th Gen's hella cute dragon, Kiryu Coco here!
Don't you wanna see my senpai take in the cheers
of their beloved fans in person
and shine on stage as true idols?
This is hololive!
They are idols!
Feel the magic from half a year ago at your fingertips!
hololive 1st Fes. Nonstop Story Live Blu-ray
will be available at BOOTH from July 24!
It's hololive 4th Genewation's Himemori Luna!
hololive 1st Fes. Nonstop Story's
Blu-way is about to go on sale!
My usually goofy senpai are acting like weal idols...
Their intense performance
made my pound go heawt-heawt!
hololive 1st Fes. Nonstop Story Live Blu-way
will be avaiwable at BOOTH from Juwy 24!