Log 005: When the Idols Have Laughing Fits
Natsuilol Matsuri
1st Gen: Natsuiro Matsuri
*drunk laughter*
*drunker laughter*
*even drunker laughter*
Bwahaha!
My sides!
Sakura Miko
Gwah
Sakusa Miko
Sorry.
*laughter*
*desk -1 HP*
Gwah
*elite laughter*
2nd Gen: Minato Aqua
2nd Gen: Murasaki Shion
2nd Gen: Nakiri Ayame
Minato Cackua
Nyukiri Ayame
*Desk: Ouch x1*
*Desk: Ouch x2*
Murasakek Shion
*Desk: Ouch x3*
*Desk: Ouch x4*
*All together now!*
*Desk: Ouch x5*
*Desk: Ouch x6*
Ho-Ho-Houshou Marine
3rd Gen: Houshou Marine
*Aho-ho-hoy*
*Arr arr arr*
*Me hearties*
Tokino Sora
Teeheeno Sora
*bewitching laughter*
*dog laughing*
2nd Gen: Yuzuki Choco
Lulzuki Choco
Aki LOLenthal
1st Gen: Aki Rosenthal
That's so funny!
Log 005: Laugh Along with hololive
Extra
Note: She's using a voice changer
Use the kiss sticker more! Come on...
4th Gen: Himemori Luna
Come on... do it like you always do!
*Baby giggles*
haa...
I can hear myself here.
I weally can't deal with this!
If anyone caught your attention, come join their streams!