Halloween! Halloween!
Halloween!
But Halloween's long over!
Desk: -100 HP
H-Hallo...
Halloween's long over!
Hallowah!
Let's just leave.
Halloween isn't over yet!
Hallow?!
But it's late December now.
Mio.
It's still Halloween, right?
Yes... it's Halloween.
Halloween! Halloween!
Halloween is long over!
Huh?
Halloween's over.
It won't come back,
no matter how much you scream its name.
Those days are gone.
It's time for hololive to face Christmas!
Floor: -10 HP
You sure?
Let's sing.
Jingle bells, jingle bells,
jingle all the way!
Today is part of a fun Christmas time.
Sorry, Rushia.
Thank you.
Have this.
Rushia...
Sure is warm this winter.
Enjoy 2nd fes!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!