I'm gonna do ASMR!
So it turns out I'm gonna be doing an ASMR stream.
Well, it's not set in stone just yet...
But yeah, I'll be doing ASMR.
Or it's looking that way, at least.
Save Electricity Month
Turn off the lights!
So I guess I'll need some nice background music to use!
I know how this works, okay?
I know all about ASMR. I read up on it, okay?
First, I'll play some pleasant background music.
Choco-sensei said, "Just play some random jazz piece."
Time to look for jazz.
Ain't got any!
I don't have any jazz,
so I guess I'll go with recorder music?
hololive 2nd Gen
Oozora Subaru
ASMR time!
Good evening.
It's me, Subaru.
Wait, wha...
Oh, shoot!
I'm supposed to keep it down.
Listen...
I'm not Donald D*ck!
Stop saying I sound like him, seriously!
Let the waves soothe your ears.
Waves...
Ouch!
Oops.
Waves...
lololol
That wasn't Donald swimming in the lake!
Not Donald!
Donald... Donald D*ck is not swimming in the lake!
Stop saying Donald's swimming in the lake!
That wasn't Donald swimming...
It wasn't Loch Ness either!
Not a monster!
There aren't any monsters here!
hololive 2nd Gen
Yuzuki Choco
ASMR is all about pleasant whispering.
ASMR.
Listen, Subaru-sama,
I'm afraid you're not cut out for ASMR streams.
What? Why? I can totally do ASMR!
ASMR!
ASMR...
*furious typing*
You don't have to get so irritated, Choco-sensei!
I'm not!
You were banging on that keyboard!
Source Stream
We're awaiting your fanwork submissions at #ホロざんまい!