Eeek!
You piece of trash...
AAAAARGH!
Go die in a fire!
Log 002: Hololive Scream Exhibition
For the thrill-seekers
Senpai isn't here.
Gamers: Inugami Korone
He didn't get attacked or something, did he?
Hyaa!
Jerk.
3rd Gen: Shiranui Flare
Hey! What the hell?!
What's with you?!
Excuse me.
Sakura Miko
Waah?!
What a creep!
You're such a creep!
"College is fun!"
Hoshimachi Suisei
Oh, you think so?
Haaah?!
You piece of trash...
Damn you...
Work...
2nd Gen: Murasaki Shion
Waaah?!
Geez!
I'm gonna strangle you.
4th Gen: Kiryu Coco
Uhh...
Argh?!
Oh, hell no!
4th Gen: Tokoyami Towa
Waah?!
Creep.
1st Gen: Natsuiro Matsuri
The boss is not in.
I should go clock in.
Aaaaahhh!
Go die in a fire!
Hololog!
For the comfort seekers
Ah.
4th Gen: Tsunomaki Watame
Turn the flashlight off and...
Whoa?!
That was so scary...
Murai-senpai!
2nd Gen: Yuzuki Choco
Gaaah?!
That startled me!
Come ooon.
4th Gen: Himemori Luna
We've covered the entire floor awready.
Ohh...
We've awready got it.
Eeek!
1st Gen: Aki Rosenthal
Aaah!
Can you stop that?
Or else I'll make you live
the rest of your life as my servant.
1st Gen: Yozora Mel
Aaaaagh!
No!
Keep running!
Run! Hurry!
Hurry! Hurry!
Ugh!
Boss...
Roboco San
Is that guy playing hookie?
He sure is...
He's totally playing hookie.
I should―
Waaargh?!
Man, that scared me!
You're the worst.
1st Gen: Akai Haato
Gyaaah!
No more, no more, no more!
No more...
Surprise?
That didn't surprise me.
Gamers: Ookami Mio
The sparrow is samba...
Samba!
Everyone is sl...
Waaargh!
Ahh! Ahh! Ahh!
Ah ahh...
Ahh...
I can't take any more...
2nd Gen: Minato Aqua
S'cuse me!
S'cuse m—
Aaaaargh!
Ah, hold on!
Hold on a minute!
*Falls out of chair*
Did I check the piano?
2nd Gen: Nakiri Ayame
Comment: Did you check the piano, Milady?
Piano? No, I didn't.
Oh!
Wha― Whaa?!
That spooked me!
Ahaha...
2nd Gen: Oozora Subaru
Yo, bossman! I'm here!
Bossman—
Hya?!
I'm gonna quit!
I'm gonna quit this job!
Hololog!
The Role Model Scream Award
4th Gen: Amane Kanata
Huh? Why isn't anyone here?
Gaaah!
The Soul Ascension Award
Murai?
3rd Gen: Usada Pekora
Is he skipping work?
Murai?
Murai's not her—
Aaahhh?!
The Cat Award
Haa... haa...
1st Gen: Shirakami Fubuki
Eek!
Meow!
The Stranger Award
'kay, here we go.
3rd Gen: Shirogane Noel
Waaah?!
What?!
"Gotcha! I surprised you, right?"
Huh?
We're not that close.
The Snarl Award
Am I the only one on shift tonight?
3rd Gen: Uruha Rushia
Wahh?!
You!
The Unfazeable Award
Tokino Sora
I like the pizza flavor.
I wanna eat one.
Oh!
Oh, what? Senpai!
The Dora*mon Award
Gamers: Nekomata Okayu
Ahh?!
Hoo!
Boo!
The Noisier Than the Monster Award
3rd Gen: Houshou Marine
Ah! Ah―
What? What?
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
"There's a flashlight in the first room."
There's a flashlight in the first room.
AAAAARGH!
AHH!
NGAA! AH!
EEK?!
Eee?!
EEEEE!
Ee... ee... ee...
Log 002: The Screams of Idols Sure Are Delish!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!