Ahem. It's time to begin our remote meeting!
But what are we going to talk about?
That's what this meeting will decide! Boom!
So, long pekory short, we're just gonna chat.
What tea would you all like?
I'll take, uh... green tea.
Not drinking it?
I can't. It's impekossible.
I'll have it, then.
What...
Anyway, it's always hard to
choose a discussion topic.
I'll go ahead and draw our agenda
from this box, then!
When did you pekonjure that up?
A remote jam session!
We Stay Home Dreamer now?
I'll play the handpan, then.
Let's go with something
a little less complicated?
Do another draw.
Fine. One more time...
Remote Jam Session
Was that the pekonly idea in there?!
Can I just say I'm starting to get hungry?
Follow the convo! And eat rice!
I have a leftover riceball
from the batch I made last time.
Give it to me!
Gimme, gimme, gim...
Aww...
This is wearing me pekout.
I'm starting to get a headache.
Is your brain okay?
Did you just diss me for peko reason?
Why wasn't I invited to join?!
My legs... are giving pekout...
That's the camera from back then...
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!