The office reeks today.
Shiranui Flare
(Yes, that's how her name is read)
I can't tell, because I'm trying not to breathe.
But why?
Summer's coming up, so I'm looking to
increase the time I can spend underwater.
And what is your end goal?
To be the ultimate VTuber!
I think you need a better gameplan.
Here we have the kusaya fermented fish
I bought for a stream.
What do we do with it?
Throw it away.
Hey, we can't waste food like that!
Don't be a bad girl!
Eat it at home, then!
Why would you bring it here?!
R-Rushia?
Gah! It stinks!
Rushia...
So that's the cause of the stench.
Oh, want some?
Not on your life.
Wow, she came back in a hurry.
I've heard that ginger and leek
can help alleviate pungent odors.
What do you even need me for?
I'll go put her back where I found her.
Please adopt me
This pekouldn't possibly be right!
Let's try stewing all this together.
No good.
The fish is too strong.
It turned the ginger and leek to ash.
Is that... really just kusaya?
What else can we turn to?
Why are you pinching your nose?
Because it reeks?
Trying to increase the time I can spend underwater.
Haven't you been at it for, like, an hour?
I... I can't take it anymore.
Hey, don't inhale so deeply near the kusaya!
Noel!
Damn it, Marine. Don't dump this on me.
Ah.
Flare.
Doesn't your hair feel strange
with nothing sticking out of it?
No way... You're not suggesting...
Just kidding.
You know I wouldn't do that to you.
Flare!
And then Pekora's tears flooded the city.
The kusaya returned to the sea, where it once belonged.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!