The Toyosu PIT concert is this weekend!
It's almost here!
Really?!
Huh?
I had no idea.
How is that possible?
Don't tell me...
Is it amnesia?
Of course not!
I remember both your names,
and I can write them, too!
Watch me!
Huh?
I can't write with this fork...
It is amnesia!
I'll search my logs for helpful information.
That's our high-spec robot!
Just searching through your logs makes you glow?
Well, Roboco-san is really high-spec.
Year of the Rat
Shampoo yummy
No clues in my diary.
What was that all about?!
Check this out!
I can walk forward when
I move my left and right legs alternately!
She can't perform like this!
What do we do?!
I hear eating fish makes you smarter.
Why not try it?
I think you need it more than her.
I've got them hook, line, and sinker...
I think?
How about a bigger fish?
The poor things don't know
we're filming for A-chan's Prank'd idea.
Where were you hiding that?!
They're trying so hard for me! Thank you both!
The plan is for A-chan to walk in
and let them know.
What's taking her so long?
I heard Sora's in trouble!
A-chan! You see, Sora-chan's...
You've been Pun...
Sorry! My hand slipped!
Where am I? Who am I?
We have another amnesiac now!
You've Been Prank'd!
Yikes. I was messing around,
but they took it seriously.
Someone notice the board!
Look at that board. This is definitely a prank.
There's no fish zodiac, is there?
Wh-What am I supposed to do?
What's this?
You've been Prank'd!
What was the point of that board, then?!
Ta-da!
We're going nonstop!
S-So yeah, we're having a concert on Jan 24th!
Don't miss it!
What? A movie?!
You guys just don't get it.
Your ideas are too simple-minded.
You're here, Sora-senpai?
Y-Yeah. I just got in.
Not the same thing we do every week?
When did you get here, Matsuri-chan?
If we're looking to change things up...
Which do you prefer, Okayu?
Barley tea or roasted?
We can't do those, either!
I know! Let's have Sora-senpai decide!
The title?
holo no graffiti the Movie: Reincarnation
Debuts Jan 24th (Fri)
in Toyosu PIT
Let me handle this one.
I happen to be an expert in these scenarios.