Kooon!
Koooooon!
Wow, it worked.
Awawawa!
All right, everyone.
Nakiri bids thee farewell.
Huh?
It'll be all right.
I'm sure this is just a bad dream.
It's reality! Get up, now!
Is it okay if I sleep next to you?
No chance in hell!
Sleep already.
Kooooon!
I can't sleep like this!
Shaddup!
Uh, F9thmc|ibqkru is louder!
I have no idea what you're saying!
Hey! Pipe down for a sec!
😔
I said Fubuki-senpai was louder, dammit!
But right now, you are.
How could you even zzz it up in this situation?
Kooon...
Ayame-chan's doing it too.
Mmnnmmm...
Sleep Breathing...
First Form...
Wake up!
So, to turn her back to normal...
Why only me?
This grimoire says...
"Fight monsters with monsters"?
Nah.
Unmanned train with bombs?
You just use this illegal mic
and recite a chant.
Huh, sounds easy!
Chant!
I-I don't like you or anything, Onii-chan!
But maybe I do, deep down, just a little...
Never mind! It's nothing!
I said it's nothing!
Shut up! Jerk! I hate you!
Oh no, I said I hate him again...
But it's not true! I don't mean it!
(passionately)
Later, groupies.
Noooooo!
Save the world!
Towa Smash!
I'm not the one with anger issues here.
You do it, Rushia-chan.
I'd love to see you show off a little.
Come on!
Please!
I beg of you!
I can't recite such a stupid—
I mean, mushy chant!
It's impossible for me too!
Let's just forget about this.
Koooooon!
Fubuki-senpaaaa
Fubuki-senpai's losing her sense of self!
Hurry up, Towa!
No way! I can't do it!
I'd rather watch the world burn
than recite this crap.
Together.
Both of you read it out together.
*yawn*
Man, I slept well.
See? It was a bad dream after...
This is the creature known as Fubzilla.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!