I want to see the same future
I want to hold that dream
Each and every different heart. Run, GO!
Everywhere seems to get dark
These eyes were just robbed of little hope
Tune well your shaking anxious heart
Muster just a little bit of courage
Delete the words of giving up and continue
The painful moments too are over because I am no longer alone.
That is why I will pursue the dream.
The excitement won't stop.
I will show you a world beyond imagination
I want to access it. I won't feel regret
Each and every different heart. Run, GO!
During moments of sadness or moments of loneliness
There is something to believe in
Never forget these heartbeats and keep it going
The overflowing smiles into the never-ending world
I want to stand on the stage of my dream.
I want to shine.
There are times I want to shed tears then laugh again
I want to see the same future.
I want to hold that dream.
A single miracle step
I want to run out of breath pursuing the dream.
The excitement won't stop.
I will show you a world beyond imagination
Shall we access it?
There will be no regrets.
Each and every different heart will make a WORLD