Time for another recording session.
Wait, what?
Huh? No way!
Is this thing locked?
I have work to do!
Is anybody in there?
'ello! Huh?
What's wrong, Subaru-chan?
I can't get into the studio.
This sucks.
What? It's locked?
Yeah. Nothing happens when
I pull or push.
If pulling or pushing doesn't work,
lift it up!
Like a shutter!
Yeah, no. Not when it has a doorknob.
Got a key?
No keyhole anyway.
Somebody must be asleep inside.
It'd be weird if they didn't react
to all this ruckus.
Maybe there's a ghost inside.
If one shows up, I'll scream so loud,
it'll shatter your eardrums.
Why are you threatening me?
Screw it! We've gotta break it down!
Your one brain cell gave up?
Shaddup! A room that can't be entered
won't be of much use!
Time to blow it up with a boom!
It'd be completely useless!
Huh? What's the matter, you two?
blahblahblah
I see! I fully understand now!
Allow me to help with my ultimate horn drills.
Yahoo!
Still breaking it down, huh?
Everyone got your Watames?
Okay, let's go!
Who you talking to?
Ugh, what a sturdy door.
Yikes, Watame died in vain.
Wh-What in the world is going on here?
A-chan!
Currently Explaining...
Oh, that's right.
You guys haven't received the memo.
Huh?
The door's been sticking lately,
so we got it repaired...
But it got turned into a shutter by mistake.
Up we go.
A-chan lifted the door.
Whoa, it opened upwards!
What? It really was a shutter!
See? I got it on the first try!
How d'ya like that? I was right!
Heh. Heh. Heh.
Shaddup! Quit trolling me!
How was I supposed to know?
Yeah, you wouldn't normally think
it'd open upwards.
My horn drills...
didn't serve any purpose!
Everyone hated the new door,
so it got swapped back to a normal one.
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!