Laters!
Take care!
Wait...
Matsuri-chan...
She forgot her house keys, phone,
purse, and P*SMO!
It'd be easier to list the things she did take!
W-We need to get them to her!
Given all she forgot,
she'll probably come back for them herself.
No, knowing her,
she must be frozen in place right now,
despairing at her memory.
Halp.
What.
Someone needs to run after her
and get these to her!
But why me?!
Thank you, Mio.
To ye I pose a problem.
Choco-sensei?
God
Not her.
Oh, you're not her?
10min
P1, Matsuri-sama, left ten minutes ago.
You, P2, chase after her
to deliver the things she forgot.
Calculate the time you'll take to catch up.
What is this, a correspondence course?!
P.S.: Matsuri-sama is moving at a speed of Mach 80.
Why so fast?!
Isn't she moving on foot?!
No, a Lamborg*ini.
Come back to us, Matsuri!
Need help?
Okayu?
What's with the wheels?
It's a Lamborg*ini!
Yeah, right!
It can hit Mach 100.
Whatever! Just give me a ride!
A-Awfully cramped in here.
Found Matsuri-chan.
You're right!
Thanks, Okayu. Let me get off here.
Sorry, can't stop so abruptly.
What was that?
Go back!
Dunno how.
You seem to be in need of assistance.
You're that goddess!
Actually, I'm P3, who moves at
Mach 100 and an angel of C.
What is that even supposed to mean?!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!