Guess The Word!
Yay!
So, about this.
In the corner I pwepared today,
the goal is to casually use a specific word or two in conversation,
and avoid the other two fwom figuring it out.
Successfully camouflaging the word
in a 3-minute conversation
scores you a point for the match.
Gotcha.
Gotcha!
That's the gist of it.
*dying Captain*
It's actually kinda tough.
Okay! Bring out the words!
Over here!
Ta-dah!
Fubuki → Nihilism
Marine → down in the dumps (lit: salt on veggies)
Luna → earth-shaking/astounding
Hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Let's start with these!
Well, well, well—
Fubuki → Nihilism
Marine → down in the dumps (lit: salt on veggies)
Luna → earth-shaking/astounding
*laughing*
Quiet down there!
Shall we get started?
Round 1, Start!
*ring goes the boxing bell*
So, are you guys eating your veggies?
I'm eating my veggies, yeah...
Well,
lately,
there's a really cool, nihilistic dude
who's a big fan of me and...
Well, that fan
doesn't really like eating vegetables.
Like, he's the carnivorous type.
My friend goes, "Not eating that."
when I pass him the veggies,
and he tells me
"We can't have both of us
"not eating them!"
So, I put on my vegetarian goggles
and eat them.
Yeah...
Ohh....
Yep, yep, yep.
So umm,
Luna
hasn't really been eating her veggies...
So, right now,
my tummy's in a state of pandemonium.
Umm...
Ever—
Every...
Eferyon...
Everyone...
Everyone is...
really
amaz...
*#%?? and... ;_;
*laughing*
amazin...
What's wrong?!?!
Why are you tearing up?!
The Law of the Jungle is... the Law of the World.
That fact is weally earth-shattering.
*laughing*
*ROFL*
Oh, so that's how it is.
That sure is...
a tough world to live in...
Well, your Captain—
Back to veggies? *lol*
So, veggies
*snicker*
really are too much
for me to handle.
That's how I feel,
but
lately I've been trying
salad and stuff,
doing my darndest to scarf them down,
umm,
Okay, so like, veggies really
aren't that palatable, right?
I prefer things that
are a bit salty.
So I've been putting salt
on every veggie
in existence...
Add salt to cabbage,
Idiom: "down in the dumps"
Lit: put salt on lettuce, etc.
or in a pickle,
or really anything.
I'll add salt to bean sprouts
and eat them like that...
lololol
Tasty!
That's totally vegetarian.
Well, anyway,
have you all figured out the words?
I've already
figured out Luna's,
Whaaaat?!
You were—
You were too obvious!
Wahahaha
lololol
No I wasn't!
I wonder...
Anyway, round over!
Ding ding ding!
Okay!
Eugh...
Yeah...
Okay,
I think I figured
I mixed in a lot
out Luna, too...
of red herrings, I thought...
Those red herrings
of yours were way too forced!
lololol
Hm...
I'm thinking that Luna's word
was "earth-shattering"...
I also think it's "earth-shattering"!
Really...
Everything before that
sounded calculated
like "survival of the fittest,"
inserting quick ones like that left and right.
Yeah, exactly!
That was too easy to see through.
Why...
That's not obvious!
How's that obvious?!
In what world?!
Tahahaha
So, as for Marine's...
I'm...
a bit lost, really...
I have no idea what Marine's word is...
All I heard from you was salt, salt, salt.
Ahahaha
I didn't use it
with its usual meaning
so it's kinda hard to tell...
Salt to bean sprouts...
Salt to cabbage...
I'm also a bit unsure
on Fubuki's word, too,
but...
I was thinking that it was
maybe vegetarian, but then again,
Vegetarian—
I thought it was vegetarian...
True, I did kind of
highlight vegetarian...
But,
I'm the one who brought up vegetables first...
I'm not really convinced,
but I couldn't think of anything
other than vegetarian...
Okay!
Let's get to revealing
everyone's answers!
What word
was given to Luna-chan?
Earth-shattering...
Well, yeah.
I mean,
I was
a total open book to everyone...
Everything you said bef—
*kissssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss*
Look! She brought out the kisses!
lololol
The salty kiss.
Nnnnngh
Okay.
Next up, what was
Marine-chan's word?
The word I got was
a bit of a weird phrase.
"In a pickle" is a phrase
that exists, apparently.
This is...
What is "in a pickle?"
In a troublesome or difficult situation.
- hololive Lookup
Pour salt deep into a salad,
or the salt deep in a pickle,
or adding salt to bean sprouts...
Oh, so that's what it was!
I used a totally different meaning for it, and
*nods in understanding*
that's how it turned out.
I see! That was clever!
*salty luna*
Yep.
What about Fubuki-senpai?
My word was
nihilism!
This really-handsome-and-cool-nihilistic-dude and...
It was like that.
Ohhh,
I see!
Yep, yep, yep...
To wrap it up,
the winners of this round,
*kisssssssssssssssssssssssss*
me and Marine-chan,
get one point each!
Oh, it's the kiss! lol
In Fubuki-senpai's
Join the Official Fanclub on NicoNico to watch the full episode!
(Currently not translated into English)
fan anecdote,
umm,
I thought something was fishy with that word soup...