Rushia! You okay?!
lololol
Gross... Who is this?
The Crazies Who Call Into Idol Streams
3rd Gen: Shirogane Noel
Oh! Hello?
mwahahaha
lolol
My name is M*w *wo.
hahaha lol
First off,
let me congratulate you on 220k subs.
Pii!
Tog*pi says congrats too.
I never expected M*w *wo to be watching my streams.
Shadow Ball!
lolol
What would you two like to eat?
Pokemon Food.
Pii!
Uh, what is Pokemon Food made of?
Sigh.
I'm bored now.
I'm leaving.
hahaha lolol
My name is Kudo Fubuichi.
I'm waiting for people to call in,
Uh-huh?
but so far, nobody's...
You're waiting?
Nobody's showed up.
Nobody?
That's a mystery if I've ever seen one.
Y-You're not Fubuki-senpai...
are you?
My name is Kudo Fubuichi.
giggle
So, Fubuichi-san, what do you like to eat?
I'd have to say...
Eel on rice, I guess?
lololol
Not lemon pie?
Kudo ****ichi's favorite food is lemon pie
Hololog!
2nd Gen: Murasaki Shion
Oh! Hello?
Uh...
Hey. Hello.
Wha...
Gross... Who is this?
I'm known as Ebifrion.
What? Really?
Shion-chan?
Uh, yes?
*deep breath*
I'll continue to watch you grow...
Maybe not in the chest area, though.
Gahahaha
lololol
pfft lol
Okay, peace.
Hold up!
That was so gross!
H-
2nd Gen: Minato Aqua
pop
Hello...
Woohoo!
lolol
This is Crayon Holo-chan!
lololol
Can you, like, do mimicry and stuff?
Huh?
That's one sudden request.
pfft
I wanna 'ear it!
Uh...
Erm...
Ah...
Him*wari!
Weh!
Wah!
Cute!
lololol
Hololog!
Huh?
3rd Gen: Uruha Rushia
Cute girl spotted.
mwahaha
Who the—?
Hello?
You see,
nobody was showing up,
so here's your friendly neighborhood old man.
You think this is a joke?!
What's wrong?
You've stopped completely.
Wha...
Sh... Shu...
Shaddup!
Just you watch!
What's the matter?
I'll get...
Rushia! You okay?!
lolololol
rawr
Ha*oken!
Sho*yuken!
Tatsumaki Senp*kyaku!
haha lol
Phew.
That was close, huh, Rushia?
Marine!
Hmm? Hold on.
That was a close shave!
That old man...
He kinda...
Hang on.
His skin came off, revealing a tiddy monster inside?
A tiddy monster?
Yeah, a tiddy monster or something!
Was totally messing with me!
I love you.
mwah
Oh, yikes.
Bye-bye!
Don't know you, man!
lololol
hahaha lolol
Oh!
Huh?
What?!
Cheetahman.
I am a cheetah.
It's me, a cheetah.
I am the cheetahman.
du du du du
It's me.
Cheetahman!
du du du du du
dun du du du du
du du du
Congrats on 200k, Rushia!
Hey!
Wait, what?
Hololog!
Aqua-chan.
Huh?
Hello.
This is Noel Deluxe.
I've been listening in,
lololol
and not responding is not an option!
S-Sorry.
Really!
You gotta make it clear!
Huh?
It's fine if she's not top of the list.
Where does she rank?
Be honest with me.
"Be honest"?!
Honest answer.
What?!
Uh...
I love everyone equally!
You... love everyone equally?
I love everyone equally, Noel Deluxe.
Perfect answer!
lololol
Congrats!
400k subs is amazing!
Seriously, there's nothing more I can say!
Just... congrats!
lololol
1st Gen: Akai Haato
Art thou listening to me?
pant
Uhh...
N-N-N-N-N...
My name is...
Yeah?
Heh.
U-Uh...
Aye.
White Shenron!
Yeah?
I hath arrived to grant thy wish.
My wish?
pant
Aq... Aqu...
A... q...
Aqua-tan...
I wanna talk to her.
Damn, you creepy!
lololol
T...
Th...
Thank you so much!
Log 003: The Host Is a Crazy Too
Extra
This isn't a solo stream.
Uh,
as you can see,
I'm waiting for people to call.
This isn't the way it ends, right?
Right?
Huh?
It's okay.
There's still time.
We...
We still have thirty seconds.
No!
Don't Kanata-ta me!
W-Wait, please...
Ah...
If anyone caught your attention, come join their streams!