I made rice omelet.
Let's eat!
There's more for seconds.
But I'd feel so bad for the chicks.
Yeah, yeah.
Hurry up and eat.
That reminds me. I've been warming an egg.
Why in there?
Didn't have to be there.
That's the problem you have with it?
Maybe it'll hatch when microwaved.
It'll explode!
Now you say the sensible thing?
I-It really hatched!
Why?
Why in there?
Still not over that?
Wh-What do we do?
S-So cute!
What do chicks eat?
Tuna?
Rice omelet?
Specialized feed for chicks, probably.
Let's go buy some!
Guys, please notice...
It's me, Watame!
Oh, hello there, Chick-senpai.
Do Not Touch
I should return to normal
if I touch that statue again.
Is this chicken feed?
Says cow poop right there.
Look, this is so cute.
Let's buy it.
Cow poop.
Cow poop!
We're back!
Eat all you want.
And grow up big and strong.
Like I could eat that!
Is it not hungry?
I'm a sheep, you know?!
Would rice omelet be better?
Uh, I don't know about that.
I'd feel so bad for the chick!
You took a liking to that line, eh?
Nothing wrong with it, but yeah.
Here, Chicky,
say "aah."
Stop it!
Sheep Power!
It flew?!
What just happened?
L-Look, everyone!
Why the hell?!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!