Look at that cute, wavy tail!
Why don't you dance it too...?
Aight.
Heeey.
Y'all seeing this?
Ha! Heave-ho―
Heave... ho...!
Are... you...
there?!
Heave-ho, heave-ho...
Heave-ho... heave-ho...
I should
pull harder...?
Heave-h― Ouch.
Oh―
Ahaha.
Are we― Are we filming?
We're filming?
This camera's definitely filming!
Give me a sec!
Ahh― Ahh― Wh― Wait―
Hold on―
Almost got it on camera.
I won't let you film me drinking water.
Ahahaha!
Whoo!
I'm just...
Just having some water!
Her alluring eyes are a charm point?
Where's the camera...?
Hoof, hoof, hoof, hoof, hoof...
Hoof, hoof, hoof, hoof...
Horn drill.
Do I?
Do I or do I not?
I-I won't?
Hey, do I? Or do I not? Do I? Or do I not?
Ehe― Ehehe― Ehehehe―
Oh, I won't.
I won't do it.
Won't do it, huh...
My... My tummy...!
Watame did nothing wrong, right?
Right?
The princess' orders are absolute?!
Get closer.
I see how it is.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
I wanna do the Nagoya Shot but I don't know how it's done.
Yaaaaay.
Hmm?
Hmmm?
You getting this?
Are you getting this right?
Heeeey.
I'll ignore Subaru-chan-senpai for now.
Let's take out Captain Marine first.
Ah, cwap!
That was close...
Okay, now for Subaru-chan-senpa―
Aaaagh!
One more, one more!
Go lower! Lower!
Start from the bottom!
You'we only showing the back!
Do it right!
Nnnnnoooo...
Oh no―
AAAAGH!
I quit.
This devil's hidden side is an angel?
I can do it.
I can do it!
I'm a―
―devil!
Nom.
Mmm... How's this?
Check...
Good!
Towa-sama's all good!
Hey, you.
Go there.
Go all the way there, okay?