I want to spread my wings and...
She went flying into the sky!
Why can't I?
Because it's not safe!
Is there a trick to flying?
Don't try to pick it up!
Anyone with pigtails can!
But wait, am I just going to give away
part of my identity as a flier?
Just have to pray to the stars!
She sus.
Aqua-senpai's lying because she thinks
she won't be unique anymore.
I'm gonna go second and become
the pirate king of the skies!
Wow, a shooting star!
No way!
Ack.
In broad daylight? How unusual, huh...
Why?
Aki-senpai, you can probably fly too.
Just try it!
Like this?
Why?
Whatcha up to?
Let me in on the fun!
She realized that only those with pigtails can fly
You're giving up?!
The game's not over yet!
Are you really going to give up just like that?
You guys...
Why?
And if you work on your core strength, you can do this!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!