Subatani Subao, FuBuKi, Kijin Hyakki, Kurokami Omi
Bingo, babeh.
lolol
We'll order a Dom Perignon Tower. (defeated)
Log 006: Let My Voice Enrapture You
The world only has two types of men:
Let My Voice Enrapture You
Me... and not me.
You two seem worn out,
Sakura Miko
hololive Gamers: Inugami Korone
3rd Gen: Shirogane Noel
so I figured I could clean your ears for you.
Wait, what?
Clean our ears?!
Going in slowly.
Ahh!
Th-This is amazing!
It's something else!
When you're with me, Kurogane,
I want you to be your natural selves.
That's... That's so nice.
We'll order a Dom Perignon Tower. (defeated)
His hands are really pretty.
I like the hands.
Let's call for Mr. Prettyhands.
Yeah, Mr. Prettyhands.
I'm Homura. You chose me for my hands.
3rd Gen: Shiranui Flare
Nice to meetcha.
You have some amusing criteria.
Are you thirsty? 'Cause I am.
What would you like to drink?
I'll take whatever you two like.
God, he's a heartthrob for real!
Would you seriously be okay
with us ordering some lamesauce?
Oh, absolutely.
I'm fine with anything you choose.
How reasonable! He's totally reasonable!
Don't say that!
You two are really so amusing.
Hololog!
Let My Voice Enrapture You
I'm a male virtual YouTuber.
My name is Tokino Sora.
Whoa...
Uwah...
You've got something in your hair!
Are those ears real?
They're super cute!
Don't be scared.
Come to me, little fox.
I love 'em.
Good evening. I'm Natsuiro Matsuhiko.
1st Gen: Natsuiro Matsuri
There were a bunch of lewd questions...
What's up with that?
Is it your fault, Matsuri?
Yo, this really makes me wonder...
What the hell kinda streams do you do?
Huh? Er...
Uh...
Y'know...
1st Gen: Yozora Mel
What's not to love about girls
who are upfront about their feelings?
Wouldn't you be all like, "I can't believe
you're professing your love to a guy like me"?
Can you do that one more time in a stud voice?
I can't believe you're professing your love
to a guy like me. You're so precious, babe.
Thank you so very much!
Hololog!
Let My Voice Enrapture You
Oh boy, my voice sounds so deep. (Just woke up)
4th Gen: Tokoyami Towa
Roboco San
It does!
Super deep. Yikes.
This is nuts!
It is.
Hold up. This is too deep.
Super-duper deep!
Do the Orochimaru for me.
You see, I...
Look, I don't know how "the Orochimaru" goes!
Say, "Sasuke-kun!"
Sasuke-kun!
I'm not sleepy at all.
It's just how my voice sounds right now.
So...
I'm going in one more time.
sharp
They want me to say something
that'd help them sleep easy?
What can I even say?
Sleep tight. Pleasant dreams.
How's that?
Did that help?
Thank you, Alphonso-chan. (Reading SuperChats)
1st Gen: Akai Haato
lolol
2nd Gen: Nakiri Ayame
3rd Gen: Uruha Rushia
Sh-Should I call you Rushifer?
Have a conversation between
Rushifer and Kijin Hyakki, please.
Sh-Should I call you Rushifer?
Thanks for coming to hang out on my stream.
No, thank you for having me on.
Hold up!
I can't stop blushing! My face is on fire!
Let's just move on! Move on!
Now hang on just a damn minute.
Subatani Subao, FuBuKi, Kijin Hyakki, Kurokami Omi
Viewy (the audience) is in love with me!
This chocolate's obviously for me.
No, you wait up.
Do you lot even know
the type of guy Viewy's into?
What is it?
Viewy loves the ripped and the swole.
No, no, wait.
Do you all even know what Viewy's favorite line is?
What is it?
Spit it out.
Are you ready? It's...
"Bingo, babeh."
I saw that coming from a mile away.
You fail.
Ayame Fail!
Log 006: Fell for the Voice? Bingo, Babeh.
Extra
Those Whose Stud Voices Failed Them
Y'know, the hosts in Kabukicho
go straight for the DomPeri Tower.
3rd Gen: Usada Pekora
As a good Bekora, I thought I should let you know.
All he's talked about since we've sat down
is frickin' Dom Perignon!
And he's basically calling us bumpkins!
What an awful host!
Right?
Can we get some water, please?
Oh, and some wet wipes.
4th Gen: Kiryu Coco
3rd Gen: Houshou Marine
Why?
Why does this always happen with me?
Why must one of us have to die?
Why? Somebody tell me why!
Uh, are you offering to off yourself?
Wait, no. I can explain.
I'm watching a Yakuza quotes compilation here.
I won't hold back.
Come at me if you're ready to die!
You can think of me as K-Kazuma, okay?
Huh?
K... Ka...
Houshou Kazuma-san?
F-Forget I said anything. I'm out.
I think I'll whisper some creepy nothings
in your ear with a stud voice.
In my stud voice.
Yeah, in my stud voice.
What? You can't sleep?
Do you wanna lie down...
next to me?
Yeah, no, that did not work.
4th Gen: Tsunomaki Watame
4th Gen: Himemori Luna
Thanks for dropping by today.
What'll you have?
Champagne? DomPeri?
Is that Crayo* Shin-chan?
Beer, maybe?
Who're you supposed to be?
Order of DomPeri, Table 1!
Woohoo!
hoo!
WOOHOO!
Hol'wup one second!
That's no stud voice!
Just for you...
I booked this room.
Let's spend all night
filling each other up with warmth.
If anyone caught your attention, come join their streams!