Haachama Is Here!
Today, we take a look at hololive
in the Cretaceous period.
They all seem to be doing quite well.
Haachama Spots Prey
Oh dear.
A fight has broken out over food.
Hmm?
But never fear,
the boss of the herd has arrived
to mediate the dispute.
Boss Playing Mediator
A job well done.
What's this, then?
It must be the competition at the time,
Duck Family
Subarusaurus
the Subarusaurus.
Shuba!
Distribution of Subaru in the Mesozoic Era
Representing the formidable idol group
that garnered fans across continents,
it is a subalive herd.
H...
Haachamachama!
A laudable attempt to intimidate,
Oh, snap...
but the Subarusaurus does not flinch.
...chama...
Shubaaaa!
And now she has been captured.
Chama!
The poor thing... But this is part and parcel
of being in the food chain.
Chama?
Chama-chama!
Other members of the herd return from a hunt
and immediately notice the change.
Jin say hanyo mu?
The Elf Family's Unique Call
Choco... Choco!
I see.
We have to go save her, or this will turn ugly.
Very ugly!
They always look to help one another.
This, too, is hololive.
The Subarusaurus nest lies
on the other side of the mountain.
Mt. Akaigatake
But a dangerous carnivore
lurks the wood at night.
Are we going for real?
Look at that setting sun burn.
It might be a better idea to set out
the next morning.
They suppress their urge to go
and call it a night.
Shuba!
Chama?! Chamachama!
And then, dawn finally breaks.
Are they all ready to head out?
Huh?
They've all fallen asleep
while playing a PC game!
How late did they stay up?
Common in the Cretaceous Period
Zzz...
Ah... zzz...
We'll do this tomorrow.
Shuba!
I-I can't swallow any more ducks!
It is morning once again...
Huh?
They're at it again?
When did they start?
Incredible.
Let's tame this Lv. 140.
Gotcha.
Tsunomaki, Tsunomaki,
Tsunomaki, Tsunomaki...
They're addicts!
Tsunomaki, Tsunomaki,
Tsunomaki, Tsunomaki...
Now...
I'm about to login too.
Oh, Fubuki-sama's online.
lol
Games over reality.
That's been universal truth since ancient times.
Look, Aki-chan!
This thing is Lv. 180...
You...
You girls!
Pop Quiz!
What's Haachama's level?
3.5 billion.
This is bad news.
Down calm! Down calm!
You're tearing her apart!
I'll tame this one too.
Shuba!
Haachamachama!
Error
Application has crashed
Desk: -100 HP
What did I do to deserve this?!
And thus, the Cretaceous period came to an end.
hololive had been active since the Cambrian explosion,
but it would go on hiatus here.
The next time hololive resurfaced
was at the beginning of the Cenozoic period.
Fin
Fiiin.
And that was hololive Cretaceous.
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!