What's gotten into Pekora-sama?
She just can't seem to stop playing video games.
Gaming addiction, eh?
There's only one way to cure gaming addiction.
You can't be suggesting
we enter the game realm ourselves?
We destroy the console!
How savage.
To that end,
I had Rushia-sensei come over.
She's an expert in death and reanimation.
Uh... Why am I here?
She doesn't even know what's going on!
You see...
I get it now!
We need to drag Pekora out of
the gaming world and back to reality, right?
Pekora, how do you do?
You gave up way too quickly!
But Pekora should go back to normal now.
Or not! She's even got tears in her eyes!
Eek! Scary!
Uh, doesn't this look kind of bad?
I wasn't expecting this.
Hello.
Oh, Pekora-chan's here.
I made too many rice balls, so have one.
No! No, no, no!
This looks really bad!
Shion-sama! Hurry up and get the rice ball!
On it!
Great.
That takes care of our immediate problem.
I'm a genius.
What have you done?!
Why'd you stuff another in there?!
You've only gone and made things worse!
I can't help. I'm just too nice.
hy on'd e dry uggiin a ibbewen onzo?
Why don't we try plugging in a different console?
Good idea.
No, I'll take care of it.
Wait, hang on... This is Batt*edome!
Not a video game.
This won't be enough to get Pekora...
Hooray!
A game!
Wait, anything goes?!
This game is for four players...
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!