What are you pounding clay for?
Making a cat.
Wow, how violent.
All done!
Huh? What is this...
Huh?! What is this thing?!
You're the one who made it!
But you were about to say
the same thing, weren't you?
Well, uh, yeah...
It's a cat, okay? An adorable kitty cat!
Be careful! Remember that it's clay!
I'd poured my heart and soul into it...
Uh, listen, you can just make it again!
Look! This leg here is still the right shape!
But that's the face.
But look!
You can see its eyes smiling here!
That's the mouth.
Look at what you've become, you poor thing.
Uh... Aki-senpai...
Who did this to you?!
It was you!
What?!
Nice catch!
Strike three.
Batter...
Out!
It's my kitty kat!
But that's a mouse!
Look forward to more hologra this year!