Another day, another overtime shift.
Yep, I knew A-chan would still be working.
The office TV's the best way
to watch a movie, so here we are.
It's not horror, right?
You're pekositive it's not horror?
Relax. It's just about someone who's a spitting image
of a character messing with the others.
That's a doppelganger! A horror staple!
Shall we switch on the Ghost Sensor, then?
What is that?
It glimmers when there's a ghost nearby.
That's pekotta be a toy sold at carnival stalls.
A-chan, horror's a no-go for you, right?
...
Looks like she's fine with it too.
As a pure pekoflake, I'd rather watch a documentary
about penguins in Antarctica.
Ta-dah.
I'm starting to feel like
horror's all right-o with me now.
Let me go grab some snacks.
I'll peko with you!
E-Eerie presence!
"Eevee"?
No, not the thing you catch with a Pékoball.
Hmm?
Someone's pekover there.
Huh? What're you guys doing here?
Why are you here?
Sora-senpai?
I was waiting for A-chan to finish up.
What's going on?
Run into someone?
We were just surprised pekause
Sora-senpai's here.
Oh, I was just surprised to find the girls here.
Huh? Anyway, give me a bit. I'm almost done.
While you're here, come watch a movie with us.
Yeah! Nice idea!
Hmm...
Peky please?
Hmmmm...
It won't be scary if we're all together!
She's right.
I'm sorry. I can't go with you.
I'm done.
Good work.
Oh...
By the way, were you the one
who switched on the TV, Sora?
Nah.
Maybe you stepped on the remote?
I'd know if I did!
Summer sure is a fun time.
Yikes! Where'd that come from?
Too bad we didn't get her.
Summer isn't complete without scary stories!
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!