Sheep Bard Who Sings Every Morning
Tsunomaki Watame
I'm stuck!
Why'd you climb up there?
To see what kinda tree this was...
The curiositree got you, huh?
You should be fine with your hooves.
That's a goat!
You can sink straight to the bottom.
That's a boat!
Hello? Is this the police?
That's a report!
Cut your life into pieces?
That's my last resort!
What goes "baa"?
That's a sheep!
Wait, I am a sheep...
Who cares? Help me!
Easy for her to say.
Got any ideas?
We do this...
and that!
Yay!
I don't want to die!
One, two, and...
As the ground drew ever closer,
Watame's life flashed before her eyes.
Oh, go buy some snacks, Watame.
Buy me a drink, Watame.
Go buy some dinner, Watame!
Go buy something.
At least...
...tell me...
...what you want,
dammit!
FamiChicken, then.
Who's there?!
Yes! FamiChicken!
Throwdown Challenge
Could it be?
Challenging Watame to a battle over
who gets to be hololive's sheep?!
No way.
Why?!
It came all the way to
this filthy human city to do this!
Accept its challenge!
I don't have time to waste
on inferior sheep like that.
Okay, let's get to it.
O-Oh no...
That sheep's a proper pro!
If this keeps up...
You can probably admit defeat now.
Huh?
Yeah! You have us, don't you?
We know full well exactly who hololive's sheep is.
Okay, Watame?
Wrong sheep!
There's only one hololive sheep, and it's this one.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!