I sometimes wonder what goes through Luna's head.
Takoyaki-Loving Princess
Himemori Luna
She does seem the type to say
the most random things.
I want snacks.
Yay, snacks!
What was that?
A coincidence?
Like heck it was!
Hmm... I want some takoyaki, too.
What was that? Explain that!
It's takoyaki.
That much is obvious!
Looks like today's the kinda day where
everything Luna-chan says becomes reality.
Talk about a lucky day.
Ugh, the sunshine's too bwight.
She grew sunglasses!
Sunglasses don't grow!
Hey.
'Sup.
Did you think of something
to surprise Marine-chan with?
Surprise?
Oh, right. Her birthday's coming up soon.
7/30
Bamiversary
Ah!
I'm all weady.
I'll surpwise her with this big bazooka.
The heck?
This could get really bad if she starts
talking about doomsday or something!
Our lives are in danger!
But that doesn't usually come up
in casual conversation.
Say, Luna.
What?
Don't you wanna take over the world?
Evil overlord much?!
Nah.
I'm having the time of my life now,
so I don't need to.
I love this agency and evewyone here!
Really?
Hngh!
Luna...
It would've been more touching
if she didn't look like that, though.
←Like that
Anything else you want, then?
I'm thirsty, so I'd like some water.
Water?
There is water, just beyond that thing!
She belongs in the Thunderdome!
Even those guys don't have
takoyaki sticking out of them!
In Osaka, then?
Want some candy, lassy?
You won't find anyone with takoyaki
sticking out of their shoulders anywhere!
Here we have Luna without the takoyaki.
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!