Yoohoo.
What are you doing?
I'm stuck.
Why?
I slacked too hard on maintenance.
Now, all I can move is my head.
Eek!
I need to fix this somehow.
I can't even stream like this.
I don't know anything about machines.
If only we had an expert here...
Hello!
Help me!
Weirdo in the house!
I slacked on maintenance,
and now I can't move.
What a disaster!
Do you have experience messing with machines?
Not really.
But I know corpses like the back of my own hand.
Eek.
Machines may not be my area of expertise,
but I know lots about anatomy!
Choco-sensei?
I'll perform maintenance on you, Roboco-sama!
Wait, you said you didn't know
anything about machines!
You're humanoid, so it'll probably work out.
Stop right there, school nurse!
Your head moves freely, huh?
You could at least consider it...
I'm sorry.
Really.
Roboco-senpai.
I tried asking people.
One's done teardowns before, so I called them.
Really? Thank you!
Dun dun!
Rushia called me, so here I am!
Noel!
I got the gist of it from her.
Leave this to me!
Please!
Sure!
Uh, Noel? What's with the mace?
It's a mace!
It can tear down machines easily.
Wrong kind of teardown!
Uhm, does Noel-sama have
the wrong idea about something?
One.
Two.
"Teardown" probably wasn't the best phrasing.
Three.
Four.
Musclebrain!
Five.
No! Stop!
Don't hurt me!
Shock therapy might help.
Just trust me.
Help! I need an adult!
Staff came in and carried out repairs
Man, I was freaking out back then.
I'm glad you can move again now.
Same here!
Hello!
Roboco developed a Noel phobia for a while.
Don't run that way! There's only windows there!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!