I should do something devilish.
Devilish Acts Done Quick
Pekora-chan.
What's up?
I got cream puffs.
Want to have some with me?
Oh, I was feeling pekish!
She's not scary at all,
which makes her the perfect target.
Whoa! These look yummy-o!
Right?
I filled one of them with mustard.
Marked with a Towa-sama sticker
Hello!
Oh!
Have some cream puffs, Sora-senpai.
Towa-sama pekought them for us!
Oh, may I? Thank you.
What? Sora-senpai's joining us?!
I'll be in major trouble
if she picks the mustard one!
It has to go to Pekora-chan, no matter what!
U-Uh, I'll take this one.
Dibs on this one!
Damn this bunny and her luck!
Was trying to get her to pick the mustard puff
I'll go with this one, then.
Yikes, no going back now.
It'll look shady if I ask to trade.
It's game over!
I'm so sorry, Sora-senpai!
Thanks, Towa-chan.
I haven't eaten anything since
recording ended, so I'm really grateful for this.
Urk!
Yum! Nice and sweet!
Huh? She's perfectly fine?
Towa-chan?!
Towa-sama?!
A While Ago
Mustard
Now I just need to put a sticker on it.
Oh, Towa-chan.
S... Sora-senpai?!
Wh-What's the matter?
Sorry, am I interrupting? I was wondering
if you knew where A-chan is.
O-Oh, I haven't seen her around.
Is that so?
Thanks, and sorry for bothering you.
Gah!
Oh no! She seems to be in a lot of pain!
You... You gimmicked these, didn't you?
Your chickens have pekome home to roost!
Don't try this at home, kids!
Waah!
'ello!
Huh? Nobody's around.
Oh, hey, a cream puff!
Time to dig in!
Any anime with a heroine throwing up is a classic.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!