'tis I.
It's gotten quite chilly lately, huh?
Right?
You agree, don't you?
Just for today, I'll bring out heating material
that we use at home sometimes.
It'll surely surprise everyone.
Let me go get it.
Urgh... Another cold day.
Cold, you say?
Where'd you come from?
Where I come from, where I go?
It matters not, my dear Miko!
I brought heating material for you,
since you're freezing.
Really? Thank you!
What is it?
This!
Return it.
Why?!
Why wouldn't you?
Where'd you even get that?
"Where"? A volcano, obviously.
Haven't you heard of those?
Oh, I'm perfectly aware!
Apologize to Mother Nature
and give it back!
It's dangerous!
But it's rare heating material that
even we only use sparingly at home!
Pretty sure you only use it sparingly
because it's even dangerous for oni.
It's all natural, y'know?!
100% Pure
Raw Material of Nightmares
It'd be weird if it weren't!
Oh, fine.
I'll go put it back where it...
Beware of winter.
Aside from using heating appliances,
try putting insulated curtains on your windows
and humidifying your homes.
Take the appropriate measures to fight the cold
and spend the winter hale and hearty!
Let's all warm up together!
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!