I've been spacing out a lot these days.
Summer blues? Have you been eating right?
Now that you mention it,
my meals have been rather monotonous.
You need to make sure to have a balanced diet!
Urk... I'll keep that in mind.
Anyway, Noel-chan,
have you gotten bigger?
Nobody has a bigger heart or upside than me!
Technically true, but I mean your surface area!
You've clearly been supersized!
I woke up this way.
What...
It's like, you know...
Your leg reflexively kicks out when
you tap the knee with a hammer, right?
Right.
Wait, isn't that a different thing entirely?
Nope. It's the only answer.
Hello...
Yikes! Huge Noel!
I don't know how to go back to normal!
I'll just have to spend my life sitting in
a corner of the office, living off nothing but air!
There's no need to be so pessimistic!
Just you wait, Noel-chan!
We'll figure out a solution right away!
After that, Roboco and Mel spent
an absolute eternity brainstorming ideas.
3 Minutes Later
Okay, let's go to a hospital.
A reasonable conclusion.
Hospitals scary!
Sorry, Noel-chan!
But it's for your own good!
Ugh, this pains my heart!
Noel-chan seems so reluctant,
but there's nothing else I can do for her!
Wait, how do we even get you outside?
Can you stop hiding and show yourself?
Roger!
Ugh... Hospitals scary.
This isn't the time.
Okay, we'll be right back.
Going to the hospital
didn't help us figure out the cause.
Wait, you're back to normal size!
Huh?
You're right! I'm back to normal!
Mel-senpai!
My size! It's back to normal!
Huh?
I'm going home because my head hurts.
In search of fun times in a fun place.
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!