Up top now
te o agete
Clap your hands, and let the sound
Clap your hands umi no mukou made
Clap your hands, sail across the seas
Clap your hands todokimasu youni
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
All together now
hora issho ni
Everybody
Clap your hands, and let the sound
Clap your hands sora no mukou made
Clap your hands, echo across the skies
Clap your hands hibikimasu youni
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
And light the way to our future
hikari sasu bokutachi no mirai
5 4 3 2 1
hololive 5th Stars
Let's begin, go diving
hajimeyou ka saa Diving
No point waiting, now's the timing
matte mo imi nai Timing
Make like that fish and go swimming, swimming
ano sakana mitai ni Swimming Swimming
Bring closer that lighting
hikiyoseru no Lighting
We still can't see it, maybe
mada mienai yo Maybe
What lies in our path ahead?
kono saki ni wa nani ga aru no?
It may be too soon to take it
mada hayai yo Take it
Till we catch up, we'll be shaking
oitsuku made Shaking
But it might be best to stop and thinking, thinking
demo tama ni tomatte Thinking Thinking
We'll make a difference and change
kaetemiseru Change
Put our best foot forward, stepping
fumidasu no sa Stepping
And seize that shining my dream
tsukandemiseru yo kirakira My Dream
Until that day comes, I'll keep my story going
kanau hi made Story tsunagu kara
Because I want you to see it all
datte kimi ni zutto mite hoshii kara
Up top now
te o agete
Clap your hands, and let the sound
Clap your hands umi no mukou made
Clap your hands, sail across the seas
Clap your hands todokimasu youni
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
All together now
hora issho ni
Everybody
Clap your hands, and let the sound
Clap your hands sora no mukou made
Clap your hands, echo across the skies
Clap your hands hibikimasu youni
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
And light the way to our future
hikari sasu bokutachi no mirai
hololive IDOL PROJECT
BLUE CLAPPER
hikari sasu bokutachi no mirai
Lyrics, Composition: PandaBoY
Vocals: Yukihana Lamy, Momosuzu Nene,
Shishiro Botan, Omaru Polka