This world is survival of the fittest.
It's eat or be eaten!
Get a load of this Jingisukan meat
mouthin' off.
Ye have some nerve to
stand up to us carnivores, eh?
Why must the world be so unjust?
In a spot of pekother, are we?
Bunny-senpai!
Hell hath no fury like a rabbit angered!
Th-This looks promising!
Beta carotene power!
Nope.
Ow! Help pekout!
A herbivore can't best them?
Gangsta Dawg Korone, here to help.
Doggo-senpai!
I'll bite your legs off!
Go fetch.
Woof, woof!
Don't run off to play!
Oh, hellooowl!
No, bad! That wasn't for you!
Is this it?
Need help?
Kitty-senpai!
I came to join in on the fun.
Dismissed!
She was the most useless one!
Their strength is overwhelming!
We can't beat them!
Join me at the top of the food chain.
And so, I set off on a journey to be a dragon.
Ohoho, this feels great.
Who's there?!
Tryin' a coup?
Get 'er!
You cheeky...
Hellooowl!
Not bad, not bad.
But I'm the king of this jungle.
A fox can outfox defeat!
Wacha!
Oops, my bad.
I went and interrupted
this tiny squabble between ants.