Man, it's getting chilly at night.
Seriously. I'd love to eat something hot...
...if we can make it back.
Don't be so doom and gloom.
Look, a ramen stall!
Let's go eat a bowl!
Why is there a ramen stall here?
Don't worry about it!
Hey, Noodleman!
Welcome!
It's Aki-chan!
Why run a ramen stall?
I've always wanted to wear
one of these headbands.
That's your reason?
It tastes good, I promise.
Two bowls of ramen, then.
FYI, salt ramen's all we have.
I'm aiming to hit peak levels of salt ramen!
Weird flex, but okay.
Two of those, then.
Right away!
That was great!
Really warmed us up from the inside.
How much, Aki-chan?
Eight million yen.
Ah, so eight hundred yen.
That reminds me of the rakugo skit
about a trick used to pay less.
Time to play a little prank!
Aki-chan, I only have small change.
Is that okay?
Sure!
Hold out your hand.
Here I go.
One, two, three, four, five...
What time is it right now?
Hmm...
Hard to say, to be honest.
Come on, how can you not know the time?
Uh, I really don't.
It makes sense, Ayame-senpai. After all...
we're on a deserted island.
Right!
We went to the beach
and drifted all the way here!
It's why I'm running a ramen stall!
That is not how cause and effect works!
When will we make it back home?
When help arrives.
But we might die and go cold
by the time it does...
Like ramen left out too long.
That wasn't very funny!
No! This can't be the end of us!
Yoohoo! We're here to pick you up!
Thank goodness!
Okayun and Korone came for us!
Truly. I was preparing for the worst.
Oh, Ayame-chan.
Could you pay for the ramen now?
Oh, right. I forgot.
Here comes the money.
One, two, three...
Wait, which hololive generation
are you a part of, again?
Huh?
Gen Two.
Don't go forgetting that!
Right, right, my bad.
Anyway...
Three, four, five, six, seven, eight!
There you go!
Perfect.
Thank you! Come again!
And that was a story about Ayame-chan
ending up paying more than she had to.
What's that? Parts of the story
bored you to tears?
That's great. Please cry more.
Like I said at the very beginning,
I'm aiming to hit peak levels of salt.
Thank you. I'll be here all week.
You've been watching hololive Rakugo.
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!