Three, two, one!
Go go go go go go go!
Go! Go-go-go-go!
Mute.
Come back, Nene...
Aww, everyone...
I'm sorry.
And, uhh...
I'm sad...
Yeah...
No...
Why... Por que...
[J*ws theme song]
[definitely]
Oooh! What shall we do?
[contemplating]
[power off]
[the fearsome shark]
[is on the hunt]
Oh?
[she's going in]
[and she nails it!]
[bye calli]
[the marvelous shark]
[returns to her den]
[to rest her gills]
[she is content]
AGH!
I knew it!
Aww, I saw that coming!
Uuuuugh.
Oh, man.
What the hell?
[death]
That was fast.
Too fast!
I saw it happen!
So,
she died by the right corridor.
"Excuse my rudeness, but could you please RIP"? lol
Yeah, yeah.
R. I. P.
Yeeeep.
I did.
I'm a ghost...
Ah, Calli. That sexy voice―
Oh?
Ohoho?
Lamy-san―
you keep getting imposter, huh?
Again?!
Okay then.
Let's try not to get caught this time.
'kay.
Ah―
Crap.
Excuse my rudeness, but could you please RIP!
Hmm.
UGH.
NO!
How could you...
[sighs]
I can still look at the cameras...
Even if I do her in now...
She's alone, right?
It feels too risky, though.
Oh, shoot!
I really want
to do Nene-chan in now!
I can just do them all in, right?
Like, just do them all at once.
I'm scared...
Hm.
Okay, Lamy-senpai seems safe.
Lamy-senpai seems safe.
Nene-chan― Nene-chan―
Ahh...
Ah.
I think Ina-san saw me...
Polka, Gura.
[gasp]
Lamy-senpai...
And then she reported it.
Hmm? Who? Me?
Wha?
Lamy sus?
Any last words?
Last words?
Lamy is...
umm...
bye-bye.
Inaaa.
Ina, Ina, Ina, Ina.
Ina.
I'll waste some time here and kill Ina.
How do I― Should I swipe slowly?
Got it!
Good. Good.
Ah!
Ina...
[ghost voice] Do your tasks... Oooh!
Oh?
'kay! Okay!
Okay! Okay! Okay! We have a meeting!
Polka killed [Ina]!
I saw it!
Ahaaa.
No, Ame-chan,
hear me out.
Nene did it.
Noooo! Ame! Ame!
[AmeLaugh]
Ame! Look! Look! Look! Look!
Trust me! Trust me, Ame!
Ame!
Kill.
Ame― Ame is
very very cute!
I saw...
Nene is
Polka with Ina, the last time.
Yes!
No. No! NO! NO!
Nice, Ame! Nice, Ame!
Watson-kun.
Elementary, my dear Watson-kun.
No.
No―
[flat "no"]
No, nonononononono.
BARITSU!
Polka-senpai...
Come on, I―
Nice, nice, nice, nice!
Not me! Not me!
Nene's trash!
Niiice!
Trash Nene! Trash Nene!
I don't know...
Yo no comprendo...
[AmeNotLikeThis]
No, no, no, no, Ame!
AME!
TRUST MEEEEEE!
Bye-bye, Omarun!
Nene's team wins this round!
Hooray!
Nice, Ame-chan! Nice!
Yaaaaay!
Very nice! Very nice!
Gimme imposter, baby!
LESGOOOOOO!
[release the shark]
Alright, we have two apex predators on the menu!
[observe the graceful shark]
[as she]
[drifts]
[along]
[the oceanic highway]
Okay let's use our telepathyyyy!
[majestic]
Du-du-du-du-dun!
Okay, okay, okay!
HEY!
Gura!
Hmm...
Ah―
[InaDed]
Pretend I'm doing stuff...
Huh?!
[LamyDed]
No one has caught me, huh? Strange.
[the shark continues to explore her surroundings]
Okay.
[bird spotted]
Hi!
[bye]
Don't kill me, Gura.
Uh...
1-2-4-5-9.
Yes―
WAH!
NO! GURA!
NO! NO!
NOOO!
GURAAAA!
Absolutely no one is making a report! lol
Absolutely no one! lmao
Yes, hello?!
WHAT.
HOW DID ALL OF YOU DIE?!
THE HELL?!
Nene's (body) is in the admin room.
Really?
I was doing stuff
in the oxygen room though.
Yeah, the one behind that.
Oh, sorry! I never noticed.
I was in the―
...Really?
Yeah, really. I was in the oxygen room...
Botan sus!
Why?
Really, why?
You look cuter than usual, that's why!
Huh?
What do you mean?
You look a tad bit cuter today.
Botan?
Bota-bota―
Noooo!
NOOOOOOO!
Damn, Polka caught on quick!
[da mi-shark impossible theme song]
[dami-dum]
[dummy]
It's me, the dummy!
Whoops, ya walked into that one, chief!
Ahaha!
Gura... Gura's safe.
AAGH! She's NOT safe!
[and so, the proud shark laps around]
[her newly claimed territory]
Why is nobody fixing oxygen?!
Oh, it's in there.
That's why.
[the cycle of life continues]
Euuugh...
Yaaaaaay!
YEEEEAAAAAAH!
Gura!
Why?
Yes!
Oh, I dunno.
I think I― I think I get it.
I mean―
So there's this, uhh, reactor room at the left end
that needs something like
two people to do...
There's one thing, where, uhh, at the reactor,
where you have to do it with two people.
Oh, I see.
You have to wait for someone to―
You need wait for someone to come, right?
Yeah, you can't do it alone.
At the reactor.
I think, uh, is there something with a― with a hand?
You have to place your hand, I think?
Okaaaay.
'kaay!
Q! Question!
ShishiBotan!
Honk honk?
Yeah, I'll lower it.
Hmm, hmm.
I'm gonna raise the player speed a bit.
This should do it.
Alright, we're starting.
Okay?
We're good! Let's go!
Okay!
Okay, that's good.
Bye-bye.
[PolkaPensive]
[Impolkaster]
HAAGH!
I saw that comin'!
Aww, I saw it comin'.
Excuse my rudeness, but could you please RIP!
(Polka Remix Part 2)
Oh, Ina...
My Ina...
Oh, my Ina...!
Nenechi...
Let's go.
Let's go together, Nenechi.
Yaaaaay!
This only means...!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, marry me?
Yeeaah, Ina...
I-Ina...
Niiiice...
Inaaaaa...!
I love Ina!
[tender kisses]
Ina♥
[trackmaker Inanis]
Huh?!
Ah, craaaaap.
WIFE!
WIIIIFE!
Where are you, wife?
Where art thou, Ina?!
Did Ina just disappear?
Ina inan't here...
Ah, wait―
That's a pretty slick pun.
Damn.
Nenechi...
Help. Thank you.
Where's Ina?
Where is she...
INAAAAA!
INAAA! INA!
Interesting! Interesting.
Very interesting.
It must be Nene, because― because―
Me, Watson, and Gura
were together the whole time.
No...
And, and, add on to that,
I think I saw somebody vent from, uhh,
possibly reactor, killed―
killed Ina,
and then vented to medbay.
So it could've been
Nene.
"Nene sus"?!
NO! NO! NO! NO!
Maybe.
Wha― Whe― Why― Ho―
Wait, wait!
You know that
Ame, Gura, and I were together the whole time.
And uhh,
the two were with me the whole time,
but I wasn't killed.
You were alone the whole time, Nene-chan!
You're wrong!
You were alone!
Okay, fine, translate this for me!
Sure.
I was with my beloved wife Ina,
with whom I have sworn my love to.
We were doing stuff together,
but I lost sight of her,
Okay.
and during that time,
Ina was killed.
Sure.
I never saw Ame-chan throughout that whole time!
Ame sus!
Ahh, so,
she says that she has been together with
her wife that she, uhh, swore her life to―
Ina,
the whole time.
But then, they were torn apart.
And she thinks it's Ame.
But I can openly say it's not Ame.
It's definitely not Ame.
There's no way she could've gotten
to the other side of the map.
Coz you...
Alright?
I mean, she's been very quiet,
so I'm a little suspicious, but...
So, yeah, uhh...
I'm sorry, Nene, but it's you.
Hey! Wait!
Wait a minute!
Relay this to Gura-chan for me!
Okay, one last statement.
You two are the most suspicious.
Kiara and Gura are very
No, no, no, no, no.
very very very sus.
Very very sus.
I'm not!
Nooo u.
Argh!
It can't be Kiara; I've been watching her do tasks.
Yes! Yes!
Oh sh*t!
Sh*t!
Bye, Nene-chan.
O'Friends is done.
Kiara, you―!
It's you!
Bye-bye!
Noooo...
Nenechi...
Nooooooo!
Yo yo yo yo, they've done it this time!
The bird and fish did me in!
Geez, man.
What the heck.
Ooooh my gah.
WHAT?!
Aaaahahaha!
HEEEEEY!
Hey!
Kiara and Gura?
Oh.
Oh wait, so it wasn't Nene-chan!
SEE?!
Geez!
Oh my gah.
[gasp]
Oh, come on, man.
Come on, I wanted to do it just once.
Oh well.
Calli?
Mm?
We can hear you.
Goddamnit!
Aaaaaagh!
F*ck my life.
Ooookay.
Hahahaha.
Ha. Ha. Ha.
My time
has finally come.
Nenechi.
Nenechi, let's go.
Okay! Okay! Come on!
Come on, my wife!
Yaaay!
The lonely Nene.
The lonely Nene!
All alone! All alone! All alone!
Oh yeah―
WHAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA?!
Nenechi...
[murder]
Ehe☆
Agh!
No!
[sus]
Nene is ded!
Nenechi...
I'm going to let, uhh...
OH.
MY.
Somebody has the, uh―
I'm gonna let the murderer
come forward on that one.
GOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOD.
Admit your crime.
Where was it?
Navigation.
I want Ina to explain why she was
in the same room as the body
in nav
on the way out.
Believed.
Ina.
[nods]
Ina?
I didn't see―
Ina. Ina.
Inaaaaa...
She's in― Inacent.
Ina, do you have an explanation?
Innocent!
I'm
Inacent.
My wife.
"let's tako bout this!"
In pasta oil!
Bye, Inaaaaa...
Bye!
Oh!
Oh yeah!
Bye Ina!
Oh, Ina.
You done it this time.
I'm sorry!
Nenechi...
"I'm sorry".
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Ahahaha.
It had to be me.
[possessive]
Love you!
Love me?
Yes.
YES.
ALL.
Yes.
I shouldn't be doing this.
Okay, I should―
I should, um―
[clear throat]
focus on―
on sabotaging
the run.