Here, Rushia, read this.
Book of BL
Bacon x Lettuce
It's a precious Bacon Lettuce book.
Uh, what are you talking about?
You have the bacon and the lettuce!
They're squeezed together!
And drenched in sesame dressing!
H-Hey! Get away from me!
So, you know,
The fluffy meatiness of the bacon...
The sloppy chewiness of the lettuce...
Together on the dinner table...
A father-and-son Caesar's salad!
Wh-What are you trying to say?
hololive 2nd fes. Beyond the Stage
Supported By Bushiroad!
Seriously, what is your deal?!
Let's begin the interview.
Sure!
Question 1:
Do you like the Landolt C?
I-I think it's interesting.
Between the Landolt C
and Pekora-sama here,
who's currently on day 1024 of overtime,
which do you like better?
Huh?
Well, uh... I like Pekora-chan more.
Oh?
Actually, make that the Landolt C!
You're hired!
5:50 AM! 5:50 AM!
I didn't know Pekora-chan was a morning person.
Shion-chan, let's go to a sauna.
Sauna? I'm in!
I'm sweating a waterfall.
Saunas sure are something else, huh, Aqua...
Aqua-chan?!
She's sweating buckets... no, Niagara Falls!
No, wait! This is mustard!
Sheesh, Aqua-chan.
I told you so many times that
it's dangerous to secrete mustard.
Hmm?!
Wait, what if I put this on a bacon-lettuce burger?
Y
U
M!
I wonder what Miko-chan gets up to outdoors.
I'm pekurious.
Eek!
Gust of wind-o!
Sudden bursts of wind
really suck for people in skirts.
Did you see that?
Miko-senpai brought out her camera in a flash
and took a bunch of upskirt photos!
Huh?
And now she's pekoding her own dating sim
right here and now!
Grr!
Mwahaha.
Yikes.
It was so stinky, I couldn't breathe!
Flare...
How could you be having so much fun
talking to someone other than me?
Now I'm mad!
I'm just going to have to
carve my own Flare out of wood.
Heh... Let's go on our honeymoon
once you're complete, Flare.
If it ain't Noel! Whatcha doing?
Flare?!
Th-This isn't what it looks like!
Uh...
I just wanted to carve you up!
Me?!
Gah! My cat reserves are low!
I need cat therapy!
A beastful of possibilities!
WowWowWowWowWow!
Stop goofing off, Koro-san.
I can't be stopped that easily!
WowWowWowWow!
WowWow!
Wow!
……
Phew. That's that.
This is cat therapy!
Roboco-san, are you done
modding your arm?
Yeah, I changed it to your crush's recorder.
Ah! A flood of libido-fueled students
rushing toward Roboco-san's arm!
She's going to be crushed under them!
Matsuri-chan?!
Ayame-chan.
We're going dinosaur hunting.
Wanna join us?
Dinosaur!
Keep it down!
Ayame-chan's busy studying for her
Electronic Calculator Certification Exam!
You mean Japanese Tea Instructor Certification Exam!
What?
Internet Travel Advisor Certification Exam?
Towel Sommelier
Certification Exam!
One, two!
Dinosaur!
Ah... This, too, is hololive.
Fiiin.
And that's all the hologra for the year!
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!