We've already started filming.
Your favorite demon doctor who's also a great cook, Yuzuki Choco,
will be making Butter Chicken Curry with Summer Vegetables.
First, cut the chicken thigh into bite-sized pieces.
Place the chicken in a plastic bag
and add salt, yogurt, Worcestershire sauce,
grated garlic, and ginger, then mix it all together.
These two look like they're up to no good.
But let's keep prepping that curry for now.
We'll cut the eggplant, zucchini, and bell peppers
into bite-sized pieces as well.
Cut eight slits into the tomato
and heat it in the microwave for 2 minutes at 500W,
medium power, then take it out and peel off the skin.
We need those tomatoes, so please don't lose them.
Thinly slice the onion.
Oh?
They can make your eyes sting, so please take care.
Place butter in a frying pan, then add onion
and sauté on low heat until the onion caramelizes.
Add the tomatoes and simmer until they release their juices.
5 minutes later
Once they've released their juices, add water,
cover and simmer on low heat for another 10 minutes.
Oh, it looks like she fell asleep...
10 minutes later
Turn off the stove, add curry roux and stir until it's all dissolved.
Then bring the pot back to a simmer on low heat.
Plate it up...
and there you have it.
Yuzuki Choco's Special:
Summer Vegetable Butter Chicken Curry
Check the full recipe in the description below!
Thank you for watching! My cute student.
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to my channel as well!
Thanks for watching!
See you in the next one!