A chance to stop dropping spaghetti!
Keep at it!
Ohohoho!
She pulled ahead! Towa-sama pulled ahead!
Moving on to the next segment!
Here it is!
The Slick Bome—
I flubbed that...
I flubbed that!
The Slick Comeback
Championship
Yay!
Okay, so this segment is
brought to you by Lamy-sama!
Please explain the rules, Lamy-sama!
Sure!
In this segment, you're given
a mundane-yet-unexpected situation,
Rules
Ex.: I broke a plate...!
and you have to guess how I,
Yukihana Lamy, would make a comeback!
Q: How would I make a comeback?
A: I'd go on a date to buy new plates!
Guess How Lamy Would Make a Comeback!
And Choco-sensei, Towa-senpai,
"Let's go buy new plates together!"
"Looks like we have an excuse
to go on a date tomorrow!"
and it's up to the viewers to guess.
Correct!
Okay!
You greet someone you think you recognize,
but they turn out to be a stranger!
I know that feel!
I totally do this sometimes.
Me too.
Yeah, I do, too.
So, we guess what you'd do then?
Yeah, what would I do there?
If it were me...
I'm writing the first thing
that comes to mind.
Done!
Now then, let's see the answers!
Ding! Here they are!
Oh?
Hm, hm...
Towa-senpai!
A chance to stop dropping spaghetti!
Can you explain?
Well... Choco-wenwei, say yours.
What's Choco-sensei's answer?
"Oh, uh, excuse me...
I'm conducting a survey.
If you're free, do you mind
answering a few questions?"
Ahaha...
*laugh*
What survey, even?
Ha!
It's a comeback!
If they actually say yes,
what would you do then?
"Do you know who I am?"
Ahahahaha!
Wow...
Aren't you being super self-important there?!
Like, "I'm doing a project
for YouTube," or something.
Ah!
I get it now!
Okay, so... Let me give you my answer.
Here!
Bam!
An opportunity to make a new friend.
W-Wha!
W—
Wai—
Isn't mine similar?!
It's kinda similar!
That's...
Huh?
Look!
What does "A chance to stop
dropping spaghetti" mean?
Like, you talk to them and try
to improve your conversation skills.
You talk to a total stranger
and polish your conversation skills.
Something like that.
That's what it means?
Yeah!
I thought we were supposed to come up with
what she'd say in that awkward situation.
Oh, but...
Well, in this dimension,
Lamy's answers trump everything.
Makes sense!
Lamy's the answer sheet.
Over here, I'm the law.
I'm the law.
By the way, Lamy-sama.
In this situation,
if you mistakenly talk to the wrong person
and then realize what you did,
what would you say?
"Oh, I'm so sorry!
I mistook y—
But that outfit looks really cute on you!"
That's just a pickup line!
Come on!
Don't hit on random people!
"Hey, do you use LINE?
Where do you live?"
You keep using pickup lines!
That just makes you a sketchy dude!
Uh, I think I left
a bad impression right there,
but this time around, I believe
Towa-senpai's answer got the closest.
Yaaaay!
Seriously?!
It's time for Choco-sensei's Physical Exam Derby!
Okay!
In this segment, we'll watch some
prerecorded physical exam footage
Rules
Predict who will come out first.
and try to predict who'll come out on top.
Okay!
This time,
Suisei-sama,
Matsuri-sama,
Towa-sama,
and Kanata-sama
are the participants!
Wait... Towa-senpai's in this group.
Well, you'll see!
I got this in the bag!
Towa-sama usually gives off very silly vibes,
so I wonder how this'll turn out.
I can't wait.
Me too!
Next up are sit-ups,
an abdominal exercise!
How many can they do in 30 seconds?
Ah...
This is a tough one.
I participated, but I totally forgot...
*laughs*
Well, I think it's hard to guess who
in this group can do the most sit-ups.
Anyway, roll the interview footage!
Let's!
Do you have confidence in your sit-up ability?
Well, uh, sit-ups?
*inhales*
Do you have confidence in your sit-up ability?
She's being pretty hesitant.
I-I dooo...
"I dooo"
Oh, sit-ups?
Nope.
This sounds like a disaster in a making!
Do you have anything to watch out for while doing sit-ups?
Nope, not at all!
She's drunk.
Do you have confidence in your sit-up ability?
*laughs*
Yes.
That's a very confident pose.
Do you have anything to watch out for while doing sit-ups?
Becoming one with my muscles.
"Becoming one with my muscles!"
Yeah, I fuse.
Do you have confidence in your sit-up ability?
Uh...
Nope, those are impossible.
None of them seem confident this round.
Do you have anything to watch out for while doing sit-ups?
Other than Towa-sama.
*stifled laugh*
Hmm...
My face...
Uh...
Um...
Nnngyangyangyangya!
Do you have anything to watch out for while doing sit-ups?
How my face does that, maybe?
*laughs*
What is she saying?
That was some crazy Japanese.
*laughs*
Let's see our answers!
Okay!
Open!
It's a miracle!
Everyone picked Towa-sama!!
Does this mean...?
It does, doesn't it?
The age of Towa, no?
It's coming!
It's the age of Towa!
A new age!
A new age is upon us!
The new age of Towa's muscles is upon us!
I'm going all-in on Towa, now!
I'm also going to believe in Towa-senpai!
Now let's move on to
the answer in the recordings...
Roll the tapes!
She's doing pretty good!
Go, go!
You can do it!
Keep at it!
Ohohoho!
She caught up!
She pulled ahead! Towa-sama pulled ahead!
Five seconds left!
Wow!
The correct answer is...
Towa-sama!
Woohoo!
Wow!
I got goosebumps at the end.
Aren't I amazing?!
Uh...
In the beginning, Sui-chan and—
The top right person
didn't move at all, probably, but....
I competed with Sui-chan
and overtook her!
Yours truly did!
That was amazing.
That really was, Towa-sama!
And the goosebumps...
I'm impressed!
Ta-da!
0 sit-ups?
Just, how?
*laughs*
In the end, Matsuri-senpai couldn't
get up a single time, huh?
Oh, but,
she really wasn't able to get up, apparently.
Um,
well...
I guess she seemed a bit loopy...
A Little More Loopy Than Usual Matsuri
Yeah, yeah!
You've got a point there!
Hahaha
Haha
"A Little Loopy"
You're right.
She really was! Can't blame her!
Next up
is a new segment.
Towa-sama's...
See Through Her Devilish Deeds!
Towa-sama, please do the honors
and tell us the rules!
Aye! In this segment,
given an everyday situation
where a prank can be played,
Rules
Ex.: Giving a present to a friend.
A: Gift them with a jack-in-the-box!
you try to guess what kind of devilish deed
Gift them with
a jack-in-the-box!
I would do!
Correct!
Got it!
Okay!
The first prankable situation is as follows!
Someone left a pudding in the fridge!
What would Towa-sama do about this?
I see!
Uh huh?
I forgot to write an answer in advance,
so I'll write one now.
This!
Hm, okay.
Devilish, right?
Exactly!
It's me, okay?
And I'm a different breed
from Choco-wenwei, okay?
Oh...?
Exactly. That's the important part.
Put simply, at least.
I see.
Oh!
I think I've got it!
I finished writing mine, by the way.
That was fast!
Wha—
Wasn't that fa—
Well, I am a devil.
This is my playground.
You've got a point!
Seriously? You're good at it?
Yeah, I am.
Well, I don't know if you'd be
more devilish than me, though.
Oh no!
I've got the perfect answer.
I'll win, probably.
Huh, wait... Why am I the last to finish?
Let's see everyone's answers one-by-one!
First, how about Choco-wenwei?
Okay!
After taking just one bite,
label it "Towa's" and put it back.
That's a good one!
How about Lamy-chan?
Snap the little thingie that helps you
put the pudding on a plate.
Ah...
I totally get it.
*the devil is pleased*
Huh.
That's really—
Ugh, wait...
Huh?
That's a great idea!
Ahahaha
* Approval of ideas is not a criteria for this segment.
Take just one bite and...
They're both good!
Approved
Anyway, I'll just reveal the correct answer.
Okay!
My answer is...
Eat it and leave a candy in its place.
*laughs*
How nice!
That's so nice!
I...
I'm—
No—
Um...
First off, I'd want to eat it all...
I'd eat it, and after I'm done...
Yes, yes, and?
I'd start thinking it'd suck
if they were really looking forward to it,
so I'd leave a candy or something.
You're such a good person!
I mean,
I still have a ways to go...
Dang...
I've got a long way to go as a devil!
What do I do?
Do I cha—
I'll update my gameplan.
Okay, so the next time I run into
this situation again, I'll...
1. snap the thingie,
2. take just one bite, and
3. label it "Towa's".
Towa-sama's Devilish Deed
Mix together everyone's ideas
I'll combine them all!
Combine them, huh?
Which one is a more devilish deed...
Hmm...
If we go by something that I could do...
This one only requires you to snap the thingie.
You've got a point!
Yeah...
But, you know, instead of snapping it
and flipping it upside-down,
doesn't Towa-sama seem more likely
to leave it upright, making it leak out the bottom?
Hahahahaha!
What do you think I am?!
But, anyway, I think I'll go
with Choco-wenwei's.
I could do that, actually.
Taking just one bite?
Yeah!
Take one bite, label it "Towa's", and put it back.
I could do that.
Mm!
I could probably get away with it,
so I'll go with that one.
Yaaaay!
Devilish Deeds!
Da-dan!
I am a devil, after all.
You've got a point!
A devil would understand "devilish" better!
Bonus Footage
What's the highest grip strength
measurement you've achieved?
About as such—
I mean, about as much as a devil
who can crush a human with their bare hands.
Aren't her legs a bit lewd?
Whoa...
It's really borderline...
Yeah.
My...
* She's trying to hide it.
My little...
cowlick can...
It just looks like
you're feeling her up...
No!
One!
Astounding Grip Strength
Grip Strength Test
Two!
Wait, that's freaky.
If you're interested, check out
the official fanclub channel on NicoNico
for the full stream archives!
What's with her?