Virtual Robot
Roboco San
Hololive 2nd Gen
Minato Aqua
Hololive 3rd Gen
Houshou Marine
So, we've got an exciting cast
here on the show for you today.
Hololive 3rd Gen
Shiranui Flare
Hololive 4th Gen
Amane Kanata
Tokoyami Towa
It's kind of like...
This feels like a pretty unusual group to see together.
Though, individually, we have interacted a fair bit.
A cast you can only see on the official channel
It does make me wonder why this particular cast was chosen.
Right? I wonder why.
Is there a particular reason?
Maybe they thought we'd make an interesting combination?
They must be expecting some kind of special chemistry.
You think so?
Let's do our best to live up to their expectations!
"Right by Dawn" is a segment where everyone is asked,
"What starts with the syllable X and is Y?"
and they come up with an answer together.
The first question is...
What's something that you always forget that starts with the syllable "He"?
I've got my answer.
It can only be one thing.
Already?
As much as I hate to admit it...
Yeah. I don't want to admit mine either!
It's that thing, isn't it?
Oh, did I guess wrong?
I can feel the synergy between them.
I know what it is!
If you think you've got the same answer,
then reveal it when I say "go", okay?
Are you going to reveal yours?
Ready? Go!
Replies (henshin)!
Hidden stash of money (hesokuri)!
I knew it!
Ah... "Replies"!
Ah, I see!
That makes sense.
I always look at my messages but forget to reply.
I went with "hidden stash of money."
A hidden stash of money?!
How did you think anybody else would write that?
Nobody would forget where they've hidden their money!
But it's true. I have money all over my room.
That doesn't sound very normal.
So is it just Flare and me left?
What did you write?
I forget to lock my door (heya no kagi no kakewasure).
A normal answer that you would've thought would be more common
Yeah, that happens.
Yeah, it does.
You worry if you've locked up or not.
Mine's...
Nobody's going to go "Ah, yeah" for mine.
I don't want to show it anymore.
What is it?
Common sense (heikinteki shikou).
Ah...
That happens to everyone sometimes...
That's...
Yeah, it does...
Ah!
It looks like we can just go with "replies," right?
Yeah, I think so too.
But when you think about it,
Captain never really seems to forget (to reply).
I don't forget very often,
but common sense is easily forgotten.
The People Who Forget
You say that like you're any different!
What's something that you always forget that starts with the syllable "He"?
The answer was "replies" (henshin).
Okay, let's move on to the next one.
What's something delicious that starts with the syllable "ne"?
"Ne," huh?
"Ne"!
There's only one thing I can think of...
I guess everyone's probably thinking the same thing.
We're all thinking of the same thing, right?
Let's all show our answers on "go" again.
Let's do that.
Sounds good!
Yeah.
Here I go.
Ready? Go!
Minced tuna and green onion sushi (negitoro).
Nerunerunerune candy
Minced tuna and green onion bowl (negitoro-don)
I wrote "minced tuna bowl."
Ah! Me too!
I wrote "minced tuna sushi."
Minced tuna sushi!
What about you, Aqua?
I wrote...
Nerunerunerune candy.
Me too, Aqua-senpai!
Oh...
Hey, why do you look so disappointed?
You should be happy!
I picked Nerunerunerune as well!
But Nerunerunerune's just not right, is it?
It's definitely the minced tuna!
You should be pleased!
Ah, I wrote "green onion" (negi)...
But that's kind of in the tuna bowl, right?
Yeah, it is.
So everyone picked pretty much the same thing.
Not us, though!
Aqua's trying to pretend that Nerunerunerune never happened
So we can basically just lump everything in together as "green onions," right?
But overall it looks like we've kind of
agreed on "minced tuna bowl."
Everyone okay with that?
Why don't we go with Negineginegine?
What's that meant to be?
Don't just go making stuff up!
What's something delicious that starts with the syllable "ne"?
The answer was "minced tuna bowl" (negitoro-don).
Now, let's move on to the next question.
Okay!
What's a common trait amongst hololive members
that starts with the syllable "Su"?
A common trait...
Su...
I can't think of anything at all.
So it's something that applies
to basically everyone in hololive, right?
Can I say mine?
Sure, go ahead!
Picking on Su (Su-gyaku).
Ah! Yeah, that always happens!
Picking on Su: refers to how everyone teases Oozora Subaru for her bad luck in games.
You mean "picking on Subaru-senpai", right?
Oh, that's what you meant!
So everyone does that...
We can't really say that's a common trait, though.
I've never seen you pick on her before, Kana-tan!
Someone who doesn't pick on Su
Yeah, she doesn't!
Roboco-san, please show us yours!
What did you write?
Sushi!
Sushi?
Sushi?!
You call things that you like "sushi"...
I see.
So that's what you meant.
Mine is pretty close to that, actually.
Mine was "liked" (sukoreru)
Ah...
That's a really good one!
I'm pretty sure that's a common trait amongst all hololive members.
Yeah!
I put down
"Start button".
Like, hololive's logo is a start button...
Well, it's more of a play button, I guess?
Ah, I see!
Can I say mine now?
Likes watermelons (suika suki)
Hm?
Huh?
What...?
What did you write, Aqua-senpai?
Why would you pick on me now?
It's actually kind of hard to answer after hearing that last one.
Why?
I wrote "super fun girls" (sugoi omoshiree onna).
That's cheating.
What do you all think?
It's true, right?
Yeah, that's true!
What do you guys think..?
"Liked" was good, right?
It was good, right?
I like it.
Yeah, it was.
I think it's pretty good.
Really?
What's a common trait amongst hololive members
that starts with the syllable "Su"?
The answer was "liked" (sukoreru).
What's something that's useful to have
that starts with the syllable "Zo"?
Here we go.
I've got my answer already.
Just go with your gut! Your gut!
Roboco-senpai, what's yours?
So mine is more kind of "something that'd be nice to have."
What is it?
Yeah, what is it?
Reinforcements (zouen)
Reinforcements?!
You're thinking big!
Why do you sound like you're on a battlefield?
Reinforcements...
The robot's always got FPS on the brain
Let's call in the cavalry!
Ah, that's what you meant?
I guess I'll say mine.
Zone!
Huh?
Ah...
You mean like "Marine Zone"?
Yeah, that!
For some reason, Marine and Flare are on the same wavelength
Yeah, that's right!
A zone makes you stronger!
So you didn't mean like "getting into the zone"?
Nah. More like "Tezuka Zone"(?)
Ah! I see...
I see...
Aqua-senpai, did you write the same thing too?
No. Mine's completely different.
So what did you write?
ZOZ*TOWN (online fashion retailer).
Is this okay?!
Is it really okay to write this?!
It would be super convenient!
Flare, what about you?
Um...
A Zojirushi-brand vacuum cleaner...
I thought of that too!
I guess I'll go.
Sure. Go ahead!
This is just the first thing that popped into my head, but...
Yeah?
A rag (zoukin).
That's pretty good!
That was probably the first thing I thought of too.
(Kanata is starting to act a little suspiciously)
Yeah.
Rags are pretty useful.
(Kanata is starting to act a little suspiciously)
But "rags" is out, right?
Yeah, that's true.
That completes the deck.
Ah... Ah...
Kana-tan, what was your answer?
Yeah, what was yours, Kana-tan?
My answer was... umm...
Ra...
Ah!
Let's move on to the next one!
That's it!
We're done!
Are you sure you don't want to use this time to promote your dirty old rags?
Hey, my T-shirts aren't rags!
★Amane Kanata merch is on sale now★
So, what should we go with?
I thought ZOZ*TOWN was pretty good!
That really clicked.
Yeah, it was.
We don't usually get out much, after all.
Let's go with that!
ZOZ*TOWN!
Thanks for going with my answer, everyone!
What's something that's useful to have
that starts with the syllable "Zo"?
The answer was "ZOZ*TOWN."
Now, let's move on to the last question.
What's a place that you'd like to visit one
that starts with the syllable "O"?
A place I'd like to visit one day..?
"O", huh?
Here's my answer.
The moon (otsuki-sama).
Ah!
Wow!
I guess you like the moon because your surname is "Tokoyami" (eternal darkness)?
Yeah, that's right.
Everyone's treating Towa like a stereotypical chuunibyou character
So that's why!
Mine is super realistic, but can I go next?
Sure!
An auction (ookushon kaijo).
Yeah, I guess it does sound interesting to visit!
Yeah, it does.
I really want to try putting in a bid!
Hey, can I turn this back around
and say something super unrealistic again?
Candy land (okashi no kuni).
That's so cute!
Then, can I bring us all back
to reality with something super real again?
The beach in (virtual) Okinawa.
Okinawa!
That's so...
That's so real...
Almost too real.
I guess my answer's kind of in the middle...
Somewhere with lots of yummy food (oishii mono ippai no toko).
That's pretty vague.
Yummy food...
That's what I said!
Candy land ≠ Somewhere with lots of yummy food
You were making fun of me, but yours is the same thing!
So Kana-tan's the only one left, right?
Yes.
Mine is more in the middle of the fantasy scale as well.
A big hololive house (ookina hololive hausu).
I feel that that's
probably the best answer for us, as members of hololive.
Yeah!
That's right!
What's a place that you'd like to visit
one day that starts with the syllable "O"?
The answer was "a big hololive house" (ookina hololive hausu).
Anyway, that's it for today!
We've got this show, "Right by Dawn,"
as well as other stuff
Check out our different videos, like live streams, hologra and
hololog on the official hololive channel, and get to know hololive!
like live streams and our 3D anime,
"holo no graffiti," or "horogra" for short, that we regularly
update on the official hololive channel,
Please like and subscribe to the hololive official channel!
so please don't forget
to like and subscribe!
Please like and subscribe!
Bye for now!
See you!
Set sail!
Join the hololive official fanclub
to see unreleased scenes!