One day, Pekora and Okayu
were on their way to the office.
It's too easy to get lost
while pekoing to the new office.
Time to ask people.
Huh?
Let's start with that
elderly gentleman over there.
What?
Here.
You're off your rocko.
Off you go.
Excuse me, mister.
Have you seen our office around here?
Can't say I have, no.
O-Of course you haven't!
Thanks for your help!
Looks like we're in for the long haul.
Oh, they probably know something!
That's a doggo! It can't talko!
No, I can see it in his eyes. He knows.
Look at his face!
I'm sure your words will get through to him now!
I pekon I disagree.
Hurry up and go!
This is our chance! I promise it'll work!
Excuse me! Have you seen our office around...
...
I knew it wouldn't work.
What is that pekosed to mean?!
I only gave it a shot because
you pekouraged me to!
We have to turn to our last resort:
getting a bird's eye view.
I see. Like from the rooftop of a tall building?
Moun...
...tain?!
Why in the world
did I follow her here like a wacko?!
Pekora.
Huh? Marine?
What's going on? Why are you all...
Okayu-senpai called us here,
using the Anywhere Door.
The physical location doesn't matter.
If everyone from hololive is here,
then this is our office!
You guys...
Can't we just go back through the door?
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!