Whatcha doin', Maririn?!
Okay.
What are you up to, Captain?
Ship in a Bottle.
It looked interesting, so I bought a kit.
Looks like it needs a lot of focus.
It does, so try to keep it down, okay?
What the—?!
We're having a party to celebrate
Coco-chan's hair growing by 1cm.
Do you have to do that now?!
Geez, I asked you to keep it down, didn't I?
Sorry.
Pin-drop silence, Coco-chan.
Roger!
Uh...
What are you doing?
Hide-and-seek.
It's hella distracting.
Do it back at your place!
You're out, Sui-chan.
No!
Ouch!
So noisy!
If this happens one more time,
I'll get mad for real, you hear me?
...and clear.
Loud...
Oh no! Coco-chan's gonna sneeze!
And there's a shaky pan
directly above the captain!
Ach...
Phew, close shave.
Crap, her hair...
Ac...
Achoo!
'ello!
What happened here?!
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!