It's not sp—owowOWOWOWOW!
I'm gonna spit fire!
Sec—
It hurts...
It hurts!
Log 007: A Series of Idols Squaring Off With Their Tolerances
A Series of Idols Squaring Off With Their Tolerances
Matsuri attempts CoCo ICHI's Spice Level 10 curry
(she usually eats Mild Level 5)
3rd Gen: Usada Pekora
1st Gen: Shirakami Fubuki
2nd Gen: Oozora Subaru
1st Gen: Natsuiro Matsuri
We have milk, you'll be fine!
We also have yogurt!
Okay.
Ahh, I'm scared!
Okay, so I'll react—
I'll give you guys
an honest to goodness, authentic reaction.
Time to eat! Spice Level 10!
Time to eat...
*cough*
*wail*
I can't...!
That's an over-the-top reaction, you know?!
She's chugging the milk down now.
Huh?!
Your face got pekoribbly red!
Her face and her mouth... lol
Oh no, she became stationary! lol
Her eyes...! lol
Her eyes stopped moving! lol
I'm out of milk?!
There's no more milk?!
Hololog!
A Series of Idols Squaring Off With Their Tolerances
4th Gen: Kiryu Coco
Time to eat!
Might as well take a big bite, I guess?
*slurp*
*sluuuurp*
It's not sp—owowOWOWOWOW!
Ow, Ow...
Yeah, this is awful!
(Now positioning hair-removal machine)
It's now or never (to remove the hair)!
Just like this!
Anergy!
Ahhh!
Let's go!
Bzzt!
Ahhh!
2nd Gen: Murasaki Shion
Hot! Hot! Hot!
Wait.
So like,
I can't eat spicy food.
So why did I attempt this without thinking it through...?
What?! It is spicy!
It really is spicy!
Um...
Have you guys tried it?
You haven't, right?!
It's easy for you guys to say all that because you haven't—
Not that I'd know.
lolol
Mmmph!
So spicy!
I'm gonna spit fire!
Sec—
Like, my mouth
feels like it'll become a flamethrower. Really.
2nd Gen: Minato Aqua
I'm gonna eat it!
Just a little...
Just a sample to start off with...
Down the hatch!
*Agonizing*haha!
M-My lips...
My lips have gone numb.
I can't feel anything
in my lips...
And it feels like my teeth are gone.
It hurts...
Ow...
Ah, wait!
*coughing*
I-I can barely speak!
It hurts!
*coughing*
lololol
It hurts...
It hurts!
I can't take it!
2nd Gen: Oozora Subaru
Huh?!
Wait, this seems really risky!
Uhh...
Just a sniff tells me that this is bad news
Owww... Ow... Ow...
I'll eat it!
Just watch.
So spicy!
This is awful!
No more, no more!
It's so hot! No more!
Seriously. This is crazy.
My mouth is stinging!
My mouth...my mouth...
Hololog!
A Series of Idols Squaring Off With Their Tolerances
hololive Gamers: Ookami Mio
Down we go...!
Mmh?!
It's spicy, but...
Ah...
It's spicy.
lolol
It's spicy, yeah...
It may be spicy,
but it's still pretty edible.
It's not so spicy that I can't eat it.
Let's try adding the oil pack
that was under the lid.
*snort*
*gags*
Adding in the oil
made it really spicy!
Adding in the oil was a mistake... lol
Spicy!
*cough* *cough*
Meow
It's sho shpicy!
Cat!
Meow
Cat!!
What's wrong, cat?
Meow
The cat's meowing a lot...
* If I finish the super spicy ramen,
this'll become an announcement stream
1st Gen: Akai Haato
So, this one is twice as spicy
as the normal flavor.
So like, if I eat two, it'll be four times as spicy...
Wait, maybe not.
*nervous giggle*
Given the shape I'm in now,
this should be a piece of cake.
Sorry, guys, but I'll probably finish
eating today's menu item in a flash.
Ahahahaha❤
Why'd you think it was a good idea
to eat the super spicy one?
Wait, this is actually pretty hellish...
Eww,
it's like one of those kinds that take effect little by little!
Bleugh...!
Huh? This isn't enough to make me throw up!
So spicy!
Uwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!!
I feel sick...
*retching intensifies*
Crap, I feel like throwing up...
*haachama rainbows*
Please stand by.
I threw up...
Am I an idiot?
Haachama must be an idiot, huh?
Haachama!
Haachama! Is!
A Real Idiot, Right?!
Log 007: Relish the Challenge of the Super Spicy
If anyone caught your attention, come join their streams!
Extra
1st Gen: Shirakami Fubuki
I smell death...
You smell death?!
Yeah, it reeks of death.
Is eating this gonna be fine...?
Well!
Let's eat!
Go on...
Oh, it's tasty!
Whaaaaaa?!
Uh, but,
I instantly felt the spice come at me the moment
it touched my tongue,
but even afterwards, it feels like the spice is building up!
*stares in disbelief*
Y'look totally fine...
You're overpowered, Fubuking.
Yeah, it's just tasty.
It's spicy, but tasty.
Yeah...
Wild...
Scoop up the cabbage leaves and...
This gal's crazy...
All done! Thanks for the meal!
You're kidding me...?
It was really yummy!
I still haven't finished half of mine...
If anyone caught your attention, come join their streams!