It's me!
No, me!
What's going on? A fight?
They're arguing over who has more endurance.
That's a lot dumber than I thought.
Seriously. Arguing over that is so silly...
when you can just decide it with a duel!
Why?!
What's going on?
Nothing says endurance more
than doing the air chair!
I figured, more or less.
No wonder they were so confident.
Neither is breaking a sweat!
This duel is kinda unexciting, though.
Nothing's happening.
You'll come to regret those words in time.
Huh?
Here we go!
Sui-chan's posture changed a little!
Is she reaching her limit?
Kanata-chan! Focus your mind
and take a closer look!
My mind?
Hmm...
Wait, no! She didn't change her posture!
She's reading a book!
Hard literature, no less!
That's no mean feat, even for veteran endurers!
And she's perfected it!
Veteran endurers?!
Meanwhile at the captain!
No way!
She's working out!
She's doing air sit-ups!
Muscles will never betray you!
I don't see how this is "air" anything!
What a heated competition!
Good thing there's no audience!
Could've hurt people!
No, it couldn't have!
Huh, Suisei-senpai put away her book.
Hmm? Looks like she's talking to someone?
That's a model scout!
She's air-turning down a model scout!
Combo activated!
I can't believe she thought of that!
You realize it's painting an awful picture?
The captain's switched gears too!
No way!
She's streaming!
She's air streaming while doing the air chair!
What?!
But an air stream can't beat
the book and the scout...
No, wait!
It's a collab!
She's air streaming a 3rd Gen collab
while doing the air chair!
Unanimous decision! Captain Marine wins!
Just do this at home.
No!
I can't believe my book lost...
Sui-chan...
You put up a nice fight.
If you'd brought out an encyclopedia,
I would've stood no chance.
Marine...
I won't lose next time.
You two are shining bright right now!
Wanna go home and eat some ice cream.
Endurance is built by
the work you put in daily!
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!