Let's form a band!
…
Form a band with me.
Phrasing isn't the issue here.
What brought this on?
I'm dead sure a TV anime's involved.
It's not!
I was watching something on Prime yesterday.
Not a meaningful difference.
I even came up with a band name.
Probably "Matsuristreet Girls" or something.
Close! It's Negative Ion Vacuum Sisters!
It's all wrong!
I even brought our instruments.
Ta-da!
Oh, hey, a triangle.
Does that really fly in a band?
I'll play the triangle. You two...
I'll consider it if I'm on vocals...
Play the violin and juggle.
What is this, a comedy troupe?
This ain't even an instrument.
AkiAki gave me this triangle.
Its tone changes depending on
how pure the person's heart is!
Wow.
A magical instrument.
Here I go!
Wake me up when the moon's out.
I get that you're hurt, but wait up!
And where'd that bed even come from?!
C'mon, cheer up!
If you wanna play it so badly,
you just need to purify your heart!
Purify my heart?
I'll help you get it squeaky clean!
Mio...
Let's do this!
Yeah!
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Hello!
Did you manage to play it, Matsuri-chan?
(＾ ‿　＾)
Matsuri-chan?
Her heart is so pure now,
she has a smile on her face 24/7.
Scary!
But the triangle should sound beautiful now!
Try playing it!
One, two...
(＾ ‿　＾)
That sound led to the completion of
Negative Ion Vacuum Sisters.
It's actually a thing now!
Comedy Troupe (?) Complete!
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!