hololive IDOL PROJECT - STARDUST SONG
Lyrics: ricono
Composition, Arrangement: Takuya Sakai (Arte Refact)
Vocals:
Shiranui Flare, Amane Kanata, Tokoyami Towa
They're watching me through the screen again
gamengoshi kyou mo mieteiru
It never changes, it's always the same smile
itsumo to kawarinai egao
On my face, is it just a mask?
matou sore wa kamen ka?
I want to show you who I really am
hontou no jibun o oshiete
Not the confident self that I show everyone
kikazari sumashigao janaku
My real self with all the fears I hide
akireru hodo okubyouna riaru
All the lies
itsuwari wa
it's all nothing
For the truth
shinjitsu o
open my heart
I want you to accept me for who I am
kimi ni subete o uketomete hoshii
This world that we live in keeps turning faster
kasokushiteiku sekai de ikiteku bokura
I'm so tired of everyone
comparing me to everyone else
kikiakita yo kurabeta gari no koe
If a one or zero is going to determine my fate
ichi ka zero ka de kimerareta unmei naraba
I'll fight it
aragau yo
And I'll find it
mitsukeru yo
The reason to be me
boku de aru riyuu
I won't be just another cute face
kawaii dake ja mou irarenai
I'll raise my voice and sing this stardust song
koe o ageteiku n da STARDUST SONG