What do you think you'll be showing off?
B**bs.
Hey!
We raise our hands towards the brightest screens
All we wish for are shinin' dreams
Starring:
Aki Rosenthal
Yuzuki Choco
Yozora Mel
This show is brought to you by Aki Rosenthal...
...Yuzuki Choco...
...and Yozora Mel.
What is rightness?
What is stupidity?
I will show you what they are!
It's finally time to start!
The Showing Off Championship!
Yay!
Now's not the time to be flirting!
We're just "showing off" to them!
I see what you did there!
Anyway,
you won't be flaunting your cuteness this time.
What do you think you'll be showing off?
B**bs.
Hey!
Rules:
Compete to see who can sing
a specific part of the song for the longest time.
What you will be showing off this time is:
Using the part in Ado's "Usseewa" where
she sings "I will show you what they are,"
show off how long you can hold the final note.
That's what everyone dying to find out!
Nope, not at all!
When management suggested this,
I thought they had gone crazy.
Apparently, they've been cooking up this idea
for a year, so it's a long time coming.
No way!
You're kidding me!
Really?
Anyway, this is a competition to see
how looong you can hold a note from a song.
So, everyone.
How are your karaoke and singing skills?
Well, usually, I'll be little bit tone-deaf
but if we're only competing for time...
I might be surprisingly good at this.
Ah, I see.
So to get started, as I already said earlier,
the first song you'll be singing is "Usseewa" by Ado.
First Song: Ado - Usseewa
Can She Show Off?!
Aki Rosenthal's Turn
Okay, so AkiRose-san will be singing "Usseewa."
Go ahead!
What is rightness?
What is stupidity?
I will show you what they are!
Oh, here she goes!
Very nice.
She's really holding that note.
I've got the timer going.
Wow, she's still going!
She's trying so hard, her head's started shaking!
Her head bobbing
feels a little... naughty.
Haha, hey!
She stopped shaking.
...And that's it!
Fin
Wow!
She held it for quite a long time.
For sure.
Yeah, she kept singing.
And AkiRose-san's total time was...
21 seconds!
Ah!
Wow!
Yay!
I got a little tongue-tied on
the part right before the final note.
It was so hard to sing!
I hear you.
What is This Vampire's True Power?!
Yozora Mel's Turn
What is rightness?
What is stupidity?
I will show you what they are!
Cute.
Cute!
She's holding that note!
She's holding it well.
Ah!
And that's... it?
Fin
Time to reveal Mel-san's results.
Mel-san's time was...
10 seconds!
Oh, 10 seconds!
That gap in expectation is
just another reason why she's cute.
Cute, but the difference in score grows.
That was surprisingly short.
So adorable.
An Expert at Making It Long?!
Yuzuki Choco's Turn
What is rightness?
What is stupidity?
I will show you what they are!
Oh!
Oh! Oh! She's going!
Keep going!
The pitch went down.
But it's fine as long as
she keeps singing!
It's so long!
Can she keep going?
That's pretty long.
Uuuh...
Fin
Oh!
Ah.
And that's it.
Nice.
That was a very nice attempt.
She held it for quite a long time, right?
Yup, yup, yup.
Time to reveal Choco-san's results.
19 seconds!
Oh!
Overall, Aki-san's in first place right now.
But that was pretty competitive.
Darn!
What are your impressions of this so far?
The vocalization and pitch are probably
the most important factors.
I see, I see.
Ah, but...
There's still one more song, right?
Come on, do whatever you can
to beat ol' AkiRose here.
Oh!
AkiRose-san's trying to light a fire under them!
Is that so?
The next song will be this one!
I'm sure you're all familiar with this song already.
Yup! Right after the "Oh yes, we know,"
"Get set and go!"
You'll be competing on how long
you can hold that note for.
Whoever sings "Get set and go" for the longest time, wins!
With that being said, let's get started!
She's Not Giving Up First Place!
Aki Rosenthal's Turn
Hmm, what should I do...
I had a strategy planned already.
But... in the name of sportsmanship...
Oh?
I guess I'll just do my best
with how I normally sing.
Ah, okay.
My shoulder angel and shoulder devil
were whispering to me.
I see.
Aki-san will now sing "Shiny Smily Story."
Go ahead.
We raise our hands towards the brightest screens
All we wish for are shinin' dreams
We make our choices with different voices
Oh yes, we know
Get set and go!
* "Sing Softly and Hold a Long Note" Strategy
Looks like she's still going.
Oh!
* "Sing Softly and Hold a Long Note" Strategy
Oh?
Can you tell what she's saying?
* "Sing Softly and Hold a Long Note" Strategy
It's pretty hard to hear.
But she's still holding on.
* "Sing Softly and Hold a Long Note" Strategy
It kind of sounds Elvish.
And that's it!
Fin
AkiRose-san's final time was... whoa!
She managed to sing for 32 seconds!
Whoa!
Amazing!
That was super impressive.
Aki-san, towards the end,
were you singing something instead of "get set and go"?
So after the "get set and go," I ended it by singing,
Gooonnn...
Ah, so you switched to an easier sound.
Ah...
Climb Out Of Last Place!
Yozora Mel's Turn
And now it's Mel-san's turn to sing
"Shiny Smily Story."
Go ahead.
We raise our hands towards the brightest screens
All we wish for are shinin' dreams
We make our choices with different voices
Oh yes, we know,
Get set and go!
Ah, she's holding the note.
Uuh...
Ah!
And that's it!
Fin
Mel-san's total time was...
8 seconds!
Apparently!
8 seconds?!
Huh?
8 seconds?
Well, well, well.
I didn't expect it to end there.
Well, well?
Based on the lip motions,
it kind of looked like she was still singing.
I think I could have gone a bit further there.
Just a bit more, right?
The Song of Destruction Resonates!
Yuzuki Choco's Turn
We raise our hands towards the brightest screens
All we wish for are shinin' dreams
We make our choices with different voices
Oh yes, we know
Get set and go!
She's really belting it out!
She's in serious mode!
Oh!
She's giving it her all.
Whew.
Fin
Oh...
Oh!
Man...
That felt amazing!
Haha, what a nice way get rid of stress.
Choco-san's final time was:
19 seconds.
Thank you very much
for that fantastic display.
Results
The queen of the first-ever
Showing Off Championship is...
AkiRose-san!
Showing Off Queen
Aki Rosenthal
Congratulations!
Congrats!
Woohoo!
Yay!
The Sounds of Rapture Championship
Sounds of Rapture Championship
and the Showing Off Championship.
Showing Off Championship
You're the queen of both competitions!
Congratulations!
Congrats!
Amazing!
My, my...
Are you sure? Crowning me
Queen AkiRose twice in a row?
Incredible.
I'm totally not jealous!
Why not? You should be jealous!
If you enjoyed this video,
If you enjoyed this video, please subscribe to hololive's
official YouTube channel and smash that like button.
please subscribe to hololive's official YouTube
channel and smash that like button.
Bye-bye!
Starring:
Aki Rosenthal
Yuzuki Choco
Yozora Mel
This show is brought to you by Aki Rosenthal...
...Yuzuki Choco...
...and Yozora Mel.