Nn...
er...
d.
Lo...
lli...
Lolli...
Hot, meaty...
buns...
Good afternoon,
hololive's masters of sex appeal.
It's time to remove your limiters
and show us everything you've got!
It's the Sexy Mishearing Prompt Battle!
Yay!
Yaaay!
Yay, yay, yay!
I'm the genius vampire from the Underworld.
From hololive 1st Gen,
I'm the girl with the cutest fangs,
Yozora Mel!
All right!
All hustle, all muscle!
I'm hololive's muscle-brained knight,
Shirogane Noel!
My best feature is usually
the mole on my huge pecs,
but these fluttery pieces
of cloth are in the way,
so you can't see them right now!
Thanks for having me!
From hololive 4th Gen,
the sexy,
mature,
pretty,
and ladylike Himemori Luna is hewe!
There is a fwightening amount of
boobies around me wight now,
but I'm going to show them how
sexiness isn't just about boobies!
What's this sassy lost child doing here?
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey!
There's some kid here.
In this Sexy Mishearing Prompt Battle,
whoever can make a regular phrase
sound the sexiest wins!
Right.
You'll each get several word prompts,
and after you pick one prompt,
Yeah.
read it out as sexily as you can.
For example, if your prompt is "Napolitan"...
Napolitan...
Or something.
If your prompt is "step counter,"
Step... counter!
Or something.
If you can make a completely
regular word sound sexy, you win!
Management has lost their minds.
I think that's always been the case.
When they picked me to host this,
They've gone mad.
I already thought that they'd gone mad.
This is a big pwoblem.
First up is Himemori Luna versus Yozora Mel!
Whoo!
Yay!
Luna-tan!
Reveal your prompts!
Thick sushi roll
Birds and bees
Oh, my!
Mel-sama has "thick sushi roll."
And Luna-sama has "birds and bees."
Oh!
Well, we'll see who can make this sound sexy.
Those are some good words.
It's time to sexy d-d-d-d-duel!
Get ready for Mel-sama's
misheard sexy line in...
Three!
Two!
One!
Act!
Ah...
Thick...
sushi roll.
Oh man, that sigh hit so different!
That was a killer.
Thank you so much for that!
By leaving a small pause
between "thick" and "sushi roll,"
I emphasized...
the exact thickness...
of the whole thing.
Right.
Now Luna-sama, get ready!
Get ready for Luna-sama's
misheard sexy line... Act!
Here I go.
B...
irds.
ees.
Oooh!
The start of it sounded so sexy,
but then she said the rest of the word...
"Irds."
That was some intense mood whiplash there.
Well, this is where babies come from,
so I thought I had to emphasize
the "b" sounds in both words.
Right.
Oh!
That's how I emphasized the sexiness.
That's so deep.
In this round,
the way Luna was saying those "b"s
Oh, that part?
sounded so sexy,
we're giving her the win for this one!
Oh!
Wow!
Congratulations!
Yaaay!
You have to get that perfect balance.
Yay!
It's time to reveal your next sexy prompt!
Nerd
Chicken gizzard
Mel-sama has "nerd."
And Luna-sama has "chicken gizzard"!
Oh...
That sounds delicious!
This is gonna be hard...
That's another tough one.
It's time to sexy duel!
Get ready for Luna-sama's
misheard sexy line in...
Mm.
Three!
Two!
One!
Act!
Chicken...
Ah... gizzard.
AHHH—
Next up...
We have Mel-sama!
Three!
Two!
One!
Act!
Nn...
er...
d.
Hold up!
This can't be allowed!
There's a story to it and everything!
This nerdy guy does
something indecent to me,
and I think, "But he's
usually such a quiet guy...!
What's come over him?!"
The "Nn..." incorporates
that feeling of bitterness.
Ah!
I can definitely hear the humiliation in it.
That's what I was going for!
That was...
Yeah?
so unexpected from Mel-sama.
I didn't think she could express
a feeling of bitterness with that "Nn..."
Right?
I see...
Mel-sama has my vote on this one!
Oh!
Yay!
Pacifier candy
Lollipop
Let's hear Luna-sama's
misheard sexy line in...
Okay!
Three!
Two!
One!
Act!
Lo...
lli...
Lolli...
po...
p...
Ah...
TIME OUT!
Next up!
It's time to sexy duel!
Three!
Two!
One!
Act!
Pacifier...
Ah...
Candy.
Ding ding ding ding ding!
Whoa.
That was so lewd!
You could hear the sucking sounds!
Well, it's a pacifier.
I didn't think Mel-sama would
not just suck, but also swallow for us.
With that said, this round goes...
Wow...
to Yozora Mel!
Yay!
Luna-sama.
What are your thoughts on
going up against Noel-sama?
She's a pro at phrasing her words,
so I have to do my best to...
Uh, that thing.
uwu
I have to do my best to keep up with her!
"uwu"?
uwu
What's "uwu"?
uwu?
I forgot how to talk.
All right then, reveal your prompt!
Hot meaty buns
Bottled beer
Luna-sama has "bottled beer."
Noel-sama has "hot meaty buns."
This sounds hard.
Oh!
Another tough set.
It's time...
to sexy duel!
First up is Luna-sama's
misheard sexy line.
Three!
Two!
One!
Act!
Bottled...
Bottled!
B-Bottled...
Bottled...
bee...
eer...
Someone bring some fresh diapers!
I'm not a baby!
Next up, we have Noel-sama's
misheard sexy line in...
three!
Two!
One!
Act!
Hot, meaty...
buns...
Yes!
That was quite...
Yeah.
Hot and meaty, right?
Nice juicy buns.
The way Noel-sama sounded...
like she was pleading for something?
My heart's fallen to the temptation.
I'll have to go with Noel-sama on this one!
Oh my!
Juiced the point!
Poison mushrooms
Thick, heavy ramen
Next up is Noel-sama's
misheard sexy line in...
Three!
Two!
One!
Act!
Thick, heavy...
ramen...
Ah!
Whoa...
Wow...
That was...
cwazy!
Beautiful.
That was thick and heavy.
Next up is Luna-sama's
misheard sexy line.
Act!
Poi...
son...
Mu...
shwoo...
oom.
Whew.
Whew!
Hey!
I see how you made that "oom" shorter.
Ah...!
She can't decide!
This agonizing voice of hers is sexy.
I'm going with Noel-sama here!
Ah...
Noel-sama has two points now,
so she wins this match!
Yay!
No!
Neeps and tatties
Spotted dick
First up is Mel-sama's
misheard sexy line!
Three!
Two!
One!
Act!
Spotted...
dick!
Oh, that's risqué.
It's just a pudding!
I paused after "spotted,"
and then put extra love
into the second half.
All right then!
Noel-sama's is up next in...
three!
Two!
One!
Act!
Neeps...
and tatties.
AHHH!
If you take "neeps and tatties"
and change one letter,
it turns into something
that we can't show on the air.
My interpretation symbolizes
the danger of neeps and tatties.
Huh...
I really can't decide
which one I like more...
I see.
I'll go with Mel-sama here.
Mel-senpai's just too sexy.
Loaded stuffed meat buns
Melt-in-your-mouth banana
Now for Noel-sama's
misheard sexy line...
Act!
Loaded...
stuffed...
meat b-bun—
Ah!
What?
Attempt abandoned
Huh?
I am ending myself.
Seppuku it is.
What just happened?
Huh?
Next up, Mel-sama!
Three,
two,
one...
Act!
Melt-in-your-mouth...
ba...
na...
na!
Ahhh!
Wow...
That's the stuff!
The way you go in
with how you say "banana"
was just so perfect...
Amazing attention to detail.
That's a pro for you.
That's a win for Mel-sama!
Wow!
Whoa!
Wooow!
Results
The ultimate sexy duelist was...
Oh?
...the one and only...
Yozora Mel-sama!
Awesome!
Congratulations!
Wait, that's not...
You can call me the
sexy vampire from now on.
If you enjoyed this video,
please subscribe to hololive'sofficial
YouTube channel and smash that like button.
And with that,
farewell!
Farewell!
Starring
Yuzuki Choco
Yozora Mel
Shirogane Noel
Himemori Luna
The Sexy Mishearing Prompt Battle
was brought to you by Yuzuki Choco, and...
...Yozora Mel, and...
...Shirogane Noel, and...
Himemori Luna!