String panties?!
String?!
It's not as thin as string...
String panties?!
AHHH!
What?! Roboco-senpai?!
Roboco-senpai's quite tenacious.
"Tenacious..."
It's started! holo's Bonjour
a variety and talk show where
one of the guests changes every month.
Let's introduce our cast for today!
I'm hololive 3rd Gen's Symbol of Purity,
Uruha Rushia.
Thank you for having me.
Our next guest is...
Here!
Om, nom, Okayu!
Whee!
I'm Nekomata Okayu from hololive Gamers!
I am not their Symbol of Purity.
Thank you for having me.
She seems the purest out of them, though.
Is she their Minister of Affirmation?
She's exuding purity.
And last but not least...
Here!
Hello-robo!
I'm Gen 0's virtual robot, Roboco!
Yaaay!
Roboco-senpai's also the pure type.
I may be... I may actually be pure...
We're all pure this episode.
Yeah. This episode is
brought to you by the Pure Trio.
I'll be our host for today.
Okay!
So? Are you worried?
Very.
Are you nervous?
I am! My hands are shaking.
Really? I thought you did
really well for the intro.
Really? I tried to match
your manner of speech for the start.
Oh?
There's one good thing about talking slowly.
Mm-hmm.
You can buy time.
That's true.
You sure can.
Yeah.
If you said, "It's started! holo's Bonjour,"
you'd only go for three seconds,
but if you say it like this,
"It's started! holo's Bonjour,"
you've stretched it out to six.
You've used up quite a bit.
Twice as long?
Yeah! It's twice as long!
Buys more time.
I think Robocosan talks the slowest and
is the easiest to listen to out of the three of us.
That's true.
Right. I...
Ah, but... I sometimes talk really fast.
When I'm gaming, I try to talk fast.
Also, when talking about my faves or hobbies.
That's inevitable.
Yeah.
You just get so heated.
Someday, I want to talk normally
when talking about my faves.
Right?
Hmm? That means...
you also talk fast when talking about
It's bad.
your faves?
Really?
Yeah. I start talking twice as fast.
Can you show us?
Then, hypothetically,
if I were head-over-heels for Robocosan:
"Seriously, Robocosan's voice
is the absolute CUTEST.
Her singing stream the other day was
PHEN-O-MEN-AL.
She was whispering and all that,
and sang in ways I wouldn't
even DREAM of being able to do."
She got really fast!
Who was that?
Who? That was me!
Well, let's start...
Let's...
move on to the next segment.
Random Rapid-Fire Interrogation!
Yaaay!
🥁🥁🎉🎉
In this segment, the two of us
who've been on the show before
will pelt Roboco-senpai with questions.
Okay!
Are you ready?
I got thiselery!
Have you really got this?
We're gonna go fast here.
I'm fast! Faster than
Okayu's 2x speed from before.
We're gonna go fast. Ready?
Yes!
Then we'll start!
Please go ahead!
Yes.
The 20 question bearage—
barrage will now start!
What are your most attractive features?
Uh... My hands!
Do you believe in ghosts?
I do!
Oh!
Would you like to befriend them?
Uh... Depends on the ghost!
Which part of yourself do you like best?
My soft, baby face!
The cutest thing about your cats.
Their faces.
How are you feeling right now?
My cat feels great.
So one's there.
Is one there right now?
Yeah, around my feet.
Okayu-senpai, did any of
the answers catch your eye?
Her most attractive feature
being her soft, baby face.
Ah! Yeah.
Yeah.
I have quite the round face.
Mm-hmm!
Yeah.
And I really like it, personally.
I feel like we all have
pretty round faces here, though.
You're right!
Everyone here has really pokeable cheeks.
Yeah. They're really soft and big.
It's cute.
Yeah. I want to stretch them out.
Okayu-senpai, I won't lose!
Oh? Is she putting up a fight?
Everyone's putting up quite a fight.
I've been called bun-face before, after all.
Can I read out some things
the comments pointed out?
Sure.
Go ahead.
They were curious about the ghost thing.
I was curious about
the "believe in" question, too.
Oh, ghosts?
Yeah.
I believe in them!
Really? Why?
A friend came to me for advice
about ghosts before.
Uh-huh.
And they told me about
these paranormal activities.
Uh-huh.
And they had pictures too,
so it made me freak out.
Because of that,
I believe ghosts exist.
I believe in cold spots being due to ghosts, too.
Cold spots too?
Oh, so that's why.
I think it wouldn't be an exaggeration to say
Rushia-chan's the closest being to ghosts.
Really?
I interact with them every day. Even now.
Right now?!
Yeah, currently and into the future.
Are there a bunch of them here?
There sure are!
They're all my friends.
I might still be able to befriend these ones...
Yeah. They're not evil, so you'll be fine!
I thought that "Depends on the ghost"
answer was really funny.
I know, right! Being friends
depends on the person.
So there are different types.
It's a big deal!
It was really funny.
Seriously.
What if they turned out to be a creep?
A ghost that's a creep?
As a ghost?
Like, a ghost that only visits
when you're in the bath.
You're right! They can
go through walls, after all.
Here's our next segment!
What do you think of me?
Poll Up My Image
Yaaay!
Ba-ba-ba-bam!
In this segment,
Rules
The viewers
Is Uruha Rushia wholesome?
the viewers will be polled on a particular theme.
Once we see the results, we'll start chatting
about a topic related to the poll theme.
35% Wholesome
HUH?
After we finish the talk segment,
the same poll will be run again.
Topic: Recent obsessions
The results of the second run will tell us
what the audience took away from our talk.
100% Wholesome!
* Wrong answers not allowed.
Mm-hmm.
Our first theme is this!
Who's the ditziest out of us?
This one's hard to choose!
Staff-san, please start the poll!
I'm at the top of my game today,
hosting and all,
so there's no way I'd get a vote.
There'd be something up.
The real deal's on a whole other level.
Did you just call me the real deal?!
Let's show the results of the poll!
Ready?
Yes!
Here are the results!
Roboco
Okayu
Rushia
There's something wrong!
Whoa!
This is so wrong!
This isn't right!
I think this is accurate.
It's accurate.
I think everyone messed up.
Messed up?
Everyone pressed the wrong option, I'm sure.
What do you mean everyone messed up?
I voted for Rushia,
but my 90% isn't reflected on her side.
You voted for me, Roboco-senpai?!
I voted for you without question.
That's strange...
I've never done anything ditzy before.
Did you do anything dumb recently?
Let's talk about it.
In that case, yesterday,
when they said it was break time,
I stretched out my arms,
but forgot that there was tea on the table
and ended up spilling the tea
all over my iPhone.
So...
I had just switched to the 13,
but I've already spilled water on it
and damaged it momentarily.
The notification sound bugged out,
which was annoying.
Seriously?
Yeah.
I put it in some drying agent
for a day, and that fixed it.
What? That's amazing.
Yeah.
So you fixed it.
I had just switched it,
but the screen's also already broken.
Wow.
Wait, why is your screen broken?
And it's making a lot of weird sounds lately.
What about you, Okayu-senpai?
Made any dumb mistakes recently?
Lately? Well, it's not much of a mistake,
Mm-hmm.
but I was putting on pan—
underwear after taking a bath,
and there was this pair
that was really hard to put on.
Uh-huh.
What kind of panties?
Just some normal ones.
Asking so casually...
I was wondering why
they were so hard to put on,
so I inspected them closely the other day.
Uh-huh.
And I found out that I was
putting my feet through the wrong hole.
That happens?
Because I was putting my feet
through the wrong place,
they felt weird when I put it on.
In the end, it was just me
putting them on wrong.
Can you even do that with panties?
Not really with normal panties.
But panties with thinner strings...
String panties?!
String?!
They're not as thin as string...
String panties?!
Okayu-senpai, can I say something?
Uh-huh, I see...
Sure.
I messed up on something recently.
Around 4 days ago... I did the same thing.
Yeah. I had a pair of 100% cloth panties,
and thought they were kind of tight.
I was wondering why, but I was in a rush,
so I just left for the convenience store as is.
Then I realized it was kind of breezy.
So I was thinking,
"Do I have a hole in my panties?"
When I got back home
and looked at my panties,
I realized I had put my foot
through the wrong place.
Let's wear panties the right way.
Have you ever put panties
on wrong, Robocosan?
Have you?
Not for panties.
But I have put them on backwards.
Though, I guess that's "wrong" too.
So like the front facing the back.
Yeah. I've confused the front for the back before,
but I haven't put my feet through the wrong hole.
I'm not that much of a ditz.
No, no, no. You are.
You spilled tea on your phone, you know.
Yeah, that's right.
Oh?
It seems...
the poll is almost finished.
Please go ahead!
Management and staff,
please show the results!
Please!
Ta-dah!
Roboco
Okayu
Rushia
Ah! My percentage went down!
Wait, what?
Okayu-senpai got more.
I got a bunch!
I only had like...
I only had 2% earlier!
You did! Only 2-3%.
You went up a bunch!
Congrats, Okayu!
You're a part of our side.
Whaaat? But I'm still light-years
away from you, Robocosan.
That's true.
This is a spell where more and more voters
will switch from me to you every time.
One sec.
Here's our next...
...segment!
Can I Affirm That For Ya?
This is Okayu-senpai's segment!
Please explain the rules, Okayu-senpai!
Okay!
Since I can affirm anything and everything,
The Fail
You went to change for PE but found out you
were wearing pajamas under your uniform!
Viewer
in this segment, I'll read a viewer's fails
I see...
and have the other two guess how I'll affirm them!
We've gathered some failures
ahead of time, so let's take a look!
Here's our first failure!
"I was heading to the restroom while spacing
out and almost went into the girls' restroom."
One response popped in my head.
You got something?
Wait, but this might be rejecting them.
You're supposed to affirm them!
You have to affirm them.
Yes, you do.
Is this okay?
Wait, now I'm scared to answer!
Wait a sec...
This one's quite difficult.
It sure is.
They were just heading to the restroom
and almost entered the wrong one.
You're both struggling quite a bit.
This is hard.
If it were me, I'd say,
"You creepy bastard!"
What do I say...
Affirmation...
Is this not affirmation?
I think you can put what you believe is right.
Got to add some support... But how...
Affirming someone is hard!
This is really hard.
You can't really give the OK
in this situation, after all...
Right? Affirmation... Affirmation...
This is super difficult!
Affirmation?
I can only think up extreme ones.
The girls' bathroom...
You're both struggling so much.
It's really hard!
Okayu-senpai's laughing so hard!
You sadist!
What is that supposed to be, Robocosan?
My brain's so confused at this point.
What is that?
I don't know!
I don't even know anymore!
What do we do, Roboco-senpai?
Well, then. Let's start with
Rushia-chan's.
Okay. Here.
Please show Rushia-chan's answer!
"Forgot your glasses at home, huh?"
Ahh... Insisting that they
forgot their glasses, huh?
Implying that they're going the wrong way
so that they realize before they walk in.
I see.
Makes sense.
Nice. Yeah, depending on the person,
they may use it
as an escape route.
Ah... then that's not good!
That's... well...
So it's not?
If they were intentionally trying to go in,
then I'll extract their soul
and take them to the Oozora PD.
It might be faster to
take them somewhere else.
Let's show Robocosan's next!
Okay.
Please show Robocosan's answer!
"There aren't any onigiri there, so why don't
you come to my stream by accident instead?"
What the heck is happening here?
I couldn't think of anything!
What does it mean?
I...
I don't even know anymore.
What happened, Roboco-senpai?
What does that mean?
What I meant to say, I think, is...
"Come to my stream by accident next time!
Visit my stream by accident
while going to the restroom."
In short:
"Come to my stream too!"
Basically saying, "Come over whenever!"
Welcoming them anytime.
I see.
I get it now.
I'd like to reveal my answer
to the troubled two now.
I want to see!
Here's my answer!
Open!
"Having more embarrassing experiences
lets you be nicer to others."
was my reply.
This...
Doesn't this seem a little sadistic?
What?!
It'll hurt some people.
It's pretty amazing, though.
Yeah.
I can't help but admire it.
It made my heart skip a beat.
They might swoon from the smoothness.
I think nice people can
be nice to others because
they're more familiar with
unpleasant emotions than others
Ah... I see.
and have experienced
embarrassing situations more often.
You have a point.
That's profound.
Now that you mention it, yeah.
So like, there are some things they can say
only because they've experienced it in the past.
Yeah.
I see!
This is deep.
It sure is.
I thought her sadistic side
was leaking, but it was just good.
It was just kind words.
My sadistic side...
Ah... I see what you mean.
Yeah.
Here's our next segment!
Robocosan SOS
Yaaay!
Yay!
This is Roboco-senpai's segment.
Please explain the rules!
Okaaay! For this segment...
I'm a high-spec robot,
but I don't have any luck.
So, in order to train my luck,
I'll have everyone play
a luck-based game with me!
Yaaay!
Well then, please look at the screen.
Oh?
Lemme see.
AHHH!
What?! Roboco-senpai?!
What happened?!
As you can see, I've been captured.
So please...
Help me... Save me, everyone!
Should we save her?
Want to leave her?
Wh-Wha... Don't leave me!
I'm your senior, save me!
She looks fine. Even happy.
I'm not laughing! I'm crying!
She looks happy.
Saving me is actually easier than it looks.
All you have to do is
push each of these buttons,
one button at a time.
However...
one of the buttons is connected to the bomb,
so if you end up pressing that one...
the bomb will go BOOM!
Which will result in failure.
Is this safe?
You'll be able to save me if you press all
the buttons that aren't connected to the bomb,
so work together to save me!
I know I don't have much luck,
but Okayu and Rushia have good luck... I hope...
I have terrible luck, you hear?
The reason your luck was bad
this whole time was for this moment.
You were stockpiling your good luck to save me!
You know what, let's bounce.
Are you saying it's a waste to use it here?
I guess we can save her.
Save me!
For the first stage, there's one out of the eight
that connects to the bomb.
Oho.
That means seven of them are safe.
So save me stress-free!
Okay!
All right, then...
Robocosan SOS... start!
Who's going first?
Since Rushia-chan doesn't want
to use her luck here,
she can go first.
Thank you.
Won't-use-her-luck Rushia will go with "X."
Wait! Wait!
I knew she'd pick that one.
Is that okay?
Doesn't the "X" seem like the riskiest one?
"I won't use my luck," so "X" meaning "No."
I won't pick the circles.
Wait,
aren't you being too hasty?
Alright...
Can you say the magic words, Boop the Button?
Boop...
the Button.
No, not this sound!
Ahhh! That was so scary!
So this one's safe?
Safe!
Believe in me.
You used up a bit of your luck, Rushia-chan.
Crud, I used up some luck.
Thanks, Rushia-chan.
Keep it up.
Then...
Next one is...
Can I go next?
Yes. Go ahead.
Of course.
What should I go with...
Maybe the green circle above the "X"?
Oh?
Oh? And why this one?
"O" is pretty pressable, right?
That's all. I wasn't thinking
it looked like a bomb or anything...
True. It looks like a bomb.
That... Saying that means you did think that!
You were thinking that for sure!
No, no, I wasn't.
No way.
No way I was.
No way, no way.
Time for the magic words...
Boop the Button.
Go ahead.
Wait, now I'm really nervous!
Is this where we say goodbye?
Okayu? Okayu?
What?
Is just one too easy?
Are you sure you want to say that?
I'll use some depth psychology for the next one.
People will most likely...
Mm-hmm?
Since there's just one...
With this pattern, and just one wrong button,
the star is probably also safe.
Uh-huh.
This is just a feeling I have, though.
But aren't stars always burning?
I see.
Don't they explode over and over?
Huh?
In space. Right? They're burning, right?
They are!
Hold on...
She has a point.
I'm a little unsure now.
You gotta go with your guts in those times.
Yeah.
Your instinct, huh.
It's fine. You two picked the X and O,
and the management team probably thought,
"What kind of idiot would pick all three in a row?"
Uh-huh.
So the star has to be safe.
Okay, sure.
Yeah.
So I'll go with the star.
Boop... the Button!
Will she self-destruct?
No way.
That... That won't...
We've been on a streak so far...
There's no way.
Oh, it was safe.
Roboco-senpai's quite tenacious.
"Tenacious..."
Why don't we start
from Robocosan this time?
Yeah. Let's do that.
From me?!
The order will be
Robocosan -> Me -> Rushia this time.
Sounds good.
Wait, I... Huh?
Seriously?
We had a lot of reddish colors today,
so maybe that music note.
Yeah. It looks pretty happy.
Yeah!
But... doesn't it seem like
it'll cause a bloodbath?
No, it's like a vibrant pinkish-purple.
It's not red. That was the "X," so...
Then we'll probably be fine!
Easy.
It's too easy!
I believe in you two,
so there's no way I'll blow up from this.
Let's go with the euphoric music note!
Boop
the Button...
She really pressed it.
Why would you say that?!
What?
Oh! It's good.
Huh? Roboco-senpai's still...
She's hanging on.
She's really tenacious.
Stop saying that!
You're supposed to be saving me!
I'm counting on you for the next one.
I guess I'll try for the explosion.
I'll pick the next one.
Stop that!
Please, Rushia.
OK, OK.
Then the circle for an explosion.
Please.
For an explosion?!
Circle, please!
Hey!
Stop it!
Even if you say that, it won't explode!
Boop the Button!
The fact that you said that makes it fine.
Whoa!
Crud, I'm using more and more luck!
It might be my lucky day today!
Okayu, please.
Then...
How about the onigiri-like triangle?
Oh? Sounds good.
Let's go with the triangle.
Yeah.
Boop the Button!
This should be fine.
She's starting to get complacent.
She's getting blown up soon.
She's totally setting herself up.
She blew up! She's a grilled onigiri now.
You okay? Need a revive?
Let's do it.
She's still breathing, though.
Is she alive?
Roboco-senpai?
Need this necromancer to revive you?
But you're still alive.
I'll shove an onigiri in her mouth then. Here.
Ah... She's d—
Ah...
Extra
Wait, is there really an Oka-rap?
What? No.
Oh?
No. It doesn't exist.
It doesn't?!
It doesn't.
I want to see!
Let's reveal the answers!
Who wants to go first?
No self-confidence
Well, but...
...and was about to fall when
the person behind me caught my fall.
Caught their fall... I'll channel Okayu-senpai.
Ah! I lost my balance!
Are you okay?
Huh? Ah. Thump.
Um... Uh...
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub channel
on NicoNico for the full stream archives!
I thought of one!