HOLOLIVE FANTASY - Interact Fantasia
Music: Ren Morimoto
Vocals: HOLOLIVE FANTASY
Key Visual Art: Modare
Mini Character Art: CHANxCO
Logo Design: Kaoru Miyazaki
Video: Ehre_origine
No stopping this hype train
Interact Fantasia!
Wake up, fantasia!
This is a neverending fairy tale
Wake up, fantasia,
let's go! Yay!
Pekora!
Du-dun-dun-dun! Aim for the top!
Follow my lead as we peko
Rushia!
W-Wait! Let's all go together!
You know, I'm not so sure about this now
Flare!
There's nothing to fear, keep going, keep fighting!
Noel!
It's okay to cry sometimes, take it as you go
Marine!
Ahoy! Once we take each other's hands
The curtain rises on our adventure!
As the days come and go
Let's take all the sights in
The vast, open skies
The ocean and the land
And use those memories to fuel us
While we face each new day
Chasing after our boundless dream
You are here with me and give me strength
When we share the burden
Of all our fears and anxieties
We can enjoy going down this untrodden path
Paving our own way
Our hearts give the signal, it's time to go
The future of our dreams is waiting for us
I couldn't do it without you, but here you are
So let's bring our worlds together
Our journey has already begun
Wake up, fantasia!
This is a neverending fairy tale
Wake up, fantasia,
let's go! Yay!
NoeFla!
Hello! Everlasting tale!
Our lives illuminated by twin quasars!
PekoMariRushi!
Say goodbye to the doldrums,
raise your voice, and start
We know you can keep up
with this twinkle dream
1!
It's time to set off
2!
Are you ready for this?
All okay?
3!
Now ring the ball
And start a new chapter of our legend
The courage to take the first step
Will cast a magic spell
Beyond the ends of the earth
Past the screens between us
We come to see you, nothing can stop us
So why don't you take a leap of faith too?
No dream is unattainable
With you, we can go as far as we want
Your incessant cheering
Guides our hands to the paper
As we chart every corner of this once-blank map
And set off
Singing our prayers out loud, we can hear it
While it may be a fantasy
playing out on the screen
Our connection is not an illusion
So let's bring our voices together
With a miracle
And break out in symphony
Forever and ever
We wanted to be stronger
We wanted to share all the laughter
So we sent out a message in 0s and 1s
And finally found you
There will be no dead ends or regrets
Every day is an adventure filled with wonder
So we keep running as we are
To wherever our racing hearts take us
Let's go
Chasing after our boundless dream
You are here with me and give me strength
When we share the burden
Of all our fears and anxieties
We can enjoy going down this untrodden path
Paving our own way
Our hearts give the signal, it's time to go
The future of our dreams is waiting for us
I couldn't do it without you, but here you are
So let's bring our worlds together
This journey will never end
Wake up, fantasia!
It's my Fantasia...
This is a neverending fairy tale
Wake up, fantasia,
let's go! Yay!