Hoof, hoof, helloof!
konbandododo!
Say your greetings together with the hololive members!
hololive menbaa to issho ni minna mo aisatsu shite mite ne!
Ready, set, go!
nunnun nunnun
How are we doing today? Tokino Sora!
minna genki? Tokino Sora
Nya-hello! Sakura Miko!
nyaharo Sakura Miko
This moment is key! This is AZKi!
konazuki AZKi desu!
Sweet bites! Yozora Mel!
konkapu! konkapu! Yozora Mel!
Haachama-chama!
haachamachama
A-quality day! It's Minato Aqua!
konakua! Minato Aqua desu!
Choc-on! Yuzuki Choco!
chokkon, Yuzuki Choco
Oh, hello, I'm Murasaki Shion.
aa, konbanwa, Murasaki Shion desu
You listenin' to me?
tte kiiteru?
Hey!
neeee
Hiya-peko! Hiya-peko! Hiya-peko! Usada Peko--
konpeko konpeko konpeko, Usada Pekor
Yay! Hel-Rushi! This is Uruha Rushia!
iei! konrushi! Uruha Rushia desu
konpeko konpeko konpeko, Usada Pekor
Hey! Don't talk-o over me!
iei! konrushi! Uruha Rushia desu
cho, kabusetekunna peko!
Ahoy! Houshou Marine here!
Ahoy! Houshou Marine desu
Uh, I don't really have a standard greeting, you see.
aaa, watashi betsu ni kimatta aisatsu toka nai n desu yo ne
Huh? Come on, Cocochi, introduce yourself!
ee!? Cocochi! chanto jikoshoukai shite!!
Hoof, hoof, helloof! This is Tsunomaki Watame!
konbandododo! Tsunomaki Watame
Sup, groupies! Behold your Towa-sama!
konyappi! Towa-sama desu!
The hololive members keep coming. Next up is...
hololive menbaa madamada iru yo! tsuzuite wa?
Lamyoohoo! Yukihana Lamy!
konrami desu. Yukihana Lamy
Good afternene! I'm Momosuzu Nene!
konnene! Momosuzu Nene desu!
Brrr. I'll persevere-Risu!
purupuru~ ganbari~ Risu!
Moon, Moon, Moonafic!
Moon Moon Moonafic da yo!
Oh! Yes, sir! Iofi, sir!
o o o! Obisa no Iofi!
Hey, I'm Mori Calliope, I bring death.
atashi ne! Mori Calliope desu
Kikkeriki! Takanashi Kiara!
kikkeriki, Takanashi Kiara!
Of course the two of us come together!
yappa watashitachi futari setto ni naru n desu ne
Shut your mouth, stupid chicken!
urusai kusotori! damare!
yappa watashitachi futari setto ni naru n desu ne
All together, here we go!
saa minna de issho ni!
Scream out your fave's name, high and low!
jibun no oshi no namae o sakebou!
All together, here we go!
saa minna goissho ni!
Can't hear you, you know?
sonnan ja zenzen kikoenai zo!
All together, here we go!
saa minna de issho ni!
That's better! Love you all!
ii kanji! minna daisuki!
(hololive)
Okay, everyone, one more time!
saa minna ikku zo!
(hololive)
All together, here we go!
saa minna de issho ni!
Let's make this a wonderful event!
sutekina raibu ni shite ikou!
All together, here we go!
saa minna goissho ni!
Raise the hype levels through the roof!
dondon moriagatte ikou!
All together, here we go!
saa minna de issho ni!
Let's create unforgettable memories
wasurerarenai omoide o!
All together, here we go!
tsukurou ne, saa goissho ni!!
Sui-chan is just as cute today!
Sui-chan wa kyou mo kawaii!
Begin the festivities! Natsuiro Matsuri!
wasshoi Natsuiro Matsuri
Alona! Aki Rosenthal!
arona, Aki Rosenthal
Hello-robo! Roboco here!
harobo Roboco da yo
Foxy Day! 'Tis I, Shirakami Fubuki!
konkon! Shirakami da yo!
Hellooowl! 'Tis I, Nakiri!
konnakiri! Yo da mio~n
O-Ookami Mio here. Hellowl...
O-Ookami Mio da mio~n
konnakiri! Yo da mio~n
Don't feel forced to hellowl, Miosha!
Miosha gimu mio~n yamete!
I'm Oozora Subaru
Oozora Subaru!
Guack! Guack! Guack! Guack!
guwa guwa guwa guwa
Ne-ko-ma-ta Okayu and...
Nekomata Okayu to
I-nu-ga-mi Korone!
Inugami Korone!
All hustle, all muscle! Shirogane Noel!
konmassuru! Shirogane Noel!
Noon-nui! Shiranui Flare!
konnui! Shiranui Flare!
You came, ta! Amane Kanata!
konkanata! Amane Kanata desu!
Gaa! Himemori Luna wuvs you all!
nnaaaaaaaaa Himemori Luna nanoraa
Now, next up is...
saa tsuzuite wa?
Lion goes roar, roar, roar! Shishiro Botan!
raraion, gao gao gao! Shishiro Botan!
Polka, you there? I'm here!
Polka oru ka? oru yo!
I'm Ku-Ku-Ku-Ku-Kureiji Ollie!
Ku Ku Ku Ku Kureiji Olllie desu!!!
Morning... Anya-wn!
ohayo Anya-san da yo
Ahem! Attention, please! Reine at your service.
gohon... Attention please! Reine de gozaimasu
Ina, Ina, Inaaa! I'm Ninomae Ina'nis.
ina ina i~na Ninomae Ina'nis desu
a
I'm shark! I'm Gawr Gura!
same desu! Gawr Gura desu!
HIC
hic
I'm Amelia Watson!
Amelia Watson
All together, here we go!
saa minna de issho ni!
Scream out your fave's name, high and low!
jibun no oshi no namae o sakebou!
All together, here we go!
saa minna goissho ni!
Can't hear you, you know?
sonnan ja zenzen kikoenai zo!
All together, here we go!
saa minna de issho ni!
That's better! Love you all!
ii kanji! minna daisuki!
(hololive)
Okay, everyone, one more time!
saa minna ikku zo!
(hololive)
All together, here we go!
saa minna de issho ni!
Let's make this a wonderful event!
sutekina raibu ni shite ikou!
All together, here we go!
saa minna goissho ni!
Raise the hype levels through the roof!
dondon moriagatte ikou!
All together, here we go!
saa minna de issho ni!
Let's create unforgettable memories
wasurerarenai omoide o!
All together, here we go!
tsukurou ne, saa goissho ni!!