Okay, that's a wrap! See you tomorrow!
Another long recording session today.
I had to down five whole energy drinks.
I only have two left now.
Phew.
Hmm?
Oh, I've got an email. Click.
"To Friend A, please help playtest this"?
"holoearth.zip."
A zip file? Is it safe to open?
Hope it's not a virus.
It could be something really good, though.
"Holoearth"?
Hello and good evening!
hololive staff member Friend A, here.
Friend A (A-chan)
I've received a mysterious
"holoearth" file from a producer,
and I'd like to check it out with you all today.
But first, I'd like to read a
follow-up message from that producer.
"You might want to invite
two more to help playtest.
It'll be more fun."
Well, that's certainly vague.
But I decided to listen to him.
Here are our guests! Ta-dah!
I'm so sleepy, A-chan!
Shirakami Fubuki
Ookami Mio
My apologies for calling you so late at night.
I'm so sleepy, A-chan!
And I'm hungry!
My apologies for calling you so late at night.
I'm hungry, too!
Okay, we can order pizza later.
And I'm hungry!
I'm hungry, too!
Okay, we can order pizza later.
Pizza?!
Really?
Can we really?
And you're paying, right?
Sweet!
We can write it off as a YAGOO expense.
A YAGOO expense!
A YAGOO expense?
What kind of expense is that?
A YAGOO expense!
A YAGOO expense?
What kind of expense is that?
No kidding.
Pizza expenses!
The hololive member pizza budget, huh?
Anyway, the three of us can have pizza later.
First, I'd like to playtest
this mysterious file with you two.
A mysterious file?
What mysterious file?
Hopefully it's safe.
What do you mean, a mysterious file?
Are you sure it's safe?
Well, hopefully it's not infected with anything.
I sure hope not!
If we're "playing" this mysterious file,
does that mean...
It must be...
Is it a game or something?
The only thing we can "play"
at the office would be a game.
I can't think of anything else.
It's pretty late at night, but I assume it's a game.
Right.
Uh-huh.
I don't know the details at all,
so let's see what we can figure out.
Seriously?
All right.
O-Okay...
You seem very wary.
This is scary!
I'm getting very concerned.
Very much so.
That's hololive for you.
What are we getting into?
Who knows what's in store?
I guess we'll find out!
I guess we will.
Let's start this up!
Oh boy, here we go.
I know.
What's the deal, here?
You're both so cautious.
Let's bring up the game's title screen.
Please join the game.
Okay!
And here we are!
First impressions?
What's all this?
What's this? Kanatan's there!
She is!
Standing all alone.
She's alone!
It's sure got atmosphere.
It does! There's even a volcano!
What is this?
What's that thing in the middle?
Yeah, what is it?
So what is this?
It's not just one static illustration, right?
I don't think so.
It says, "Touch Start."
It sure does.
Shall we enter?
Sure!
We can enter it?
So can we press start?
Go for it!
Let's do it!
Okay!
Here goes!
Whoa.
I see a "miooooon"!
This looks like a world without overtime!
Wow!
I see a Fubuki in the shadows!
Here I am!
Fubuki-san, Mio-san, where are you?
I wonder if I can...
Oh, there you are!
Hey, what's up?
Wow, look at all this.
Well met, adventurers.
Wait, you're an NPC?
Well met indeed.
Welcome.
Give me good stats, please.
What's this thing?
I dunno.
Can you punch it? Oh, you can!
Oh, you can punch it?
Yeah!
What is it?
It's emitting this blue beam of light.
I'm doing, like, light punches.
I'm curious.
Yeah, it's...
What is it?
I dunno.
Let's walk around a bit.
This place is huge!
We're on a cliff!
It's a cliff!
Whee!
It was nice knowing her.
RIP.
It's fine. You can jump down.
Really?
Jump!
It's safe to jump?
Whoa!
Oh, I'm swimming!
It seems safe.
I'm swimming!
This is really...
Wait, what's that?
What is this thing?
It's like a jelly.
What is it? What is it?
What happens when you touch it?
I think it likes me!
Seems so!
Take that!
You can attack it!
Ow! Ow!
It dropped something!
It did.
Try picking it up.
"F."
"F"?
I picked it up.
What was it?
I can open my inventory with Tab.
What is this?
Looks like the hololive triangle.
A triangle?
It's "metamaterial."
Ooh!
I wonder what it's for.
Oh, you can make things!
There's a "quick craft" menu.
Oh, really?
So you can craft things.
So you can make...
Oh, there are stones on the ground.
You can pick it up!
You're right! Stones.
So pretty!
Let's gather them.
Hey, it's night.
There's an aurora!
Whoa!
It's so pretty!
We're right below it!
We sure are!
Is it cold here?
This is so cool.
Oh, and you can run.
Mio!
What's over there?
Mio, do you know where I am?
It's pretty obvious!
Your name is showing.
Dun-dun-dun!
How creepy!
Scuttle-scuttle!
Ew, what are you doing?!
What button is that?
Mio-san!
It's V.
V?
This is so weird!
Ew!
Now we're like monsters!
Miooo! Miooo!
That's so creepy!
Mio-san! Mio-san!
Those trees there
look like your symbol, Mio.
Indeed.
They're like your tree.
You're right!
I wonder if we can punch the trees.
Think we can get wood from them?
You can punch them!
Oh, you can!
This is hurting my fists!
Are there animals we can hunt?
Good question.
Ow, my fists!
Yeah, these fists aren't...
Stone knife...
Oh, you can craft a knife
with three stones.
You're learning quick!
Mio-san and I are doing things
the dumb way.
Hey, I found animals!
Is this even working?
Oh, really?
I don't think so.
We're not getting anything.
We're just hurting our fists.
Oh, I can put it in first-person view.
Maybe we should try again later.
Ahh! The boars are chasing me!
Fubuki-san!
Where are you?
They stopped.
She got away.
She sure did.
They're not hurting me?
Oh, there are a lot of boars.
Something's glowing.
If you go behind...
How cute.
Something's glowing.
If you hit them from behind...
Oh, you can attack these?
It dropped something.
Well, this is easy—
Wait, they're attacking me!
Hang on!
How do you dodge?
Are there no defensive moves?
You can do it!
This really—
A huge one came!
A-chan!
Help me!
I just got isekai'd! I don't wanna die!
Those things are no joke.
Reincarnated and...
She's now a red beam of light.
Please, avenge my death.
Those are tough.
Oh, there are emotes.
Victory pose.
Don't do a victory pose!
I can emote!
Oh, I respawned.
Ahh, hold on!
She fell down.
You okay there?
Sorry, I slipped and fell.
Anyway, I'm back.
I guess it's okay if you die.
It wasn't a big deal.
I found flint!
Let me get some, too.
I wanna craft that stone thing.
Where can I get more stone?
Let me get some, too.
I wanna craft that stone thing.
Where can I get more stone?
This thing turns into triangles!
There's lots of stuff.
Some of them shoot things, so watch out.
Found some stone.
It shot triangle things.
Triangle things?
Now I have enough stone.
I made a stone knife.
Wow, already?
Lemme try...
What button is it?
If you press G, you can quick craft.
Oh, really?
You can craft water out of metamaterial.
You can make water, too.
There's quite a lot of stone around.
In the bottom right,
it's got like your HP, hunger, and hydration.
So we need to eat and drink?
So you die without them?
This is a survival game?
Since when is Holoearth about survival?
Oh, I got wood!
You got it?
Nice!
Oh, I had stone.
Well done.
Hah! Take that!
Can I make something?
Wait! I'm crafting, too.
Hang on!
This is great!
It's so easy with a weapon!
Whoa!
I slew a Watame!
Watameee!
Watame-san?
Where are you, Watame?
They coded her in?
Watame-san's in this world, too?
Did they code a Watame-san?
Yep, she's here.
What a mighty sheep.
Got a bunch of stuff.
Watame was here.
I've lost you, Mio.
Me too.
I'm over here.
Where? I don't see you.
If your name is too far...
Behind you, behind you.
Behind me?
There you are!
Right behind you.
Found you!
Mio, watch this.
Which one was it? Here.
I can breakdance.
How do you do that?
Do we need this feature?
Control brings up
an emote and expressions menu.
You're right!
It sure does!
You gotta hold it.
Okay. Dance for me, you two.
Yay!
Gotta show my authority.
Oh, you can take pictures.
You can?
Take pictures?
Yeah, like this.
That's handy.
Wow!
It is.
Wow.
How cute.
We look like the
"these are your Apex champions" screen.
We've got no kills, though. In fact, I died.
"These are your champions!"
And if I select this, I smile! Wow!
I'm smiling!
So cool!
You're angry!
Oh, I messed up.
This is "Hip-Hop Dance 1."
I'm like that Touhou meme.
Ooh, cool, Mio!
Ah, very nice.
This is "Hop-Hop Dance 2."
Wow, cool!
Very cool.
We're all dancing.
I snapped a photo!
You did it?
It'll be a good memory.
I can change the expression...
There's "surprise" and "anger."
I'm angry dancing!
Hi-yah! Hi-yah!
That's cool. It keeps my expression.
I'm doing an exasperated pose.
Exasperated!
You're A-taro.
"Good grief."
It's A-taro!
That's so cute!
But Mio, you're clipping your sleeves!
So cute!
That's very cute.
Wow, what's this pose?
"Cat pose."
Meow!
The fans will love that.
It's the meowing pose.
Victory pose!
Lying down pose.
Oh, I'm lying down.
You sure are.
Anyone out there?
In this vast field of grass.
It's very idyllic.
Idyllic indeed.
Is nobody else around?
You would hope.
Are we the only ones here?
Is Kanata-san here?
Yeah, is Kanatan around?
We could go look for her.
Hey, there's a glowing rock over there.
You're right.
There is!
Let's check it out.
I wanna check it out.
There is!
Let's check it out.
I wanna check it out.
What is that?
Oh, you can run with Shift.
Go, go, go!
You sure can.
So fast!
What's this?
What is this thing?
Good question.
You can gather metamaterial here!
And tons of it!
What's this stuff for?
You can make water out of it.
Don't attack me from the rear!
No rear attacks, please.
Hi-yah.
Do you get anything from this?
I got metamaterial.
You're right!
Do its drops stick to it?
It kinda looks like that.
What is metamaterial, anyway?
Dunno. But you can make water with it.
I guess it's water?
Water, huh?
You can craft campfires, too.
Wow, really?
You're picking up on this fast.
I see, so you need to refill your thirst gauge.
That's right. You need drinking water.
I see.
Lemme take a drink.
It worked!
Oh, wow!
It's a campfire!
Wow!
A campfire!
Can we cook meat on it?
That's right. Should we hunt some boars?
Yes, you can!
Oh, you can?
"Heals 30 HP."
I'm gonna go attack these two boars.
I can take 'em.
Now that I'm armed.
When the meat's done,
it just drops on the ground.
Oh, does it?
Nice!
So unsanitary.
Nice, we got a lot of drops.
Grilled meat... Can't pick it up...
Can we eat the meat?
Oh, I got it.
Let's try cooking the meat.
Ah, so peaceful.
I think you need flint.
Flint? I see.
Whoops, I ate a piece.
Was it good?
So-so.
So-so?
A little gamey.
Is it?
Wild boar, you know.
Yeah, that would be gamey.
Just a bit.
Did you not get any mutton?
I think they only drop wool.
Oh, good point.
Just wool, huh?
Guess Watame-san is on a diet.
Not much meat on her, huh?
Indeed. Too lean.
Wait, I found something huge!
Where, where?
A giant one of the jiggly things!
Fubuki-san...
Wait, where are you two?
Oh, I see you!
Found you.
There you are! Over here!
Coming.
You won't believe this!
Is it a boar?
No, a big jiggly thing!
A jiggly thing?
A huge jiggly thing!
Wow, it really is huge!
What in the world?
Is it a boss?
A boss?!
Can we escape once we beat it?
Who knows?
Shall we give it a shot?
Let's try.
We're taking it on?
It turned into a cube!
Whoa!
What the heck?!
It's got impact!
Huh? That was weak.
That's it?
That was easy.
Huh?
Surprisingly weak.
We showed it!
It disappeared!
Oh dear.
Did it drop anything? Metamaterial?
Yeah, I picked it up.
Really? Good to know.
I'm swimming on the beach.
Ooh, there's a beach.
It's like you're the Shirakami of the River.
I'm just like...
So you can't pick up this stone.
Yeah, I couldn't.
Wow, I'm swimming one-handed.
Why is that?
You are!
Maybe because you have
a weapon equipped?
Oh, is that why?
Too cold.
It's cold in the shade.
There are more sheep.
The big guy respawned!
It respawned!
You're not so tough, are you?
Wait, it engulfed me!
Aw, jiggly thing!
Hey, it's cute when it's defeated.
Cute indeed.
It's got the >< face.
Anything else around here?
Can we get up there?
Wanna try?
We've been down here this whole time.
Yeah, I wanna climb up to that cliff.
Let's go for it.
Up the cliff!
Don't you wanna climb up it?
It looks so climbable.
Maybe we can get up from over there.
Wanna give it a shot?
We can circle around.
Are we all doing fine on thirst and health?
I'm fine—Wait, my health is low!
You okay?
My HP's pretty bad.
Oh, mine too, I think.
Should we start a campfire?
Let's do that.
Where's that, again?
Ow, ow, oh crap!
Oh crap!
My screen's turning red!
So is mine.
Uh-oh.
We underestimated that little guy.
We sure did.
That's not good.
I don't have enough flint on me.
I've got one.
I can't craft a campfire.
Lemme chop some wood.
Just gimme a sec.
I've got normal stone.
I can craft it once I get some flint.
I can give you my flint.
I've got one.
You got it?
Yeah, I should have enough now.
That's good to hear.
I'll place the campfire here.
'Kay.
Oh yeah, sheep don't drop meat.
Oops, I'm short one wood.
I've got a piece.
I think I can drop it.
It worked.
Great!
How do you drop items?
Just by dragging and dropping.
Oh, really?
Just toss from the Tab menu.
And with that...
Campfire... Campfire...
Campfire, campfire, campfire!
She's begging for the campfire.
I'm placing it.
The warmth!
Like a mother's embrace.
So warm!
It really sets the mood.
It's quite nice.
Despite how we're sitting.
That's true.
Now, put the meat on the fire.
I should pose lying down.
Ahh...
This is relaxing,
but I wish the grass was shorter.
Ah, there it is.
This is relaxing,
but I wish the grass was shorter.
Ah, there it is.
Okay.
And eat it.
There we go!
I healed up to my legs.
I could use more, though.
Wait, why can't I cook my meat?
You need to have flint.
Right, you mentioned that.
It takes meat and flint
to make one cooked meat.
Is that why?
I'm gonna go find some flint.
Gotta find some.
The place where A-chan died
is still emitting red light.
My spirit must be haunting it.
Your spirit is near it?
Oh no!
My spirit is near it?
Aw, crap, I died again!
Again?
A-chan's turned into red light again!
My apologies.
I generated another red light.
It can be a landmark.
We'll always know where we are.
They're really feasting on my corpse.
Crap, I'm glitching out!
A-chan's glitching out!
A-chan!
I seem to be enjoying myself.
You do.
You seem very energetic.
Indeed I do.
But I can't move—Oh, now I can.
Jumping freed me.
We've turned into debuggers!
We have!
This is now a debugging stream.
It sure is.
I could use some more meat.
We gotta find some more bugs.
Yes, hopefully we can.
Anything else?
Is there flint here?
Flint...
Please wait, miss!
Seems like it's just as I thought!
Sheep can drop only wool.
Ah, is that so?
Only wool, huh?
What can you craft with it, even?
No idea, but there should be something, right?
Hold on, two is too many.
Nothing here either...
The boars are the best source of meat, huh?
Yeah.
There's a ton of them... Hey!
No flint here either...
Where's all the flint at...
Wasn't there some at the waterside?
Waterside, huh?
Flint? I have two or so.
Uh-oh, I'm gonna die!
You okay there?
Oh no! Mio's gonna become red light too!
Oh no, more red lights!
Phew. That was a close one, but I'm fine.
Nice.
Good job.
Watame!
She's just bleating at me!
Thanks!
Have this... and this.
She's lost her ability to talk...
Ability to talk...
So this is what
the Alternative was all about.
Yeah. This is hololive Alternative.
I see.
Watame-san has regressed.
Indeed.
Watame...
Ah, there it is!
Ouch! What the—
What happened?
Some projectile just hit me!
Ah, yeah, slimes are quite smart apparently.
Hitting it with a fist is quite inefficient.
Sure, I have meat, but my HP keeps going down.
My health...
It's quite rough out here, isn't it?
Oh, it is.
Aw, back to square one!
Yeah, it's quite rough.
Oh no! I don't want to die to a slime!
Whoa, something's flying—A triangle!
hololive is flying!
What's the flying hololive triangle
trying to do to our talents?
Stop that!
Using hololive as a weapon is quite a stunt.
They made it fly.
They made it into an attack.
Well, it's pointy, so it must hurt quite a bit.
Ah, A-chan is done for.
I tried to collect my own drops and died.
I'll use your death to go on.
Go ahead. Feel free to see if
you can make use of my belongings.
Nice, nice.
I'm getting reincarnating the most.
Like the main character.
"Collect all."
I'll just pick up everything you dropped.
Oh, there are deer!
They tend to run away.
They are quite fast!
Let me try chasing one.
I barely deal any damage too.
I retrieved all your items.
Thanks!
I'm playing tag with a deer.
Oh, you can make a crafting table.
Eat this!
Stones... Need two more stones...
Oh, hololive is flying at me again.
Don't run away!
Ouch!
Ah! It ran to where I can't go!
No fair!
I'll make us a crafting table.
Oh, really? Oh, I lost the deer.
Are you on the upper side? Or below?
Below.
Got it.
We're near the fireplace by the river.
Ah, I see.
Wait! Don't attack me!
Boars just jump into attack right away.
"Crafting..."
Oh, you can't run if you get tired.
Oh no!
Yeah, there's a stamina bar.
Hold up! Timeout!
I barely exercise, so I don't have
the stamina to run away from a boar.
The crafting table should be...
The crafting table?
Rotate... Rotate...
I realize civilization is evolving, but I'm fighting
boars over here... I'll join you later.
Rotate... Rotate...
I realize civilization is evolving, but I'm fighting
boars over here... I'll join you later.
Oh! You can craft tons of stuff
with the crafting table!
Oh?
What do we have here?
There's a stone pickaxe...
Wow!
There's a table too.
"Cat plushie"! I want to craft it!
You can make it
with animal hide and wool!
You can even make a plushie, huh?
I have some wool.
I'd like some of it.
I think I'm lost.
Here!
Thanks!
Wool and...
Around here—Ouch!
One more wool and two more pieces of animal hide.
I think I have a single piece of animal hide...
Oh, I have four, actually!
Oh, you do? Gimme!
Come here.
Only wool left. Gimme wool!
Hmm?
I want some wool!
I'll go hunt some, then.
Please do.
Is there a map?
Maybe if you press M... Nope.
Oh, there's none.
Yeah, seems like there isn't one.
A bit troublesome when you're lost.
Looking for sheep...
Found them!
I-I don't want to say it,
but go kill them!
I'll get them.
Please do!
It's Watame-san's fate.
I'm a wolf after all.
Oh, right.
Hunting sheep is...
Your forte?
Guess you have to.
...my natural instinct.
Your instincts took over.
Yeah.
Oh well.
Oh, found you!
Here they come again!
Wow, so strong!
Awesome.
They dropped a lot of stuff.
You can take it.
Got wool!
You did? Yay!
Now you can craft
that cat plushie, right?
Yup. It's somewhat familiar.
Hmm? I wonder who it can be.
I do too...
I'm quite excited about crafting it.
I have a bad feeling about it.
If it's the one I think it is...
I wonder if we're thinking of the same one.
Oh wow, a crafting table!
I'm heading to our riverbank spot.
Okay!
Slimes are quite persistent.
Do they respawn here?
I'm out of flint again...
Flint? I have some! Two pieces.
Gimme!
Here.
Thankies!
Here's the wool.
Thanks for the wool, too!
It's suddenly become the main outpost.
Thanks, guys!
You can craft it now, right?
I should be able to, yeah.
The cat... Pfft...
Hey, it says "Aqua's NEKO" here...
Aqua's huh...
Done! Wait, no.
Here they come again!
Yikes!
Whoa!
Take this!
And this!
All good.
Aqua's NEKO...
Where'd it go?
Aqua's NEKO?
It's right here!
Oh? Oh, it's in there.
What do I do with it?
What can I do with it?
Okay, so here's Aqua's NEKO...
Can you place it?
I can, but it's red...
Red?
You probably need a desk
or something to put it on.
Ah!
You can't just place it randomly, huh?
Yeah. It's just red—
Oh, it says, "You can't place this here
since a required item is not found below."
I see.
Ah!
Guess we have to craft that as well.
I'll go get some wood, then.
Is this a table?
Oh, I need seven more pieces of wood.
Got it! I just chopped down a tree.
Seven more, got it.
How quick!
Big thanks!
I'll go get some too.
You need a table, right?
Yeah, I think I need a wooden table.
I have tons of metamaterial if you need it.
Oh, seems like we need a wooden base first.
A base?
You put a table on the base.
We need more wood,
so I'll go chop some.
I see. About weapons...
Does the knife you two are using
need wood to craft it?
Nope!
Ah, three stones! Then, just one more...
No, only three stones.
I think you can craft a stone axe too.
This shouldn't be too painful.
Got it.
I think it's easier with it.
There, stone axe—
I need one more animal hide.
Oh, I have that.
There, stone axe—
I need one more animal hide.
Please give me one.
I'll drop it here.
Thanks!
Animal hide... Here!
Yay!
The slimes come here often, huh.
Oh, I actually needed more wood...
And stones!
I have four...
Wood and stones...
This should be enough, right?
Did you make bases?
Let me try placing them.
Yeah.
This and...
Did you place them?
Oh wow!
I did!
Looks like you can make a bunch!
Really?
Whoa!
There you go.
A dance stage! Amazing!
Ouch! The audience is already here.
The audience...
They're quite persistent.
Oh no no no!
Mio-san, are you okay? What happened?
Did she lose all her stuff?
Did she?
Ah! How cute!
Here's NEKO.
Yay.
Just placed it here.
How cute!
Hmm? Where did Mio die?
Anyway, here's Aqua-san's NEKO.
We crafted one.
Amazing.
It's bouncing 'n' all.
It's moving!
You're really getting a close look.
It is! It's bouncing weirdly.
You don't have to get that close.
Wow, it moves a lot. Scary.
It's springing here and there.
It is! Wow!
If we keep crafting stuff like that,
it feels like we're developing a culture, a civilization.
Yeah.
There's a slime staring at us like it wants to join.
Oh yeah, I see it.
Whatchu standing there for?!
They like to appear here.
A-chan, isn't your screen kinda red?
It is.
Your HP...
I may look like I've got this,
but deep down, my HP is quite low.
Now, there seems to be
a mission from the producer.
Let's try tackling it.
A mission?
Yeah.
"Work together and build a beautiful house!"
We have an hour, it seems.
Yay!
"Yay"? Can we do it in only one hour?
We've struggled to get this far,
and now a house?!
Yeah! How long did it
take us to get here?
An hour, or maybe even two.
Exactly!
But now, since we're used to
the controls and everything,
let's make a house
for the three of us to live in.
Got it!
I see!
If we build a house, we won't be
constantly attacked like this—
Ouch!
Aah!
Cracks!
The floor! The floor cracked!
Oh well.
Anyway, it's going to be hectic...
Is the house gonna be okay? Will it be broken down?
It may get destroyed
if monsters can damage it.
Yeah.
Let's try and build one
without it breaking down. Yay!
I thought you got this.
Let's try and build one
without it breaking down. Yay!
But, uh, I think I saw a huge golem once.
Let's try and build one
without it breaking down. Yay!
But, uh, I think I saw a huge golem once.
Huh?!
Well, seems like we need a lot of wood.
I'll go die for now.
I think we need
a huge amount of wooden bases.
We might need a lot, yeah.
Oh, I've gotten myself a stone axe,
so I'll go do some wood chopping.
All of the home parts require wood.
We need tons of wood, huh.
What is that...
There's "something  garden stone."
What is that, even?
Oh, there's so much stuff to craft.
Chopping wood, chopping wood.
There's tons of stuff.
Demolition hammer, for example.
Wall torch, big wooden chest...
We need to make a lot of things,
so I'll go chop some wood.
Surprisingly, you don't get much wood.
Felling the trees takes a while, huh?
Oh wow, with an axe—
But with an axe, it's much easier, yeah.
I, uh, have no food,
so I might just starve to death.
Starve to death?!
Guess if I just die here, I can
recover my stuff anyway, so whatever.
"If I die here," she says...
Lately, I'm...
Not afraid of death?
Yeah, I'm not afraid of death anymore.
I mean, we're immortal after all.
Yeah.
Yikes... No more boars, please.
Oh, the night is upon us.
It's quite hard to see, isn't it?
Yeah, it's so dark!
Yeah.
How about moving our base?
Oh, nice idea! Let's do it!
Yeah, let's move it to
somewhere we can chop trees easier.
There's also a lot of slimes here, so...
Yeah, yeah. They respawn a lot.
Aah!
Are you okay there?
Return by Death...
Those... slimes... They're too much.
Ah, you've died.
Could it be that without a demolition hammer,
you can't move the crafting table?
Those... slimes... They're too much.
Could it be that without a demolition hammer,
you can't move the crafting table?
Wh-What? That would be quite rough.
I'm lost! Where should I go...?
Tell me, Watame... Hey, Watame...
Let's find a good spot first.
We can think about
where to move.
Wouldn't the starting spawn point
be a good place to move to?
Oh, sounds nice!
Easy to meet up, too.
Yeah, I feel like it would be
the most comfortable spot.
Should we meet up, then?
Yeah, let's do it.
At the blue light?
Yeah, at the blue light.
Yeah. It's the most noticeable landmark.
Hmm? Where is it, though?
Okay.
Oh, you can't go any further.
Yeah, a deer ran away from me
there earlier. I couldn't pass.
Deer only!
Exactly!
Hmm? Where's our base?
It just ran off outside the walls.
We're lost, huh.
Hmm? Where's our base?
We're so lost...
Wasn't it behind?
Let's try a different direction.
This way.
Ah, Mio-san is here too.
Hi there.
I can't see the light pillar.
Oh yeah. You can't see them
unless you get close enough.
I guess.
Should be this way...?
Ah, there it is!
I got closer, and the light pillar appeared.
Oh, you're right!
I see how it is.
Here's my grave.
And that one should be mine.
"Collect all..."
Can we take the crafting table
and the rest with us?
Phew, it's all here.
Let me take it back.
Anyway, I'll start building
a base near the spawn point.
Got it!
Will it break...?
Oh, it's breaking!
Really? Oh, you're right!
Keep going.
With a crash!
Oh, hey, it became a portable crafting table.
This too—Oh, the cracks are gone!
NEKO!
It's all covered in cracks now.
I want to take it too.
We're like barbarians.
Oh no, NEKO!
NEKO!
Is this horror?
It got hololive ERROR'ed!
Almost like we're in hololive ERROR!
NEKO gets covered in cracks too
when you try to break it, huh.
That's pure horror... How terrifying...
Those cracks...
It was really scary.
You can break NEKO too?
Yeah, you can.
Yeah, I did.
It's not something you'd want to break.
Its face got all covered in cracks.
That's just too scary!
It became a horror game for a second.
It was just like hololive ERROR.
I wonder if they would also release
a hololive ERROR version.
Scary!
But you can make it a
haunted house horror game I guess.
Sounds fun, though.
But you can make it a
haunted house horror game I guess.
Yeah! I'd play that.
Sounds scary.
I have a lot of meat,
but almost no flint, so...
Flint is quite hard to get.
I have... three pieces!
Really?
Yup.
Here's the crafting table.
Well, then...
Thanks!
I'm gonna drop it for you.
Thanks.
Here.
Oh, you can break stones?
Oh, apparently, you get
a lot of flint from breaking stones.
For real?
Really? Oh, yeah,
you can punch them.
Ah, it takes some time
with just a knife.
We might be better off
with a pickaxe or something.
I have something.
It looks like an axe, though.
Didn't you have just an axe?
I have something.
It looks like an axe, though.
Ah, I see. I wonder if it will be enough.
Ah, nice.
I'll go try breaking some.
I need some animal hide...
Okay!
Take that!
Break, you stone!
That's a wolf for you.
You stone!
Break!
I'll provide the little bit of assistance I can.
Just break already!
Oh!
Wow! It dropped lots!
Feel free to take it.
Wow! That's a lot!
Wow! It dropped lots!
Feel free to take it.
Really?
It was around 20 pieces.
That's huge!
It dropped a lot.
Whew. I'd like some wood...
That means...
The flint is no longer an issue, right?
Yeah.
Where can you get animal hide?
I think you have to hunt animals for it.
I think I picked up some from boars.
I just killed one, and it didn't drop any...
Maybe it's boar RNG.
RNG?! Oh, man.
"Create..."
I'll cook a lot of meat,
so feel free to take it when it's done.
Thank you!
You're everyone's mom, even here.
Mama...
I'll go chop more trees.
Okay.
Oh, I can craft.
What should I make...
A house should have a door, right?
First of all, we need more bases.
Right, bases.
I'll make some, then.
They're the top priority, yeah.
Would one be enough?
Or should I make more?
More! We're building a house after all!
I'd like a spacious house!
Greedy!
Oh, it's raining.
It's our first home, after all!
Oh, you're right. It can rain, huh?
Oh, yeah.
There's weather too, huh.
Uh, I can't pick it up, can I?
Uhh, I can't pick up
the bases I crafted...
"Try mouse scroll"?
Oh, you're right!
A voice from the heavens
told me how to do it. Thanks.
Should we start the house right here?
Yeah, it should be fine there.
Got it.
Our own house!
Yeah!
Around here should be fine...?
How do I...
I chopped down a lot of wood,
so let me try crafting too.
Go ahead.
Oh wow!
How many bases do we have now?
I have four on me.
I have eleven.
Wow, eleven!
That should be enough, then.
I'll go with...
I'll make walls, then.
We need them too.
Walls sounds good.
Oh, wait, I have only six bases,
not eleven, sorry.
I'll craft walls, then.
Okay!
Where should we build it?
How many do we need...?
Oh wow.
You can make a bunch.
Different types, too.
Oh! Six already looks pretty good.
Does it?
Yeah.
Oh, you're right! It's pretty big.
There's so much space.
Looks good.
Nice.
By the way, how do you place it?
You have to put it in the bottom bar first
Okay.
and then left click.
Ah! Got it.
Ooh! That's pretty spacious.
Wait no, not this.
The B button...
Ah!
Wow, so that's how.
The B button makes it easier with Architect Mode.
Oh, really?
And the button to place is...
Wow.
What is this?
And the button to place is...
I can't break it.
You can craft stairs too.
Really?
I can't place it.
I want to make this...
Shoot, it's off!
You can make a chest too.
They'll get mad at me!
That would be nice.
It looks weird now.
It's a wall torch!
A torch would be nice too.
Oh well.
Yeah.
It'll be fine.
Oh no! The gap!
"Gap"?
N-No, it's nothing.
Nothing's wrong here.
Not at all.
Hey, wait a second!
A-chan, this is...
Oh crap, she found out.
What's wrong?
She noticed it.
She's awful at this!
I tried to expand the house a little bit.
You're not cut out for this.
Is it really that bad?
She's just placing bases! What's there to mess up?
You're not cut out for this.
That's awful!
What were you going for here?
You got me wrong! I wanted to
make it look bigger than it was!
Ah...
Let's tear it down.
Let's.
Let's demolish it.
Disassemble!
Let's break it apart.
It's breaking.
I guess you have to put it down properly.
You actually have to aim.
Yeah, you need some accuracy.
Can I just leave it to you two?
I don't have much confidence in my aim.
You just gotta put it where it needs to go...
I end up making gaps.
...and you ended up with a bunch of cracks.
Nice!
How skillful.
I'm impressed.
I'll try placing the walls, then.
I have one more.
I'll try putting just one down.
Ugh... Like this?
Can I do it from the outside?
There!
Hmm... Well,
I'm sure they won't notice.
Notice what? You're scaring me.
What?
It's nothing.
Really?
Let's make a great house together!
A great house...
A great house we can all live in.
Is this fine?
Is this going to be okay?
We'll be just fine.
I'm getting worried about her.
I'm a master architect, so we'll be fine.
There's definitely something up here!
A-chan, this is totally off!
No, no!
It's because of subsidence.
You're going to make people with OCD mad!
Sub— Ahahaha!
I will, huh.
Subsidence is the one thing you don't want.
You're not supposed to
build on that kind of land!
And I would've gotten away with it...
Now I sound like a cartoon villain.
I would've gotten away with it if I'd said nothing.
Your building skills are atrocious.
It really is misaligned.
You're just imagining it, Mio-san.
The floor's off, so the wall's off too!
The wall too...
Skills, floor, wall, all off.
It's not nice to accuse people like that.
I made some stairs,
but there's nowhere to put them.
I see.
Where should I place this...
Give me one second,
I'll make this an entrance.
Thank you.
The indicator's red the whole time,
so I probably have to stick this onto something.
You probably need to connect it to a base.
I see.
Oh, so is this for a base?
I guess I don't need four of them, then.
You would've never needed that much.
We have a door now!
Thank you.
And now...
We need to make a roof too, right?
Right.
We want one since it rains too.
A roof is essential.
Ah, the rain cleared up.
How pretty.
The rain let up.
The sunlight is really nice.
It's calming.
We need so much wood.
I'll leave my wood here. I have 29 of them.
I'll go get some wood.
Okaaay.
Oh, you can place it diagonally too.
I wonder if we can
fell this huge tree too...
I wonder.
Ah, apparently we can't.
The big one's not possible.
It seems so.
Let's cut down the trees in the area.
Okay.
I think we'll need a theme for this house.
What do you want to do?
A theme!
Like "Cute" or "Stylish."
What kind of house would you like to live in?
Probably an office.
An office?!
You workaholic!
She's a complete corporate slave.
Do you live for work?!
Yeah, tell her!
I do!
Don't you feel unfulfilled like that?
After all, I have you all with me to... yeah...
"Yeah."
The only thing you could think of was "yeah..."
I don't think that gets a pass.
You need a bit more conviction than that.
I'll harvest some wood.
Wooden flooring...
I made a pickaxe!
Can I make a second floor?
Mm-hmm! Of course.
Sure. I don't think we can all fit
without making it more spacious, anyways.
Mm-hmm! Of course.
Sure. I don't think we can all fit
without making it more spacious, anyways.
Then... I'll make one of this
and a few of these.
I can harvest wood so fast now!
If someone from EN comes over,
like Sana, for example.
Her scale is kinda galactic, so you know...
I think this room's a bit small for Sana.
It's too smalll!
I guess she won't fit.
The stone pickaxe is amazing.
The boars die in two hits now.
I want one too...
Oh, you need animal hide.
I see.
Yeah, hunt some animals.
The pickaxe is so nice.
It definitely makes architect work
faster too, doesn't it?
It's amazing.
There's a wooden roof
and wooden diagonal wall,
so I think I can make a roof with these.
Yup. Make the roof.
What happened?
What do I do?
I can't figure out this architect mode.
Mio-san?
You were making fun of me earlier,
but did you perhaps...
Not at all.
You were making fun of me earlier,
but did you perhaps...
That's an interesting place to put the hole.
My head's hitting the ceiling!
It is?! Is the ceiling too low?
It's too low.
Please make it higher!
We sure can't go in here.
I'll have to take it apart once.
I see.
Bam.
Maybe the stairs aren't supposed to be here.
You can't go up here, I see.
Oh, so you can get it back
as an item even if you break it.
There's something there.
Oh, so you can get it back
as an item even if you break it.
What are you?
Oh, yes.
There's something there...
What's there?
There's like a golem here.
A golem?!
What?!
I want to see. Where are you?
Hello there.
Oh, it's not moving.
Nice to meet you.
Will it give us material?
I wonder.
It has an HP bar!
HP?
It's not moving, though.
Is it a nice golem?
Fubuki-san, where are you?
I wonder. It's hard to explain.
I can still see the blue beacon, though.
I see.
A golem?
You're right!
It's just sitting here.
It looks really strong, doesn't it?
But it's not attacking.
It's a friendly material.
It's friendly, but I'd like to see what it drops.
Ah! It came apart.
Raw meat?!
Hello?!
What's a golem made of?
What's a golem's meat like...
Another one spawned.
Ah! It's moving!
But it's really glitchy!
It's so laggy!
Its framerate!
It's shaking!
So is it still being fine-tuned?
It stopped.
It's spazzing out!
It's shaking a ton.
It's shaking.
So it's struggling to stay standing.
It's still a—
You're still a work-in-progress.
It's like a baby lamb!
A baby golem learning to walk.
It's a bit tragic to kill it, then.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I cracked it.
It twitches every now and then.
It's too cruel to bully it.
Yeah. I feel bad for it.
Oh, wow!
The 2nd floor is being completed.
Wow.
It sure is.
I fell.
It's not noticeable, is it?
You can get up now, right?
I can!
Wow!
What a nice view.
Let's work on it a bit more.
The part I worked on is a little... tilted.
That's your fault, you know.
Feel the weight of your sins.
It's that "Count your sins" line.
Right.
My hair's standing on end.
How scary.
Now for that roof...
Wow, it's starting to look like a house.
Guess I'll just put it somewhere.
It's looking like a house now!
Doesn't it?
It does! It does!
Amazing.
Huh.
Oh! That's how it works!
I see!
How are you doing there?
I'm a bit concerned if you're up for this.
Don't worry!
Sure you can do it?
I'l do it! I'll build the roof!
Look! I'm doing it!
You're right.
Okay, I'll leave the roof to you, then!
I'll do the roof, okay!
I'll go ahead and handle the interior design.
Please do!
I made something!
What is it?
A scenic rock.
A scenic rock...
What is that?
Aren't these the ones in Zen gardens?
I can see it.
You need to cut down all this grass,
otherwise it's not scenic at all.
That makes sense.
It needs to look fresh.
Let's put four...
Oh, I need some wool. Okay.
I'll go hunt some sheep.
Ah, as expected.
Stay safe.
Yeah.
My arms are getting buff
from all this chopping.
Every house needs a bed.
Don't you guys agree?
A bed would be really nice!
That's true.
And for that, we need wool.
We can make beds?
Ah, crud!
We can!
Really?
Oh, A-chan...
What?
Don't worry about me.
I just fainted for a bit.
A-chan...?
What exactly is this world, I wonder?
We don't know.
Good question.
We still have no clue.
All we know is that we're here.
Right? Why are we here?
How did we end up in this place?
Good point.
Thrown into a survival situation...
Exactly! We're in
a sudden survival situation.
Stuck in a deserted island...
I think I've heard of idols going
on survival situations before...
Stuck in a deserted island...
I think I've heard of idols going
on survival situations before...
It's that... sort. Yeah.
Like, "It'd be good to have Mio
with me on a deserted island..."
That would be nice.
I'd live, probably.
Oh, Watame hasn't respawned.
You really have to wait
It doesn't, huh.
quite a while for it to respawn.
I wonder if there's others around here.
No sheep in sight...
So peaceful...
It is.
What a tranquil world this is.
Enough to make you sleepy.
Right?!
Makes you not wanna go home.
Makes you wanna throw away your cares
in the world and just work here.
Stay here...
Makes you wanna throw away your cares
in the world and just work here.
Staying here forever...
Making this my home.
What if we summon YAGOO in here...
Make an agency here?
If YAGOO was here,
would we need to work?
What do you mean?
There's probably a world where we can avoid work
by locking YAGOO up somewhere.
We can do that?!
That's what you're going for.
That sort of world, huh?
It's possible.
That's the Alternative world!
Having lost YAGOO,
We have lost him.
we ended our idol careers
and forged our own paths.
And became survival specialists.
That would be cool.
We became survival specialists.
Our house is looking nice!
It does look nice.
It's more of a house now!
Adding a roof does wonders.
Dandy, isn't it?
Right? Quite dandy.
Good to hear some praise, finally.
It's quite dandy.
Survival takes a lot of work, doesn't it?
Agreed.
Gotta make everything yourself.
Pretty much, yeah.
We have 30 minutes left.
Thirty minutes...
Thirty minutes, yeah.
I think we have time for making furniture.
We probably have the time.
There seems to be iron in this game.
Iron?
Huh?
You need iron to make a big wooden chest.
Could I get it from mining rocks...?
Iron's too valuable.
I don't think we can get it yet.
We haven't made that much progress here...
What, there's no iron around here?
We haven't reached that tier yet.
Is that how it works?
So we can't make a large chest?
That's something for next time.
This sure takes effort.
Oh, found them!
It sure does.
The little people!
What are you guys?
What could you be?
What indeed?
What are you?
What are you guys?
They're going, "Wah-wah."
"Huh-huh-huh."
Oh, the people we saw earlier?
Yeah, them.
Oh, you're right!
Are they friendly?
Apparently not!
Are they enemies?
They're attacking me!
Uh-oh.
Oh, no!
What do you guys drop?
But they're so cute.
Take that!
Hi-yah!
Oh, they drop flint.
Wood, too.
Even stone. All sorts of stuff!
They must be a civilized race.
Yeah.
Oh...
Farewell.
I wonder if their base is this way?
Who knows?
Yeah. Oh, there are a lot of them.
Oh, really?
Maybe there is something.
Wonder what I should make next.
Hmm...
There's a waterfall.
There's a big waterfall.
Fubuki-san's exploring way out there.
Did I go too far?
I think you've gone pretty far away.
Wow, that waterfall.
Yeah, we can't even see her anymore.
Right.
Just wanna know how far you can go.
So curious.
You've got quite a sense of curiosity.
My curiosity?
How far can I go?
I get the feeling, though.
It's like figuring out hitboxes.
Yeah, like how big
is this thing's hitbox?
Right, hitboxes.
Yeah, like how big
is this thing's hitbox?
The question is,
can you get back?
I'm not sure.
I'm a little far.
But I can see the blue light.
Ah, that's good, then.
Glad we made the house here.
Agreed.
And now the roof...
Oh, what's this?
You can get a lot
of animal hide from deer.
Yeah, deer are good for that.
Oh, can you?
Right.
The deer drop a lot,
but they're hard to catch.
Yeah, you gotta really chase them.
Right.
I see.
I feel my feral instincts kicking in.
It's like I'm hunting in the wild.
The instincts of a hunter.
Indeed.
How frightening.
That's me.
This place is seriously huge.
Feels like I could keep going forever.
It really is a massive map.
Are you sure you should
leave the building to me?
Oh, no!
We'll end up with a crooked house!
Hey, I've got this handled!
Everything will be off!
I can make a house, at least.
I'm not so sure.
Me neither.
25 minutes left.
Gotta get back...
No, it's all right!
Keep exploring.
No, I think I'll head back.
You sure you can do it?
Let me handle the house.
What's this place?
Can we leave you to it?
Such a big map.
Yes, of course.
It just has to be livable, right?
"It just has to be livable"?
Are we talking about "livable"
by your standards, here?
For reference, I can sleep fine
on the office floor.
That is not reassuring!
Uh-oh!
So this house will be at least that livable.
Now, then.
While we've been away,
what did A-chan... Oh?
Oh!
Wait, it looks the same as before!
Welcome back!
Come on, no it doesn't!
Wait, so she didn't do anything?
The roof isn't completed at all!
No, I've made progress on it!
Hardly!
Give me some credit!
But there's a giant gap in the middle!
Now it's just a roof terrace!
But the right side is all filled in!
Not bad for a day's work, I'd say.
I think you can do better than that!
Finish the whole roof!
I was like, where's the roof?
No, see, it's an open concept house.
Open concept?
Yeah, the roof...
I'm pretty much just guessing
the placement of these pieces.
Hopefully it's right.
This roof is bigger than I thought.
No kidding!
It's really big!
The roof's looking...
Something's not right!
Wait, what?
It's not matching up.
The roof is all messed up from the back!
What happened?
It's not working right.
It's all messed up!
From the back—Come here, Fubuki!
Yeah?
Look from here!
Come on, it's fine!
Please don't nitpick!
Isn't it messed up?
What happened? It's all zig-zag!
Yeah, I dunno how it got like this.
What in the world?
You see?
How did this happen?
I dunno, I couldn't get it to line up.
How did you mess this up?
I can see why.
Oh, great, now water's getting in!
Rain will do that.
Alas, this rain.
Oh, I can make a wooden bed.
I can't place this...
Nice.
Let me do that.
I can't place this...
Make a wooden bed...
Why can't I place it?
Oh, you can make a demolition hammer.
Is that for, like,
tearing things down?
Oh, "Demolishes various materials in one hit."
Ooh, handy!
That's convenient.
It sure is.
That's handy.
That's a ton of NEKOs.
Ah, I sat on the table!
A lot of NEKOs.
I sat on it, somehow.
Oh, yeah you did.
So you can sit on it.
Let's face the other way.
I can't—I can't face the other way!
I'm just facing the wall.
I want a demolition hammer.
Sounds good.
I should make one.
It'd make things easier when we're laying things out.
Five pieces of animal hide?
Pretty expensive, huh?
...That's one hit.
Ah! You can sleep in this! Cool!
You can?
Whoa!
Really?
I can sleep!
Your pose is like that of a sleeping baby.
I'm sleeping!
So touching.
Whaaa! Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Oh, pressing F gets you out of bed.
It does work!
She's sleeping!
I'm sleeping on the job.
Definitely just lazing around.
Get off the bed and work on the roof!
This roof work is pretty bad!
Please finish up the roof!
A-chan...!
I'll do it! The roof! The roof, right?
Want me to teach you
how to make a roof, A-chan?
Yes! Please do!
You had no idea?!
So first off...
We might need to make more walls.
I see!
Hold on for a sec.
Sure.
Just adding parts of a roof
doesn't make it a whole roof, huh?
Mmm, that's a pretty naive approach to it.
That's how it works in my world, so...
It doesn't work like that, sorry.
It doesn't, huh...
We need to flip
a few of these walls, don't we?
Flip the walls?
Flip them, yes.
Flip the walls?!
I'm gonna... umm...
I'm gonna disassemble
these roof parts for now.
Please do.
I'll start by tearing down
these sections that look off.
Thank you—
Oh, so you'll be breaking them first.
Can you actually break these?
I can't reach it.
The roof break sound is pretty loud.
This wall is definitely off.
How do I tear down this part?
Maybe you're not reaching it?
Probably need to jump into it.
What do we do with this?
How are we gonna break this down?
Gotta do it like this.
Ooh, you break the wall itself!
Sorry for holding it up.
I feel really dumb
for being unable to do anything.
I'm gonna tear down
all these walls for now.
Sorry for letting you do all the work.
This is all your fault, y'know!
Damn, you'll see me lazing around!
Let me get...
Wow, there's an extra cat here.
Also, cute.
Cute, isn't it?
Amazing.
Good feature.
Great pose.
Now that's creepy.
You try sitting here too.
Let's see— Whoa!
The pickaxe sticks out too much though.
It does! You look scary!
I think there's space
for you to sit beside me.
Wow, I can!
Though, I'm sitting on a NEKO—
We're doing the same pose
but this is good.
It's a pretty unique pose though.
Straight out of Jojo.
Jojo-style sitting stance...
Can I put this here...?
Oh, cool!
The time stream's glitching out!
Oh, man.
This is so out of place!
We fast-forwarded a few centuries.
We did!
We skipped some steps.
"One-meter radius," it says.
This fusion of—
Fusion of East and West.
The worldbuilding's all over the place,
but that's how you know it's hololive.
Are we just gonna leave it at that?!
You can think of it that way.
Are we sure about that...?
There's like eight roof tiles over here.
Oh, I made those and left them there.
I see! Okay.
Now then...
I'll be taking these roof tiles.
Sure thing. Do you need more?
I don't think we need that many.
Hmm, I mean...
Gotta put them up to see if we do.
Oh, stylish.
Hunting monsters...
A-chan might be best suited
for monster hunting.
That's possible.
It's possible, yeah.
Should be a good stress outlet
since I don't really get to move much.
A stress outlet, huh.
(cat noises)
Shirakami's just a cat now, isn't she?
Total cat mode.
She added something
completely unnecessary there.
Interior design art, maybe?
It does look like
an interior design art piece.
I want some indoor lighting too.
Oh, what's this?
A wall torch!
We can make wall torches.
That should be useful.
I'll make one, then.
And it's made.
Whoa, it popped out.
Wall torch, wall torch...
Hmm, I guess...
Huh... Whoa! There's light now!
I can't place a chest...
Guys, look! The interior's lit up now!
This is probably the very first time
I've made myself useful.
It's so bright!
It is bright!
It got a lot brighter in here now!
Yep! This light's pretty useful.
Put one up here too.
Alright. Let me make one more.
Ah, wait. I'm climbing— I'm climbing?
I'm climbing the ladder here,
but my head's just bashing the ceiling.
Must be one of those cosmetic ladders.
Ah, right.
I'll go make another torch.
Second floor done!
Thanks for the work.
Excellent.
Torch... Gonna make
a demolition hammer too.
So umm... I'm just talking
to the wind here, but...
I think it'd be nice if
we had some pillars back here!
That's a good idea.
Maybe as a selfie spot too...?
Pillars though, huh?
Some pillars would be nice.
Here, yeah?
Right now this part is just floating.
Don't mind me, though!
Just talking to myself!
What do we need to make a pillar?
For a pillar, we need... stone?
No, not stone.
Wood. Let's get lots of wood.
I don't think we can make pillars
on the crafting table at the moment.
Oh, that's right!
Would be nice if we could make them!
Counting on you, devs!
That makes sense.
Wow, the thing you built
out here is pretty nice!
I wanted to place
a chest here but I couldn't!
It's a cute little outdoor deck!
Right? It's a nice little deck.
Those torches are pretty bright.
We should make some chairs.
Oh? I'm actually making one right now!
A stool, huh?
Chair... Need more metamaterials.
C-Collider interference?!
I can't place it because of collision physics!
Is that bad?
Where am I gonna set this chair?
I can't set it... I can't set it anywhere!
This chair is bugged!
Can't we add more lights?
We probably need one more.
Lights? I can make another torch.
Also...
...Ah, I died.
You died? How?
I probably died of thirst.
You die if you're too thirsty.
This whole wall is shifted.
There's an entire gap...
I see it! I see it!
Huh, it is. Why is it like that?
The demolition hammer
should work for this, right?
Let's tear this part down and rebuild it.
Use the demolition hammer.
I broke a bunch of stuff, I think.
A whole bunch of stuff?!
The top parts also got blown off.
I see!
I blew up the floor panels too, it seems.
The flooring was mismatched too.
It was?
The floor isn't lined up.
Ahh!
Yep, it needs fixing!
Damn, Mio saw through it.
The floor was off-alignment.
The floor wasn't aligned to begin with.
Can't hide my mistakes forever.
Add a new floor panel first.
Add the floor.
No use crying over my mistakes,
so let's start anew.
Then the walls.
No use crying over my mistakes,
so let's start anew.
And another wall here.
And another wall on top.
Thank you for your work.
Oh, this window shouldn't be here!
It's fine.
I guess the window goes there now.
Then put the floors back upstairs.
Is there something up here?
Can I climb any higher?
Huh, I can grab onto the wall.
This looks so weird.
Place the floor panels here.
It's all aligned now!
Yay!
Finally!
Thank you for your work!
It's been bugging me for a while now, y'know?
The wind's been passing through the gaps.
You can hear the wind
whoosh into the house!
Exactly!
You can hear the wind
whoosh into the house!
Exactly!
Time to strike a pose.
Looks cool at least.
These windows look pretty,
but they'd be prettier if we had
glass panes on them.
We can't get glass
in the game yet, I think.
It's not yet in the game, yeah.
Maybe they'll add it in the future.
We managed to make
a decent house in an hour, huh?
I tore down a lot of stuff!
Well, that was a jinx.
It totally was.
Let's start with the easy parts.
Wait, I just noticed—
This wall and the roof
are passing through each other!
Oh, you're right.
Take it down! Take it down!
If you hit one of the parts at the bottom,
the stuff on top also comes tumbling down.
So that's how it works!
Here. Go here.
Whoa. Nice, nice!
This is great.
It's complete!
Why don't we take a closer look?
Let's go take a look.
Here is the NEKO Altar.
They're cute.
Altar?!
It's an altar.
That's a lot of NEKOs we have here!
I think we can sit here too.
We can probably sit on this table.
Trade places with the NEKOs?
Ah, the NEKO are clipping through!
Can you sit with us, Fubuki-san?
I think I can.
Our sitting poses are all the same too.
I can't sit.
Oh, you can't? Only two people at a time, huh?
Two people only.
This looks good. Keep the pose, you two.
Sure.
Adorable.
Okay.
That was interesting.
Very cute.
Now...
Let's go inside.
Oh, there's a side window now.
Yep, there's a window now.
Ooh. Installed while I was dead.
We even have a bed.
Good night!
Whoa, cool!
Zzzz.
Zzzz. And wakey-wakey!
Good morning.
There's also a second floor.
Ooh, it's pretty up here.
It has a moody atmosphere to it.
We also have a proper roof
over our heads now.
Yes, it's amazing!
An actual solid roof!
I made parts of that roof!
Huh?
Hmm?
And so, we have made
a pretty good house.
It's really good.
This window has a tad bit
too many holes...
We goofed up a bit on that window,
but we'd cause too much damage
if we break it down.
...but overall we have
a good ambiance going for it.
but we'd cause too much damage
if we break it down.
...but overall we have
a good ambiance going for it.
I think the roof I made
had a unique flair to it, though...
I think calling it unique is a bit...
It couldn't even keep out the rain.
Our former patchwork of a roof
had also been neatly fixed up.
That's true.
Our former patchwork of a roof
had also been neatly fixed up.
We managed to fix it up now,
didn't we?
Yes, we did.
And we ended up
with these four NEKOs.
Yeah.
A wonderful home.
That was probably a good way to close.
It seemed to be, yeah.
Okay! We managed to do
a lot of things today,
but what are your thoughts
on this mysterious file?
Did you guys have fun?
It was!
Hmm, let's see...
It was pretty fun, and I think
there's a lot more in store for us.
But I am pretty surprised at how well-made
this already was for a first preview.
It is, right? It was playable!
We managed to make
a nice-looking house too.
I'm sure we have a lot
of expectations for this game,
but could Fubuki-san and Mio-san, in that order,
give their initial impressions first?
Sure!
I'm really interested to see
what this game can turn into!
I do think it'd be great if we can do
more stuff in-game besides build.
That's true. There are some
peculiar structures here too, after all.
Yeah, precisely!
What are those, I wonder?
It would be cool if we could
get to fight monsters and such.
I see, I see.
Let's look forward to what they add next.
Looking forward to it!
Now then, Mio-san! Your thoughts, please.
Okay! Man, I've gotten
more excited for this game now.
Since our characters
are already in the game,
it'd be great if we can hear
some battle voices too.
Ooh, that'd be great!
it'd be great if we can hear
some battle voices too.
I'd be happy if we could
get our voices in here.
It's a great idea.
I want it to happen!
There's a lot of requests on the table,
and it'd be exciting to see those implemented.
Personally, I'd want the
building mechanics to be a bit easier...
Huh?! It's already pretty easy, though!
I probably still lack the skills for it.
Really now?!
It's already really easy to understand.
But yeah, that's all
our thoughts on the game!
So we actually have a message from
the producer of this game, Producer U.
I'll be reading it out now.
Okay.
Seems like they want the fans
to take part in developing this game.
Sure sounds like it.
I kinda wanna see
Hatotaurus in the game.
I also think it'd be great if different
world settings and areas are added to the game!
Will he be an enemy to beat?
I also think it'd be great if different
world settings and areas are added to the game!
Like a Japanese-style area
or other settings.
Having a couple of
differently-themed stages would be fun.
Same here! Thank you for the opportunity!
Thank you for letting us play!
I've been a bit curious about
what sort of game is this, so...
It was worth checking out.
A sequel?
Oh my.
Oh my. I wonder how much would this game
have changed when the second video comes out?
That's a good question!
I think it's already pretty solid so far...
But we want to know how much more
they can improve on, right?
That's a good question!
I think it's already pretty solid so far...
But we want to know how much more
they can improve on, right?
That's right.
With that said, we're looking for and
hiring people who want to develop for this project!
What'd ya say?!
We don't have enough staff on it?!
Furthermore!
There might be a ton more stuff to
add to the game, such as story scenarios.
If you're watching this video
and you're interested in helping out,
please send in your application to
COVER Corporation's Careers page!
Apps are open!
Please apply!
We'd be really happy to
have you support this project with us.
That's all for today!
Today's show was
brought to you by Friend A...
Shirakami Fubuki!
And Ookami Mio!
One-two!
Thank you for watching!
Bye-bye!