Be pushier, yo!
Mel-senpai's answer was better...
Yeah, you're right.
She's just been going,
"Yeah! I'll do my best!"
I'll do my best!
Mel, doing her best!
This private school is nuts...
Next up on the show is this segment!
Subaru's School of Retorts!
Yay!
In this segment, I've had some clips of
Rules
A clip in need of a clever retort
hololive members' streams prepared for us to make retorts to,
so we'll watch them, and the two of you
will see if you can come with the same retort
Guess what Subaru's retort is!!
that I thought of.
Okay!
Got it!
Roll the tape!
"Can you recommend me a girl from hololive to watch?"
Streamed on 2021/04/24
[Singing stream] Anime songs only
[Shirogane Noel/hololive]
Someone from hololive I'd recommend?
Huh...
I don't know...
Oh, yeah!
How about someone with a big presence?
Um...
Look here, Furari Tabibito-san!
I think...
Called out their name...
you should go with someone who can leave an impression!
Look here!
Hey!
Looky, looky!
How scary is that?
Let's reveal everyone's answers, then!
Why don't we start from Omaru Polka-san?
Okay!
And here we have Omaru Polka-san's answer.
Go ahead!
Looky, looky!
That's so cute!!!
Oh, I see.
That's so cute...
A straightforward reaction. She's just cute.
It's not a retort...
It's a safe and neutral answer.
I'm just speaking for everyone out there!
That's how everyone feels.
My Oma-sense told me so.
Yeah, they definitely do.
You retorted, "Commander Noel's so cute,"
on behalf of everyone.
Yeah...
I see.
Next, then!
Let's respect it.
Okay.
Respect...?
Next up is...
Mel-senpai's answer! Roll the tape!
Looky, looky!
Stop it already!
You're gonna make me fall for you, yo!
Wow, someone's touchy.
It's hilarious how you sound almost angry.
Why did you rap it?
Yo!
I thought it would soften it a little.
Whoa...
That's so advanced.
I used some special techniques.
That might actually be a pro gamer move.
Can I use some of your moves?
Adding a bit of seasoning to soften the flavor?
Yeah.
Here's my answer!
Roll the tape!
Looky, looky!
Be pushier, yo!
Yo?
Yeah...
I think...
Mel-senpai's answer was better.
Yeah, you're right.
Ms. Subaru!
You're losing this battle!!
I've been forced to multitask today
so I'm not doing very well.
How could this be?!
Let's move on to our next segment!
Omaru Polka's
Rescue Operation!
Yay!
This will be Polka's segment!
Go ahead and explain it!
All right!
In this segment, we'll watch clips of me flopping
Rules
Scene where Polka bombed
and see what you might have done in that situation.
What would you have done?
Is there even any hope here?
What should I have done instead?
Let's salvage Polka's flops!
It'll be a good time to reflect on my flops
while also salvaging them.
That's the general idea.
Here's our first rescue operation!
Roll the tape!
Let's pretend someone called in already.
Streamed on 2021/08/25
5th Gen Evaluation Meeting
[Omaru Polka/hololive]
Shishiro Botan? Okay.
So Shishiro Botan is here now.
Hey, it's Shishiron!
You want to play again? You really enjoyed it?
Oh, great!
If it hadn't been for your quick thinking,
Shishiro Botan didn't show up.
I would've have had to force the ending so awkwardly.
Thank you!
Nice.
It can't go wrong.
Perfect.
Please write down your answers...
Don't worry!
We can save her!
Can we really...?
Seriously?
Shishiro Botan didn't mute herself or anything.
I'm just talking to an imaginary Shishiro Botan.
It's an invisible Shishiro Botan?
Yeah, an invisible Botan.
Chat is saying it'll be a difficult operation...
How will you rescue me, Subaru-senpai?
Please go ahead, then.
Uh...
Do it off-stream.
Do it off-stream
What we have here is...
All the rehearsing for your stream
should be performed off-stream.
So,
you didn't have to show us any of this.
You don't have to hurt yourself like this.
You know, I...
You might not believe me,
but I didn't feel embarrassed at all at the time.
Even in that case...
Hmm...
Do it off-stream?!
You should probably do it off-stream...
I'll start doing stuff like that off-stream from now on!
I'm just too airheaded.
That's what that was?
But you know...
Did I screw something up again?
Hey, that was cool.
You sounded like some final boss.
Did I screw something up again? I didn't really...
That's so cool!
feel anything from that.
You're so cool!
Does this hurt you?
Is this pain?
Pain?
If that had been me, I think I would've died.
A fatal dose of fail
I want Mel-senpai to rescue me as well!
Yeah!
I'll rescue you!
I'll do my best!
U-Uh...
You've been saying,
"Yeah! I'll do my best!"
I'll do my best!
Mel, doing her best!
What should I have done instead here?
Boom!
Ta-da!
You should've recorded her voice
and chatted with Shishiro Bot instead.
Oh...
That would've made it a whole event, then.
Yeah!
Didn't Mel-senpai just...
Didn't you just do this...?
Well...
Weren't you just talking to another Mel?
Earlier
She's also known for having wonderful breasts!
What a shock!
That wasn't another one of me though.
That wasn't?
That was just some random woman.
Some random woman
Wha—
Oh, I see.
That wasn't you?
It was just some random woman walking down the street.
Personally, I didn't really think it was a flop,
but this clip was suggested to us
by people who tweeted with the hashtag.
So, yeah.
Yeah.
Did I really flop?
Wait, so does this mean you were backstabbed by a fan?
Yeah.
Huh.
We await your reports of more
Omaru Polka flops with this hashtag: #ぽるすべ
My own fans stabbed me in the back...
Show her some kindness, guys!
You'll love this next part.
It's time for Mel-senpai's segment!
Genius Vampire Test!
Yay!
Yaaay!
Please tell us about your segment, Mel-senpai.
Okay!
In this segment,
Rules
A middle school-level quiz
you just have to fill out a middle school-level quiz
and see how much you can score!
How much can you score?
Oh!
But you know...
I'm a genius vampire from the Underworld,
so there's no way I can be wrong!
Literally can't be wrong
Are you setting yourself up for failure here?
No, Mel-senpai literally can't be wrong.
Oh, I see.
That's right!
Capiche?
So that means
whatever I respond with is the right answer.
Mel's answer is always correct
Everything else is wrong.
This private school is nuts...
Next problem!
Hit me, teach!
Okay!
I'm ready!
Okay.
What the...
Fill-in-the-blanks!
"To ____ common sense on its head."
How will Subaru-chan answer this question?
Ta-da!
Poop?!
You're not going to take this seriously?!
It's not like that!
Why?!
No, wait!
Listen!
What happened here was,
uh...
We answered these just before we started filming!
We had no time to read through it either!
"Oh god... I have no idea.
I played so many... games today, my brain's all...
What do I put in? Whatever!"
You used up your brainpower on games?
And I just put in "poop" because I was too tired.
Basically, she procrastinated too hard
I'm sure Mel-senpai would just put in "poop"
if she didn't know otherwise.
So basically, you thought I'd write "poop"?
Senior
Junior
Oh, sorry—
U-Uh...
Ahh...
Uh oh...
Hey, why don't we look at what Polka said?
Oh, right.
Watch what I do to your common sense!
Show me what you have!
Here is...
my answer!
Ta-da!
What is that?!
That looks like poop.
No it doesn't!
It's definitely shaped like it.
What now...?
Well, Mel-senpai...
Well, my answer to the question...
is right here!
Ah!
"Flop"!
Oh...
That was it?
That's the answer.
I'm shocked you came up with that...
For real.
Polka's answer might've been a bit funnier.
Uh, what?
Flip...?
Flop?
What?
Oh, nothing! Mel-senpai is right!
Flip... flop?
Didn't she spell "flip" wrong...?
Hm?
Uh...
This is how you spell "flip" now.
Everything I speak is the law, so...
Mel is world!
That's right.
True!
Stop forming your own thoughts.
So sorry.
I attempted to form a thought.
I apologize.
No thinking allowed in front of our queen.
Mel-senpai is the law here.
"Aim to make my streams 'fun.'"
Problem two
The question is which part of speech
the word "fun" belongs to.
Isn't this easy?
Huh?
Oh.
I thought it would be...
Right?
I know, right?
What's a "part of speech"?
This is easy!
Let's look at your answers.
Here's Subaru-chan's answer!
Okay!
"Adjective"!
Obviously!
Obviously, it's an adjective.
You spelled it wrong!
Hahaha!
Diiid nooot!
Yeah, that doesn't look right.
It's a problem with my tablet pen!
Well...
Let's look at Polka-chan's answer.
Oh, okay.
Here it is!
"Wildin'."
What's supposed to be wildin' here?
I thought "part of speech" meant...
to make something simpler.
I see.
That's true.
That's not a wrong answer.
Wha—
Mel-senpai?!
Wait, I'm so—
Let's take a look at my correct answer!
Time for the real answer!
Huh?
"It's very partial."
Hold up...
"Part of speech" refers to how partial something is.
Exactly.
Yeah guys, "part of speech" refers to
how partial something is.
Thought is forbidden
Yup!
That's how it works on Bonjour.
I understand perfectly!
Yup!
Yup.
Extras
Prompt: The person most likely to stockpile water at home
"The person most likely to stockpile water at home."
Stockpile water?
Stockpile?
At home.
St-Sto...
pile?
Oh...
Stockpile: to accumulate stock for the future
Right, "stockpiling" means to—
To have lots of water!
I've never paid attention to how someone smells!
Oh, but I've caught the smell of melon
coming off Okayu before.
What?!
Melon?
Polka starts sulking after finding out
Mel and Subaru went on a date
Mel-senpai, could you just...
drop a pick-up line on Polka
before we call it a day?
She's all moody now.
Sure!
Polka-chan...
Stay by my side.
I will.
Q20: Please tell us your best pick-up line!
I-I will.
Okay.
I'll be with you.
Someone must put an end to this living hell
(pants)
H-handshake?
Handshake...
Sh-shake on it?
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub channel on NicoNico for the full stream archives!
Shake!
Oh, shake!
Thank you!
I'll always be with you!
Thanks!
Wait...