One little nudge and we'd have gotten
a pretty crazy abbreviation, wouldn't we?
"Bought a cutter but my wallet barely made the cut."
Hahahaha!
She's laughing!
Bell peppers?
No bell peppers allowed.
Welcome to the show!
This is holo's Bonjour,
a variety and talk show
where one of the guests changes every month!
Now then, let's introduce our gwests for today!
I'm Hoshimachi Suisei and I'll be your MC this time.
Also, it's surprisingly hard to say "Guest!"
Do your best!
"Gwest!"
"Guesht"
Our second guesht today is...
I'm your second guesht!
hololive 5th Gen's Shishiro Botan here!
Thanks for having me!
Thanks for coming!
Happy to have you here!
And our third guest is...
That's me! I'm your third gwest,
Aki Rosenthal a.k.a AkiRose!
Thanks for having me!
Yaaay!
And our fourth guest is...
Ta-dah!
It's your shooting star, your diamond in the rough!
Idol VTuber, Hoshimachi Suisei is here!
The three of us will be presenting doing today's show!
One person extra
We're already turning into a horror show off the bat.
Everything okay?
There's an imaginary Sui-chan with us.
That's scary.
Anyways, it's the first time the three of us
are co-starring together, right?
Yeah.
That's right.
Botan-chan and I were both
in the last episode of Bonjour.
Yeah, we were.
Both of us were there, but as for Aki-chan...
When was the last time we collabed?
It doesn't feel like we've collabed in a looong time.
No way! We didn't for that long?
We didn't, yeah. Let's collab again!
Sure!
Yeah, let's do it!
Let's set a date first.
Yeah, let's!
We can't do anything if we don't set a date.
Yeah.
Now that we've established
our relationship with each other,
I'd like to start digging deeper.
Let's start with our first segment!
Sure!
Oh!
Ta-dah!
Random Rapid-Fire Interrogation!
Yaaaaaaaay!
Yaaaay!
🎵 Dun dun duuuun! 🎵
Wait, isn't that the one for slip-ups?
Yeah, it's like you messed up.
That sounds like there was some epic fail.
For this segment, Aki-chan will be pelted with
a stream of questions from the veterans, me and Botan.
Oh my!
Yup.
I'd like you to answer all of them.
I say "All," but there's just 20 of them.
I mean 20 questions is still a lot.
True. What happens if she can't answer them all?
I guess Aki-chan's gonna just go "Hm?"
I probably didn't hear them, I guess?
If I can't answer a question,
it'll be considered a fail, I guess?
I suppose so.
I see.
But unfortunately, you'll have to answer every last one.
Please try your best!
Even if you have to brute force them.
It'll count either way.
Even if I have to brute force them, I see.
It counts as long as you think "This is probably it."
All right. So I just answer from my heart, right?
Please do your best.
I'll give it my all!
Please do!
Well then, are you ready, Aki-chan?
Phew! Yeah!
Okay, let's begin!
The 20 question rapid-fire starts now!
I'll go first.
Q1: What's your favorite drink?
It's gotta be wheat juice.
I see.
Ah, okay, I see.
Next one.
Q2: What drinking snacks do you recommend?
Ah... there's too many, BUT!
My answer is... smoked eggs!
It's smoked eggs!
Smoked eggs?
Q19: Tell us one of your specialties!
A specialty of mine...
Uh...
What was that?
I can't think of one!
The rapid-fire's continuing! Ra-ta-ta-ta-ta!
She's gonna fail!
Got it! Making gyoza!
Ooh! That's nice!
Yeah!
Last one!
Q20: If you could bring any one item with you
to a deserted island, what would you bring?
A deserted island...
I've learned this from survival games!
It's water!
Water!
That's it! Thanks for answering!
Okay! Thanks for your answers!
With that said, you survived!
Although you almost failed at the end there.
That was close.
You were really close to the edge there.
Right?
I barely answered all of them.
You did, yeah.
Now I'd like to go through some of my questions.
Sure!
Firstly, your recommended drinking snack is...
What'd you say it was?
Smoked eggs?
Can I look that up real quick?
You mean like smoke-infused eggs?
Like those quail egg thingies?
Oh!
Yeah!
Smoked eggs, in other words, smoke-infused eggs.
I see! In that vein,
one little nudge and we would've gotten
a pretty crazy abbreviation, wouldn't we?
That's a little...
Hold on, stop.
Phew. It's a good thing this is a fanclub-only stream.
That was close.
It's fine, it's not public.
You said one of your specialties was making gyoza?
Yup!
Making gyoza... wait, you mean
you make them completely from scratch?
Yeah.
You take cabbage, ground meat, chives, and...
the most important ingredient is enoki mushrooms.
Enoki?
Yeah. If you chop them up small and mix them in,
it amps up the umami by a ton!
Really?!
If we're talking about fried gyoza,
there's a variation with banana.
I think I've eaten those before.
Huh?! A fried banana gyoza?
Yeah! It's like you're having dessert.
Uh-huh. Sounds nice.
It's one of those recipes
that uses gyoza wrapper, right?
Yeah, that's probably it!
I see.
Uh-huh.
I wanna do a gyoza party with everyone
once everything goes back to normal.
Me too!
And try a bunch of recipes using gyoza wrapper!
Yeah!
Like using them to make mini pizzas and the like.
I wanna try that.
Sounds great!
Yeah! I wanna do something with everyone!
I'll bring out the bell peppers, 'kay?
Bell peppers?
No bell peppers allowed.
The bitterness of bell peppers
doesn't translate well to tastiness.
Yeah. It just makes your tongue recoil.
Your tongue just hates it, like it goes,
"Wait, this is bell pepper! It's bell pepper!"
And it just blows the whistle.
And it's like, "Get it out! Remove it!"
"Any more and you'll never taste
sweetness again in your life!"
Yeah!
"This is the Bitterness Police! Stop right there!"
That's basically how it feels like.
Exactly!
I can't say anything because I totally relate.
Right?!
Here's our next segment!
Wish Away Your Worries Upon a Shooting Star!
Yaaay!
I yelled that like my life depended on it.
To explain this segment simply,
our viewers have sent in some minor problems
Rules
Every single thing my beloved shooting star does
is so precious, I'm starting to get addicted to her!
What do I need to do to actually develop an addiction?
they have in their daily lives.
Befitting of a shooting star, I've come up with
Suisei's answer
Don't get addicted.
quick and haphazard solutions to those problems,
Suisei's answer
???
and you'll try to predict what they are!
Guess Suisei's answer!
Got it!
Okay!
"The recent summer heat's killing me."
"Stupid random stuff keeps popping
into my mind but they're all bad puns."
"How do I stop the puns?"
Uh-huh. I see.
Well then, let's solve this problem!
Thinking time starts now!
Do you make puns often, Sui-chan?
I like them quite a lot, actually...
I see...
Let's look at your answers!
Botan-chan went first earlier,
so let's go with Aki Rosenthal
who should definitely know how it works now!
Sure!
Here's her answer!
"Just spit them out! You'll kill even the summer heat!"
Ah... that's a good one!
It is!
And it certainly solves the problem.
The summer heat's definitely an issue for others as well,
so if you just spit the puns out,
you'll solve the issue for everyone!
Since bad puns just freeze everything in place,
it can probably solve the heat issue,
True.
'Cause everyone forgets about the heat.
and it goes full circle!
Yeah.
They help each other forget.
It goes full circle?
So you trade puns back and forth.
Exactly!
Okay, I see. You trade bad puns to kill the heat.
Yup, exactly!
Exactly.
With all that said and done,
let's look at Shishiro Botan-san's answer!
Here it is!
"Like what? Make a pun!"
She'd totally say that!
Originally, I went with the flow earlier
and wrote something like
"It's fine to keep going, ain't it?"
But I feel like that's too outdated,
and I'm guessing Suisei might throw a curveball soon,
like maybe she'd ask what kind of puns they'd say.
Well, that is true.
I wanna see what kind of puns they've got.
What kind of puns would everyone say?
Can the people in chat throw us some examples?
"A 100 yen coin! Coinks, no food!"
Hehehehe.
That's actually good that it's annoying.
It's pretty funny, yeah.
"Bought a cutter but my wallet barely made the cut."
Hahaha!
She's laughing!
She's laughing her guts out!
I like that one.
Isn't that doing the opposite
and heating you up, though?
I'm sweating!
Let's look at my answer, then.
Sure.
Yeah!
Here it is!
Just stay as you are.
Huh?
Ooh!
Dammit!
It's not like you have to solve it, right?
Yup. Like, everyone has problems,
but it's not like they actually have to be solved.
Therefore—
Is their—
Is their problem something that needs no solution?
Yeah, they don't need one.
Really?!
Really?! They sent it in hoping for a solution.
Is it okay to not solve it?
This one doesn't need to be solved.
They're fine as they are, basically.
I see.
Exactly!
Isn't it fine to just stay the way you are?
Ah, I see.
That's deep.
Enlightening!
Yeah. That was some deep talk.
Anyways, it's fine to just keep doing
something that pointless.
Let's keep going!
Let's!
Well then, did we solve your problem?
Let's move on to the third minor problem.
Don't say, "This problem doesn't need to be solved."
then do a 180 and ask, "Did we solve your problem?"
That's actually a bit psychopathic, isn't it?
That's my solution to their problem.
"There's no solution."
So this is the Suicopath.
"Recently my motivation to do club activities
has been dropping. What should I do?"
Isn't this...
Ah...
A big one?!
Isn't this problem a big one?
This is a pretty serious one.
An actual problem has appeared!
It's a serious one!
Let's do our best to solve it.
Uh-huh. I see.
All right, let's do it for real this time.
Thinking time starts now!
This is quite the problem.
I really wanna solve their problem.
Yeah!
The question here is whether or not
I want to solve their problem.
That's what you girls need to figure out.
Okay, I see.
This is a problem-solving segment!
We're. Solving. Problems!
We go both ways!
All right! Thinking time's over!
🔔🔔🔔
Now then, let's take a look at your answers.
Let's start from Botan-chan this time.
Okay.
Here's her answer!
"Do something else for now!"
Ooh! I see.
Ah!
I thought about this seriously.
If you try to do something while you're demotivated,
you'll just stay demotivated, wouldn't you?
Since that's the case,
forget what you're doing and do something else!
When you feel like doing
what you were doing before, you can go back!
This is a good solution.
Although if I had to say
if you'd answer this way, Suisei-senpai...
That'd be a tough question.
Will our answers sync or not is the question.
Yeah. It's whether or not our answers will sync.
All right. Aki-chan, you're next!
Let's look at your answer!
Sure!
"Try doing something else!"
Oh!
Same answer!
It is!
We're the same!
That's where the sync came in.
Can we maybe get 2 points for that?
Can you?
You might be stuck in a rut
because you're bored of something,
so if you try doing something else, you might realize,
"I'm actually good at what I was doing before
and I wanna continue doing that."
and then you'll find the motivation
to go back to doing that.
Yeah, that's true.
I'd like them to keep on with their club activities.
And if you realize that it's just not for you,
you can drop it quickly.
Exactly!
Yeah.
Well then!
Both of your answers synced, but...
This is nerve-racking!
What about this shooting star's answer?
Can she go back to the light?!
Don't turn to the dark side!
I'm begging you, please join the light side!
Let's take a look at my answer!
Here it is!
What's her answer?
"Look for a different hobby
and try immersing yourself in it."
You both guessed right!
Isn't that great?
We all have the same answer!
Everyone synced up!
This is the first time everyone got it right, isn't it?
It is!
Isn't that amazing?
I do this quite a bit myself.
I'll look for a completely different hobby
and immerse myself in it if it's interesting.
Then, if I feel like going back,
I'll go back to what I did before.
I've always done this quite a lot.
Like I was hooked on drawing, but then
I got bored so I started making videos and such.
Ooh!
Then, even though I made videos, I'd feel like
I don't have any good ideas and move on to singing.
But now you're doing all of them.
Yup!
Not only does it maintain your motivation,
it gives you more options and skills.
I think it's good to look for different hobbies.
It gives you a change in perspective.
I see.
Yup.
I agree!
We completely solved their problem, right?
They even wrote it at the bottom of the screen!
They even played the sching sound.
Sching!
So they DO play it!
That's the first time I've heard it in person.
Here's our next segment!
Okay, Shishiron! Search and Lock On!!!
Wow!
That's some punch packed in that voice!
Botan-chan will handle this segment!
Please explain the rules!
Okay! So, for this segment,
you all know how whenever you look up
Rules
stuff you don't know in a search engine,
you'd see the number of hits, right?
Shishiro Botan
Like if you search for "Shishiro Botan,"
you'd get about 2.8 million results.
About 2,800,000 results
In this segment, you'll also use the AND function
of the search engine to narrow down the results.
Goal: Reduce to around 600,000 results
The goal here is to get as close as possible
to the target number of results.
For example, if you search for
"Shishiro Botan," spacebar, and "Cute,"
Goal: Reduce to around 600,000 results
Shishiro Botan cute
Add search terms
you can narrow down
the search results to around 600,000.
About 600,000 results (0.52 seconds)
You'll be using these functions to see
who can get the closest to the target.
Who would be closest to the goal?
However, you will receive a penalty
Shishiro Botan shiitake
if you go below the target number!
Going too low nets you a penalty!
The penalty is that you'll slowly fade away!
They'll wipe me out of existence, huh.
Your search term is "cicada."
If you just search for "cicada,"
you'll get about 84.4 million results.
Around 84,400,400 results
Oh.
Ooh.
Your goal is to reduce it to 7.7 million results.
(Less than one-tenth)
Around 7,700,000 results
Oooooh...
Whaaat?
That's a steep dive.
7.7 million...
Cicadas always scare you with their
Final-Last-End-like movements.
Ah!
Like they keep twitching.
Yeah.
This is... how about this...?
It might work. Let's go with this.
Although it may be a bit... yeah, I'm ready.
Me too!
Me three.
Well then, here are our answers!
Ta-dah!
Ta-dah.
Let's start with Suisei-senpai's answer first!
"Encyclopedia."
Yup.
Well, if we're talking bout cicada encyclopedias...
There'd be images of encyclopedias
or the different types of encyclopedias
or where you can find such encyclopedias.
Considering all these possible results,
maybe it's enough to hit around 7.7 million results?
I see. As for Akirose-senpai, you chose "How to eat."
Well, in a way...
That's scary!
There are places where you can eat cicadas,
so I'm thinking "How to eat" might snag
some results, especially the survival stuff.
Ah, I see!
I see.
As for mine, I've got "7 years is a lie" written
but there's a small mistake. Sorry about that.
It's supposed to be "7 days is a lie."
"7 days is a lie"?
It's said that cicadas stay in the dirt for years before emerging to live for only 7 days, right?
Yeah!
But I think there are searches for how that's all a lie.
Like in reality, isn't it a lie
that cicadas only live for 7 days?
Don't those freaking things live for 2-3 weeks?
You're kidding!
That can't be true!
It is!
I think cicadas live longer than we give them credit for!
That's why I think there might be people
who've realized that and looked it up to see if it's true.
I see... my dreams have been crushed...
We lived with the noise thinking they had fleeting lives...
Okay, let's look at the search results!
We'll go in order of Akirose-senpai,
me, then Suisei-senpai.
Sure.
Okay. How many results did Akirose-senpai's
"Cicada" and "Eating Method" get?
🥁🥁🥁🥁🥁
OH!
30.8 million results!
That DID narrow it down, but...
It did narrow down the results!
It DID drop...
It cut the results down by half!
Aren't there dishes made from cicadas or something?
Ah!
Like "Cicada ***" dishes.
True.
Apparently, they taste like peanut butter.
The cicadas?
What?!
Yup.
Heck no.
Next up! Suisei-sen—
Wait, no, it's me.
My turn next!
"Cicada" and "7 days is a lie."
Here are the results!
🥁🥁🥁🥁🥁
Huh?! 30.3 million results!
We're close!
Seriously?
See? About half of the population—
A third of the population in Japan noticed it!
A lot of people noticed those buggers live long.
You're kidding! I didn't notice!
Last one!
Suisei-senpai's
"Cicada" and "Encyclopedia"!
What are her results?
OH!
Huh?!
Oh?
Wait up.
4.36 million results! Well then...
Please wait!
That's well below the goal of 7.7 million,
so that means you fail, Suisei-senpai!
Noooooo!
So you're the one to fade...
Still, isn't "Encyclopedia" the likeliest to—
Ah...
She's turning see-through!
She's fading!
🎵 Just like a ghost! 🎵
"Encyclopedia" seemed like
it'd have the most results too!
Right? Turns out it isn't.
Yeah.
There are more people looking up how
the "Cicada 7-day lifespan is a lie"
than there are people who are curious
about encyclopedias.
The internet sure made a lot of things easy.
Yeah.
Even so, I was the closest to the target, okay?!
That IS true.
That's undeniable.
You're the closest to the goal
but also the closest to being a ghost.
The next segment is...
Alcoholic's Concentration Game!
Alcoholic's
Concentration Game
Yaaay!
Yaaay.
This one is Aki-chan's segment
Aki-chan, please explain the rules.
Okay!
This is a new segment.
I made a game of Concentration
with my favorite drinks and drinking snacks!
Please take a look at this!
Alcohol
Snack
There's a blue and red section,
labeled drinking snacks and alcohol respectively,
with cards placed randomly.
So...
In this segment,
you select a number from
both the red and blue sections.
(4)Shochu + (6)Dried Squid
And I'll judge you on whether that combination
goes well together or don't.
On whether that alcohol and drinking snack
go well together.
I see.
We'll have three rounds,
and whoever has more points at the end wins.
So, to summarize,
this is a concentration game
based on your personal preferences.
Exactly.
So it depends on how well
you think I'd like that combination.
Well, you can also try to make it appeal to me.
Ah, I see.
Yeah.
If you manage to convince me of its appeals,
you just might get a point.
Sound good.
Sounds great.
I'll keep those smoked eggs you talked about
at the start in mind.
It might be one of the cards.
Oh?
It might be.
It's possible.
Nice.
Well, then.
What should we do for the order?
Who wants to go first?
Let's rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper... Rock!
Rock, paper... Paper!
I lost!
Yeees.
Then, Botan-chan will start us off! Game... start!
What should I pick...
Well, since my name is Shi(4)-shi(4)-ro(6),
I'll go with alcohol four and snack six.
The alcohol is... shochu!
And snack six is...
dried squid!
Oh!
How's shochu with dried squid?
This combination...
(4)Shochu + (6)Dried Squid
is...
good!
Yaaay!
Isn't this
a pretty standard combination?
Isn't it?
It's the starter pack of drinking.
You often see those middle-aged men
ordering them together at an izakaya.
Yaaay.
Does dried squid go badly with any drinks at all?
I have this image that it's...
Ah...
I feel like it doesn't go well with, like, wine.
I see. So I might've been in trouble if I drew wine.
So, that's how it works.
Sui-chan, ready when you are.
All right, I'll start.
I don't even know eight kinds of alcohol.
She chose based off her name earlier,
so, since my name is Suisei...
Hmm...
She's betting it on her name.
Since it's Su-i(1)-se-i(1), I'll go with double ones.
Alcohol one and snack one, please.
Number ones, coming right up!
Tequila!
Tequila with a side of...?
Fish sausage!
(1)Tequila + (1)Fish Sausage
I see...
How is this combination?
How's fish sausage with that?
Uh...
No, it's really really good.
After you squeeze some lemon on it
and take a big bite out of it,
the sourness of the lemon pairs really well
with the fishiness of the sausage.
Like, really squeeze it on.
The lemon is the saving grace at that point.
This combination...
is...
Is...
bad.
Ah... it's bad.
If there were some lemons, it'd be a little different,
but it's just the sausage.
Right.
Next is... alcohol seven!
And snack... eight!
Seven is... whiskey!
Whiskey.
And snack eight is...
...salt?
Wh—
Salt?
Salt as a snack?
What do you mean by salt as a snack?
Sorry, I'm not a drinker so I don't comprehend.
This is...
Salt your mouth then drink?
This is an alcoholic's reasoning
that if it's edible and it has a taste,
then it can be a drinking snack.
Oh, really?
I didn't know that.
Soy sauce works, fermented plums work,
and even salt works.
Really?
Isn't that bad for you?
So how's whiskey with salt? I feel like it could—
It's summer, so...
It's summer.
Hmm...
Whiskey, huh...
No, I think it can work.
She's contemplating, good. Good.
It doesn't go together, does it?
But, like, it's summer, you know.
If it were any other drink, salt could work, but...
But it's summer.
I'd like to make this decision
(7)Whiskey + (8)Salt
with my pride as an alcoholic on the line.
All right.
This combination
is...
bad.
Ah...
Heck yes!
I'll get another one.
Then, I'll go with... two!
Number two, coming right up!
Lemon Sour.
How's lemon sour?
Wh-What?
L-Lemon sour?
It's fairly popular.
Wha— Then...
Then, snack one.
The fish sausage?
The fish sausage.
You're going with that?
Lemon sour and fish sausage go well together, right?
Hmm...
Since we didn't have lemon earlier.
True.
It's lemon in the alcohol, though!
(2)Lemon Sour + (1)Fish Sausage
This combination
is...
good!
Heck yeah!
Darn.
About this.
Quite a lot of people buy and drink canned lemon sour.
Ah, right.
They buy it at a supermarket or convenience store.
Mhmm.
So fish sausages end up
being a staple drinking snack with it.
I think the guys and girls
who live alone buy these together
then chug their drink and nom on their sausages
in the comfort of their homes.
Nice.
So this combination works.
This combination is...
(6)Sake + (4)Pickled Veggies
The two started the 3rd round tied.
good!
Yaay!
This combination
(5)Wine + (5)Chicken Tendies
And they ended the 3rd round tied.
is...
good!
I did it!
Let's go!
So we have an overtime round.
Let's settle the score, Shishiro Botan.
Okay, let's settle this.
Then, one we haven't opened.
Alcohol three.
Please open alcohol three.
Ooh!
Umeshu?
Yeah.
It's a sweet alcohol.
Oh, it's sweet?
And for the snack, number three!
Number three, coming right up.
Ah!
Fish sashimi!
That sounds great together.
Isn't this good?
I have a feeling sashimi goes well
with any alcoholic drink.
Well.
(3)Umeshu + (3)Fish Sashimi
This combination
is...
good!
Yay! Glad it is.
Sashimi is omnipotent.
Yeah.
Sui-chan, will you be able to grab the lead?
Let's see...
Which alcohols have we not checked yet?
Maybe seven and eight?
Seven and eight?
Then, seven!
Ah, right. Seven was whiskey.
Ah, yeah. Whiskey was one of them.
Right.
Hmm... Argh...
Number two.
Hm.
What'll it be?
Number two, coming right up.
What is it? What is it? What is it?
Chocolate?!
Sounds good. There are whiskey bon-bons after all.
Right?
Yeah.
This might be good! How is it, Aki-chan?
This combination
(7)Whiskey+ (2)Chocolate
is...
good!
I got the point.
And now we're tied again.
This one's the jackpot, isn't it?
I feel like it is.
This one's a big, big, big yes.
Oh, yay!
Nice.
I'm glad.
Whiskey and chocolate go really well together.
Like the chocolate bon-bons you mentioned earlier.
Yeah.
They go so well together they have
chocolate candies with whiskey inside.
I see.
Ooh.
That's interesting. I'm learning so much.
Right?
I don't drink, so I never learned about any of this.
And so,
Botan-chan vs Sui-chan ended in a tie!
We tied!
We tied, huh?
We couldn't settle the score.
Extra
You get only 600k searches (from 2.8m)
from just adding "cute" to "Shishiro Botan," right?
You lose like 2.2m search results, right?
Oi, don't point that out as if I'm not cute.
This combination...
What was the thing?
What did I say before?
My stomach kept growling because
we talked about a bunch of foods,
so I've been muting and unmuting myself over and over.
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub channel
on NicoNico for the full stream archives!
It was food torture.
Yeah.
Like, "Oh shoot, it's about to growl! *mutes*."