hololive IDOL Project - Taisetsu Photographs
Lyrics: Ren Morimoto
Composition, Arrangement: Kazuma Ito (Arte Refact)
Bass: Naoki Kobayashi
All Other Instruments & Programming:
Kazuma Ito (Arte Refact)
Singers: Shirakami Fubuki, Minato Aqua,
Houshou Marine, Amane Kanata, Momosuzu Nene
Past that all too familiar door
minarekitta doa no saki ni
Waits an unchanging smile
kawaranai hohoemi
If I reach out for a surprise hug
fuini gyutto dakishimetara
You can see that beautiful smile bloom again
hora mata egao ga saita yo
Let's take this album of our lives
tori tameta nichijou o
Scatter it all across the table
yosegaki mitai ni atsumete sa
Lock away the goodbyes we need to say
sayonara wa mune ni shimatte
Lean up against each other
kata o yosete akiru kurai
And talk forever
hanasou
With all of our countless memories in our pockets
kagirinai omoide poketto ni tsumekonde
We can be there when we need us most
kujikesou na toki mo tomoni sasae aeru
As one precious photograph
taisetsu fotogurafu
We'll be together forevermore
haruka mirai no saki e korekara mo issho da yo
Holding hands, saying cheese,
and singing our hearts out
omoikkiri waraou te o tsunagi utaou
In this moment that will live forever in our hearts
kono isshun ga itsumademo daisuki
Chorus: ricono
Recording & Mixing Engineer: Tsukasa Kikuchi (Arte Refact)
Recording Studio: Studio Arte
Mixing Studio: Studio Arte
It's okay to stop and cry
tachidomatte ochikomu hi mo
Everyone does at times
tamani wa ii yo ne
But if we can all share that burden
wakachiatte yorisoetara
Those tears will become lifelong memories
namida mo omoide ni kawaru
We can find small fragments of happiness
sasayakana shiawase wa
Hidden in the most mundane of days
kazaranai mainichi no naka ni atte
The nonchalant conversations we had
futoshita kaiwa ya
Walking alongside each other
tonari aruku hibi ga
Have become my treasures
takaramono nanda
I have so many great memories, I can't count them all
omoide wa afurete ryoute ja tarinai yo
We can laugh together, in joy and in sorrow
ureshisa mo tsurasa mo tomoni warai aeru
As precious photographs
taisetsu fotogurafu
I wish for lives filled with smiles and happiness
saikou no egao to tobikkiri shiawase o
For all the people I love, as cliched as it may sound
daisukina minna e sukoshi kusuguttai kedo
Thank you for always being there
itsumo arigato ne
We'll be together forevermore
haruka mirai no saki e korekara mo issho da yo
Holding hands, saying cheese,
and singing our hearts out
omoikkiri waraou te o tsunagi utaou
In this moment that will live forever in our hearts
kono isshun ga itsumade mo daisuki
Sound Directed by Nobuyoshi Kohama (Arte Refact)
Sound Produced by Satoru Kuwabara (Arte Refact)