Say aah.
Here's your takoyaki.
Om...
Mmm!
Yummy!
Gosh, Luna-sama!
I'm a pushover for your cuteness.
I'll do anything you want.
Nothing's taken my fancy lately.
Wow...
Lucky Luna,
getting the princess treatment and all.
Did you miss the ominous subtext there?
Hey, Mio-sen!
Hmm?
Aah.
What's this? Playing Merlion?
Ew! Gross!
C'mon, I just want you to
give me the royal treatment.
How, exactly?
By feeding me, or helping me stay on my feet.
Uh, call a nurse?
Is there anywhere you'd like to visit, Luna-sama?
I wanna go to Dweamland!
Certainly! I'll take you soon!
Man, that's a first,
seeing Choco-sensei melt like that.
Right, Polka?
I wanna go to Shodoshima!
Nobody's stopping you.
I wonder what separates
Luna and me in this sorta thing.
Is that a joke?
Overreacting much?!
I don't know, your presence or aura...
or something.
You mean this?
Yeah, a colorful little...
Hold up! You can emit a visible aura?!
I'm gonna go do some rounds outside!
Wait! Turn that off!
I got questioned by a cop...
This sad creature...
Look what you missed while you were goofing off.
Huh?
Luna-chan's popping off.
Whoa, what is that? Mind Force?!
Oh, come on...
Fine, I'll just take it up with her!
Hey, wait!
Luna!
Oh, hey, Polka-chan.
I'm gwad you're here!
I've been wanting to see you!
Me? Really?
That's wight.
I wanna talk to you loads!
Muh eyes!
Too dazzling! Too radiant!
This... is what a real princess is like...
No! Polka!
Who wouldn't want the royal treatment?
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!