One day, I found my eyes set on a distant dream
itsunomanika mitsuketeta tooi yume
A scene that I couldn't see just by myself
hitori ja mienakatta keshiki
With the wind rustling in my ears,
namiutsu kaze no ne to kasoku shiteiku omoi ni
and my desire growing stronger
I was at a loss for what to do
tomadoi o oboeta
I've been trying for so long to reach the me in my dream
zutto oikaketa risou no sugata wa
I'm still not there yet, she's so far away
mada todokanakute tooi kedo
But together here right now, with all of you and no one less
kitto kono shunkan o kakegae nai minna de
Come on, let's all go!
tomoni iku yo!
Everyone hand in hand
te o tsunaide
3, 2, 1!
3.2.1!
With a sparkle in your heart
kagayaki yadoshite
To the place in my dream!
yume no basho e!
Rushing on forward, the light of our youth keeps going
kakenuketeiku bokutachi no seishun no hikari wa
No one can stop it!
dare ni mo tomerarenai yo!
Every smile that we'll make
warai au bun dake
Gently
yasashiku
Even the tears that we'll shed
koboreru namida sae
Now
ima
koboreru namida sae
Come on, make them shine
hora kagayakase
We're taking them all into tomorrow
ashita e hakobu kara
To be with you, we'll cross the line between our worlds
kimi no tonari e bokutachi wa sekai o koeteiku
hololive IDOL PROJECT - AsuiroClearSky
(Tomorrow's Bright Clear Sky)
kimi no tonari e bokutachi wa sekai o koeteiku
Lyrics, Composition: Ren Morimoto
Arrangement: Masatomi Waki (Arte Refact)
kimi no tonari e bokutachi wa sekai o koeteiku
We'll come to get you
mukae ni iku yo
Vocals: Roboco san, Yozora Mel, Aki Rosenthal,
No one knows what tomorrow holds
mada mienai ashita mo
Vocals: Natsuiro Matsuri, Minato Aqua, Ookami Mio,
But we can make it shine bright, I know
kirameki ni kaete kitto
Vocals: Sakura Miko, Shiranui Flare, Tokoyami Towa
To a bright and brilliant future
bokutachi ga mirai e to
We'll take you there with us!
tsureteiku kara!