Cuuute!
Not the watering can, Aki-senpai!
AkiRose-senpai, what the hell are you doing?!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
It's summer...
It's so hot!
It is!
But I'm dressed light, so I'm just fine!
We're fine since we're all summer-born!
The Summer-Born Trio
You're right!
Can I ask you three something?
What is it?
I've been meaning to ask...
What's the relationship like
between hololive's generations?
Subaru-chan and Captain Marine are always so scary...
3rd Gen
4th Gen
2nd Gen
Imagination
A sudden confession?!
We treat you so well!
That's not true!
You seemed the most relaxed out of all of us.
Jokes aside, I'm the newest here,
but these two are still really nice to me,
along with all the other older members.
The newer members can get along with them.
By the way, how is it like with you, Boss?
This is about a comedian friend of mine.
...A friend?
It's a story the boss heard from a friend.
Apparently, she's working at a place called "Yoshimoto."
The major entertainment company?!
There, when she and her coworkers go to eat together,
if everyone's newer than her, she has to treat all of them.
It's quite brutal.
*strut*
Yeah.
Oh? Oh?
I heard there was a store that would
treat me to something nice today.
Today's Guest:
Aki Rosenthal
Wait, but you've been in hololive for the longest out of us!
1st Gen
You should treat us!
There we have it!
Our guest today is Aki Rosenthal-san!
Aki Rosenthal
About Her: Whimsical
Hobby: Drinking
Finishing Move: AkiRose☆Alona☆Sexy
(Effect: Makes you do any one thing she says)
MENT
LUCK
She supposedly has maxed out stats—A perfect elf!
But her finishing move seems rather problematic!
Is your finishing move one of those sexy types?
Finishing move
AkiRose☆Alona☆Sexy
(Makes you do any one thing she says)
Captain has a sexy one too.
Do you wanna compete to see whose is sexier?
Overlapping moves?
Let's do it!
The sexier move gets to stay.
A sudden challenge!
The Maruyama Championship! Sexy Battle!
Take this, AkiRose-senpai!
Sexy Beam!
Muah.
Take my finishing move!
AkiRose☆Alona☆Sexy!
First I've heard of it.
Boss, look at just how unfazed Towa's stance is.
Let's seal Alona Sexy away.
Sealed
I can't take any more of that.
Now that I've unleashed my finishing move,
I'm down to 1-star on all stats.
MENT
LUCK
Finishing move
AkiRose☆Alona☆Sexy
(Upon failure, it lowers your stats)
That's one scary finishing move (for you).
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Can you tell us what you've been
having problems with recently?
Whenever I'm working,
I always end up thinking about what more
I could be doing or about wanting to do more
to the point where I can't really switch gears afterward.
So you're a workaholic.
How can I relax at the end of the day
while drinking some tasty wheat juice?
Are you sure you don't just want to drink wheat juice?
So you want to learn how to switch off of work mode.
You're not supposed to mention that
I do!
Then leave it to us!
There we have our request!
Thank you for the request!
Aki-senpai's problem is, in short:
She wants to improve her lifestyle by
learning how to switch off of work-mode!
We've got just the game for this troubled Aki-senpai!
Oh? What is it?
It's this!
Ta-dah!
Rune Factory 5!
The fifth installment of the widely popular
Rune Factory series has been released!
It's a fantasy RPG with tons of ways
to enjoy the game in both adventuring and life!
Fight threats to the town with your comrades
as a part of a security organization.
At home, you can farm or fish.
Moreover, you can date people in town!
Would you like to experience the excitement
that daily life and adventure have to offer?
Let's learn how to switch gears with Rune Factory 5,
the latest game in a series that lets you experience
both adventure and daily life!
Yay! Let's learn!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
All right, I'll start!
Yeah!
"Kingdom of Norad."
"Remote forest."
It's a forest.
Starts near the border, huh?
These are some pretty graphics.
Whoa!
Cuuute!
Cute.
Is she okay? She seems scared.
Is she in danger?
She's got animal ears.
What's happening?
My, how cute.
What was that?
"I think I heard something."
Ah!
They give you a choice, Aki-senpai!
You can choose between
boku (masculine) and watashi (feminine).
When I play games, I like playing
as a male character named "Swolenthal."
A buff character?
"I (boku) have to save her!"
Nice.
How manly.
"The protagonist will be set to 'male.'"
We'll play as a man. "Are you sure?"
Yeah!
Swolenthal has been born.
He's dead!
That he is.
He's handsome!
He's good-looking.
It's a fern.
The Boss is hungry.
Is that what stands out to you?!
It caught my eye...
"I can't remember anything..."
The dude's an amnesiac!
He's got pretty eyes.
The amnesiac protagonist remembers
that he has to save the girl.
There's voiced lines.
He's speaking! Wow, is this fully voiced?
The music's really nice.
The voice acting is a good touch.
This girl's really cute. Can we clear her route?
I wonder.
"Monster"?
Are we gonna battle?
A battle right off the bat?
The monster looks pretty cute from the back, though.
It's kinda fluff—Wait, ain't that hella cute?
I'd feel a little bad beating it.
I wanna catch it and raise it as a pet!
Wooly
"Broadsword"
You can tame monsters!
Swolenthal is getting riled up.
Then, I'll use the sword.
Yeah.
You're gonna attack it when it's that cute?
You're really gonna beat it up?
I'm sorry!
Slash!
Take this!
No mercy!
He's already down!
Lawnmower Swolenthal
Stop! Stop! He's already dead!
Even as more monsters show up,
he defeats them smoothly.
The two safely reach the town despite being wounded.
There, it's revealed that Hina-chan was in the forest
because she was separated from her mother.
Of course, from here, they leave to search for her mother!
Now then, to the forest!
Let's go find her mother!
Off to the "Whispering Forest" in search of Hina's mother!
Ah, this is where he woke up!
Yeah, there were ferns where he woke up, too.
There's a treasure chest. What will you do?
He seems to have noticed something.
He heard someone's voice!
I wonder what's inside.
I'm curious about the scream,
but let's open the treasure chest first.
When your skill levels up, your protagonist's stats
will increase, and you'll be able to learn
charge attacks as well as combo attacks.
Skill up.
Nice!
What's that?
He's holding like a shield or something.
Maybe you have to store it?
Ah, so that's what it's about.
Okay, okay.
There're enemies about!
These guys are totally enemies!
Can we just ignore them?
"When you can't proceed to the next area,
defeat all the monsters first!"
So we can't ignore them.
Nice.
You're doing good.
Nice!
You're so good!
Ow!
No mercy!
Let him die!
They push forward deeper into the forest!
Cuuute! What is this thing?
Huh? I have to kill this cutie, too?
Ah... I'm so sorry.
Even though you're all so cute.
The enemies are adorable.
I feel bad about killing them.
I feel so guilty...
I spot a treasure chest in the back!
Yay!
What will we find?
I am speed!
Enemies defeated! Now time for the loot
She's opened it... and it's a skill up!
You get pretty nice progress in the beginning.
Isn't that armor?
It is!
It's—Ow!
What was that?
Cute.
Let 'im have it!
That's enough! Leave him alone!
If they defeat the enemies past this point,
they'll have their first boss battle!
Almost time for their first boss battle!
The low HP is a little worrying, though.
There's something there.
It's yellow-ish red.
It's like a gate thing.
We're aiming to reach the ball.
Nice!
Ah! Shoot!
Ahhh! He got you.
Wait, you're dead!
Defeated right before the boss battle...
Game over.
Who would've thought.
What a nutty turnout.
Before they could reach the mother.
Mommy...
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Aki-san died right before the boss fight,
but she's trying again,
paying attention to her HP this time.
And finally, it's time for the boss battle!
All right.
Finally, the boss battle!
Here we go!
Is it time for the boss?
Can she beat the boss?
Ooh! It's all smoky.
It's here!
This seems bad.
How sinister.
The lightning looks insane.
Will I be able to beat it?
What's gonna come out of the smoke?
Ah!
Whoa!
It's so cool!
I only have a single sword right now. Can I do this?
Ready? Battle!
It's huge.
Wh—That thing's huge.
She's got a watering can. She's watering.
You use the watering can when farming to water crops
This isn't the time to be watering the soil!
It disappeared for a moment!
It's cute!
She's gonna come after you.
Look out!
Nice evade!
Fat fingering the evade!
You're so good at dodging!
You're so good, Aki-senpai!
This seems good!
It's wide open!
Once the Nine-Tails glows gold, focus on dodging!
The fireball it fires afterward...
Ahhh! That's the fireball!
Nice, nice.
...is immensely powerful and will one-shot you,
so dodge it at all costs.
She dodged it quite well there.
During battle, you can pick a preferred style
of combat based on the weapon of choice.
For weapons, you have swords, axes,
staffs, among other weapons,
and by using the same weapons,
the protagonist's skills level up
and they learn moves such as
the charge attack and supers.
A super sounds cool!
I wanna try it!
While she was talking about that...
Nice, you're really good at going behind it.
Yaaay!
Nine-Tails defeated!
Unbelievably, she beat it to death without using her super!
And then...
As expected.
Wh—
Whoa, she's cuuute!
Wait a sec.
Wait!
It's a hottie.
Cute.
Don't be fooled!
It's a fox playing tricks!
Oh no, I beat her.
But she's still cute!
She is...
That was quick.
D-Don't let her deceive you...
Wait...
Mom?
What?!
Aki-senpai, what have you done?!
Did I just kill her mom?!
You've done it now!
Just as they suspected,
the Nine-Tails ended up being
the mother they were looking for.
Aki-san beat her up pretty bad...
Well, that was surprising.
I [redacted] them before I realized who they were.
You did.
Now that that tense battle is over,
would you like to switch gears, Aki-senpai?
Switching moods!
I do!
The Rune Factory series is known for letting you
experience both adventures and daily life!
So, please soothe yourself by assimilating
back into daily life after your adventures!
Change of pace 1
Fishing and relaxing after battle!
We'll have Aki-san try out the fishing!
Ah! I wanna fish!
Go ahead and fish!
Here I go!
I wonder what she'll fish up.
Can I catch a tuna here?
T-T-Tuna?
Tuna?!
This is a river, you know...
Aki-senpai, this is a river.
She was supposed to be leisurely fishing, but...
she can't catch anything.
Th-The river's the other way...
Aki-senpai! You're rushing it too much!
Powering through it too hard...
Be a little more patient! Patience!
You have to wait!
She's still got adrenaline from battling.
Yeah, I'm still a bit riled up.
Hold. Hold.
You have to pull it up after they bite.
Not yet?
Now!
Yeah!
Masu trout?
Look! Look!
Appreciation time!
Ta-dah!
I believe we've relaxed quite a bit,
so let's go back home!
Switching over right away!
Let's go home!
Change of pace 2
Trying "that" out after fishing!
Now that she's relaxed,
she'll try that exciting thing next.
Aki-senpai, can you try talking
to that girl with the pink hair?
Okay.
She's sitting in a cute outfit in the back.
Look, I caught this fish! See?
Approaching her with fish?
Oh?
Ah...
She looks uncomfortable!
Did she not want that?!
Boss would've loved it, though!
Meow!
She was so hyped up earlier.
Maybe talk to her first.
Hello♪ Nice weather we're having.
It's perfect for some laundry.
Seems good so far.
There's an L and R option.
What's this?
She didn't seem to like the fish, but...
there will be some rapid developments!
What does it do?
By continuing the conversation...
"I'm going to the lake with Fuka-chan."
Do you want to come with?
?!
Is this... love?!
Is she inviting me on a date?!
Is she?!
She probably has feelings for me!
Huh?!
Isn't this way too sudden?!
Change of pace 2
Confessing after fishing!
Here we go!
Let's gooo!
But we're quite dense when it comes to romance.
Boss, what do you think?
You should confess right away.
Go for it!
I... I love you!
Ah... I see. I think you should save those words
for people that are precious to you.
Hard pass
Cats just aren't built for romance.
That was unfortunate.
Y-Yup.
That's quite painful.
Switching moods!
We've prepared a little something for Aki-senpai
now that her emotions are wandering off.
Ta-dah!
There's something here! It's so cute!
Change of pace 3
Vent the stress of a failed confession with adventure!
She's still a bit out of it from that obvious outcome.
Let's vent out those feelings through a little adventure!
This is—Please don't release it.
This is my personal save data where I've tamed a party member!
She prepared it for the customer!
You've got a bit of an outfit going on.
I've dressed him up, yeah.
By the way, I've actually cleared this
until right before the second boss,
and I'm all geared up as well!
Whoa!
Like the ribbon.
So now, we'll go with our party to beat up the boss!
And vent all of our emotional stress!
Let's go!
It's got quite the aura.
You can feel the presence.
Aki-chan's pretty good at combat, so I feel like she can do it.
I wonder.
She beat Nine-Tails with 0 damage taken, after all.
A perfect run is impressive.
But if I defeat this boss...
Oh sh*t.
I want a little reward.
It seems a little strong!
It has three whole heads!
Cerberus!
I feel like I can do it.
I thought Cerberus would be on all four legs.
Yeah, this one's standing.
The same race?!
It's kinda novel.
You can do it!
Nice! Do your best!
Take my fist!
Fist?!
Would you like to equip a weapon?
There're a few weapons you can choose from, Aki-senpai.
How's their pet looking?
Your buddy's getting beat up!
It's so squishy!
It's already down!
It got done in...
Thine honorable death
I'm sorry!
It had so little health!
It lived and died fast.
That's a watering can!
Equip a weapon!
How can I revive it?
Water it with the watering can!
Is that all I can do for it?
Watering does not revive teammates
Weapon... weapon...
I've got a ton of weapons!
You'll get hit if you attack from the front,
so try to go to its flank.
What are you even doing?!
This is no time to play Lion King!
B! B! Press B to equip!
She looks like she's presenting it to Cerberus...
B! B!
I said, press B to equip!
AkiRose-senpai, what the hell are you doing?!
I'm pressing it! I'm pressing it!
Please don't present it to the boss
Equip it, please!
Look out!
I can't stop laughing...
Your buddy's dead, and this battle's all over the place...
Nice! Nice evade. Your evading is still good.
Press Y again. Not the watering can!
Fighting with the watering can!
That was dangerous! But she got a skill up!
What skill could've possibly leveled up from that?
She's good at dodging, at least!
Uh, are you ever going to fight it?
Press Y! Press Y!
I am! I'm pressing it, but nothing's happening!
Yeah! Like that!
You got it!
Just do it barehanded!
My body's my weapon! Swolenthal Punch!
Fists FTW!
Dodge! Dodge!
Heal! Heal! Heal! Heal!
She's in a pinch! Does she have anything to heal with?
There's an item!
This could be bad if she doesn't heal!
Aki-senpaaai!
Huh?
Subaru had commissioned it
If you commission for backup from a Seed member, they'll come help you when you're in a pinch.
A helper arrived!
Thanks, Subaru-chan!
Let's continue!
Shoot!
Nice! Nice dodge.
Aki-senpai, take it slow!
It's better to go around to its flank!
She's reading the boss perfectly.
It finally feels like a battle!
Dodge!
It's aiming... and firing!
Her HP is dangerously low!
Let's heal!
I wanna heal!
Open up your item menu.
Not the watering can, Aki-senpai!
She really likes that watering can!
She's taunting the boss at this point.
I'm pressing Y, but... I have no idea what's wrong.
How do I open up that menu?
She's good at pulling out the watering can and dodging.
I can only pull out the watering can.
That's all you need!
I'll kill you with my trusty watering can!
Whoa! The watering can does damage too!
The watering can's all I need!
She's gone...
Defeat...
Aki-senpai...
Before anyone could come save her.
She died before she could be saved.
That was chaotic!
You can only taunt the boss so much!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Regrettably, the demo ends here!
It didn't seem like she could beat it... so it'll end here...
I wanna play some more!
How was Rune Factory 5?
It was seriously fun, and it seems like
there were a ton more things I could do.
And this is just something I heard,
but you can get in a relationship,
have kids,
and divorce.
Don't divorce them!
The freedom of choice is one of
Rune Factory 5's selling points.
By the way, have we solved your problem?
Oh, right...
Have we?
You have!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
We have one last question for you!
Please tell us the member who shined the most,
the Twin-crew for today!
Subaru! Subaru!
The Twin-crew for today was...
Subaru-chan!
Yay!
Today's Twin-crew
Oozora Subaru
Subaru-chan again?
Second one!
Yeah... Towa-sama and I didn't do anything for her.
Marine and Towa's role for today:
Extras
Seriously!
She prepared all the equipment for me and stuff.
It was thanks to her help.
Well, it was the least I could do.
Towa-sama, we gotta catch up!
Promotion to boss with 100 Twin-crew stars!
Let's steal them off her!
I want some too!
Let's defeat her and take them!
What's with the dance?
I want some too!
Wishing upon the stars dance ♪
That looks pretty effective.
Subaru-chan, do your best with the rest of the 98 stars!
Yeah!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Challenge From the Boss: the Maruyama Championship!
Yay!
It's habbening!
This season's minigame is...
Puyo Puyo Tetris 2's Endless Fever mode!
At the moment, the current high scorer
is still Marine with 57,726 points.
What? That high?!
That's right!
Get a load of this, Aki-senpai!
Every episode, the challenger is some third-rate loser.
Marine-chan the Braggart
They always say they can win.
I wanna taste defeat for once!
I didn't want to know.
Aki-senpai, you should smack her good. Smack her!
Graah!
Arr! I'm sorry!
I win.
She's too strong! Swolenthal's too strong!
Swolenthal!
So, Aki-chan, how confident are you?
I played Puyo Puyo when I was a baby elf,
but my friend was really good
and always beat me really badly.
I got traumatized, so I stopped playing.
Oh, I see.
And your really good friend was me!
Now's your chance!
Time for revenge!
Curse you!
Na-ha-ha-ha-ha!
I need to get over my trauma, so maybe I'll do my best!
Aki-senpai, you can do it!
Then let the game begin!
Okay!
It's starting now!
It's starting!
Aki-senpai, you can do it!
Will she be another third-rate loser?
You only get 60 seconds!
That's right!
Stack them fast!
Hold on, the controls...
We're starting with an all clear.
It's surprisingly... Yes, it's surprisingly quick.
That's what you call serendipity.
Ah... Hm...
I hope Aki-senpai can cross the Subaru Line.
The Legendary Subaru Line: 2,516 points
Can you stop calling it the "Subaru Line"?!
She's already crossed the Subaru Line.
Currently 3,000 points.
You're right!
Hold on, how did you make the Line?
I don't know!
I don't remember what I did!
The current max chain is 1.
Shoot, shoot, I'm panicking.
1?!
Don't panic, don't panic.
Stay calm.
Isn't this the same as what I did?!
You still have 25 seconds.
She's very good at 1-chains.
Each piece is very important.
There are 20 seconds left!
Oh, got it!
Oh, nice!
That's a 2-chain!
I've beaten Subaru-chan's record!
Why do you have to say that?!
10 seconds left!
10 seconds?!
9! 8!
6! 5!
3! 2! 1!
You got it! You got it!
3-chain! 3-chain! 3-chain!
It's over!
Wow!
She got a 3-chain!
3-chain and all clear at the end!
Wow!
But how did she do?
But how did she do?!
Wow!
Let's see that final score!
22,894 points!
Wow!
That's 22,894 points!
And that puts her in 3rd place!
Congratulations!
You went down one, Towa-chan.
What? Seriously?
She beat you.
Wow, you caused a miracle.
Will a monster appear and beat the high score?
Tune in next time and see!
Thank you!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
After Hours
How did you enjoy this episode
of Game Shop Maruyama?
I've asked Subaru to stay back this time!
Yay!
Thanks for having me!
Now, let's give our viewers
some advice with their worries!
From @tsumayoji_r on Twitter!
Ever since my friend from high school got married,
it seems his wife holds his purse strings by the balls,
so he can't buy a new console.
I'd like to play a game together with him.
How can I get him to buy one?
That's the question.
Oh, I see.
Marriage is hard, huh?
This is a tough problem,
but really...
Don't make him buy it. That's the easiest way!
An unexpected answer?!
Wait. What? Wait... Howzzat work?
Well, basically...
You should give it to him as a gift!
Oh!
That's how you do it.
That's genius!
Heh-heh-heh-heh.
Amazing!
That's how you do it.
I see!
If you want to play games with him that badly,
buy a used console or something and give it to him!
You can give him a hand-me-down of your own,
just give it to him!
Was that a tongue twister?!
So genius that Boss is on fire!
Yes, that's exactly right!
That's perfect!
Precisely!
Prove your gamer spirit!
Prove it!
That's a really good answer!
If you actually do it, make sure you tell us how it went!
Tell us!
And now, we're accepting requests for advice from you.
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique,
personally signed request fulfilled sticker.
Yay!
So please send in your submissions!
Nice!
Send 'em in!
Send 'em! Send 'em! Send 'em in!
Send 'em in dancing you off for next time!