Hey, um, hi...
Just wondering, like, how you're doing...
Man... this mood sucks.
Suzune-san, it would be best
if you say it clearly and directly.
Is this all because of that dumb rumor?
Y-Yeah, I know. I know...
So, um, I'm... I'm sorry!
You don't believe it, Hanabi-san?
You know how I hit you the other day?
Of course not.
But Inari's totally convinced...
Well, I really didn't mean to hit you.
This can't go on.
We gotta do something.
I was... trying to do physical intimacy...
Allow me to elaborate.
Should we do some research?
Suzune-san was working on her flirting skills,
If it's related to this school,
the school library should have...
and therefore wished to practice physical intimacy.
No, it doesn't.
Yeah, exactly!
I was trying to bond with you, you know?
I had the same idea,
but I checked and didn't find anything.
So I really didn't mean to hit you that hard.
Nothing at all?
I'm so sorry. It must have hurt...
That doesn't seem right.
I'll ask my grandpa once I get home.
Can you... forgive me?
Actually, I can ask around town.
Somebody must know.
Really? Thank goodness...
If the same thing has happened before
and nothing came of it,
You see?
As I told you, a proper apology was all it took.
You worry too much.
that should convince Inari
that the rumor is nonsense.
But after what Inari told me...
Good idea. I'll ask my mother.
I got so scared.
What if we never saw each other again,
and all because of me?
She used to attend our school.
Oh, dear...
Suzune-san, don't tell me you believe that rumor?
Maybe she knows something.
Thanks!
It's clearly nonsense,
so please stop worrying.
Man, I hate having stuff like this
hanging over my head.
Ah, my apologies!
You see,
Inari-san was saying some peculiar things...
Best to clear it up as soon as possible.
Touka, you're gonna tell them?
That's for sure.
Summer break's just around the corner.
Is it okay to tell them?
Let's start it on a good note.
I believe it is best if they know.
Please do not be disturbed by what I say.
You see...
Wh-What the... What's this sound?
Hey, Touka!
What in the... No, it can't!
No, I'm scared...
What is happening... I don't know... I don't know!
No...
No!
Unless... it was true...!
Noooo!