uwu
Why are you lazing around, Luna?
What's up?
I wanna fly.
People can't fly, okay?
Subarucha-senpai... Don't you have
any imagination? Hopes? Dreams?
Brutal!
Anyway, I wanna fly!
I wanna, I wanna!
Stop spinning!
What's the matter?
You talk her down, Mel-senpai.
I believe I can fly! I believe I can touch the sky!
She's been like this since I got here.
Zoom!
Oh dear.
If she really  wants,
she can die, and then I'll take her to the heavens.
Cool your head!
There's a lot I still
wanna do in life.
I happen to know an easy and reliable way.
Sounds like you're pitching an MLM scheme.
Bite, bite, bite, bite!
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
Let me bite you and turn you into a vampire.
Then you'll grow wings and fly!
Cool!
Don't throw away
your humanity!
Hmm? What's up, Luna?
Gah!
What are you doing?!
Put these on for me.
Got it.
She's already lost all traces of a human heart!
Goo...
Gaa!
Yikes! Luna crashed into the ceiling!
Dearie me.
Amazing!
I actually got to fly!
You're satisfied with that?!
Ah!
I wanna eat ice cream!
Please go buy me some!
Just get back down here!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!