This girl's as lewd as they come.
Thanks for having me!
...present your chest...
Ooh~
It's a Double Attack!
Are you ready to kneel to me in defeat?
As if.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Woo-hoo!
Woo-hoo?
What's with the woo-hoo-ing?
So, summer's here!
And summer means summer songs!
So what are you girls listening to?
Can I go first?
Go right ahead.
For summer, you want a song that'll get you hyped,
and I think 5th Gen's "Blue Clapper" is perfect for that.
Ooh!
Ah, I see!
Just so you know, Boss,
"Blue Clapper" is one of hololive's original songs!
Really?
Good to know!
Can I go next?
Let's hear it.
You want a hype summer song?
Just ask a woman of the high seas!
Oh?
"Ahoy!! We Are Houshou Pirates"!
Which happens to be my original song.
Yes, we know.
I could tell from the title.
You're just promoting yourself!
This is self-advertising!
How about you, Subaru-senpai?
Well, when it comes to summer,
there's only one song for me!
Only one?
You can now listen to it streaming
on iTunes and other services.
A streaming song?
"Taiyou Shoujo"!
Ozora Subaru's original song! Give it a listen!
You're self-advertising too?!
Mark that as promoted content!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Oh! Welcome to the store!
Well, who do we have here?
If it isn't Matsuri-senpai!
Ta-dah!
Today's guest:
Natsuiro Matsuri
Gosh, her skirt is short. Welcome!
I'm here!
Speaking of summer, right?
Yep! Summer's in my name!
So what generation are you?
1st Generation!
I have seniority.
So you're the most senior of everyone here.
That's right!
Respect me!
So what's she like, as a senior member?
She's a perv.
A-A perv?!
A perv?!
This girl's as lewd as they come.
Thanks for having me!
She's a real perv.
Just go up to her
and present your chest...
Ooh!
See what I mean?
Oh, come on!
Like a magnet
Hey! We're on the official channel!
Oh, right! This is official!
Someone get the spray bottle!
Almost got in trouble!
Spray bottle!
Today's guest is Natsuiro Matsuri-san,
known for her somewhat perverted behavior.
Natsuiro Matsuri
Favorite game genre: APEX
MENT
LUCK
Natsuiro Matsuri
Most attractive features:
Side hair
Large eyes
What could she be seeking advice for?
Towa-chan, tell us what she's like.
Well...
She's pretty...
She won't like what I say
I mean, well... like...
She's at a loss for words!
She's really...
She's doesn't know what to say!
Abusing seniority in 5
She's just...
Yes?
Abusing seniority in 4
What past trauma does she have?
Abusing seniority in 3
Spit it out.
Sh-She's flat as a wall.
Abusing seniority in 2
A wall?!
Towa: Pleads the Fifth
Abusing seniority in 1
A wall?!
Hey! You're flatter than me!
Abusing seniority!!
Get back here!
You've got more cleavage, though.
I see.
Weak point: Lack of cleavage
Sucks for you!
Sorry, you lose.
See? I win again!
Wait, MENT 1? Are you that weak-spirited?
Wait, really?
Didn't expect that!
I thought nothing could faze you.
I'm actually pretty sensitive.
So you're sensitive about being flat?
That's why you're upset?
Quick, say sorry!
Wait, me?
Landed the fatal blow
See, you made her cry!
You meanie! She's crying!
Landed the fatal blow
Apologize already!
Tsk-tsk.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for telling the truth.
What?
Get back here, you!
Uh-oh.
You'll pay for that one!
Abusing seniority!
You crossed the line there!
Are we sure she's that sensitive?
I don't think so.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
So, Matsuri-chan, what worry
would you like us to resolve for you?
Right!
I know I don't have very good Strength or Speed,
but it would be tough for me to train those stats now.
That's true.
That would be difficult.
So I wanna know how to become powerful
without relying on strength or speed!
I see!
Leave it to us!
And there we have our request!
We have just the thing!
Matsuri-senpai's request is, in short,
to get stronger without strengthening herself!
Leave it to us!
We have the perfect game for you!
Ooh!
The game we recommend for today is...
Monster Hunter Stories 2: Wings of Ruin!
Ooh!
That's right!
Ruin?
"When the wings unfurl, disaster will befall the land."
Monster Hunter Stories 2: Wings of Ruin
is the second RPG installment in the popular
Monster Hunter action game series.
Players take the role of monster riders in an exciting story.
In co-op quests, you can acquire Monstie eggs,
which you can enjoy hatching and raising!
In Monster Hunter Stories 2: Wings of Ruin,
we'll dive into a new MH world and...
All together, now!
Go for a hunt!
Let's go!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Let's first have a versus battle
against the Monsties I've been secretly raising,
so I can teach you the controls and the three attack types.
The three attack types?
Three attack types?
Well, it'll be quicker to show you.
Let's set up a match and get right into it!
Okay!
You can learn as we battle!
Okay, Matsuri-senpai! Our battle is beginning!
Ooh!
First, players choose an item set.
Sets are specialized for offense or defense,
making this an important strategic decision.
See, for this,
It's strategic.
you gotta predict your opponent's choice.
Marine chooses the Balanced Set
That's true.
So we can't peek.
This is part of the strategy.
It sure is.
Matsuri-senpai, are you sure...
Based on her personality, I pick this.
Ah, I see.
Based on my personality, huh?
Matsuri chooses the Fortitude Set
Marine-san takes the Balanced Set.
STEP 1: Learn the 3 attack types and battle basics!!
Matsuri chooses the Fortitude Set
Marine chooses the Balanced Set
Matsuri-san predicts Marine-san will be aggressive
and chooses the Fortitude Set.
How will these choices affect the battle?
Whoa, they're facing off!
Here we go! VS!
Whoa!
So cool!
So you can use monsters like pals?
Exactly!
From the attack menu,
you can press L and R to switch
between Power, Speed, and Technical.
These are the attack types?
That's right! The three attack types.
They work like rock-paper-scissors.
The diagram shows you what's strong against what.
Oh, the arrows tell you!
Yeah, the arrows show you.
So you gotta predict what your opponent will choose.
Gotta be one step ahead!
I get it!
You only get to select your character's attack, here.
Your monster's attack gets chosen automatically.
I see.
So what is Matsuri-senpai going to choose?
Let me think...
Hmm, but maybe...
Ooh, this is hard!
Picked one!
Wait!
I predict she'll choose this.
So I'll go with this.
Matsuri-san picks Speed.
Marine-san picks Technical.
I just noticed, but you're "Subageezer"!
Oh, the in-game name!
Subageezer
Yeah, the name!
The name says "Subageezer," but it's Matsuri-chan.
Subageezer!
Whoa!
You're so strong!
Matsuri-san has the attack type advantage,
Oh, no!
but Marine-san's Monstie hits super hard!
What's going on here?
Take this!
And this!
Still, you should get at least one—
Well, let's see.
Oh, no!
She's losing!
You've got three hearts,
Right.
and you lose once they're all gone!
I see!
So that's how it works!
It's not over yet!
But Marine-san's powerful onslaught continued!
She's on a totally different level!
Hm?
Something's fishy...
Gosh, you're too good.
And I think this should do the trick.
This should do it.
Oh, you can use items!
Yeah, I wanna use some of these items.
What, you don't want to lose?
Well, duh!
Of course I don't!
A total newbie like you?
She uses an item!
Oh, my!
Okay, okay! I survived!
A surrogate?!
Not too shabby.
Ooh, spikes.
Using your head—
Ah! But wait...
That took her out! Killer Crush!
This is gonna hurt!
Nice!
Not bad.
You refuse to go down, huh?
Well, you'll learn the truth of the matter eventually.
"Truth of the matter"?
What truth?
Curious? I'll tell you later.
Heh heh heh.
I see how it is.
Matsuri-chan, shouldn't you heal?
I'm gonna heal!
Attagirl.
Your Monstie's drooling there.
Dust of Life!
They healed so much!
Back to full HP!
Come on!
Resistance is futile!
Dang! She's too strong!
No mercy for you!
Take this!
Against Marine-san's utter domination,
Matsuri-san didn't stand a chance!
Marine Wins!!!
But there was a secret to this victory.
Yar-har-har-har!
Oh my goodness.
Har-har-har!
Not a shred of mercy!
Feeling pretty smug, huh, Captain?
Yeah.
Well, to be honest, it was thanks to my equipment level.
Wait, what?!
We just played Versus Battle with No Limit Rules.
So you get the full effect of differences in equipment level.
Basically, you couldn't have won, no matter what you did.
I see!
But for Versus Battles, you can also pick
Balanced Rules, which evens out your levels.
Why aren't we playing that?
We will, but first...
let's try out this installment's new Co-Op Quests,
where we can obtain Monstie eggs.
Ooh! Sounds nice!
Shall we go another round
with our very own precious Monsties?
I'm in!
Next step:
STEP 2: Obtain Monstie eggs from Co-Op Quests!!
Find monster nests,
which spawn randomly in Co-Op Quests,
and take home some Monstie eggs!
Then, challenge Marine-san to a rematch
with her newly hatched Monsties!
Okay! Let's start this quest!
Let's do this!
Stop being so hyper!
Calm your tits, Matsuri-senpai!
I'm just so excited!
Matsuri-chan, calm down!
Okay, let's head out.
Matsuri-senpai, if you press B,
you can use your special skill.
Ooh!
See, I can go stealth mode.
Whoa, that's so cool!
Isn't that neat?
Are you keeping up, Matsuri-senpai?
Wait up, Captain!
She's booking it.
She's too fast!
The Captain's too fast.
Also, she's in stealth mode,
Shadow
so I can't even see her!
I'm still invisible!
Well, what have we here?
Found something?
Uh-oh!
We'll have to take care of this!
It's right by the eggs, so we gotta deal with it first.
I see.
Go get it!
Let's get it, Matsuri-senpai!
You can do it!
Here we go!
Yeah! Here we go!
It's like an RPG encounter!
We've taken its rear!
That's a cute rear!
Nicely done.
He's quite thicc.
That's a big advantage.
It's wide open! Attack!
What'll be effective against it?
Choosing attack type
But, hmm...
It looks like a Power type.
Agreed!
Go with Speed!
Just my impression, though.
Then let's try attacking with Speed.
Matsuri-san and Marine-san both choose Speed!
Is it effective?
Oh?
Subageezer.
Nice!
Wow!
Lookin' good!
Yeah!
Great!
Wait, this thing's strong!
Yeah, it's tanky!
I'm gonna try Technical.
Right.
Then I'll try Power.
Sounds good.
Which will be effective?
Let's find out.
It's a Double Attack!
Whoa!
Wow!
It's super effective!
Take note!
Double Attacks are a great way to turn a battle around.
Try it out for yourself!
Right!
Oh, crap! It's enraged!
Anjanath: Mad AF!!
It's angry!
Oh, no!
Its face is all red!
I see.
Once the gauge is full, you can do a riding attack.
You can ride them!
I can target the snout and ride my Monstie!
Maybe I'll do just that!
Do it, do it!
Ride on!
So cool!
Nargacuga!
Ride that baby!
There's a Kinship Skill button!
I've gotta try this!
I wanna see that!
Here I go!
How's that?
Show your kinship!
The snout! I can target the snout!
I'm going for it!
Yeah, the snout!
I'll snap that snout right off!
Ride on!
Ram that thing!
Go, go!
So cool!
That was so cool!
Woo-hoo!
Wow!
That was impressive.
So cool!
It's so dynamic!
So awesome!
HAAAAA!
Whoa!
Nailed it!
Ah, so cool!
Oh, it's down!
Wow!
Let's stick to the snout.
Okay! Snout it is!
Sounds good!
Snap that thing right off!
Sounds painful.
The Matsuri and Marine duo continues their assault!
Victory is within reach!
You got a part break!
It's down!
Beat it up!
See, while it's downed,
you can get a ton of criticals!
Go get it!
That's nice!
Switching Monsties
At this point, both teams will switch out their Monsties.
Who will they send out next?
Velocidrome.
Kulu-Ya-Ku.
That's a cute name.
I think I'll go with Kulu-Ya-Ku.
Kulu-Ya-Ku, I choose you!
Come back, Nargacuga!
I think...
Go, Kulu-Ya-Ku!
I'll switch too.
And...
I think I'll try using a skill!
Matsuri uses a skill!
Look at you!
Keep up the pressure!
Nice critical!
Oh?
Charge Tackle! Good one!
Nice hit.
Ooh!
Switched in Monsties are doing work!
Whoa!
Nice, Kulu-Ya-Ku! Doing great!
Whoa, that's strong!
That one hit deals a lot!
Head-To-Head!
Focus Slash!
Take that!
That's awesome!
Not bad!
Go, go!
Nice!
Doing good!
So strong!
You're on a roll!
Oh, spam A!
Come at me!
Take this!
You got a lot of nerve!
My finger's gonna cramp.
Nice!
But I won!
Your gauge charged all the way up!
Oh, nice!
It's nice how they give you these dramatic beats.
Time to ride!
Cool!
Ride!
Let's go!
Should I use my Kinship Skill?
Do it, do it!
Go for it!
What's it like?
Marine uses a Kinship Skill!!
Oh?
Ooh!
What's happening?
Eggsplosion!
Whoa, cool!
It's me!
Who's this?
Boss is assisting!
Boss!
Wow, that's powerful!
Whoa!
What's it doing? That's scary!
Oh, crap!
Uh-oh! It's storing fire!
It's charging up! Not good!
Oh god, oh god, oh god...
Whoa!
Nice critical!
Nice!
Almost there!
Nice going!
That was strong.
Oh, it's weakened!
It is!
Okay, my turn!
It's gonna freak out.
Matsuri mounts her Monstie!!
Ooh!
Is...
Onto its back!
You're doing it!
Is it gonna guard?
Here I go with a Kinship Skill!
Here comes a cool one!
Go for it!
Chaaaaarge!
Nice!
Part break!
You're really good at those!
Glad we went for it!
Awesome!
Almost there!
Just a little bit more!
Finish it, Captain!
In that case,
I trust the Captain to finish it off,
so I'll heal her.
Leave it to me!
I will!
Get healed!
This is true co-op!
Nice!
Take this!
Focus Slash!
So cool!
Schwing!
We did it!
Nice!
The power of kinship!
Man, battling together is fun!
It sure is!
For sure!
We did it!
We really did!
It was an excellent fight.
Okay!
S-rank!
Amazing!
Now that we've beat it,
let's get what we came here for!
Time to take home some eggs!
Yay, eggs!
Right, the quest isn't over yet.
I forgot the objective was eggs.
C'mon, Matsuri-senpai, let's swipe the loot and run!
Wait up!
I'm picking an egg!
Matsuri is selecting an egg
Hup-hup! Hup-hup!
Swipe and run!
Ah, that one's cute!
This one's cute too.
It's super cute.
Ah, the eggs disappeared.
Oh, you're right.
You'll have to take that one.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
C'mon, Matsuri-senpai! Swipe and run!
Wait up, Captain! Wait for me!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Swipe and run!
Swipe and run!!
No kidding!
Ready to leave!
Yeaaah!
Nice!
Nice.
Next, can you talk to that Felyne for me?
Sure. This one?
Yup.
Okay.
So cute!
I know, right?
Even cuter than Boss.
*growls in Cat*
That sure got Boss's dander up.
She's having a fit of rage!
Select "Hatch Egg" from the menu.
That's so cute!
And as you can see,
this is where you can hatch the eggs
that you brought back with you just now.
Okay.
Right!
I'd like to hatch this one!
Go for it!
Whoa!
Whoa, what's this?
Yian Kut-Ku!
Its face is huge!
That jaw is huge!
It's got a giant chin!
That jaw is too powerful!
Looks strong.
It's got cute, round eyes.
I hatched a super cute one.
Names, names...
Whoa!
This one's a cutie.
It has such pure eyes.
Yeah, it's really cute.
It really is.
What should I name it?
Oh, a name!
Gosh, that's hard.
We've named them with love. Time for the reveal!
Right!
I'll start, with my sweet, adorable... Just look at it!
"Pure Eyes Rhino"!
Name: Pure Eyes Rhino
Just look at those pure eyes!
Those eyes are sparkling.
And also,
it's got a horn like a rhinoceros beetle.
Oh, I get it!
That's what it's named after!
Okay.
I'll go next, then.
Okay!
Name: Chin Chomp lv. 100
"Chin Chomp lv. 100"!
That's the stuff of nightmares!
I get it, though.
It's got a giant chomper!
'Cause it'll chomp you with its chin!
Oh, that's what you mean!
I thought it ate chins!
Yes: Chomps with chin
No: Chomps on chins
Other way around!
It doesn't eat them!
Which freaked me out.
That'd be scary!
Let's test our love towards our Monsties
Uh-huh.
with another match.
Matsuri-senpai, it's time to settle our score!
Ready when you are!
We'll be using Balanced Rules, which evens out our levels!
I'm in it to win it!
Here we go!
STEP 3: A rematch using the hatched Monsties!!
It's the long-awaited rematch
using the Monsties they hatched!
The rules are Balanced!
Both sides are here to prove themselves!
Oh, it's starting.
Yeah. We're playing with Balanced Rules,
so our levels are all evened out.
So that's your Chin Chomp lv.100?
That it is.
Show her the power of your Chin Chomp!
No amount of chomping
will damage these pure eyes!
That chin's seriously huge.
These eyes will teach you a lesson!
Oh? Matsuri-san's already utilizing her items.
Let's use this.
What? What is that?!
Wait! Don't do it!
Wake up!
Are you all talk?!
Sweet dreams!
How dare you!
Go get her, Chin Chomp!
Wait, I'm not ready!
Nice work!
So Chin Chomp pummels with its chin...
Yeah. That's right.
It's still sleeping.
This is not good, so not gooood...
And while it's still asleep...
Matsuri-senpai, that's overkill!
Come at me, I won't lose!
Both fighters continue to make use of their items!
It's not working on Chin Chomp!
Fall asleep!
Take this!
While it's still sleeping.
Go to sleep already!
Ah! It's finally awake!
That's my Pure.
What?!
Your sleep won't work on Chin Chomp!
Chin Chomp's so strong!
What is that? What is that?
Stahp it!
They're both setting so many traps.
There's more where that came from!
There we go!
All this strategy!
That trap's as obvious as daylight!
Oh, traps can be avoided.
What?!
Do you take me for a noob?
I wouldn't fall for such...
This is where the real battle starts.
You can't fool these pure eyes.
Kinship...
It's just RNG.
She keeps using underhanded traps.
I won't fall for that!
Another draw?
Uh-oh!
Nice.
Oh?! It's paralyzed!
Yay!
Oh no! It's in pain!
Shock Trap activates!!
Take that!
Oh, snap!
Curse you! You won't get away with this!
How's this?
Oh?
What kind of trap is this?
This one has to work.
What kind of trap is it?
There it goes!
Tranq Trap activates!!
Nighty night.
Nice call, Captain Marine!
Ah! It got out of the trap.
It broke free.
What an exciting match.
This is starting to get interesting.
Ah! It's finally time.
Ride on!
Get ready.
What's this? She's using a riding move?
This looks bad!
Chin, wake up!
She uses a nulberry! Will that wake it up?
Say what?
It doesn't!
So it doesn't work!
Ready?
AHHH!
You're kidding me!
AHH!
Oh, no!
This is bad!
Was that—Wait, was that not on purpose?
Mine's down!
My turn!
Oh no!
When someone screws me...
Don't do it!
...I screw them back!
Oh no, no, no, no.
And twice as bad!
Let's do this!
Mess it up! Mess it up!
Munch, munch.
Delicious!
Ah!
Cu—
AHHH!
Pure Eyes Rhino!
That's so strong!
They're evenly matched!
I wanna win so bad!
Not on my watch!
What's this? Marine-san is swapping out
the Monstie she hatched!
Darn it!
It's now or never!
Go for it!
Let's go, Pukei-Pukei!
Wait, what happened to your partner?
Yeah, your partner!
You're switching?
Well, yeah.
All's fair in love and war for Marine.
But your special love...
Don't be silly!
That won't work!
Keep it together, Pukei-Pukei!
Don't take that from her!
It's paralyzed!
A draw, huh?
But that did a lot of damage!
Yeah, that did a lot!
The two opponents continued to trade blows!
Oh, no!
Nailed it!
That won't work!
It didn't fall asleep!
Pukei-Pukei is a bird that never sleeps!
Venom Blaster!
Take this!
Lookin' good!
Oh, no!
That can't be pleasant!
Not good! Not good!
What a nasty attack!
Time to swap!
Matsuri-san also swaps her Monstie!
Have a good rest, Chin!
You're switching now?!
Nice move!
She's already weak, Matsuri-senpai!
All right, then.
First off,
I'm in a pretty bad spot, too,
so I'll heal myself.
Oho?
You think that'll save you?
Are you ready to kneel to me in defeat?
As if. I'm gonna win.
Ouch!
Here comes my ultimate Venom Shot!
No!
This is bad!
There, you see?
You're kidding me!
Oh, no! Hang in there, Matsuri-chan!
Matsuri-senpai, you've got this!
Take this!
All right!
Ah! Crap!
Both are down to their last heart!
The next person to get downed loses!
This is bad! This is bad!
No! Crap! I lost!
Did I do it?
AHH! AHHHH!
I did it!
I won!
No!
Darn it! I made the wrong read!
Matsuri wins!
Yay!
And with that, Matsuri-chan has claimed victory!
Hurray!
Darn it!
I messed up on the last prediction!
I didn't think she'd pick that.
Wasn't there a wager?
Yeah!
I don't know what you mean.
You mentioned something about...
About getting ready?
Wasn't that fun, Matsuri-senpai?
It was so fun playing with you!
Oh, so much fun!
Why the sudden cutesy act?
No kidding.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
I have one last question for you.
Please tell us the member who shined the most,
the Twin-crew for today!
Can I ask one thing first?
What is it?
Didn't the Captain ask me if I was ready to kneel in defeat?
She did!
Did not.
Well...
since she was the one who lost...
Never said that.
You know what that means.
She's shaking...
She's shaking in her boots!
Ye want me to kneel, eh?
Me, the one and only Cap'n of the Houshou Pirates?
That she is.
You do want to be named
today's Twin-crew, right?
Ngh...
Ngh... Ah...
Oh? I've seen this before!
She's doing it!
Argh... nrgh...
Guh-guh-guh-guh...
Guh-guh-guh... gah...
I... am...
truly... sorry...
It's Hanzawa Marine!
Hanzawa Marine!
Goodness!
Okay, then let me ask again.
Please tell us the Twin-crew for today!
Sure!
Today's Twin-crew goes to...
Subaru and Towa-chin!
Shock!
Utter shock!
Hanzawa Marine failed!
She kneeled for no reason!
Did I miss something?
Did something happen?
She's blocked it from her memory!
I don't think anything did.
The shock erased her memory.
When someone screws me,
I screw them back!
And twice as bad!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Challenge From the Boss: the Maruyama Championship!
Yay!
At this point, we'll have our customers
try their hand at a minigame.
The one who finishes the season on top
will receive a trophy!
This season's minigame is...
Puyo Puyo Tetris 2's Endless Fever mode!
At the moment, in first place is Marine
with 57,726 points, so do your best.
So, Matsuri-san, how confident are you?
This is my first time playing Puyo Puo—
Puyo Puyo!
It's her first time saying it too.
Natsuiro Matsuri is a Puyo Puyo beginner!
It's my first time playing,
but I'll do my best!
Then let the game begin!
You don't get much time, so drop them quick!
Go for chains! Chains!
Let's stack and build chains.
Matsuri-senpai, do you know what a chain is?
Does she know what one is?!
I think you're underestimating her too much.
Oh? Starting with a 1-chain.
A 1-chain!
Yes, yes.
A 1-chain.
You get more points if you get a 2-chain or higher.
At this point...
Huh, I feel like Matsuri-senpai
might be joining us at the Subaru Line.
Really?
No, I don't think so.
I think she'll be fine.
Nah, no way.
Ah.
How's this?
Oh, I see. That's how you play it.
At this point...
We don't know that yet. Not yet!
What'll happen?
Keep going!
I'm getting a little worried now.
Really?
Matsuri-senpai, you can take your time.
Her score isn't rising very quickly.
Not a good place.
Huh? What? What?
You have 20 seconds left!
You're in trouble.
The Oozora Subaru Line?
Things don't look so hot.
Matsuri-senpai, you can get a 2-chain.
10 seconds! 9!
But if you put it there, you can't...
5 seconds!
4! 3!
What?!
2! 1!
This is bad!
It's over!
Yeah!
Oh?
Your final score is 2,629 points!
That means that
compared to Oozora Subaru-san,
you win with a 100 point lead.
Yay!
That was close!
Too close.
Well, I beat Subaru, so I'm satisfied.
What kind of comment is that? What the heck?
Will a monster appear and beat the high score?
Look forward to it!
Natsuiro Matsuri
Thank you for your patronage!
Look forward to it!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
After Closing
How did you enjoy this episode
of Game Shop Maruyama?
I've asked Marine to stay back this time.
Let's give our viewers some advice with their worries.
Okay!
From @pinmiruuuuu on Twitter!
I started my second year of middle school,
but I was absent for the first three days,
so I wasn't able to find a group. I don't have any friends.
Please tell me how to make friends!
This is a perfect question for you, Marine-chan.
I see!
They're in their second year of...
Wait, middle school?!
Right, middle school.
That's young!
See,
when Captain was in
her second year of middle school,
I was one of those apocalyptic emo-goth types.
Oh, really?
As for how I'd make friends,
I'd look down and depressed like this.
Like, dead on my desk.
When I'm sitting like that, someone'd get worried and ask,
"Are you okay?"
Oh, I see!
You were an attention whore!
Yeah.
Wait, so that was your tactic?
Well, I was totally emo.
Damn.
The kind who'd never tell you how they felt?
You serious?
That's how I made friends.
Hang in there and do your best!
Do your best!
And now,
we're accepting requests for advice from you.
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique,
personally signed request fulfilled sticker!
You got it.
So please send in your submissions!
We're waiting for them!
I said it!
You said it!
I said it without stumbling!
Nice!
Yay!