Hey, you two are too close to the TV.
Get back a little.
'Kay!
Didn't you say you would get back?
Do it. Now.
'Kay!
What would you two like to eat?
'Ka—
Owie!
Pay attention!
You'll ruin your eyesight if you binge like that.
Objection, Your Honor!
What is it?
We were just watching.
We weren't binging or anything.
Objection denied. Stop quibbling and be quiet.
That looks fun...
The Next Day
Hello.
Bad news, Choco-sen!
Okay, keep it down!
Rushia and Watame are on a TV binge!
Again?
They're not even watching!
They won't even budge!
Did you try detergent?
They're not grease!
Literally glued to it!
Oh, I have an idea.
You two cicadas?!
Naughty, naughty girls.
Maybe the TV should go.
Please, no!
Wadda waj deebee!
Wanna watch TV!
Their faces are a mess...
If I see you glued to it again, it's gone.
Okay!
We'll keep our distance!
The Next Day
Maybe I should sneak a peek first.
wham
Dumb and Dumber!
Ru-chan, it's almost time.
Time for television, huh?
What are they so hooked on?
Time for Next Tambourine Club!
What the hell?!
hei! hehei! tanbarin kurabu!
Hey! Hey, hey! Tambourine Club!
aitsu no akarusa sanshain!
So bright, it's almost sunshine!
hei!
Hey!
hei! hehei!!! tanbarin kurabu!!
Hey! Hey, hey! Tambourine Club!
The heck? That actually looks kind of fun...
To the world of tambourine!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!