Secret Society holoX: The Founder
The one who established Secret Society holoX.
She was originally known for her vast power and intelligence,
but most of it is now sealed away.
She is vaguely aware of the debilitating nature of her shackles
but does not remember when or how they got there.
The crow by her side is a long-time companion.
Birthday: May 25 / Height: 139 cm
Secret Society holoX: The XO
The executive officer of Secret Society holoX.
As holoX's point of contact
and the one in charge of external affairs,
she is the de facto leader of the group,
handling matters that the founder cannot.
While she may seem aloof
and standoffish at first glance,
she is a compassionate person
who cares a lot for her subordinates.
Unfortunately, she is also rather prone
to screwing up in crucial moments.
Birthday: June 11 / Height: 161 cm
Secret Society holoX: The Researcher
The one in charge of R&D in Secret Society holoX.
As part of her studies into human behavior,
she meddles in the other members' affairs
and tries to help them out at every turn.
Possessed by an insatiable thirst for knowledge,
she may sometimes also deliberately
mess with people just to see how they react.
The self-proclaimed "brains of the operation."
Her areas of expertise, however, are pretty limited.
Birthday: March 15 / Height: 153 cm
Secret Society holoX: The Cleaner (Intern)
An intern who acts as a fixer and cleaner for Secret Society holoX.
Calm and composed at all times, she carries out
her orders without so much as batting an eyelid.
She loves music and can be found
listening to it every chance she gets.
And while she denies it vehemently,
she apparently tends to come across as guarded.
Birthday: May 18 / Height: 148 cm
Secret Society holoX: The Bodyguard
Secret Society holoX's insurance policy.
Hailing from a remote mountainous area,
she left her home behind and, along with her companion,
set off on a journey to achieve her dream of
seeing and learning more about the outside world.
Nowadays, she handles security detail and bodyguard
missions for holoX, making enough money to get by.
Birthday: June 18 / Height: 156 cm