"So thick and sticky...
"Aah..."
"(3) Peach boobies licky licky!"
Whaa...?
She's very cute.
lol
Our next segment is
A Love Letter from Nene!
It's finally time!
This will be the last time
we have this segment.
So sad!
So in this segment
Rules
I send a love letter to another one of the girls,
then everyone guesses what they wrote in their reply.
The contents of this letter will be turned into a quiz.
It's a quiz where you fill in the blanks.
Fill in the blanks!
Watame-senpai, Subaru-senpai, and all our viewers
will be guessing.
With that said,
let's take a look at the letter that I sent to Flare-senpai.
Yeah!!
Here it is!
To Flare-senpai,
"So thick and sticky...
"Aah...
"The strong, sticky bonds that we formed together on Bonjour..."
Cut
"Please yell out a dirty phrase!
"Ready, go!"
That was the love letter that I sent her!
And this is the reply
that she sent back!
Oh?
▽Reading the question▽
"To Nene-chan,
"I can't believe you actually sent me a letter!
"Actually, I often get told that my retorts come off a little strong
"and that I come across as scary at first, but
"(1) ???????"
"I really love you
"...you"
...love you
Can we please just move on already?
▽Reading the question▽
"Give it a break!
"Why do you want to know what my shampoo smells like, anyway?
"You're going to (2) ????, aren't you?
"Like some kind of (2) ???? !
"About your new outfit,
"(3) ?????? !"
"From, Flare"
Amazing.
None of that sunk in at all.
Hehehe.
Ahahaha!
Hahaha!
Now, please reveal your answers!
Okay!
Then, let's start with Subaru-senpai. Please go ahead.
(1) "You're always cheerful and kind, and I really love you for that."
(2) "Why do you want to know what my shampoo smells like, anyway?"
(2) "You're going to come dry my hair, aren't you?"
(2) "Like some kind of kinky porno!"
(3) "About your new outfit... boobehs!"
That's it.
I see.
I feel like the "like some kind of kinky porno!" part
is something that Marine's mentioned before...
Hmm...
I guess the overall message is pretty close.
Next Watame-senpai, please read yours.
"But you're never afraid and hang out with me anyway,
"and I really love you for that."
"Why do you want to know what my shampoo smells like, anyway?
"You're going to rub it on yourself, aren't you?
"Like some kind of pervert!"
On my body?!
Yeah.
"About your new outfit,
"(3) Peach boobies licky licky!"
Wha...?
Please don't react like that!
Watameh...?
Don't look at me like that!
I think Watame-senpai's answer to (1) was closer.
Oh, really?
Yeah,
but for the other ones,
both your answers were really funny so I'll give you both full marks.
What's with that?! (mad)
Because they were funny?
And lastly we'll take a look
at what Flare-senpai actually wrote.
"You always approach everything in a bright and positive manner,
"and I really love you for that.
"Give it a break!
"Why do you want to know what my shampoo smells like, anyway?
"(2) You're going drink it, aren't you?
"(2) Like some kind of weird fetish!"
That's totally different!
"Weird fetish"!
"About your new outfit,
"the boobs area is super lewd!"
(3) Actual answer: The boobs area is super lewd!
(3) Subanswer: Boobehs!
Isn't that pretty much what I wrote?
Yeah, but,
the way she wrote "super lewd" is lewd in itself.
Professor Watame,
what do you think?
Is Flare lewd for saying it's "super lewd"?
"That's nothing." - Tsunomaki Watame
She has to do the licky lick at the very least.
Right? You have to licky lick at the very least,
if you want to call yourself a real pervert.
Note: Shiranui Flare has never claimed to be a pervert
We have received special permission to air this today.
That's right. She hasn't even made it to the start line.
The next segment is,
"I want to see all their nice parts"
Old Man Watame's Best Pictures Quiz
Old Man Watame!
I've been waiting for this!
In this segment,
Rules
Pick a screenshot from A to D
of the four images shown,
one of them is a picture that I, Tsunomaki Watame,
saw on a stream and thought, "Oh, nice!"
Oh, nice...
and took a screenshot.
It's a quiz where you guess which one is my favorite shot.
Correct answer
I chose one of the images,
and the other three were chosen by management.
I see.
And the next best shot, is one of these.
Which one is it?!
I'll definitely get it this time!
Whoa! It's Aqua!
In the same generation
Sorry 'bout that.
About what?!
So, which one is my favorite?!
Umm...
Hmmm?
This is pretty hard isn't it?
This is a super hard choice!
Time's up!
Viewers' responses
Oh, D!
Hey, D!
Right? D sure is great, isn't it?
No, it's not!
Is there any point to this being Aqua?!
It's just boobehs!
That's all it is!
Yeah, that is kind of true.
So moving on from that, the one I picked was...
Eh? Don't you have to see our answers too?
For sure!
Ah, yeah.
Forgot
Old Man Watame?!
Sorry, sorry.
We picked different ones.
We did too.
Nene-chan, what did you write there?
Shy boobs.
Shy boobs!
Hahaha!
New vocab!
What the heck?
Is that Nene-nese?
Hahaha!
No, not at all!
It's nationally recognized Japanese.
There's no way that's true!
Don't lie!
I think that
Aqua looks the cutest in B
so I chose B.
I couldn't decide. I was stuck between B and C as well.
My answer is...
The answer is?
Please!
I'll get it this time!
Come on!
It's A!
This is too hard!
Well, like...
Wh...
Why would you pick this?
I guess... Umm...
I just wanted to see up her skirt...
I just wanted to see...
I wanted to see so bad...
And I...
I ended up taking a screenshot...
I just wanted to see so bad.
So Old Man Watame, you like...
decide just by looking at their body.
Is it all right to sum it up like that?
I look at their expression too,
but yeah I mostly decide by looking at their body.
So it is the body after all!
90% of the time...
You pretty much decide just by
looking at their body.
Yeah!
That's right.
I decide about 99.9% based on their body.
Next up, we have Subaru-senpai's segment.
Subaru's School of Retorts!
It's finally time!
This'll be fun!
Umm...
In this segment,
I've had some clips of
hololive members' streams prepared
Rules
that we can make retorts to.
I see.
We're going to watch these clips together
and see if you can make the same comment I'm thinking of.
Guess Subaru's retort!
Basically, in this segment I want all of you
to guess what kind of retort I'm going to make.
I see!
And now, moving onto our last clip.
Here it is!
Mel is so cute.
Yozora Mel?
Hmm, yeah.
She's very cute.
Hahahaha!
Ahahaha!
She's a cute genius that lives in the demon world
and she's a very pure vampire girl.
However, she is not into blood.
She prefers acerola juice.
Pffhahaha...
This gag grows on you.
She also has a reputation for having wonderful boobs.
What a shock!
So that was our clip.
It's chock full of things to comment on.
Now,
please sum up this video in one phrase.
Which part do we even start?
So, with this,
it's probably easier if you think about
the whole thing rather than "which part".
The whole thing, huh?
Also Mel-senpai,
you should probably consider her standing
as a senpai as well.
Think about "Mel-senpai" while you think of your retort.
Ah...
Let's start with Nenechi!
Okaaay!
Please tell us your answer.
Here's the clip!
I feel so mellow!
Thanks to you, Mel.
What a tenpai!
Let's look at what you wrote.
It's easier to understand in writing.
This is what she wrote.
I mixed the words "genius" (tensai) and senpai together to make
"What a tenpai!" (genius senpai)
Are you a genius?
This is absolutely genius!
The idea to mix the words "genius" and "senpai" together...
Yeah! (?)
Watame is starting to make some pretty sharp retorts too though...
Yeah...
Let's see how Watame's progressed,
and take a look at her answer.
I feel so mellow!
Thanks to you, Mel.
Mel-senpai, where were you trying to go with this?
So harsh!
But it was pretty good.
It was a nice, sharp...
I was...
trying to take a good stab at her.
Taking a stab!
And now, I'll share my answer too!
What did Master write...
Master...
Mel-senpai, something bothering you?
Answer: Is something bothering you?
Ah, you were so close Watame-senpai!
I was thinking like,
"I should probably draw the line here?"
It's a gentle retort.
Well, I was actually thinking,
"Where were you trying to go with this?"
but I tried to make it a little softer.
Like, I'll just put this away.
Nenechi's, umm...
sudden gag/retort was super funny,
and Watame's...
"kick them while they're down" retorts were just...
No more nice Watame...
No more nice Watame!
Your razor sharp retorts were really funny too.
I think it'd be great
if the two of you could develop on this.
Yes, Teach!
Okay!
Understood!
BONUS
Q12: What sport do you like?
What sport do you like?
Mixed martial arts!
Q13: What have you eaten today?
Eh? What?
Miiii...xed... Martial... Arrrrrrrr.....
Nene, have you just come out of the shower?
"Sniff, sniff!" (deep breaths)
Aahh...sss
It's just the best!
What was with that "Aah"s?
Did you become one with the planet?
No! lol
By the way, what fragrance shampoo do you two use?
Sunflower
Aah...
Oh!
That's what it is...
Ewwww...
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub channel
on NicoNico for the full stream archives!
Officer, over here! She's the one!