Suisei Train goes choo, choo, choo...
You wanna get on, don'tchu, choo, choo!
Suisei... Train?
You! The Kanata over there!
How would you like a ride on the Surly Suisei Train?
That was you being surly?
Weren't you singing and stuff?
No mood lasts forever, okay?
Scariest look ever!
Anyway, you should give it a shot. Come on.
O-Okay.
What the...
Okay, hang on tight.
Suisei Train has...
left the station!
Yaaaaaaaaaaaaaay!
We've arrived.
How'd you like it?
Oh, you had so much fun,
you're in seventh heaven?
I caught a glimpse of my homeland!
What's with all this childish crap?
I-It's you!
Marine Bike!
It's a tricycle!
Kanatan, don't you think mine's a fancier ride?
But... it's a tricycle.
I know that, dammit!
But everybody's first time
is with a tricycle!
Eek! I'm sorry!
And hell, that's just cardboard!
Okay, but I've got the Midas touch.
What's that mean?
Enough is enough.
I-It's you!
Botan Racing!
Where'd you even get that?!
Neither of your rides look durable.
You can't win this fight
if you ain't souped up right.
What fight?!
But I worked so hard to paint this thing!
And this tricycle was expensive!
Why's it hitting them so hard?!
There you are, Shishiron!
Gah, Momosuzu Nene!
Give back my DeLorean!
Don't wanna!
I don't care!
I need it to win the lottery!
Don't wanna!
Zoom!
What was that all about?
We can't let this stand.
Let's get out there and race!
Bring it!
Uh, it's raining outside.
Okay, Old Maid it is!
The Rainy Season Ends
Pretty early this year, huh?
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!