Hello, everyone!
I brought cards! Let's play!
Yay!
I'll put my spot as idol on the line.
We're all idols here!
I shall put up Shishiron's very soul.
Good!
Leave the poor soul alone!
No bets. Let's just play normally.
Loser gets a dare, then.
Huh?
Speak Like a Spoiled Rich Girl for a Month
I can't afford to lose this!
Jingisukan for a Month
Don't wanna be last! Don't wanna be last!
No Booze for a Month
I've barely recovered since Daifuku
took away all my booze the other week!
Limited to 2 Extra Servings of Beef Bowl
Why are you being so soft on yourself?!
Boo! Hiss!
No Beef Bowls for a Month
I never should've suggested
a dare for the loser.
And so began a fierce battle
of Old Maid.
The card on the right is mine!
Are you sure you want that one?
Let it go!
You're so obvious.
My killer instinct says this one.
Pick one and go!
Yikes. They're way too into this.
Which one? Right... no, left?
Actually, right? But then I go left.
Wait, stop.
I shouldn't overthink this.
This is a 50 percent game.
1 or 0, yes or no,
other girls or Flare.
If it's between other girls and Flare, I'd pick Flare.
Get a move on, Noel-senpai.
There!
Fffff...
Hmph.
Dun!
Aww...
Game over. No beef bowls for a month for you.
Senpai!
Eek!
This is for Subaru-senpai!
We swapped bodies!
Wow! I want to swap places
with my booze too!
Lamy!
Things got a little out of hand...
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!