One culprit prevails!
Yikes.
Help, Super Sleuth!
What's up, little lamb?
Forcing her juniors to call her that?
The carrots in my hair are gone!
Okay, that is big trouble.
Begin investigation!
Fanservice In Progress
Hmm...
I played darts with them yesterday.
Maybe they're still there.
Hi-yah
It was you?!
Thanks, Super Sleuth!
There's no mystery I can't solve.
Why're you acting smug over that?
And put that pipe away! It's bad for you!
Fine.
Help, Super Sleuth!
The game is afoot! Let's go, sidekick!
Ugh, she was talking to me!
I lost my bag and purse.
File a report with the cops.
Have you no pride?!
Thank you very much!
When the going gets tough...
...you send your client packing.
Emergency, Super Sleuth!
I'm on the case!
There's been a murder!
Tomato Juice
Ghosts need to complete their tasks too
We have a bloody corpse!
Hmm? What's up?
Investigate the case!
Uh...
I can't handle blood, sorry.
What kind of detective are you?!
Hang on!
I've got an ace up my sleeve!
I introduce to you Pupper Sleuth!
What's the point of you, then?!
Go on, Josephine! Get deducting!
She was stabbed in the head
with this pipe.
I believe it was used as a projectile.
The killer is among us!
Hello, police?
The Oozora Police Force is no joke.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!