Hm?
What's wrong?
Take a step with both feet!
What does that mean?
Sui-chan will never give me anything in return,
but I can't live without her!
An unsettling relationship
Coming up is...
the next segment of the show!
What?!
Omaru Polka's
Rescue Operation!
Yaaay!
In this segment,
we'll watch clips of me flopping
Rules
Scene where Polka bombed
and see what you might've done in that situation.
What would you have done?
Is there even any hope here?
What should I have done instead?
Let's salvage Polka's flops!
It's a segment where you think of ways to rescue me!
Roll the tape!
Hm?
WARNING: Beware of secondhand embarrassment
"Where is this underworld that
Leader Tokki is going to?"
Streamed on 2021/04/22
[Legend of Polka] I didn't want anyone to find out!!
"That's actually...
a place they built next door,
called 'The Underworld'."
"What's up with that?"
"Aqua. I'll go home for a bit."
"Those girls came, I see...!"
"Shrinking down"
"Waaaarh!"
"Tokki?!"
Tokki became smaller here.
Tokki became smaller.
Tokki?
By the way, this is from
the video series I'm making, Legend of Polka.
It's from the momentous very first episode.
I read a manga I drew during my regrettable childhood.
Huh...
It's from the very first episode!
Right...
Hm?
What's wrong?
It seems fine. Perfect for a first video.
POLMAO
I'm ready!
Oh, you actually wrote something for me!
Yeah.
You're so kind!
Mel-chan is also ready, by the way.
Yeah!
You guys are amazing!
I might actually cry now!
I've never seen such kind responses...
Let's just get going.
Let's start going through them.
Yeah.
Yup!
First is Suisei-senpai's answer.
Yup.
Here it is.
Boom.
Stay true to yourself.
Mel-senpai...
Yup!
Ta-da!
If only you'd met me when you were a child.
Ah...
Ah~...
Yeah.
Ooooh...
What?
You're flopping, you're flopping!
OooOoOoOooH!
Wait,
I'm feeling emotional!
Let me feel a bit emotional!
There's no need to get emotional right now.
I'm not flopping at all!
But you know...
I'm just so happy right now!
Yeah, but,
if you're going to be flopping...
I want to see you keep on flopping.
Wow, that's, uh...
kinda scary.
Just make flopping your whole personality.
But yeah,
those people definitely exist.
Yeah, for sure!
I... understand.
Yeah.
Wow...
I just took a screenshot so hard.
A screenshot...?
She's feeling emotional.
She's being emotional?
I should've stayed true to myself,
and I should've met Mel-senpai when I was a kid.
I think what you need the most right now, Pol-chan,
is a gadget to help you time travel.
Yeah.
Oh man, this is going to take a long time.
It's gonna be a long battle,
but the two of you will fight with me, right?
Thank you both.
That's gonna be it
for my segment for this month's show!
Hell on earth ends here
Stay tuned for the next episode of
hell on earth
All right!
I feel like many other things inside me just ended.
Thanks for watching!
Let's start off our next segment!
Genius Vampire Test!
Title card.
Yaaay!
Yay!
This is Mel-senpai's segment! Please tell us about it!
Mel-senpai!
Okay!
In this segment,
Rules
A middle school-level quiz
you just have to fill out a middle school-level quiz
and see how much you can score!
How much can you score?
I see!
Yup.
Definition: An awesome person.
Kind of a big deal.
But you know...
I'm a genius vampire from the Underworld,
so there's no way I can be wrong!
Right...
Of course!
Right?
R-Right.
Yeah.
The Law of Mel-senpai.
Yup, that means...
all of my responses become the right answer!
Mel's answer is always correct
Every other answer is wrong!
Okay!
Got it!
Let's take a look at the first problem, then!
Okay!
Here it is!
Complete the following computation.
Okay.
We have to think about it like an Underworlder.
Yeah.
I've actually already submitted my answer.
But, well...
I'm pretty sure I'm right!
I'm pretty sure we can agree on this one too.
It's just the first question, right?
I think we can agree on this.
Let's start from Sui-chan's answer!
Okay!
Here!
2.
What?!
What?
2!
No way...
Is it not 2?
Let's see what everyone's saying.
Lots of confusion in chat.
It's not 2?
Apparently it's correct to humans.
Wait, this has to be 2, right? Right?
You scared me just now.
Is it 2 or not?
It's 2 in the human realm.
You don't know what the correct answer is yet.
Oh, oh!
This is correct in the human realm.
Yup.
Next up is Polka-chan!
Okay.
Here.
Oh...
But—
The "2" is technically right.
Can you explain yourself to me? What's this?
Polka gets called out
It feels like being called outside by my boss.
Please explain yourself.
What's this?
Why am I being called out by
Suisei-senpai instead of Mel-senpai?
I'm telling you,
It's (-4)-(-6), so...
-2. Perfect!
And there were parentheses,
so I added those too to round it out!
Hm...
Oh...
Isn't this backwards?
This is (-6)-(-4), isn't it?
Huh?
Take four from six...
But if you take four away from six...
Wait, it turns into a plus?!
What...
Well, I want to see Mel-chan's answer now.
All right, and my answer is...
here!
Huh?!
What?
You answered 2?!
I'm right!
Sui-chan managed to answer correctly!
Oh, yes!
I got it!
Come on...
I did it!
I told you!
It doesn't matter if you're a human
or if you're from the Underworld.
By the way, Pol-chan...
were you actually trying here?
I was!
I was serious!
You didn't get it wrong on purpose
thinking I'd get it wrong?
Of course... not.
Right.
I took the longest to answer everything!
You were thinking about it for a super long time.
Both Mel-chan and I didn't even need ten minutes.
Yeah.
You two were just pumping answers out.
I was like, "What's going on there?!"
Let's move on to our next segment!
What could it be?
Wish Away Your Worries Upon a Shooting Star!
Tell us about your segment, Suisei-senpai!
Okay!
Since I'm here,
I get to host my own segment!
For this segment,
Rules
our viewers have sent in some minor problems
they have in their daily lives.
Every single thing my beloved shooting star does
is so precious, I'm starting to get addicted to her!
What do I need to do to actually develop an addiction?
Befitting of a shooting star, I've come up with quick and haphazard solutions to those problems,
Suisei's answer
Don't get addicted
and you'll try to predict what they are!
Suisei's answer
???
Guess Suisei's answer!
That's the quick rundown of what we're going to be donig!
Oh, that sounds great.
Yup!
Here's our next problem.
Here!
Ta-da.
Hey!
When I walk, I don't know whether
to start with my right foot
or to start with my left foot.
Which foot should I step forward with first?
Okay.
Okay then! Your thinking time starts...
That's cute. How old is this person?
now!
Wha are you all gowin to say?
Wha?
You'll find out in a bit!
It's a vewy hard pwoblem.
Couldn't tell what they were saying
Whaaa?
Huh?
You know, wike maybe...
a baby sent us this pwoblem.
A baby!
It's from a baby?!
He might be taking his fiwst steps.
So he hasn't even started walking yet?
He's probably thinking about the future.
"Once I'm able to walk,
which foot should I start with?
Is my first step gonna be with my left or right foot?"
I think that's it.
Wow, we have to decide
something that important for him?
That's just my theowy!
Let's start fwom Mel-san's answer, then?
Got it!
Here you go!
Wha-Wha...?
Take a step with both feet!
Wha does dat mean...?
A jump?
A jump.
It's a jump!
Take off!
Wow!
Take off?
Wooow!
Take a step with both feet, and then take off?
Wow!
I see.
Pol-san's turn, then.
If you don't know which foot to use,
just step forward with both feet!
That's true!
If you're not sure, just pick the neutral option.
Exactly!
Works for all problems.
"Neutral" means both feet...?
It's a compromise.
You compromise by using both feet...?
What's your compromise, Pol-san?
Uh, well, here's mine.
Okay.
Don't think about it.
Don't think!
Is this something that requires thought?
Is this your own response?
Or what you think I thought?
They both happened to be the same!
I see!
Yup.
I see, I see.
I was like, "I think it's like this. Right, Sui-chan?"
And you were like, "Yeah! Totally!"
Oh, just in your head—
Oh, she's completely addicted to me.
She's hallucinating about me now.
She's seeing things.
Sui-chan will never give me anything in return
but I can't live without you!
An unsettling relationship
Let's take a look at my answer.
Here it is!
Okay, next problem!
Hm?
Whaaat?!
What?
Oh god, oh god, oh god!
She didn't write anything!
Ha ha ha
Oh god, oh god, oh god!
Extras
How did you come up with 2.18x?
Oh, I just added everything.
You added the 2 as well?
Yup!
I added everything.
Just add, huh?
By the way, the human answer to this
is x=27.
Two seven.
Huh?
Why?! Why?! Why?!
Why?
Wait, why—
Teach me, humans.
Human...?
Paging all humans.
Humans?
You're the host of a 24-hour program!
What's the show's slogan?
If there was some 24-hour program,
it could be, "Suisei saves the world!"
or something.
Oh!
I get it!
How about, "It's your shooting star...
incoming, about to destroy the world."
That makes it sound like
you're actually a shooting star!
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub channel on NicoNico for the full stream archives!