Oh, she's picking a fight!
You want a piece of me?
The hell're you saying,
no way she'd do that!
You're like two minions and the boss.
Starring:
Nakiri Ayame
Nekomata Okayu
Uruha Rushia
This show is brought to you
by Nakiri Ayame...
Tch...
...Nekomata Okayu...
...and Uruha Rushia!
This is a place where the spokespersons
for angry things assemble:
The World of Rage Acting!
Today as well, the three girls have
come together, brimming with anger!
The hell is this place?
I can't hold it anymore...
Are you kidding me?
I'm so pissed!
Man...
I'm gonna bite someone's head off!
I'm so livid!
I'm done, I'm so freaking done...
Ohh, you bastard!
I'm done!
I'm so hecking mad right now!
Are you for real?!
I'll burst!
They're so angry that
they can hold it no longer!
Ya talkin' to me?
Wanna go?
What's your problem, can't you
see how pissed we are?
Ah, sorry, I apologize...
I'm so mad that I'm gonna...
crack.
Crack?
What happened to you?
Here are the rules for today:
All of you one by one will have
to act as something and flip out.
The other two will have to guess
what that person is acting as.
The International Society of Rage World will grant
to the one who will show us the best fit of rage
the title of the Rage Acting Queen!
It's a world-renowned title!
Such a distinguished honor!
The hell is that?
No one told me about that!
First one will be... Nakiri Ayame-san!
Can I just go berserk right from the start?
What is she acting as?!
Nakiri Ayame's fit of rage!
What is Ayame-san acting as?
Start the rage!
Every damned day you just keep
punching me... Well, not punching...
You're pressing me too damn much!
Like...
Pressing?
You know...
Your slams and hits...
they're quite painful, you know!
And also...
Raise a voice if you think you got it.
Dirt just keeps piling up in the gaps...
What is it?
Would be nice if you cleaned me once in a while!
Dirt?
Gaps?
What is she on about?
Dust piles up too...
Just makes me blow a fuse!
I think I got it.
Oh? What's it, Okayu-san?
People often slam tables, so could it be...
Rushia-chan's table?
A personal item?
Rushia's?
Sadly, that's a wrong answer!
What else was there...
You also often show me off,
doing those
clickety-clackety things.
I'd like for you to not do that, yeah.
I think I got it!
Yeah, you better stop it.
Oh! Rushia-san!
A PC mouse?
Ah—
That's also wrong.
But...!
Wrong?
I got it! I got it!
Was I close?
Hm?
A keyboard.
Oh!
Ah...
That's correct, Okayu-san!
You got it!
That "clickety-clackety..."
Ah, that part...!
Ah...
What's up with that?
I slid in a hint around the third part, yeah.
Not bad.
How kind of you.
That was a kind rage.
Next up is Nekomata Okayu-san.
What is she acting as?!
Nekomata Okayu's fit of rage!
What is Okayu-san acting as?
Start the rage!
Hey, hey, hey, stop rubbing my head,
it's damn hot!
Hot!
Hot?
And stop erasing
all that stuff by rubbing me!
I got it!
Oh?
Huh?
Ayame-san, please!
It's an eraser, right?
Oh, that's right!
Correct!
Wow, that was quick!
Wow, how did you guess it?
Heck yeah!
What gave it away?
Amazing!
The head rubbing part.
I see, I see.
Ah, got it. Rubbing the head
leads to erasing things, right?
Yeah, that!
That "erasing" was like a direct hint.
Very skillful.
I thought it was some bathing accessory.
So far, Rushia-san was like, you know,
Wooow...
carefully observing.
Oh, she's picking a fight!
Oh, a fight?
You want a piece of me or what?
I might not make it out alive.
Are you gonna let this one slide?
She's done for.
You're like two minions
and the boss.
What is she acting as?!
Uruha Rushia's fit of rage!
What is Rushia-san acting as?
Start the rage!
Stop staring at me all the time!
Huh?
Starting, huh.
That's it?
Don't leave—
Don't leave me on, it's hot, dammit!
Got it!
Oh? How quick!
Ayame-san?
Not sure, but...
A TV?
Oh, TV is...
Oh, hmm...
incorrect!
Not that, huh.
Me, me!
Hm?
A PC?
Is it a PC?
No, but close.
Also incorrect!
It's not a PC.
And stop dropping me here and there,
it freaking hurts!
I can break, you know!
Figured it out!
Oh?
A smartphone!
And that's correct!
Correct!
Yay!
"Stop dropping" has to be
what gave it away, right?
Yeah, exactly. That one.
It was a pretty big hint.
Do you drop your phone often,
Ayame-senpai?
I do, I drop it a lot!
That's expected.
It just slides out of my hands all the time.
Don't you also drop it
quite often, Rushia-san?
I don't, though?
Oh, you don't, I see.
Who do you think she is?
Sorry, I'm sorry!
The hell're you saying,
no way she'd do that!
Did you blow off some steam, Rushia-san?
Is there anything on your right?
It wasn't enough for you, after all...
Huh?
Are you listening?
I was looking at lava!
Ah, lava!
It was quite lacking!
Lacking...
You wanted to go for more?
Yeah.
Want to go one more time, then?
Are you trying to knock me down
by making my blood boil or what?
Your blood...?
What—
What's going on?
Once more, since she didn't have enough!
Uruha Rushia's fit of rage!
Rushia-san...
Yeah!
Don't stare at me!
Huh?
Do I need to introduce you again?
She's ready to start, come on!
What are you waiting for? Come on!
What is Rushia-san acting as?
Start the rage!
Stop staring at me!
That again...
Similar to the previous, huh?
What can it be?
I... might be for a show, but stop glaring!
What's that all about?
Cut it out!
I know!
Oh?
I figured it out!
What is that, Okayu-san?
Huh?
It's Uruha Rushia!
That's not it!
Quite a philosophical answer, but nope.
For a show but not for glaring?
Something flashy?
How do you even have the nerve
to make something even taller than me!
She's quite cautious about it.
Something tall?
Tall?
Don't climb me
if you're gonna pee your pants!
That high?
Recently there's been...
something...
Yes?
Something even taller than me!
I see! So you lost your title, right?
Who the hell do you think you are?
It was your pride.
Ah, I got it!
Don't come to compare!
Tokyo Tower?
Wow, how?!
Congratulations!
That indeed is Tokyo Tower!
Oh wow!
Amazing!
How did I guess it?
That was incredible.
I'm speechless.
Ayame-san might as well be
the Guessing Queen.
I might have a knack for that.
Most likely.
Sadly, we don't have that kind of title here.
But you were stunning today.
Whaaat?!
Then go and make one! Right now!
Okay, okay, I will!
Results
The very first title of
Rage Acting Queen goes to...
Nekomata Okayu,
who excelled at acting as an eraser!
Congratulations!
Rage Acting Queen
Nekomata Okayu
Congrats!
Huh? I don't need it, though!
I never asked for this!
Reasoning: She accurately laid out her anger
I thought she really aced it.
Like, her ability to lay out the problem.
I agree. You realize it instantly
when you notice the hints.
Yeah, she really nailed it.
If you can see it,
you figure it out right away.
I'll erase all of you with that eraser!
Say your goodbyes!
If you enjoyed this video,
please subscribe to hololive'sofficial
YouTube channel and smash that like button.
Lastly, let's all angrily say goodbye.
Bye-bye!
Huh? You call that "rage"?
"Bye-bye!"? Really?
Are you picking a fight?
If you want to see more, check out our channel.
Wanna go or something?
Starring:
Nakiri Ayame
Nekomata Okayu
Uruha Rushia
This show was brought to you by Nakiri Ayame...
Tch...
...Nekomata Okayu...
...and Uruha Rushia!