One day, we were barbecuing it up on the moon.
It's summer and all, y'know?
Uh, hold up.
No, listen, I get it.
You wanna know why we're on the moon, right?
Who are you talking to?
Let me explain.
We made the long trip from Earth
to solve humanity's greatest mystery:
"Is there a bunny on the moon?"
Nah, nobody cares.
Earth to crater...
'Ello! Anybody home?!
But you know...
Why bring a BBQ set to the moon?
BBQing while gazing at animals
would be quite poignant, no?
Did you leave your empathy back in the office?
Look, a bunny!
P... Pekora-chan?!
Gotcha.
Perché?
It's summer, y'know?
That explains nothing!
Hey, wait!
Stop! Hear me out!
I come bearing gifts!
I brought you something useful!
Yeah, right. Bet it's something stupid.
Ta-dah! A spaceship...
AkiRose in need is AkiRose indeed!
...themed slot machine.
...
Wait, timeout!
Let's do this.
"I thought we could finally go home...
Obviously, it was too good to be true.
But having recreation in this hellhole with
nothing but craters and a BBQ set was a big respite.
5 stars from me."
Quit playing!
How are we supposed to make it out of here?
Calm down.
For now, enjoy some BBQ while
gazing at my bunny ears.
Not helping!
-10 HP
...
No BBQ is complete without lemon, eh?
Right?
Hey! Your clothes are on fire!
The moon's on fire too!
I repeat: The moon. is. on fire!
Ever since that day,
our world came to have two suns in the sky.
The fox days of summer continue!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!