Offence is the best defence!
She landed it!
Take this fist o' mine!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Summer's here...
So hot!
Our season has come, me hearties!
It is!
Do you all have a fond memory
from your summer breaks?
Me first! Me first!
I was really happy I finally got to
split a watermelon at the beach.
Watermelon Splitting
Ooh! Good for you!
How about Subaru?
I lined up a bunch of these mortar fireworks
and pretended to be a pyrotechnician.
Pretending to be a pyrotechnician
Don't try this at home.
That was my favorite memory!
You seem like you'd do it even now.
I don't!
How about Captain?
I was on an online drawing board,
and they were holding an original Pokemon contest.
I voted for myself several times and won.
You're a scumbag!
It was really fun!
That's not cool.
Also, has nothing to do with summer.
That's so nostalgic.
Let's go ahead and open up the store!
Okaaay!
And we already have a customer!
They see me rolling, they hatin'.
Yay, Botan-san!
Today's Guest:
Shishiro Botan
So you've come.
Welcome!
Shishiro Botan
Personality: Free-spirited. A little careless.
Hobby: Games
Finishing Move: Shishiro Kick!
MENT
LUCK
Today's guest is Shishiro Botan-san!
Her MENT is 5 stars.
Her mental fortitude is something to take note of.
She's got an unwavering mental fortitude
and a heart rivaling that of diamond.
Ooh!
Diamond's that gem that never breaks!
Um...
I'm completely okay with horror games.
Really?
Ooh.
Boo!
Wot?
Yeah, that was pretty tough just now.
How was your heart just now, Marine?
I could feel it shrinking.
She didn't get spooked at all!
You don't seem like you'd have any issues.
I have worries too!
Oh, you do?
Pardon me.
What kind of worry?
Well...
I'm growing this aquatic plant at home.
Really?
How cute of you.
The thing is...
it's not growing that much.
I see.
And seeing that, I realized,
"I haven't been growing much recently, either..."
A-Are you okay?
You doin' okay?
Is your mental health okay?
Are you really okay?
I'm starting to worry about your mental health.
Really?
I want to improve myself.
Ooh! She's critical of herself!
I see.
Leave it to us! And there we have our request!
Yeaaah!
Her problem is, in short:
She wants to actually feel like she's getting better at games!
...
Yaaay!
What was that silence about...?
Leave it to us!
We have the perfect game for you, Botan-chan!
Oh? What is it?
The game we recommend today is...
This!
Guilty Gear -Strive-!
Yaaay!
The fighting game so popular, both in and out
of Japan, that it has its own esports event,
Guilty Gear's latest entry, Guilty Gear -Strive-.
It has an innovative battle system, gorgeous animation,
and tactical battles for you to enjoy.
You're sure to fall in love with
the unique characters and diverse effects.
Botan-san, would you like to give it a try?
I do! I want to play!
I applaud your proactiveness.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Have you played a Guilty Gear game before, Botan-chan?
Nope! This is my first.
Ooh!
I'm excited to see how you fare.
Have you played a fighting game before?
No, I haven't.
But because I haven't, I think it'll help me improve.
Right.
Grow like your aquatic plant.
Like my aquatic plant.
Yeah!
On that note,
let's all have a match with her!
What?!
Botan's road to self-improvement!
Defeat Team Maruyama!
It's a trial for Botan!
Improve yourself by defeating Team Maruyama!
The rules are as simple as can be!
Botan runs the Team Maruyama gauntlet!
Can she improve match by match?
We'll test her to see how many matches she can win.
And lastly...
The final boss, Boss, is awaiting you at the end!
Find a way to improve yourself amidst the fierce matches!
Yaaay!
I'll bring this whole shop down!
Don't do it! It's your store!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Let's start off with a bit of practice!
Last-minute training in Dojo Mode
And so, they're doing last-minute training in Dojo mode!
Can the inexperienced Botan-san pull off the inputs?
Already?
Yeah!
There.
Ooh! You're so good!
Wow.
Team Maruyama is also full of beginners.
They're practicing for the gauntlet as well!
The first match is against Towa-san!
It's a battle between a lion and a devil!
I'm always being looked down on,
so I'll put her in her place today.
Ooh, big words.
She's unleashing her devilish aura.
There are all these handsome and pretty characters.
I'll go with Ky-san.
All right!
Okay!
I'll go with...
Jobana?
Jobana!
It's Giovanna
Whoa, she looks strong.
1st battle...
Fight!
It's habbening!
Looks like Condor is Condorejoicing too!
What?
Condor is Condorejoicing...
Condorejoicing, I see...
Say it with me next time.
Next time.
Now that it's cold in here...
It's cold, huh?
I'll heat us up with a fiery match!
Ah, nice idea.
That's our Towa-sama!
Right.
Yeah.
Pout...
She's sulking.
No one wants to play along...
Let's get started!
Let's!
Here we go!
All right!
I really don't wanna lose!
I won't lose!
He's cool.
He is.
That line fits him!
Duel...
Start!
That's one hell of a posture.
There!
The music is great.
She attacks.
Towa-sama's really aggressive.
Right?
She just keeps pressing.
Crap!
Towa-sama's so aggressive,
you wouldn't believe it's her first time!
The aggressive Towa.
She goes on the attack.
She's pressing hard.
Ahh!
This is an intense back and forth.
Subaru-senpai, who do you think will win?
This will become a battle of wills, probably.
Ahhh!
Go, go!
Take this!
Botan's in a pinch!
Don't lose out in will!
Their wills are quite the spectacle!
Ooh!
Towa-sama takes the first round
She landed it!
She did something!
The hyper-aggressive Towa-san
finished her off elegantly at the end.
Botan-chan, you want to win, right?
I do!
Go get 'er!
Towa-sama's pretty aggressive, so...
I have to, like,
win out in spirit cause she's scary.
Botan-chan, how about you guard and go for a counter?
Yeah, you have the option to block and then hit them back.
Counters do lots of damage
I see.
Be as underhanded as you can be!
Sure.
She's being really aggressive,
so you can block her, then counter.
Are none of you rooting for me?
She blocks, but gets hit right after.
Talk about me too!
Towa-sama, you'll keep going
even if we don't tell you anything.
Yeah.
Nooo! Stop it!
Nice!
Nooo! Stop that!
She's using some cool-looking moves.
Her guarding is really—
Offence is the best defence!
She landed it!
What was that?!
She used a complicated move while button mashing!
Overdrive Super
Powerful special attacks that every character has
Impressive.
Is this what serious button mashing looks like?
Yay! Yay!
You're really good!
Can I end it?
Can I win with button mashing?
Nice, you're pushing her back!
Towa-sama, one more hit!
Wait! I can't land the last hit!
Don't lose focus!
Nice!
Yaaay!
I got kicked!
That was an insane battle...
Wow.
She was really aggressive.
What incredible talent.
Sorry I put you in your place.
Sorry about that.
Towa-sama's really good.
Botan-chan's seriously reflecting on the match.
I'm not, I'm not!
You okay?
It's just, she was amazing.
She was, right?
The super was the highlight!
Yeah.
Her next opponent is the manager
of an eSports team, Subaru-san!
I have a feeling she'll be strong.
I might make quick work of her.
But Botan-chan's also gotten better now, hasn't she?
I think I've gotten a little better.
That's true.
Want to pick the same characters?
Good idea!
Blue is Botan, Red is Subaru
The 2nd match is an unexpected mirror match!
They'll face off in different colors!
2nd battle...
Fight!
Condor is...
Condorejoicing...
Condorejoicing!
Uh-huh.
It's like...
I feel like I lost a part of me from that.
Why so?!
We're just enjoying our youth!
I'll do whatever underhanded methods it takes to win.
It's a mirror match!
How will this turn out?
You can do it!
You're guarding too!
Neither side is giving an inch.
Yeah.
Oh, nice hit.
Stahp!
She's got her ankles!
Oww!
Are they not gonna use the flame move?
I wanna—
Ah, you're right!
What was it called... Bonflame?
Flame!
Hell yeah!
Reverse Flame!
ARRRGH!
The Gun Flame she learned while practicing
Get her!
AHHH!
Burn her down!
One of those moves you want to use after learning
Stop doing that!
Just guard! Aren't you good at that?
I am guarding!
I wanna use Flame too!
Use your flame too.
You're not using it, Subaru-senpai!
Yeah!
Heeey! Stop that!
Don't steal my Flame from me!
It's a Flame buffet!
There it is!
Use other moves, too.
Ah, you used something!
Oh? Oh?!
That looked cool! What was that?
What was that?
Roman Cancel
Cancels your own attack while creating a shockwave that slows down the opponent's movement.
That looked cool just now.
Oh? Shishiro Botan, you almost have her!
You can do it!
Slobberknocker?
What a fierce fight...
Now this is a slobberknocker!
They don't have much time left on the clock!
Stop it!
Stop it, Botan-chan!
Stay on her!
Don't take my Gun Flame from me!
My Gun Flame!
Botan has the advantage
This is a close fight!
Four seconds left! Three!
Two!
You can just run now!
One!
NOOO!
Run awaaay!
Nice!
Why are you running?
Don't run away, Botan!
Here we go!
Well.
Well, well, well.
Will Botan-chan get her first win?
Well.
Just a little more!
Botan-san!
Opposite of Boss's thoughts,
Subaru-san came out on top in the intense second round.
It's starting to get exciting!
Botan doesn't get the consecutive win
It's time for the decisive third round!
The winner of this round will win the match!
Who will reign supreme?
Hey, don't dodge my Gun Flame!
A Gun Flame to start us off!
She keeps a solid guard.
You're getting good at defending,
so you can beat her if you attack.
Level Up
Botan's defence leveled up
Are you going for a Gun Flame?
AAAARGH!
Wait...
Subaru-senpai's going insane.
Either of them could win still.
This is getting heated. Subaru, stay focused!
They're pretty evenly matched.
Don't go on the defence! Attack!
That's...
That's easier said than done!
The aggressive one wins!
Really?
Go! Attack!
That was close!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Attack!
Don't worry about it! Attack!
Can Botan finish her off?
This is bad!
Just a little more!
Wait! My Gun Flame! Gun Flame!
Your Gun Flame!
My Gun Flame!
There it is! Gun Flame!
All right!
This is... Ah!
Heck yeah!
It's not looking good!
Shower blows on her!
Stay calm! You've got this!
OH SHI—
What the heck was that?!
A counter bursts forth!
Botan...
I wanted to fight you...
The winner of this life or death battle is Botan-san!
Congratulations on your first victory!
Her next opponent is Captain.
Watch out for the power of her sexiness.
3rd battle...
Fight!
You just have to win!
Is it time for... that?
Condor is...
Condorejoicing!
Thanks, everyone!
Your dying throes seem like they'd be noisy,
so let's settle it in the wastelands.
Uh-huh.
Wut?
Are you sure? There's no ocean here.
Your dying throes seem like they'd be—
Cuuute.
"You done talking?"
You done talking, Marine?
He's talkin' smack.
That's scary...
I'm a little scared.
What's she gonna start with?
What's your move?
She's already—She's already going on the attack.
Like this, right?
Nice! Nice!
Ah! This is bad!
Nice!
Ah, this is bad!
You're doing really good!
Steadily improving
Time out!
Oh? She threw her!
Go get her, Captain!
Captain's fighting back.
Go! Go!
Captain, do your best!
Wait, don't do it!
Wait.
Botan's so good.
Gun Flame's OP!
She's really—
Yeet!
She tosses her in anger!
Nice!
You're putting up a good fight!
Am I?
Yeah.
Ah, it's not working. My moves aren't working!
It's now a button mashing battle!
It's a button-mashing battle!
Take that!
Nice!
Mr. Dolphin...
I can't get Mr. Dolphin to come out!
Their HP is neck-and-neck.
Oh no, no, no, no!
You can do it!
This is a close battle!
It's really close!
Mr. Dolphin, please come help!
AAAH!
Happens.
I think I pressed it.
Which one of you
pressed the button?
What do I do?
What do I press?
Captain was the culprit
It's player 2.
Ah, we're good. Here I go.
Regroup and resume
Okay. Let's continue.
Start!
You can do it!
Please!
Some move! Any move!
Go for it!
She's got no health!
Only a sliver of health
Oh no!
They're both in trouble if they get hit once!
AHHH!
Marine...
Captain Marine!
Captain takes the first round
Captain!
You're better than I thought.
Nice one.
Either of them could still win!
The match isn't over yet, though.
Taste the power of my dolphin!
He's not coming out.
Summon him!
He's not coming out!
How do you use the dolphin?
Wait, what?
Hey.
The home screen came out instead
Hold on.
This is way too clumsy.
Marine...
Calm down.
Calm down!
Yes, I'm sorry.
You can't help getting that absorbed.
Stop summoning the home screen instead of the dolphin.
Ah! Wait!
I'm going with Gun Flame!
Use your Gun Flame!
Gun Flame!
You know, May-chan's voice sounds a little like—
Ah.
I keep pressing it!
Marine, don't cut me off!
I keep pressing it somehow!
You're pressing it too many times...
This is unreal.
I keep ending up pressing it!
Yeah... I'm sorry!
Forgive me!
It's fine.
Ah! Mr. Dolphin!
Dolphin!
Wait, that might've been the seal.
Mr. Dolphin!
I'M SO SORRY!
I'M REALLY SORRY!
Hey, seriously.
Can we just count this as my win?
Wait, please!
If she does it again.
Yeah, if she does it again.
Loud and clear.
I won't press it ever again. I promise.
Go! Go!
30 seconds left!
AAAAAAAH!
This is, uh...
And the winner is... Botan!
Let us play until the end at least!
👏👏👏👏
Let us play until the end...
Okaaay.
I think I got it! I keep pressing it cause I'm using this.
I'll change it to this! Okay?
Because of her oversized sleeves...
Okay.
I'm sowwy...
I'm really sowwy...
We'll really make Botan the winner next time.
Okay...
I'm sowwy...
I'll be more careful...
How will this turn out?
I'm messing up my inputs!
Nice one.
Nice combo.
Botan-chan, you can do it!
Yeah.
Captain's fighting against something else.
Try not to press it... Try not to press it...
This is getting close!
It's getting close!
Botan-chan might be in trouble.
Botan, there's no time!
Keep going!
Nice guard.
Captain.
Ahhh!
Botan-chan, this looks bad!
Ah, you're doing good.
Nice! Nice!
Will she be able to turn it around?
Ah, time's up.
Is this Captain's win?
Captain.
Waaah!
But Captain pressed the PS button too many times, so...
Those mental blows were devastating, huh?
I'm sorry!
This is, in essence, Botan's victory.
Yeah.
It's finally time to fight the final boss, Boss!
Just how good is she at fighting games?
It's time for the final battle!
Starting from the character selection!
I've already decided!
Potemkin!
I'll be fanning the Boss with these folding fans.
If I happen to lose, I'll close this store.
Wait, Boss?!
Closure notice?!
Boss?!
Are you sure about this?!
It's become quite the situation.
Neither side can back down
One last time, Condor is...
Condorejoicing!
Condorejoicing...
Condorejoicing.
You guys don't seem very excited.
Condorejoicing!
Condorejoicing.
Remember she's closing the store if she loses.
Heck yeah!
Condorejoicen't! Condorejoicen't!
Final battle...
Fight!
Can I take off my weights?
Your weights...
The nametag?
Can I open my eyes?
Ah, yeah. Sure.
Cheer for me!
Whoa, what is this place?
It's fitting for the final battle.
The stage is kinda...
What is this place?
Where are we?
A fitting place for the final battle.
He's so cool!
Just you wait for my character.
Ooh...
Thanks for waiting.
His pecs are huge.
He can talk!
He can talk?
He's really cool.
Think you'll be able to hit me?
Will he hit?
How cool!
He'd be pretty lame if he got hit now.
It'd be lame if I got hit.
You can't get hit, Botan-san.
Without further ado, start!
A-da-da-da-da-da-da-da!
Abadada!
Boss...
Boss is winging it!
A-da-da-da-da-da-da!
Boss, you're not landing anything!
Boss's fierce onslaught (None of it's hitting)
Boss...
Boss—
His—I see!
Boss, are you...
I see how it is!
Boss is mashing buttons at random!
Boss, are you...
Button mashing!
She's button mashing!
She sure is!
Button mashing-jing-a-ling!
She's overwhelming her even while button mashing!
Oh no!
She's overwhelming her with the build difference!
Seriously?!
Take this fist o' mine!
She's pressing her!
Boss!
Abadada@#$@^&@&@!
Boss, you're the loudest you've been today!
If you want this store, you'll have to get past me!
Boss!
A-da-da-da-da!
Botan-chan, you can't lose to her!
Boss, you're scaring me.
You're losing in willpower!
Yeah!
I'll finish you off with this move!
Take this!
It's not landing.
It's not—
AHHH!
She's not the Boss for nothing!
Boss is so good!
Botan-san,
you're being pushed back by Boss's aura.
You're right.
Release the aura of the king of the jungle.
That's right!
Here I go!
Go!
Don't even think about getting first blood!
Hey.
Boss, why are you the most energetic you've been all day?
A-da-da-da-da!
I'll avenge Subaru! This is for Subaru!
Avenge me!
And this is for Marine!
When you take a step back, Boss is just flailing around.
And this is for Towa!
Boss!
It missed!
You missed Towa's.
Why only me?
I feel like you could beat her easily if you go for counters.
Oh, no you don't!
I'll match your movements.
I want Botan to win!
Don't lose to this button masher!
Botan-san?
Let's do this and this and this!
Botan-san!
This is...
This is looking bad.
Boss is just mashing buttons, so maybe don't rush in?
That's true.
I got the throw! Heck yeah!
This is gonna hurt!
She pulled something off!
Whoa.
Boss!
Heck yeah!
Boss was really good!
It was how hard I wanted to protect the store.
I'm not sure if I should be happy.
Aren't you all a little turned off?
A little.
Yeah, I can tell.
Boss...
You were mashing pretty seriously.
Yeah.
Boss reflecting
I...
Sorry about that.
Well,
I rushed towards her
so that I could get better.
That's Botan for you.
Botan-chan's backing you up!
As you've seen,
Botan-san finished with 2 wins and 2 losses.
She started from a defeat,
but she improved while fighting.
Have we solved her problem?
Finally, let me ask you a question.
Please tell us the member who shined
the most, the Twin-crew for today!
The Twin-crew for today was...
Yeah!
Mhmm.
Uh... Towa-sama!
Yaaay!
Today's Twin-crew:
Tokoyami Towa
Hooray!
You definitely have a thing for me!
She pulled off a lot of finishing moves.
Yeah.
It was amazing.
Since Towa got selected as a Twin-crew, we'll give her a star!
Yay! It's a star!
You'll be the boss at 100 stars, so keep doing your best!
We've got a long road ahead of us!
Yeah!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Challenge From the Boss: the Maruyama Championship!
Yay!
This season's minigame is...
Puyo Puyo Tetris 2's Endless Fever mode!
At the moment, in first place
is Marine with 57,726 points.
And in last place is Ayame-chan with 2,512 points.
Botan-chan. One of us.
Subaru & Ayame Line
Botan-chan
One of us
No, don't read it!
Botan-chan, what do you think?
I want to shoot for first!
Oh? Really? Really?
What?!
At the very least—
Captain Marine's been all smug for so long!
Really?
Do you really think you can beat me, Botan-san?
I'm dragging her off her high horse!
Steal it! Steal her throne!
Then let the game begin!
Press the start button!
I get 60 seconds, right?
What stacking do you do?
You start with the side, right?
She's fast!
She's way too fast at deciding where to drop!
Yeah, she's definitely a frog stacker.
Frog stacking, huh?
I don't think I've seen anything but frog stacking.
Everyone loves frog stacking!
Wait, hold on a sec!
You messed up?
I think I messed up.
It's okay! You can rebuild!
You're okay! You're okay!
There's still plenty of time.
You've got 40 seconds!
What's this thing?
A 2-chain!
She got a 2-chain!
Just relax. Relax.
I'm relaxed.
And she's already passed the Subaru Line.
Stop calling it that!
Past the Ayame & Subaru Line
It's the 2nd Gen Line.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
She passed the 2nd Gen Line.
And now, that's a 2-chain.
Wow!
A 2-chain!
Nice!
How long left? How long left?
22 seconds! 20 seconds!
20 seconds?
She has a max chain of 2.
Okay.
You can do it! Take your time!
You've got a good bit of time.
Will we see a new high score?
Right, right, right. I have time.
And there's less than 15 seconds left!
Nice. Very nice.
10 seconds... 10 seconds left?
10 seconds! 9!
Oh, I was off!
No, you're doing okay.
5 seconds!
5 seconds left!
4! 3!
You want to clear that-nice!
2! 1!
I was off!
It's over!
Ahhh!
So close!
Let's see that final score!
9,784 points.
You're beneath me!
Like...
Darn!
You're beneath me!
Shut up!
Provocational Demon Towa
Kanata lost her temper the same way.
She said she'd beat the Captain.
(Temper) Loser Angel Kanata
Really?
Yeah, she came at me the same way with frog stacking.
Look out for Beat the Captain Scams
How do you feel? Unfortunately,
you weren't able to get a new high score.
Well, you know, I'd love to try again if I get another chance!
Oh?! The game changes, so give it another try
Yes, please.
the next time you come by!
Will a monster appear and beat Marine's high score?
Tune in next time and see!
Look forward to it!
Shishiro Botan
Thank you for your patronage!
Yay!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
After Closing
How did you enjoy this episode of Game Shop Maruyama?
I've asked Marine-san to stay back this time.
Yay!
Now, let's give our viewers some advice with their worries!
Okay!
From @mikino_holololo on Twitter!
Hello, everyone!
Hello!
I've taken on a stark raving mad persona, and it's stuck,
and now I have to live while acting out this persona!
What should I do?
Ah!
Huh?
I feel you!
I feel you so much, I'm gonna fall over!
The curtains rise on Marine Theater
So, like, the Captain...
Huwhawhawhawha?
You see, I...
You see, your Captain knows exactly how you feel.
Yes, yes, yes?
Yes, I know.
You—
I knew the darkness that lurked in your heart!
Darkness in my heart? What?
I was worried for you.
If anyone has a stark raving mad persona...
Yeah, it's the Captain.
Huh? Hold on a sec.
Is that what you—
Well, yeah.
So I've always thought you've been worried about a lot.
Y-You were really worried about me?
Yeah, yeah.
No, that's not it!
It's not?
I didn't want to talk about people thinking
I have a stark raving mad persona.
Huh?
You don't?
I wanted to talk about how everyone thinks
that I'm a boomer, and that's stuck.
Oh.
That?!
I'm not actually that much of a boomer! I'm really young!
Oh, yes?
Oh, that?!
I'm not a boomer, but they all think I'm a boomer,
so I thought my boomer fans would be sad...
And that's always been a worry of mine.
Oh, I see! I see! I see!
Oh, I see. (/s)
Then it's good that we got this worry when you were on.
Did you think I had a stark raving mad persona?
Well, you see...
Well, yeah, but...
Uh...
I don't think it was only me.
Then what should they do?
Right, right, right! We need to get back.
Having to act out this persona all the time
is taking a toll on Mikino-san here.
Do... Do they want to go back to normal?
Do they have to act this way?
No!
How do they want to be perceived?
You can slyly change your persona!
Like how?
I'm Houshou Mawine.
I'll be in your cawe, Boss.
Uh...
Um...
Uhh...
Um, I'm sorry...
Uhhh...
Uhhhh...
I'm not good at talking to people...
I'm sorry...
Huh? What?
Was that taking a stark raving mad persona
and doing a subtle shift to a stark raving mad persona?
Into another stark raving mad-
It obviously wasn't!
Just shut up, you!
Should she be this into it?!
I'm Houshou Mawine. I'll be in your cawe, Boss.
And now...
Yes, we're accepting requests for advice from you.
Yup!
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique, personally signed request fulfilled sticker.
So please send in your submissions!
Send 'em in!
Send 'em in! Send 'em in!
Send! Send! Send! Send! Send!
Send 'em! Send 'em!
And I fall over again.