Vroom!
Noble Snow Elf
Yukihana Lamy
Thwack
What in the world is Lamy-chan doing?
Mimicking a lawnmower because she's bored, apparently.
Of all the things to mimic...
Okay, time for a break.
Where did that come from?
Y-You can't have any!
I don't want any!
Not in the middle of the day!
I hear she's got booze hidden
in every nook and cranny of the office.
This booze?
That booze.
So, like, this here?
Yep.
And this?
And this?!
Yep.
Seriously, this too?
Then how about...
Wait, I don't have time to be sitting around!
I have to get home and do
an evening drinking stream!
You just want to drink, don't you?
Not happening.
...
Glare at me all you want,
I'm not backing down!
And what are you trying to do, Senpai?
Figured I'd prep this meat for dinner.
It's not meant to be eaten!
So you two insist on getting in the way
of my evening drink...
Wait, why so mad?
And why am I included?
Come forth, Daifuku!
Oh hey, Daifuku-chan.
Evolve!
Why does it have a lawnmower?!
Go back to normal.
Okay, Daifuku!
Have these two join me for drinks!
Waah!
What are you doing, Daifuku?
Stop it!
So, uh, what is Daifuku, exactly?
Waaah!
Don't worry about it.
Muh booze!
Sh-She's part of hololive's wholesome gang...?
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!