I normally use the "armpit bewb" rule but
there's no bewbs here.
Uwwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhh!!
Owaaaah!
Here I go!
I'm doing it now!
Okay!
Something seems strange...
Yeah, something seems off.
Ah! Look!
See!
Let's move on to the next segment.
Okay!
Now we've got
Old Man Watame's Best Pictures Quiz!
So in this segment,
Rules
Pick a screenshot from A to D
of the four images shown, one of them is
a picture that I, Tsunomaki Watame,
saw on someone's
3D stream and thought
Oh.
Ah.
"Oh, nice!"
and took a screenshot,
and you have to guess which picture that is.
Correct Answer
Okay!
Oh?
This is... from quite a while back!
That's right. It's from Rushia-senpai's
3D reveal stream.
This is hard!
This is definitely hard.
This is the last one for today.
I normally use the "armpit bewb" rule but
there's no bewbs here.
I'm lost.
Don't say "there's no bewbs"...
[B] does have it though.
Ah... I didn't mean it like th@$%#...
That's definitely not something you should say...
"There's no bewbs."
- Oozora Subaru
Stop right there!
Are you going to be okay?
She might put you in her fridge, you know?
Have an answer?
I have!
Please show us your answers!
[A]!
[B]!
Why did you pick A?
I considered the armpit bewb in [B] but
just then, you said that you want
to be sandwiched between bewbs
and I thought that [A] would be
something more along those lines,
and it is you we're talking about here
so "I want to stick my head up her skirt"
is probably a thought that
has crossed your mind before too,
which is why I picked A.
You're good!
Yup.
I know you're praising me
but that doesn't make me happy at all.
Why not?
[A] is what a boy would like.
This is what a young boy would be into, not an old man.
Really?
It's totally what a young boy would like.
Her hair is fluttering in this one
and her sleeves are all floaty
and you can see her armpit! (Very Important!)
This one is perfect!
Nooope!
Old Man Watame doesn't care
about how good the picture is.
The only thing she cares about
is if she sees something that she wants.
That's just the way Old Man Watame is!
I guess I'll announce the answer now.
Weeh!
I scared to know!
The one I chose was...
It was [A]!
Uwwaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhh!!
Owaaaah!
Uuughhh!
A-And can you tell us why you picked [A]...?
Well... I did say that you were good before...
I'm scared!
The thought that there's
a little bit of this psychopath inside my head
scares me!
You're amazing Subaru-senpai (monotone).
Congratulations,
I'm scared!
Welcome to the dark side!
Subaru-senpai.
Turn me back into my old myself!
Good for you.
Nonono... Umm... Ummm...
Like,
Like, you know...
We should just go back to being friends of friends...!
Spend some time apart...
No, that's weird!
We can be friends again
after I return to being my old self.
Please.
This isn't good...
Did you really want to stick your head up her skirt?
I guess... so.
I'd like to pay a visit.
You want to visit...?
But I'd be alright with not doing that too.
I'm already plenty grateful for just this.
Subaru-senpai...
Okay, let's go to the next one.
That's even more realistic and frightening...
Let's get away...
We'd better escape while we still can...!
Right?
This is trouble right here...
Subaru-senpai, let's escape while we can.
Don't run away!
And here's our next segment!
Subaru's School of Retorts!
This is Subaru-chan's segment,
so please introduce it to us.
Okay!
In this segment, I've had some clips of
Rules
Clips to retort to
hololive members' streams prepared for us to make retorts to,
so we'll watch them, then the two of you
will see if you can come up with the same retort
Guess Subaru's retort!
that I thought of.
Okay, then moving on.
Making retorts is hard!
Let's start!
State your name.
Streamed on 2021/03/03
[Waiting for call-ins] Annual Miko Advice
Call-in Stream [Hololive_Sakura Miko]
It's started.
My name is Ookami Mio.
Ookami Mio's concern
Worried about if
the motherly image
she has is really okay
Well, I am aware that
there are
some people in hololive who want
to go back to
being babies.
However,
Who's she on about?
there is something that only
you can do, is there not?
There are lots of mothers in hololive
but I believe you are
the only one who can be
the mother of all mothers!
Huh?!
This is pretty hard too!
Hold up! Hold on!
You'd probably
just want to let that slide if you could.
It's just that hard
to comment on!
Where do we even star...
Hah...
Heh...
This is... just...
I guess you don't really have to make a retort,
just reacting is fine!
It's fine if we just brush it over, right?
Okay!
It looks like you're done
so why don't we start with Watame?
OK!
...the only one who can be
the mother of all mothers!
Does anyone have a real god on speed dial?!
To be honest,
I really like it!
How did you come up with that?
Any god on 9-1-1?
I felt like things were getting a bit over the top
and that we should get an actual god to come...
Ah, I see!
Yeah.
This is good. I like it!
Next up... Polka!
Let's see yours.
Sure!
Okay...
...the only one who can be
the mother of all mothers!
Someone, please help me out here!
Ahaha!
Ha!
That works fine.
I mean I said that it works fine but
Making it someone else's problem!
I really like it!
"Someone, please help me out here!"
She would totally say that!
So now for what I would actually say,
here's the video!
...I believe you are
the only one who can be
the mother of all mothers!
Sorry to have bothered you...
You seem kind of tired.
Correct answer:
Sorry to have bothered you...
You seem kind of tired.
This feels kind of...
But I really liked both of your answers too.
You're on a different level though.
No, not at all...
I mean, like, both our retorts were just
throwing the problem to someone else,
both mine and Watame-senpai's...
Yeah!
Yeah...
But,
Subaru-senpai actually took responsibility
and handled it herself.
So much praise
It felt like a gentle retort as well.
But honestly, I'd rather avoid it too!
Correct answer: Actually wants to avoid it too
But you accepted it and dealt with it!
The next segment is
Omaru Polka's
Rescue Operation!
Save me!
This is Polka-chan's segment.
How does it work?
Yes.
So, I'm always super serious about whatever I do, right?
But, somehow,
I always seem to flop,
so we're going to look at some of my flops
Rules
Scene where Polka bombed
and see what you might have done in that situation?
What would you do?
Is there even anything that could've been done?
What should I have done to try and salvage the situation?
Let's salvage Polka's flops!
That's what this segment, Polka's Rescue Operation, is about!
So, our first rescue operation...
I'm kind of afraid to watch the video...
...is this video.
Is this hell?
Just endure the secondhand embarrassment.
Rich coming from you!
I, Omaru Polka, will be trying to juggle today!
Ah, no... This isn't good...
Streamed on 2021/01/10
[#OmaruPolka3D] Should I reveal my 3D model?!
Polka's here! [Hololive]
Ooh! Look at that!
It's your 3D reveal.
Okay, let's do this!
Yes.
Ah...
*breathes out*
Ah, that was...
Please don't look...
Hup!
This is a long video!
It almost seems like...
the clubs have gained self-awareness
and are trying to escape.
Here I go!
I'm doing it now!
Okay!
Something seems strange...
Yeah, something seems off.
Ah! Look!
See!
See? See! See!
Under suspicion of cheating
Lookie, lookie!
Couldn't you have done that a better way?
Pfft!
Haha.
Hey, old man! Hush! Don't say that!
So... What should I have done?
You're such a good girl for reflecting on what happened!
Can you rescue me?
Can you save me?
Can it be done?
We can...
Huh?
We ca...
Wait, did I even flop at all?
You... definitely flopped.
I see...
I flopped there...
Yeah, we were all kind of holding our breaths.
Watame-senpai! What should I have done?!
Are they going to play the video?
I-I don't wanna see...
What should I have done?
Actually, the studio staff said that
we'll give the video a rest.
Even the staff are feeling embarrassed by it!
"Let's give the video a rest." (being considerate)
Well then, Watame-senpai!
Okay!
Please tell me your rescue plan!
Attach a string to your sticks!
Answer: Attach a string to the sticks!
That way they'll definitely return to you!
I'm not sure that would fly for a member of the circus!
Well then, Subaru-senpai, can you help me?
This is
what I'd do!
Answer: Don't juggle at all!
Don't juggle at all!
She rejected the whole thing altogether!
Just don't juggle at all!
You're kind of
laying it on too thick with the Tendon.
Tendon
A comedy technique where
the comedian performs the same gag repeatedly
She's commenting on the actual performance itself!
In order...
In order to salvage this kind of situation,
it's probably best to make it easier
for people to understand that
it's alright for you to bomb there, or...
How do you get people to understand
that it's alright to bomb?
After you flop,
instead of,
"Did I screw up?!", you should be more like
"I bombed. So what?"
and make an expression like that.
Smug face!
If you make a smug face
then it'll probably be easy for people to tell.
"I just bombed!"
That good?
That's great!
If you flop,
I think you should just put it out there.
"Yup, I just flopped!"
"I'll bomb the next one too!"
Does that sound good?
Yeah...
You should probably just not do it again...
Yeah, just stop right there!
Should I just say, "Look, there's strings attached!"?
I'll just announce it next time, then.
Now I'm kind of interested in
what your next stream is going to be like.
Let's look forward to her future streams
I really want to see it now.
Yeah, I'm so curious!
So curious!
Extra
May I please introduce the people
that will be present on the show today?
You may.
You obviously may, young miss.
Then first off...
Wait―
You want me to leave?
Eh?
Talking with this Old Man
gave me a stomach ache,
so can I go to the toilet?
Of course you can! Go ahead!
So this is what Bonjour is like?
Eh? Do I...
Subaru disappears
really have that much of an effect...
What's [A]?
Is it her back?
Yeah, it's her back.
But it does kind of look like bewbs.
Actually... we've just received some
Yeah, we've received some shocking news
shocking news.
just now.
[A] is actually an image of her front...
So this is actually bewbs.
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub channel
on NicoNico for the full stream archives!
We got it totally wrong!