DAILY DIARY
From me to you
todokechaou
Playing my life through
se~shun jikkyouchuu!
Streaming all things new!
cho~sen haishinchuu!
Playing my life through
se~shun jikkyouchuu!
Streaming all things new!
cho~sen haishinchuu!
Fun things are hiding in plain sight
hora ne, tanoshii o
Found one!
hakken!
I've gone and discovered yet another new love
mata atarashii "suki" ga mitsukatta yo
A new cafe in the neighborhood
kinjo ni dekita kafe no
It has cake!
"keeki"
And it was kinda, like, super delish!
nanka sugoku oishikatta n da yo
Games I've never heard of
shiranakatta geemu ya
Songs I've never listened to
kiita koto nai uta
They catch my eye, and I dive in
chotto ki ni nattara te o dashichau
Join me once more
ho・ra・ma・ta
And we'll play together
issho ni asobou!
Let's do a ten roll
juu ren gacha hiite miyou
Let's play a horror game
horaa geemu yatte miyou
Let's sing that one song
ano kyoku utatte miyou
It's all so much fun
zenbu ga, mou tanoshii no!
I see your smile past this window
mado no mukou no
And I have to wave to you!
egao ni te o fucchau!
Playing my life through
se~shun jikkyouchuu!
Streaming all things new!
cho~sen haishinchuu!
Playing my life through
se~shun jikkyouchuu!
Streaming all things new!
cho~sen haishinchuu!
DAILY DIARY
From me to you!
todokeyou!
hololive IDOL PROJECT - DAILY DIARY
Lyrics: Yohei Matsui
Composition: Yuuki Honda (Arte Refact)
Arrangement: Takuya Sakai (Arte Refact)
Vocals: Natsuiro Matsuri, Oozora Subaru,
Sakura Miko, Shirogane Noel, Houshou Marine