I know that you've gained a bit of weight lately.
AHHHHHH!
YOU BELONG TO ME!
Hey, everyone!
hololive's symbol of purity and everyone's idol,
Natsuiro Matsuri here!
I opened a host club recently,
but it went under.
The name's Amane Kanata.
Here representing FAMS,
I'm FUBUKI the White Fang.
A pleasure to be here.
*clearing throat*
Are you all right, there?
Everything okay?
From hololive 4th Generation...
cool as a cucumber, it's me, Himemori Luna.
Someone's choking her!
You sound half-dead!
Do you need help?
Are you okay?
That's right!
Everyone's speaking like suave (?) guys
because of what we have planned for today!
Let's hear the title, all together!
"Heart-Racing Declarations of Love!"
Yay!
Guys declaring their love for Matsuri
Kanata-san, Fubuki-san, and Luna-san
will play the part of guys
declaring their love for Matsuri-san.
Compete to raise her heart rate the most
They'll compete to see who can raise
Matsuri-san's heart rate the most,
that is, whose declaration
made her heart race the most.
How do our talented contestants feel
about their chances?
Quite confident, of course.
I've got this in the bag.
No problemo.
Luna-chan, are you sure about that voice?
Help! I can't do a sexy guy voice!
You're starting to sound like M*wtwo to me.
It is I... M*wtwo.
I am M*wtwo.
First up is Kanata-san!
Set the scene for your declaration of love!
Certainly.
This scene features
an upperclassman in a club activity (me)
and a junior member of the same club (Matsuri).
Oh, I'm the junior member.
We'll first take a look Matsuri-san's current heart rate.
Let's see.
It's currently 98 BPM.
Her heart's already racing!
Her resting heart rate was around 60 BPM, so...
Really?!
Oh no, oh no!
Oh my. She is so into me.
You wish!
And with that, let's hear Kanata-san's
Heart-Racing Declaration of Love!
Matsuri, good work today.
You too, senpai.
Right, so...
are you free right now?
Right now? Sure.
I wanna talk to you about something.
Okay.
So, Matsuri, um...
are you going out with anyone right now?
Huh? Oh...
No, not right now.
Oh, I see.
There's something I've been meaning to tell you...
Yes?
Matsuri, you know, you're cute, and you're always...
so kind and considerate during club activities.
Doing good so far!
But for a while, not long ago,
you seemed to be feeling down.
During that time, I just...
Matsuri-san's gonna lose interest if this drags on.
Seeing you like that,
I felt I had to protect you.
But Matsuri-chan's still paying attention.
Yeah, she seems to be interested.
Which is why...
JUST A SEC!
A COCKROACH!
THERE'S A COCKROACH! THERE!
Oh, I don't mind them.
Oh... You don't mind them...
Her heart rate's falling!
BPM dropping
Is everything okay?
Are you scared of cockroaches?
No, not at all!
Lemme go squash it.
Oh, glad to hear.
I guess he was trying to raise her heart rate.
Your fearlessness around cockroaches...
is another thing... I like about you...
Matsuri-san's losing interest.
Her heart rate's dropping fast.
Crap, her heart rate...
Anyway...
There's something...
I've kept secret from you for a long time...
A secret?
You can do it!
That's right.
Measuring...
I've always... been in love with you.
There it is!
Ooh!
Not bad!
Will you... go out with me?
What?
Sure.
Wait, really? Are you sure?
I... don't actually have the guts
to squash cockroaches...
Are you sure?
You were cute, so sure.
Matsuri!
I promise to make you
the happiest girl ever! Matsuri!
And stop!
Matsuri...
So what did you think about
her declaration of love?
At first, you seemed
really earnest and sincere,
which had my heart racing,
but then a cockroach showed up
out of nowhere
and completely killed the mood.
Your heart rate went down sharply!
I saw your heart rate drop by about 10!
I started panicking!
If anything, my heart rate rose.
I see.
Now, the moment of truth.
Did that declaration
get Matsuri-san's heart racing?
Time to announce her max heart rate!
The number to beat is...
Amane Kanata's Record: 123 BPM
Congratulations!
That's pretty high!
It sure is.
It's twice her resting heart rate of 60.
Double!
Wow.
Victory is mine.
And so is Matsuri.
Next up is Fubuki-san.
Set the scene for your declaration of love.
This scene features
a broke band member (me)
and his live-in girlfriend (Matsuri).
I see!
I can't help but notice the backdrop...
There's no furniture!
Nothing at all.
I'm a broke band member, remember?
That broke?
It looks like we're about to skip town!
Fleeing debt collectors?
Time to see how much Fubuki-san
can make Matsuri-san's heart race!
Here's Fubuki-san's
Heart-Racing Declaration of Love!
Hey, Matsuri?
What is it, Fubuki-kun?
We've been dating for three months as of today.
We sure have.
I saw you always in the front row at our concerts,
I fell for you, and I asked you out, and ever since,
you've meant the world to me...
but there's something I haven't told you.
Something you haven't told me?
You see, I'm in debt.
Huh?
You're in debt?
Wait, what...
How much?
3 million yen.
3 million?
I can pay that off for you!
It's no problem!
It's all because my little sister is in the hospital...
Because?
He is so lying!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
This dude's a scam artist!
Oh, but...
I don't want to be a burden to you.
Not at all! 3 million is nothing.
Really?
Yeah, of course.
That's my girl, Matsuri!
That's what makes you so cute.
Gosh, stop it!
So, hey...
You know how...
before bed, you've got that white stuffed animal?
Cinnamo-you-know-who.
Right.
The way you sleep hugging it,
or how you're too lazy to cook,
so you order Uber Eats every day.
It's really adorable.
That's for sure!
The girlfriend must have a lot of money.
What was that you ordered recently?
The one high in calories. Go on, let's hear it.
Oh, u-um...
There were a lot... The chicken cutlet curry?
Chicken cutlet curry, huh?
What was it before that? We ate it together.
Huh?
We get Uber every day, so I don't remember.
You don't remember?
Gosh, you sure love eating greasy stuff every day.
But you can't hide it from me.
I hear you can't fit
into your favorite skirt anymore?
True story
Watch closely!
And I also know
that you've gained a bit of weight lately.
AHHHHHH!
But even so,
I love watching you
AHHHHHH!
happily stuffing your face
with sweets and greasy food,
AHHHHHHH!
STOP IT! STOP IT!
with your cheeks bulging like a squirrel's!
Loading your body with all those calories!
But don't worry. You'll always have me.
Really?
So you just keep smiling by my side
and supporting my career.
I will...
So please, don't abandon me...
I won't.
Not even if I end up 120 kg.
Don't you worry.
Don't you worry!
I'm prepared to carry that weight.
Oh, I'm so glad!
So, hey, Matsuri...
Uh-huh?
Before we're off headlining in the Big Apple,
Apple?
will you join me for a sweet honeymoon?
Crap, she doesn't know
what Big Apple means.
Would you rather go apple picking?
Let's go apple picking!
Apple picking! Great, let's do that!
Any other fruit you'd like to pick?
Or how about a buffet?
Let's go to a buffet!
What kind of buffet?
Beef!
A beef buffet! All right.
Stuff your face with barbecue!
Dripping with fat!
Yay! I love you!
We're off to get some barbecue!
And stop!
I needed popcorn for that!
I'm curious about how this will develop.
We'll be inseparable lovebirds now.
A happy couple.
Yes, very happy.
Indeed.
I can see this relationship
lasting a very long time.
Yes, a long and happy relationship.
The part where she said things
you didn't want to hear,
I saw your heart rate really spike.
Matsuri-chan,
do you really order Uber Eats every day?
No, but... lately...
I've maybe been ordering Uber a lot...
She was eating before this recording, too.
Yeah, I was.
What were you eating?
It was like...
seafood over rice,
but with meat in it, too.
Is that what it was?
So extravagant!
I treated myself.
Are you celebrating something?
My mouth was watering.
Wow.
So how much did her heart race?
Time to announce her max heart rate!
The number is...
Shirakami Fubuki's Record: 125 BPM
Ooh!
What?!
Really?
I think that's a new record!
Are you serious?!
Amane Kanata
Yes, indeed!
It was close!
Incidentally,
it was highest, as I'm sure you've guessed,
during the discussion about calories.
She hit me where it hurts
and made my heart race.
The talk about her weight
seemed to really hit home.
Weight
It was like watching a professional at work.
She knew just what to say.
It was very impressive.
You're up next, Luna-san.
Seeing the other two, how do you feel?
Right now,
I wish you could see my own heart rate.
It must be very high.
Are you nervous?
This is so much pressure.
So cute.
Hang on! I don't wanna do this anymore!
You can do it, Luna-san!
Just skip me!
You'll be fine!
Fubuki-cha-senpai was too good!
You'll be okay!
I don't think I can do this!
I'm running away!
Last but not least is Luna-san!
Please set the scene for us.
The scene is a company office.
Matsuri, it's just you and me.
We're alone in this place,
working overtime.
I'm young, but have climbed
my way to section manager.
Impressive!
A hotshot!
Matsuri, you work under me.
I see.
Got it!
All right, then!
How much can Luna-san
make Matsuri-san's heart race?
Time for Luna-san's
Heart-Racing Declaration of Love!
*appwoaches you*
Oh?
Matsuri.
You're still working overtime?
Oh!
Senpai! Yes, I am.
I've got a lot of work
piled up to get through.
Let me see what's in that pile.
I'll help you out.
Oh, you will?
Well, I'm having trouble with this part...
Where? Show me.
Right here. Do you see it?
How old is this guy?
Quite a bit older, it seems.
Matsuri! Is it all right
if I press my body against yours?
Huh?!
Yikes!
Wait, what do you mean?!
Sexual harassment?
Like, hug me?
I need to get close to use your computer.
That's all there is to it!
I have no indecent motivations whatsoever!
Oh, I see, no other reasons?
Nothing indecent at all!
I have only the purest motivations, to help you!
I see... Go ahead...
That's exactly what someone
with impure intentions would say.
Where are you having trouble?
Oh, um... Right here...
You do this part like this.
I see! I knew you could help me!
Well? Did that make sense?
Oh, um, right, uh...
I get it now.
Thank you very much.
See you tomorrow.
She's trying to leave.
But you still have more work left!
No, it's okay...
I'm gonna help you with all your work!
You'll do it all for me?
Of course!
Why are you being so nice to me?
You're a new hire, just out of school,
and a very precious subordinate to me.
Thank you very much.
So I can't ignore you when you're having trouble.
I see.
So you would treat anyone this way?
Not at all!
I can't unhear M*wtwo.
You're special...
You're the only one I'd do this for!
Why can't you understand that?
He's obsessed! I'm scared!
So weird!
He's on the brink!
This is scary!
Why can't you understand? Huh?
Huh?
I'm scared!
Huh? Yes, um...
I...
Get over here. Closer.
Okay... I'm coming...
Closer!
Like this?
*slam*
Her heart rate's going crazy.
C-Can I...
Can I trap you between my body and a wall?
I think you already are!
My heart's racing.
Hey.
Am I not enough for you, Matsuri?
What a creep!
I've always been watching you, you know.
Oh... Really?
I have eyes only for you.
I know how hard you're always working.
Get back to work!
How long does this go?
Am I not enough for you, Matsuri?
Huh? Am I not enough?
I'm scared...
Don't be scared...
Don't be?
Tell me what's in your heart.
Do you have feelings for me?
Thanks, but no thanks.
He's shocked!
It can't be...
I won't allow it!
YOU BELONG TO ME!
And stop!
Someone report this to HR!
File a complaint!
I'm scared...
Security!
I really love Luna herself,
Yes, she's cute, isn't she?
but I don't think I can ever like
that section manager.
I see.
All I felt was fear.
He might have successfully gotten
your heart racing, though.
Yeah, for a different reason.
Luna-san, how do you think you did?
It doesn't matter.
Either way, Matsuri belongs to me.
Is that so?
We're entering dangerous territory, here.
How much did that declaration
make her heart race?
Our hearts raced just watching it.
Time to announce her max heart rate!
The number is...
Himemori Luna's Record: 142 BPM
Amane Kanata
Shirakami Fubuki
Congratulations!
Section Manager!
The section manager
has claimed victory!
Like I said. Matsuri belongs to me!
You've got to be kidding me!
Her heart rate shot up
after your last dramatic declaration.
It all makes sense.
Indeed.
YOU BELONG TO ME!
Finally,
let's have the winner,
section manager Luna-san, give the outro.
Please like this video
and subscribe to our channels,
the hololive official channel.
You know what to do.
Smash those buttons!
We're counting on you!
Please like and subscribe!
Section manager's orders!