You can go straight.
Eep!
What is this?
Shoot!
She hasn't...
has...
She noticed us!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
It's July! You know what that means!
Guys!
Have you guys decided your Tanabata wishes?
I have!
Yeah!
Towa, what was yours?
Of course,
I wished that I can think up lots of devillish deeds!
What about Captain?
I'm quite considerate,
What?
so I wished for Subaru-senpai to finally become a human.
What the hell's your problem?!
What's your problem?!
I hope you'll turn into a human soon.
Me! Me! Me!
I have one too!
Yes, Subaru?
Okay!
As for me,
I want Captain to be curs—uh...
C-Cursed?
Cursed?!
Did you get cursed?!
Subaru fumbles her words from excitement.
Redo! Redo!
P-Please no flubs.
I wish for Captain
to be freed from the concept of "age."
Ahhh!
That's...
*pissed off*
Time certainly didn't wait for that pose there.
Marine's movements are old-fashioned
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Ah! It seems a customer is here!
Excuse me!
Welcome!
Today's Guest: Amane Kanata
Kanata-chan!
What the hell are you here for?
It's Towa!
Hey, everyone.
Wait a sec.
Do you two not get along?
We're on super bad terms!
We're the bestest of friends!
We're hella enemies!
'Cuz she's an angel and I'm a devil!
So you two mix like angels and devils.
I'm actually an angel! See?
She has wings!
That's cute!
Cute!
It's all right.
That's scary!
Amane Kanata
Hobbies: Staring at cute girls
Finishing Move: Squeeze, Squeeze❤Gorilla Power
MENT
LUCK
Today's guest is Amane Kanata-san!
Truly an angel!
But she has a finishing move that's contradicts her looks...
I have quite a bit of power.
P-Power?
My grip is a little strong.
A little...?
How strong is "a little strong"?
My grip strength is 50kg.
50?!
That's one step from becoming a gorilla...
Nah.
No, Boss. She is a gorilla.
No, I'm not!
I tried to peel a steamed potato,
Squeeze, Squeeze❤Gorilla Power Example
and I ended up squeezing it to smithereens.
Smithereens?
Like powder-size?
I was watching her at the time,
You were watching?
and I felt bad... for the potato.
Anyway, what are you looking for today?
I want to ask you guys at Maruyama for some advice.
Yeah?
I have pretty bad luck...
Aren't you an angel?!
True.
Go get some divine blessings!
To summarize what happened to me last year:
Amane Kanata's unlucky events that happened last year
Hospitalization.
Hospitalization♥
Hospitalization!
Traffic accident.
Amane Kanata's unlucky events that happened last year
Hospitalization♥Traffic Accident♥
Traffic accident?!
Theft.
Amane Kanata's unlucky events that happened last year
Hospitalization♥Traffic Accident♥Theft♥
Theft?!
That's about it!
Why are you so nonchalant about it?!
That's no joke!
Do you have any methods
to dispel a gloomy mood?
Leave it to us!
And there we have our request!
Thank you!
Kanatan's problem is, in short:
she wants to improve her fortunes
with a change of pace.
Exactly!
Maruyama's game recommendation is...
*drum roll*
this!
Ta-dah!
Resident Evil Village!
As shown by the roman numeral in "Village," VIII,
the survival horror game, Resident Evil Village
is the eighth and latest game in
the numbered Resident Evil series.
The goal for the eighth game was to make
a completely novel survival horror game.
The protagonist is the same as
Resident Evil 7: Biohazard, Ethan Winters.
It takes place in an old castle near a remote village.
You have to use various items and weapons
to deal with the encroaching threats.
What awaits Ethan at the mysterious village
he visits in search of his daughter?
If Lady Luck won't smile upon you,
then maybe Lady Dimitrescu will!
Learn how to deal with hardships head-first,
and aim to improve your fortune!
And so,
with the newest survival horror game,
Resident Evil Village,
raise your luck!
Raise your luck!
Good!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
So, since Marine and Subaru have played the game,
Subaru & Marine
Have played Resident Evil Village before
form pairs with the two that haven't played.
We have the Marine & Towa Team,
and the Subaru & Kanata Team!
Maruyama Team Faceoff!
Resident Evil Village backseat battle
Stage: Dimitrescu Castle
The first team to take down Dimitrescu wins!
Platform: PlayStation 5
Resident Evil Village backseat battle!
In this competition, the two teams
will start outside Dimitrescu Castle,
and they'll compete to see
who defeats its Lady Dimitrescu first.
Player
Advisor
The players are Kanata and Towa!
Please enjoy the rich graphics of the PlayStation 5!
Let's hear their thoughts going into the competition!
First up is the Towa & Marine Team!
Yeah! We actually
have a unit name called "Marine Towa-nette!"
Unit Name: Mari Towa-nette
Whaaat?!
Never heard of it.
We'll win with our honorable France power.
Let's do it elegantly.
Of course.
Let's set up the tea time for after we win.
Facing off against them is the Subaru & Kanata Team!
Yeah!
We're the "Primal Instincts! Wild Beast Team"!
We're wild beasts?!
Unit Name: Primal Instincts! Wild Beast Team
My, how unrefined.
How utterly unrefined!
We're a gorilla and a duck!
Then, let's get started!
Maruyama Team Competition:
Resident Evil Village backseat battle!
We've already taught them the basic controls.
The gist of it.
Can I start?
Let's get in the mood first.
The visuals are so pretty.
Yeah.
It's a castle.
This is already scary.
Make sure to interact with the white dots.
This way?
Will something pop out here?
Pick up bullets and stuff.
This is quite an old castle.
You can just go ahead and explore where you can.
The red places...
still have stuff in them, I think.
I'll go ahead and explore here...
The red rooms have something in them.
The rooms you haven't been to have a white door,
so head there.
Like at the bottom left.
It's white, right?
Ah, this, huh?
So doors you haven't gone through are white.
That's right.
That's easy to understand.
As you'd expect from Captain.
Let's start from the rooms we haven't been to!
You can go in there.
Go straight.
Okay.
You can go straight.
Eep!
What is this?
Shoot!
Subaru and Kanata are being attacked by something.
Do we fight her?
No, there's an escape behind you.
What will they do?
Run behind us? Then...
The planks on the right there.
They're tearing the planks on the right off.
There should be a button. Back off for a sec.
Get back a little.
Walking back.
That! That!
I'm tearing it off!
The backseater's panicking too!
Now go straight! Go!
OK!
And to the left.
Okay, nice!
Progress! Nice.
This is actually a puzzle.
Switch to the handgun.
The handgun?
Ah, okay.
Wait, so this...
Yeah! Yeah!
You light them on fire.
While Subaru and Kanata rejoice, the others get anxious!
Nice!
So I light all of them on fire.
You're a genius!
I'm a genius!
I won't let them call you a gorilla anymore!
I've got this in the bag now.
It should open now.
The gorilla and duck are really loud.
It's open!
Nice!
I'm sorry I'm such a genius.
So dark.
You can find gunpowder and stuff here, so be thorough.
Ah, okay, okay.
You should explore thoroughly.
Let's look at everything.
Mari Towa-nette following the same route
She seemed to be crouching.
She was.
Okay, nice!
Okay!
Let's proceed onwards!
Perfect.
And now what? Does something open?
It opened!
It's open!
This is scary!
Eek!
They suddenly appeared! What will she do?
While she screams, she stabs at their face.
Go away!
Towa-sama is going apeshit with the knife!
Stop it!
Towa-sama!
What?
You can shoot them with your gun!
Let's aim for those headshots!
Get them!
Go get 'em!
Nice!
This is bad!
Nice.
You're doing good.
She's getting those headshots.
I don't like this!
You're doing fine.
You're staying calm! You're doing good!
I can't do this!
Nice!
Ah, you gotta reload.
Let's reload!
Ah, this could be bad. It might be better to heal.
Towa-sama, guard!
Towa-sama, your guard!
What will happen to Towa-sama?
Ahhh! Nooo!
Game Over 💀
Ah... Marine & Towa Team died once!
I screwed up!
Towa-sama! Towa-sama!
Hmm?
You know...
I feel like even if we switch to "Casual,"
they wouldn't even notice.
You can switch to Casual difficulty
from the Standard mode's game over screen.
I feel like we could...
They'll never catch us!
Go! Do it!
I will!
Mari Towa-nette's shortcut to victory #1
Switching to Casual mode.
All right! Let's go!
Here we go!
I think you can just dodge them.
Dodge...
Okay! Just proceed.
Right there.
To the left.
And then go straight.
I'll just avoid all of them!
Okay, nice!
Nice!
She'll chase you here.
Probably good to heal.
Heal? Okay.
Reload your weapons, too.
They're already using their medicine.
Check your weapons.
Check if you have ammo
and if you have more heals.
Okay, okay.
Ammo...
Four shots.
I should reload these, right?
Reload them.
They're reloading.
Eep!
There she is again!
She's here!
Do we fight this time?
Run! Run! Run! Run!
Okay, okay.
Towards the light!
The light!
You can shoot her now!
I can shoot her now.
Um,
she's weak against cold air,
so lead her towards it.
You can shoot her now.
Right here?
Should I just keep shooting?
Nice, nice.
Nice! You can shoot her!
Okay!
Guard! Guard!
She's weak against cold air, so they're debuffing her here.
Nice! You did it!
Nice!
Heck yeah!
Nice! That was perfect!
They froze her!
Nice!
They froze her... and broke her into pieces!
That's good.
Pick this up...
It's the door to the left.
So it's this one.
This leads to the courtyard.
Go!
There we go!
Hell yeah!
Let's go!
I don't remember much from here on...
Hey, tell me you're lying!
From here, you go... straight?
There's nothing there! You're kidding me!
The wild team has the lead so far!
Will Mari Towa-nette catch up?
Go down to the first floor
Mari Towa-nette lagging quite far behind.
and open the door to the courtyard.
Ah, so it's this way.
Can you do this, Towa-sama?
What is this?
Wanna swap?
Th-They'll...
Currently committing ultimate devilish deed
Mari Towa-nette's shortcut to victory #2
Swapping with the experienced player
Huh? Wait... Huh?
Sneakily...
They're talking about something? Hmm?
Sit over here.
Boss turns a blind eye
Let's swap.
Hmm? Huh?
Towa-sama, where's the courtyard?
Huh?
I don't know either!
Where's the courtyard?
Subaru-chan, got a sec?
Huh?
Where's the courtyard at?
Mari Towa-nette's shortcut to victory #3
Asking the enemy team!
The courtyard...
Are you saying you want me to help you?
N-No.
Yeah.
Well, that much is fine.
Where's the courtyard?
You can borrow my duck.
Well...
There's quite a big gap between us, so I don't mind.
It's here.
Ah, it even says it!
Courtyard, found!
They missed the text!
Where are you guys right now?
It's a careless mistake!
We're here right now.
We're pretty far.
You guys walked so far away!
Huh?! It's this door!
This has got to be a wall!
It's not a wall! Actually interact with it first!
They're being told to actually interact with it.
Wall...
They put the key in, and it opens!
Well, I love Resident Evil, so.
It was good advice.
You can go now!
By the way, there's four more doors after this. Should I stay?
There're four more doors. What will they do?
You can watch if you want.
Bluffing
Should she tell them for now?
You can watch for now.
I wonder where we go from here.
It's probably to the right.
Ah...
Subaru's talking to herself!
It's probably to the right.
There're two doors...
Guiding them by talking to herself!
Towa-sama, Towa-sama.
Currently committing ultimate devilish deed
Hmm?
She didn't point out that I was the one playing.
Yeah, she didn't.
I'm a devil, after all.
Subaru shows an alarming lack of attention.
What is this place?
Looks scary.
Kanata just keeps going ahead.
I gotta go fast.
Aren't you scared?
You're amazing.
Kanata...
Eep! That's not good!
Eep! This is bad!
You're apeing through this too hard.
You gotta get out of these places as fast as you can!
Are you serious?
Pick this up.
Are you seriously saying that?
Eek!
Eek! Crap!
This is bad!
Looks like I gotta kill this one.
I have no choice but to kill this one.
Kanata starting to fight back
There's only one way through.
It's a one-way path.
Keep going forward, and then?
RE's so fun.
Yeah.
Right?
There's something here.
Let's gooo!
What is this? I'm scared.
Ooh.
It's the crazy part.
Crazy part?!
The crazy part.
In what way?
But I got past this part with willpower alone.
A part you get past with willpower?
Kanata...
Is this it?
You never lose your nerve.
Look at this cutscene. Don't skip it.
What's gonna happen?
No!
Eek!
Huh?
Crap!
Kanata!
Dimitrescu appears!
This is bad!
You're in trouble!
This is crazy!
Please stop.
Crap.
By the way, that move is a one-hit-kill.
F-F-F-F-F-For real?
The lever! Go back to the lever!
Wait, wait, wait.
Isn't that way bad?
Ahhh!
She got me!
You're still alive.
Heal! Heal!
My right arm!
Go straight.
There.
She's coming, isn't she?
Where is she?
She's coming from behind.
She attacks in a pretty wide area.
OK! Nice.
Run away over here...
Nice!
Do a loopty loop!
Okay!
All right!
We got through!
Is it this way?
Ahhh! We can get away!
Let's go!
This one! This key!
That was so close.
I forgot if we even got the key just now.
I got cold sweats back there.
What is this?
We gotta gather these masks.
Oh! Masks.
It said that earlier.
Yeah.
See ya later!
Farewell.
I wanna play too, now.
Do you wanna play, Subaru-senpai?
I can?!
You know, those guys...
Yeah, they're, uh..
They swapped, didn't they?
I thought that too.
Finally noticed
Mari Towa-nette's shortcut to victory #2
Swapping with the experienced player!
They're like...
In effect!
Something's off...
Try it! Try it! Subaru-senpai!
Wait, why is Subaru-senpai playing now?
Shut it!
You guys are doing it too!
Both teams have started to notice the irregularities!
To be continued in the fated second half.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Mari Towa-nette keeps committing devilish deeds,
and now they're catching up!
How will this turn out?
They've raised the lever again!
Ahhh!
My arm!
Her right arm has sustained damage.
Let's skip.
We gotta skip to catch up!
Wh-What just happened?
Huh?!
What do we do here?
This is bad.
She's chasing them.
This isn't good!
Give us a moment.
Where are you going?
There it is!
Ooh!
They've raised the lever again!
Please! Please go up faster!
Dimitrescu will come if they don't hurry.
Faster!
Open the hell up already! Why are you so damn slow!
Open the hell up already, you idiot!
You're so damn slow!
Captain?! Captain,
Remember, France.
Right, France.
France.
Oh, nice!
Twist! Twist!
Ooh! Wow!
What's this? Looks fun.
The Marine & Towa Team have gotten their first mask!
You guys are already at that part?
That was seriously fast.
Mari Towa-nette's rapid comeback
We've gotten to the annex, but is this the right place?
Is the annex the right place?
I want to go to the annex too!
They're already at the annex?!
Is the annex the right place?
Oi! It is. How do I get there?
This isn't good, Subaru-senpai!
Marine's catch-up game is godly.
Will we catch up?
They're catching up so fast.
Open up already.
They put in the right key, and here we have!
It's here! It's here!
They get their 4th mask!
4th mask obtained
Wait, this is weird.
Hey, where did you guys get a mask?
Huh? What's the matter, Subaru-senpai?
What?! We missed one!
Dimitrescu appears!
Subaru-senpai, you have to go to the armory.
Really?
Thank you.
A friend in need is a friend indeed!
I'm indebted to you, after all.
For real. How many times do you think I helped you?
Yeah!
It's finally time for the boss battle!
We're getting there!
I'll go ahead and sneak behind her.
They've done a great job gathering four masks!
Lady Dimitrescu is just huge.
She hasn't... has...
She noticed us!
One more!
O-Okay.
Uh... This one.
Open up, already!
Open it up, already!
Faster!
Crap!
Open up, already!
Ah, it's opening. Faster!
Faster!
Hey!
What's it doing?
Open up, already!
Whoa, amazing!
We're out!
Ah!
Fresh air is the best!
She's not chasing after us! Nice!
We lost her!
Mari Towa-nette go on to the final battle first!
Where will this seesawing battle take us?
Open, open, open, open open.
What? Do they get up?
This here...
Marine and Towa have opened the coffin.
This is a poisoned dagger.
They opened the coffin and pulled out the dagger.
You need this to beat her.
Yeah.
Do I stab her with this?
Oh?
No!
What? Is he okay?
They're getting their guts ripped out.
Huh?
You stabbed her!
You stabbed her. Now what'll happen.
You did her in now!
What? Is that the end?
No, it's not over yet!
It's not over. This is where it starts.
Look out!
What do you think's gonna happen now?
Uh...
She's got some big boobies.
They kiss?
No!
Like hell they would!
This ain't some chick flick!
Oh, they don't?
This is the start, but not of a relationship.
Now, after this...
What happens to Dimitrescu?
We'll skip this part.
Mari Towa-nette at the final showdown!
Whoops! There she is!
Let's pull out the rifle for now.
*distant duck screeching*
No! No! No! No! No!
She's totally freaky!
Crap! Crap!
Beat her with your Captain powers!
No!
Eek!
Towa-sama!
Slowly! Slowly!
Nice! Nice!
Her aim's so good!
It's auto aim!
Thank you, auto aim!
Hey, you're using auto aim?!
Mari Towa-nette's Protips: Use Auto Aim
Thank you, auto aim!
Seriously?
Wow, nice!
You're so good!
Nice!
Where'd she go?
Eek!
No!
She's gonna eat you! Oh wow.
She's got you now!
Eek!
Help!
Oh crap!
Mari Towa-nette's about to get swallowed legs first!
No!
Give me a second!
She's gone! She's gone! She's gone! She's gone!
You just climb up here?
We're coming up on the climax now!
No!
You're at the top of the tower! There's nowhere left to run!
What are they going to do now?
They're breaking the vases.
Bullets? Bullets?
What will they find inside?
There are shotgun rounds inside.
Where? Where?
Shotgun rounds? Okay?
She's outside!
Very useful.
There! There! There!
She's flying fast. You can't get a lock.
She's flying around! She's flying around!
Eek!
She's come in from above!
No!
Nice!
Wait a sec! Wait a sec!
Wait a sec!
Nice aim!
You're okay.
No! No! No!
You're okay! You're okay!
She's close. You got this.
She's shooting her good.
Nice!
Just take some time and reload.
Will the Subaru-Kanata team reach the Dimitrescu battle?
Nice! Nice!
No! No!
What a picture this is!
Oh?
Oh? What's this?
Oh? Could this be?
Maybe just a little more?
Is this it?
No!
Huh? What's this?
You get her?
Did I do it?
They're getting taken down with her!
What's going on?
Asking that is a death flag.
Oh?
Oh my.
Go!
Could this be the end?
Beat her?
Oh, she's gonna curse you?
Would you look at that! They've beaten Dimitrescu!
You've done it!
Yay!
We did it!
Boss!
One of the two teams has won,
so we'll call it a game!
What?!
Kanata!
Mari Towa-nette wins the backseat battle!
Congratulations!
Hold on, but they...
We did it!
Hey, wait, like...
Like, did you have enough bullets?
Um... well, you see...
Uh...
Oh?
Actually...
Yes.
We played it on casual mode!
Hey!
No way!
You! Seriously?!
We're sorry!
Protip: Beginners can take it easy on casual mode.
Sorry!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
So what did you think of the game, Kanata-chan?
It was really fun!
I got really into going for headshots!
Also, ignoring stuff.
It put my ignoring people skills to the test.
Kanata was totally crazy in there.
She just kept barreling past everything.
Huh? Huh?
The whole dungeon...
Gorilla Running Kanatan!
Name: Gorilla Running Kanatan
She was totally crazy!
You were pretty good too, Subaru-san.
Yeah!
I started playing RE from 7.
It's so fun!
I got addicted! I love it!
So now,
Kanata-chan, in fulfilling your request,
which of our staff shined brightest?
We'll call them the "Twin-crew."
Okay!
Can you tell us who was the Twin-crew this time?
Who shone brightest in fulfilling the request? Get enough titles, and you might get a reward?
We'll have the customer decide who was the Twin-crew starting this time.
Today's Twin-crew is...
Who is today's Twin-crew?
Subaru-senpai because she was so good to me!
Yay!
This week's Twin-crew: Subaru
Yeah, we didn't do anything for Kanata.
You got that right.
Subaru-senpai was so good and nice to me.
Really?!
I could feel her love for RE too.
Oh, good!
She mentioned all sorts of little details.
And so, since Subaru was selected as Twin-crew,
she gets a star!
What?! A star?!
If you get 100 of these stars,
you get promoted to boss! Work hard for it!
Wait, Boss, what about you?
Yay!
The CEO. I'll be CEO!
You get promoted?
I get promoted.
Why do you get promoted?
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Challenge From the Boss: the Maruyama Championship!
At this point, we'll have our customers
try their hand at a minigame.
Whoever finishes the season on top
will receive a Special Maruyama Trophy!
I want it!
This season's minigame is
Puyo Puyo Tetris 2's Endless Fever mode!
I heard a primal shout just now.
Yes, this one's mine!
At the moment, the current high scorer
is Marine with 57,726 points.
Yes, that's right.
Wow!
She's way too good!
Yes, that's right.
Just so you know, I was the best at Puyo Puyo in elementary school.
Title: Puyo Puyo Marine
Hey, that's pretty good.
On that note, how good are you, Kana-chan?
I'm really good at Puyo Puyo too!
Oh? Seriously?
What kind of stacking do you do, Kanatan?
S-Stacking?
You know, that.
Kanata stacking!
That's so cool!
What's Kanata stacking?!
Fighting over who's better at Puyo Puyo
I invented it myself.
Then let's see this Kanata stacking!
Then let the game begin!
Okay!
Start!
Kanata stacking, you heard?
Ready!
Oh, it's started!
Okay! Okay! Okay! Okay!
There! There! There! There!
She cleared it?
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
She cleared one at the start?
She cleared that?
Shoot, that was too early.
Oh, I see. That's what you're doing.
Like this, see?
She's stacking them all on the right-hand side.
Oh, I see, I see.
What's she doing?
It looks like total chaos to me.
What? How does this stacking even work?
No, no, no, no! No, no, no, no!
She's thinking and stacking. Oh, there's a 1-chain!
Well, just to fix it.
I don't get it. What's she doing?
Well, you see...
Captain realized after watching.
This is frog stacking.
This is "frog stacking"?
Yes, it's called "frog stacking."
No, it's not frog stacking.
It's also called "nohoho stacking."
Yeah, see? This is frog stacking.
Hey, watch this! Watch this!
It got cut!
I've never seen chains not happen this fast.
It's coming up. Just you watch.
She hasn't had more than a 1-chain.
I'm getting serious now!
What's going to happen?
Well, to explain the technique,
you throw down three columns at random
and clear them at random.
Kanata! 10 seconds left!
You okay? 10 seconds!
What? 10 seconds?
10 seconds left, Kanatan!
This is bad.
This might be bad.
Crap! Crap! Crap!
7! 6! 5!
Wait! Wait!
4! 3!
The chains just aren't happening.
2! 1!
Oh, crap!
And it's over!
How did she do?
No way!
Kanata?!
What a surprising development!
What happened?
Let's see that final score!
9,391 points!
Seriously?! Why's it so short?!
You were so confident in yourself before.
4th! Congratulations on 4th!
Only 4th?!
Are you serious?! Come on!
Now, now, now, now...
I thought I could do more. That was too short.
The time limit was the problem.
No, hold on, let me give a technical explanation
of the frog stacking technique.
Oh, she's giving commentary.
You stack the right three columns,
connecting what you can,
so if you clear one, you get chains at random.
Right, right.
It's a stacking technique.
I've hit a 12-chain with it before.
It's random?
12 is definitely exaggerating!
But if it's stacked right,
you can probably get a 7-chain.
I mean, the max chain this time was 2.
That's true.
How do you feel about it?
I want to give it another try.
Another try?
Then next time you come, you can try another game.
Maybe next time I come.
Yes, please do come again.
Will a monster appear and beat Marine's high score?
Tune in next time and see!
Look forward to it!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
How did you enjoy this episode of Game Shop Maruyama?
I've asked Marine-san to stay back this time.
Yay!
Now, let's give our viewers some advice with their worries!
Yeah!
From @00Tanukinoponta on Twitter!
Hello, Boss and Captain Marine!
Hello!
I have recently taken in a kitten.
What a nice person.
I took it to the vet, and they said that it was perfectly healthy.
However,
Yay!
I can't decide on a name for it.
Arr!
Would you please be so kind as to give it a lovely name?
Thank you very much.
Wow!
It's cute!
Oh, we have a picture of a cat here!
There certainly is a resemblance.
H-Huh? What?
A resemblance?
It looks like me.
There is?
Oh, looks like you?
Yes.
Sorry, I didn't get that for a sec.
Like this part, and the stripes.
Uh...
Let's think up a name for it.
Please give my kitten a name!
The two of us, right?
Yeah.
But we don't know if it's a boy or a girl.
Yeah, you're right.
So let's handle both cases?
Let's handle both cases. Yeah, we should.
Right.
Okay.
Then let's each say a word and stick them together.
Oh? That's a good idea.
It's a collab! A collab of love!
Boss and Captain's Love Collab!
Okay, then let's start with a boy name!
Okay! A boy name! One, two...
Seaweed!
Dandy!
Ehhh?!
Crap, crap, crap!
This is bad. We're in trouble.
His name's Dandy Seaweed!
Name (boy): Dandy Seaweed
Dandy Seaweed! What if it's a girl?
Let's do a girl name too. On three again!
One, two...
Coral!
Sexy!
I knew it!
It's bad!
Name (girl): Sexy Coral
So bad!
What the heck is Sexy Coral?!
We're accepting requests for advice from you.
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique, personally signed request fulfilled sticker.
So please send in your submissions!
Send 'em in!
Send 'em in! Send 'em in! Send 'em in! Send 'em in!
Send 'em! Send 'em! Send 'em in!