e la ci fu ya ba we le
se ya ku la ci ta wa ku
Amane Kanata, Tokoyami Towa - madoromi
Lyrics, Composition:
Taketeru Sunamori (Mirai Kodai Orchestra)
e la ci fu ya ba we le
Keyboard, Strings Arrangement:
Miyako Matsuoka (Mirai Kodai Orchestra)
se ya ku la ci ta wa ku
Recording & Mixing Engineer: NNZN (OFUTONE)
Vocal Direction: Kassan (Neko Hacker)
madoromi
Deep in slumber
samezu ni obore yuku
Trapped in an endless siesta
sagasu sagasu sagasu sagasu iriguchi
I search, I seek, I scout, I scour for a way out
nukarumi
Stuck in a mire
sukueba te ni tokete
It all slips through my fingers
kioku uzuku tsuzuku kuruu kutsuu
My mind aches, wide awake, it can't take this heartbreak forever
inishie
Never changing
shirusare sonomama no
Recounting the memories of yore
akai akai akai akai kizuato
These crimson, claret, scarlet, blood-red scars of old
utakata
Evanescent
samezu ni kiete yuku
Fading away in this endless dream
watashi watashi watashi koko ni ita
What was once me, myself, and I was right here
mabuta no mukou kara
Beyond the closed eyelids
mitsume kaesu hitomi
A steady gaze meets mine in turn
kagami no mukou de wa
Inside this hazy mirror
kurueru tenshi ga mau
A frenzied angel flutters in the wind
ochite ochite yuke
Further and further you fall
negaeba ushinau to shiri nagara soredemo
Knowing that reaching out will only get you spurned
fukaku tada fukaku motomete shizume
Still you seek and sink deeper and beyond
ochite ochite yuke
Farther and farther you fall
hitokire no hikari sae sutetara sore de ii
Leaving behind the ray of light that shines upon you
sakasa mawaru tokei michibiku hate de
All the way to where this clock in reverse leads
deau no wa kami ka akuma ka
Who will you find there, God or the Devil?
hoshikuzu
Stardust
naraku no chi no soko de
Even in the darkest depths of Hell
sakasu sakasu sakasu sakasu hanataba
Budding, burgeoning, blooming, blossoming, a bed of flowers
madoromi
Deep in slumber
samezu ni obore yuku
Trapped in an endless siesta
nigetai ikitai kietai deguchi wa nai
Want to leave, want to live, evaporate, there's no escape
fa ve te fu
e la ci fu wa ya u u we
ko fi to ko fi to ko fi to hu se fu ye se nu so
fa ve te fu
e la ci fu wa ya u u we
ko fi to ko fi to ko fi to la ci ta wa ku
kono sekai ni kamisama
If our world is home
amarinimo ooi nara
To one god too many
dokoka ni sutereba ii
Banish them forever to
mienai tsuki no ura
The dark side of the moon
mabuta no mukou kara
Beyond the closed eyelids
mitsume kaesu hitomi
A steady gaze meets mine in turn
kagami no mukou de wa
Inside this hazy mirror
kurueru watashi to au
My frenzied self and I are intertwined
ochite ochite yuke
Further and further you fall
negaeba ushinau to shiri nagara soredemo
Knowing that reaching out will only get you spurned
fukaku tada fukaku motomete shizume
Still you seek and sink deeper and beyond
ochite ochite yuke
Farther and farther you fall
hitokire no hikari sae sutetara sore de ii
Leaving behind the ray of light that shines upon you
sakasa mawaru tokei michibiku hate de
All the way to where this clock in reverse leads
deau no wa kami ka akuma ka
Who will you find there, God or the Devil?
e la ci fu ya ba we le
Drums: HAZE
Violin: Atsuki Yoshida (EMO strings)
se ya ku la ci ta wa ku
Violin: Anzu Suhara
Viola: Izumi Kawamura
e la ci fu ya ba we le
Cello: Kirin Uchida
Bass: Takumi Kagahara
se ya ku la ci ta wa ku
Recording Studio: studio MSR