Houston, we have a problem.
What's the matter, Polka-chan?
Oh, hey, isn't that Okayu-chan's handheld?
Wait, really?
I totally dropped it earlier!
So it's hers? If she finds out...
You fool! I'll turn you into a rice bolka!
Eek! Have mercy!
I've seen the future...
Yoohoo. What's up?
Well, Polka-chan had the handh...
Forgive me, Senpai!
Could you rewind that footage for me?
Hmm? Oh, sure.
A blindingly quick karate chop,
impossible to spot without my superior vision.
What's gotten into Aki-chan?
I know, right? Spring's so comfy,
she's turned into Aki Rosenotatall.
Sure looks like it. Want a rice ball?
Pui Pui Akicar.
Oh, right.
Know where the handheld
I'd left on that table went?
What are you talking about?
There's no table anywhere!
Is that so?
Wonder if Aki-chan meows anything.
Nah, I doubt it!
Besides, she's out like a light!
See?
Pui Pui...
Polka-chan dropped the handheld...
Polcar!
I-I'm feeling out of sorts today,
so I'll take my leave.
Okay, but gimme back that handheld before you go.
H-How long have you known?
Since around the time
you knocked Aki-chan out.
Busted!
I swear it wasn't on purpose!
It just fell off when I was cleaning!
I see now.
But it's not mine, actually.
...¿que?
I borrowed it from Koro-san.
Try this game, Okayu!
It's really fun!
I'll even lend you my handheld
because I'm so big-hearted!
...she said.
Th-That's awfully nice of her.
FYI, she's right there.
You borked my handheld, huh...
C-Can I reload my save?
It's game over for you!
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!