Magic tricks?
Indeed! Let me blow your minds!
Hup!
Whoa!
Sure you didn't mean black magic?!
Marine, could you ever provide
entertainment so high level?
Well?
Grr...
You have no idea how far I can go with this.
Oh, I wish you'd go far away.
Show me more!
Here.
Whoa.
Booyah.
Whoa!
Whoooa!
Nothing magical about that last one!
Wow!
Clap!
But it works, huh?
Do more!
Wow, she's got so many tricks up her sleeve...
Hold up. Is she out of material?
What is she gonna try now?
"Peekaboo!"
For cryin' out...
She loves it...
Now for an impression of Houshou Marine.
Go for it!
Not even a trick!
Wanna romance a grasshopper...
It's on now!
...
Wow, that didn't land, huh?
Tough crowd... to make sense of.
Peeka...
boo!
Shion-senpai vanished!
What? How?!
Oops, I used a warp spell by mistake.
Who's this girl? And where'd she come from?!
She could be an enemy spy!
What the hell are the cops doing?!
Heeeeeelp!
Wait, what? What are they saying?
My magic tricks and I are innocent!
...Or so claims the trespasser arrested at Harvard U.
Wow, Shion-senpai's incredible!
*clap*
...
Yikes.
*clap*
Needs to train more, both in tricks and the dark arts.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!