Suppies! Tokoyami Towa here!
You suck! She'll be here soon, so cut it out.
Not even close!
Hmph!
Why me too?
Bad mimicry is bad form.
Good day. I am Tokoyami Towa,
the Professor of Manners.
Bwahahaha!
Whomst?
Check out those glasses!
Enough chatter!
You two need a lecture
on social behavior.
What?
Take this general knowledge quiz and learn.
You two frequently display a lack of common sense.
Take this chance to learn societal rules
Nene-chan, y'know,
we don't usually treat Towa-sama
with a lot of respect.
and behavior more becoming of idols...
She wants to act superior for once.
Ah. Guess we should play along.
And there you have it. Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Good.
Let's start with Q1.
You're halfway down a crosswalk
when the light starts blinking.
What do you do?
Break it!
Not a solution!
Next!
Q2. The top three delicacies of the world
are foie gras, caviar...
and...?
Watame.
She's not food!
Next!
Q3. What's the famous quote
by the first astronaut in space?
The Earth...
is white.
That's the moon!
The Earth...
is fake.
Where're you from, then?!
This ain't happening!
Teaching these fools common sense
is beyond me!
Actually...
Shouldn't you be learning from us?
Huh?
A life shackled by norms is no fun.
True that!
W-Wait a sec...
I'll show you what lies beyond the rules.
Huh? I, uh...
Okay, Q1.
Hellowl!
Wha?
T-Towa?!
Rules are meant to be broken!
Got carried away, huh?
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!