Widdle Wamy whims her whammies
powwing snow with fwimsy woes.
That's so cute!
Starring:
Sakura Miko
Tokoyami Towa
Yukihana Lamy
This episode of holo World Records
is brought to you by Sakura Miko...
...Tokoyami Towa, and...
...Yukihana Lamy!
It's finally happening again!
Challenge everything!
holo World Records!
Yaaay!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Wowowowowowow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
All right, enough. Thanks for the hype.
By the way, Miko-san, have you ever
set a record in your life?
*inhales*
Uh...
A... record...?
She's trying not to look at me.
Growing my cowlick super duper long.
Oh, growing your cowlick. (lol)
Isn't Lamy's longer?
Yeah, I think it is.
Hold it right there.
Now that you mention it,
I think mine's longer.
Mine's just limp, that's all!
Yours is shorter, Lamy-chan!
A record I've set
throughout my entire life is
getting an absurd amount
of mouth ulcers.
Yikes.
How many have you had at a given time?
Three at once.
Oof.
That's rough!
My face is a liver!
I'm Yukihana Lamy
and I'm from 5th Gen!
The best record
I've set up until now is...
Drinking 56 different brands of sake
on stream ever since I joined hololive.
Thanks for having me.
56 different brands?!
That's just...
Amazing!
The three of you have
some pretty good records,
but if you manage to
break the records shown in this show,
the title full of renown:
The hololive World Record Queen,
will be yours!
I've never heard of such a title!
First time I've heard of that!
The first challenge you girls
will be taking on is this!
High-Speed Blinking World Record!
You'll be tested on how many blinks
you can do in just 15 seconds.
Seriously? Wow!
The current world record holder
for this category
is the High-Speed Blinking Queen,
Shirakami Fubuki!
Her record is 68 blinks.
Oh! It's Fubuking!
68 blinks?!
Yikes!
Okay. Miko-san,
who has been spacing out!
How many blinks are you aiming for?
I'm going first?!
I'm gonna
bust out a record
that'll forever be
impossible to beat.
Can she set a new record?!
Sakura Miko, aiming for elite results!
You can do it,
Miko-senpai!
Let's get started!
I believe in you!
Ready?
Begin!
Oooh!
She's trying her best!
She's squinting more than she usually does!
That's sort of cute!
How am I doing?
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two! How's it looking?
One!
Okay, time's up!
Fin
That's too short!
Isn't it too short?
I need more time!
Well then, Miko-san's record is...
47 blinks! Wow!
Nooo!
One more try!
You weren't even close!
Ugh...
Okay, next up is Tokoyami Towa-san!
If you will.
Yaaay!
Does she have the power?!
Tokoyami Towa swoops in!
Without further ado...
Ready?
Begin!
15 seconds on the clock. Oh?
That's really quick!
Looking good...
Fast! She's fast!
She's doing pretty well.
She's really fast!
Whoa!
Whaddya think?
You can do it!
Five!
Four!
I think you've got this!
Three!
Two!
You're so fast!
SUPER fast!
One!
Time's up!
Fin
That was insane.
You kept a pretty good pace the whole time.
She did really well, right?
Tokoyami Towa-san's result is...
Wow! 60 blinks!
Ugh! Just 60?!
You were so close!
What a shame, indeed.
I was so close!
My eyes are absolutely dried out.
They are? (lol)
My eyes weren't watery enough.
Ah, true.
You've got this, Lamy.
I sure do. I'm moistening my eyes now.
Oh, really?
Nice! Keep it up!
How cute.
You gotta store up enough moisture!
Aiming for a World Record with Moist Eyes?!
Yukihana Lamy whamming it up!
What's your target score?
100 blinks.
Now that's just pushing it.
She's aiming for a three-digit score.
That's just crazy!
Well, then.
Ready?
Begin!
And we're off!
Oh?
Hahaha!
Ah, okay. Looking pretty good.
You said 100!
One hundo!
Isn't she kinda slow?
Five!
Four!
Can she make it?
Three!
Two!
One!
Time's up!
Fin
She was definitely slow.
She probably blinked less than me, didn't she?
You all just keep prattling on! Sheesh!
Well, Yukihana Lamy-san's result is...
24 blinks! Just about half of Miko-san's score!
HAH!
Why?!
That's nowhere near 100!
You're trash!
No way! You can't be THAT bad!
Trash?!
I'm sorry, okay?!
Trash!
Garbo!
Noob!
And there we have our results!
The reigning queen still
gets to keep her throne!
What a shame!
Nooo!
Boohoo!
Come on!
Why!
And the next challenge is...
The Tongue Twister World Record!
Yay, yay, yaaay!
Whoa!
Tongue twisters are the bane
of my existence right now!
Currently suffering
from mouth ulcers
That's a win in the bag.
It's an easy win for sure.
Thank you, Towa's mouth ulcers.
Each member gets their
own custom tongue twister
and passes if they say it
three times without stumbling!
As for whether or not you stumble,
that'll be judged by me, Friend A,
and the holo World Records
Tongue Twister Committee.
They're a world-renowned committee
and the ones passing judgment,
Who're they?
so don't blame me for your scores!
Our current world record holder
for this category is
Shiranui Flare-san!
Her record is 9.0 points,
with a maximum score of 10 points.
Whoa!
Damn!
Amazing.
You're scored on multiple factors,
(Rules)
Points are awarded based on
accurate reading of the tongue twister
+ the challenger's cuteness, etc.
so things like cuteness,
your expressions, winks, and the like
Ah!
all factor into your final score.
Seriously?
We need to take those into account?
Miko-san's winks are
already 9 points alone.
Let's go with Yukihana Lamy-sanfirst, shall we?
Oh? Straight off the bat, huh?
She's got a smooth tongue but can she ace this?!
Yukihana Lamy rises to the test!
Here's your Tongue Twister challenge, Lamy-san!
Little Lamy whims her whammies
plowing snow with flimsy hoes.
You'll need to read that three times in a row.
By the way, Miko-san.
Can you try reading it once?
Sure.
I wanna hear it.
Widdle Wamy whims her whammies
powwing snow with fwimsy woes.
That's kinda cute.
That's adorable.
That's so cute!
Well then, Lamy's Tongue Twister
World Record Challenge starts...
Now!
Little Lamy whims her whammies
plowing snow with flimsy hoes.
Faster!
Little Lamy whims ?@>%$"?^
#@?>0&%$"??@>%$?* hoes!
And that's it!
Fin
Whoa!
The third one might've been
too fast for humans to catch.
Ah, I see. So, uh...
Stop abusing your Elf Privileges!
Your result is...
6.2 points!
Exquisite.
Whaaat?
Whoa.
The reason behind your scoring
is that you started off
pretty slow and that, uh,
while it's slow for a tongue twister,
you got 3 extra points from cuteness.
I see.
That's frustrating.
Can she set an elite record?!
Sakura Miko leaps on stage!
Here's your Tongue Twister challenge, Miko-san!
What is it?
Sakura Miko meets a meek gato
sacking sakura shaking her into a mess.
What kind of situation is this?!
It is pretty chaotic.
All right, then!
Miko's Tongue Twister
World Record Challenge starts...
Now!
Sakura Miko meets a meek gato
sacking sakura shaking her into a mess.
sacking sakura shecking her into a mess.
Sakura Miko meets a meek gato
sacking sakura @"$& her into a mess.
That's it!
Fin
That first one was really good!
Aaargh!
It was super smooth!
I screwed up!
Damn
It!
I screwed up!
Damn
She's a mess!
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Damn
I screwed up!
It!
Now then, your result is...
8.2 points!
WHOA! THAT'S AWESOME!
No way!
Well, I'm bad with my vowels
but I think I can handle
everything else just about fine.
It seems so!
Will she be okay with those mouth ulcers?
Tokoyami Towa blesses the field!
Here's your Tongue Twister challenge, Towa-san!
Towa trotted towards a toddler
with cotton candy as a token.
That's so easy!
Isn't this too easy?
Okay!
Towa's Tongue Twister
World Record Challenge starts...
Now!
Towa trotted towards a toddler
with cotton candy as a token.
Oh?!
Ooh...
Towa trotted towards a toggler
with cotton candy as a token.
Towa trotted towards a toddler
Wooow!
Fin
Whoa!
That's definitely a high score.
Your result is...
Did she do it?
...9.1 points!
WHOA!
It's a new record!
Congratulations!
Tongue Twister Queen
Tokoyami Towa
Amazing! Congrats!
Yeees!
Thank you to all my fans
throughout the world!
From now on,
I'm Queen Tokoyami, got it?
She's getting too big
for her britches.
Suddenly her head's inflating.
Miko-san, Lamy-san,
do you both want a retry?
We actually have
some more tongue twisters.
YES!
DEFINITELY!
I wanna retry!
Give us a retry!
Burning with vengeance,
Yukihana Lamy rises from ash!
Here's your Tongue Twister challenge, Lamy-san.
Shatter a sliver of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery dummy suite.
What the heck's with the "dummy"?
What the heck is this?
All I see is a Riffing Challenge!
Shatter a sliver of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery dummy suite.
Why not just read it like you're rapping?
Oh, yeah!
Oh, good point.
Nice idea.
...sleepy Lamy's shivery...
Just feel the rhythm!
Shatter a sliver
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
That sounds pretty cool, no?
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery
dummy suite.
of slippery ice
Yeah! Sounds great!
Aw, yeah!
Are you ready, Lamy-san?
Skrrt ♪
She's dialed in.
All right!
Skrrt ♪
Lamy's Tongue Twister
World Record Challenge starts...
Now!
Shatter a sliver of slippery ice
in sleepy Lamy's shivery dummy suite.
Oh! That's really good!
Fin
That's awesome!
Your result is...
Wow!
It's 9.1 points!
Which means you're tied for 1st place!
IT'S A TIE!
We have a tie!
You're both tied!
And that means we have
two queens in the room!
My, oh, my!
It's the birth of Queen Lamy.
You're kidding me!
Miko-san's face is completely blank.
Her eyes are all over the place.
But if you beat us, Miko-senpai...
Ah! You're right!
You'll be the one true queen!
YEAAAH!
Trampling on everyone's record!
Sakura Miko awakens her elite instinct!
Here's your Tongue Twister challenge, Miko-san!
Sakura Miko prosed her amigo's prospective
probability proposals for the Virtual World.
There you go.
That first half is tough!
Sakura Miko prosed her amiko's...
It sounds like Miko when she says "amigo."
Yeah, it sounds like that!
Are your ears stuffed with wax or something?
Can you say it one more time?
Sakura Miko prosed her amiko's...
Uh-huh...
Hm...
...prosed her amiko's...
Yeah, sounds like
she's saying "Miko."
Sounds scuffed to me.
You all need to get your ears checked!
Okay! Miko's Tongue Twister
World Record Challenge starts...
Now!
Sakura Miko prosed her amigo's prosbective
probability proposals for the Wirtual World.
Sakura Miko prosed her amigo's prospective
probability proposals for the Virtual World.
Fin
Okay! That's it!
That's the face of someone
who went all in.
That was the most effort I've given
for a tongue twister in my entire life.
Ah, I see!
Your score earlier, Miko-san,
was 8.2 points!
That was a pretty good score.
That's pretty high.
Yeah!
I hope you went over it this time!
Let's see her score!
It's 7.3 points!
It dropped!
It went down!
Why?! Why'd it go down?!
That sucks...
That's all the challenges, folks!
How was it for you girls today?
Some of you actually became queens too.
Well, I think I became one in my own right.
You didn't become anything!
You struggled the most out of all of us!
You didn't even come close!
If you enjoyed the video,
please like the video
and subscribe to
the official hololive YouTube channel
as well as our guests' channels!
Please subscribe!
Let's meet again on the next episode
of holo World Records!
See you!
Starring:
Sakura Miko
Tokoyami Towa
Yukihana Lamy
This episode of holo World Records
is brought to you by Sakura Miko...
...Tokoyami Towa, and...
...Yukihana Lamy!