Go forth and seize this shooting star
tsukamaete, hora kono shooting star
A world of our fiction awaits...
I felt like something was amiss in my normal life,
zutto onaji mainichi ni mayoi ga atte mo
But I always pretended not to notice
kizukanai furi o shiteta n da
I couldn't put forth even an ounce of courage
honno chotto no yuuki ga mada dasenakutte
So I dreamily drifted through space
madoromu uchuu de samayotte ita
I'll raise my eyes to the night sky
yozora ni ukabu
And wish upon that star
hoshi ni negai o kakeru n da
I hope...
I never want to give up on
idaiteru yume o
The dream I hold so dear
zettai akirametakunai
So I'll begin this journey
hashiridasu kara
Chase after that shooting star
oikakete ima ano shooting star
As we move forward to a brand new story
mita koto no nai sutoorii susunde iku n da
Hoping that someday
itsu no hi ni ka kitto
It will bring us to the world that we dreamed of
egaita sekai e tadoritsukeru youni