Gah!
Yikes!
Aaahhh!
Guys!
Another chaotic day.
*cough* How do things always end up this way?
We're supposed to be idols,
but we're more like comedians now.
That, too, is hololive.
Remember what happened the other day?
Oh yeah, that was pretty nuts.
Focus on work,
or we're never gonna finish.
'Kay.
Hmm?
Say, what do you think this is?
I found it while cleaning up.
Let's see it.
Interim Report on This Year's Expansion and Effects
Huh?
What is this?
Expanding ********* so quickly past 100 is having adverse effects.
Hang on...
Is it talking about us?
What?
Like, look at this.
Expanding ********* so quickly past 100
This 100 here may be referring to
crossing 100 million views.
******* and ******* only evokes laughter,
showing how far we've strayed from our original goal.
And doesn't it seem like it's complaining
about how we keep doing comedy?
So what's this about getting rid?
Firing?!
Considering the D ****** rating,
we should get rid of the **********.
No way. I've been a proper idol.
But it says here that "it can't go on like this."
Aaaahhh!
I still haven't seen
Lamy-chan's panties!
I still haven't paid off
my PC loan!
Wha...
What's wrong?
Wh-What is it?
What?!
Fired?!
But I've been a pure and lovely idol
the whole time!
You have?
Okay.
It's not too late. Let's all train
to improve our abilities as idols!
So...
What's happening here?
We went and bought
some classic idol merch!
Dress up first, ask questions later!
Why does it sound convincing
coming from you?
We all picked out
things for ourselves.
You be the judge, Mio.
No way! You guys are sure
to mess around!
Just trust us.
Okay, I'll lead things off.
Why is even your idea of idols
so damn boomer?
Pop culture always gets rebooted. Always.
Ow!
Next!
Hey! That's my nostril!
No! Give it back!
Stop it!
Okay, seriously,
you're crossing the line here!
Oh, zip it! What are you?
An idol!
And where are we?
hololive!
Then we don't have a problem, right?!
Right?!
Cut it out, Marine!
We're training to be better idols here!
Stand down!
Somebody grab a rope!
This is hopeless.
We're becoming better comedians
instead of better idols!
We're screwed if we don't do something!
Waaah!
Say... What makes an idol, anyway?
Hmm... When you shine on stage?
When you're angelic?
When you Just Do It?
Well, I...
I think an idol is someone
who shines and puts smiles on faces
while devoting themselves to something they love.
I don't care if people say
the things I do aren't fit for an idol.
To me, playing games and talking on stream
are my way of shining.
I want to do the things I love,
together with the fans and the rest of hololive,
That's the kind of idol I want to be.
Well, everyone's got their idea
of what an idol should be.
That's right!
And it's not right to judge and fire people
just based on that alone.
Let's all go talk to the brass tomorrow.
Yeah.
Sounds like a plan.
You in here, management?!
Don't see 'em.
Are they slacking off?
But look. A-chan's here.
Hmm?
Oh, hello, everyone.
A-chan!
Yes?
We may be the furthest thing
from perfect idols!
But it's up to us to decide
who we want to be as idols.
Together with our fans,
we'll keep getting closer to our goal.
And we don't think it's fair for someone else
to judge us and lay us off.
We want you to reconsider the whole
judging and firing thing.
If you don't, my ship will...
My dream will sink!
My loan!
Hmm...
Well, we're not laying anyone off, for one.
And we think it's great that you're all
growing into your own, unique idols.
Right?!
Wha?
Huh?
But it says right here
that you're considering layoffs!
Uh...
Oh, you know what this is?
One of the staff members' diet manifesto.
What's the 100 for?
They crossed a hundred kilos, apparently.
And the D rating?
Their medical checkup result, I believe.
Get rid of what?
Excess fat.
Why were parts of it redacted?
I think they felt embarrassed
after writing it out.
H...
How misleading!
Heh heh...
Hmm...
Oh, while I have you all here,
we're currently planning
the next phase of our idol project.
The idea is to form various units
and hold a concert.
What? Tell me more!
Wow, that sounds fun.
Count me in!
I wanna do, like, comedy skits during the concert.
Having trio units will let us land a wider range of jokes.
Back to comedy again?!
The excitement we've longed for draws ever closer
As it spreads like wildfire across the world
We'll shine a light that puts smiles on faces
Because we're not alone, because we have rivals
Even the fiercest competition
Becomes part of the fun
Dear My Friends
When we sprint toward our goal, it'll be fantastic
We'll make our hopes bloom into our future
Take it one step at a time and aim for the top
Believing in ourselves will bring our hearts happiness
Let's relish this with all we've got
Because it will, one day for sure,
Make our wildest fantasies come true
Dreaming Days
Make sure you don't miss our idols shining on stage!
Here I begin to blossom.