When it's cold, hotpot's the way to go.
Yay!
So, here's today's.
It begins! It begins!
S-Subaru?!
We got a case!
Police! Police!
H-Hold on a second.
Your excuses fall on deaf ears!
Curse you, impostor!
I was just told that duck hotpot is good!
For real?
Hmm, how intriguing.
Plus, it'd hurt to see
a fellow 2nd Gen behind bars.
That ain't me!
What?!
Indeed. This is a rubber duck.
Come on!
You tricked us?!
But we've successfully
lured the real duck out now.
Crap, I fell for a trap!
Capture Subaru!
I can't believe they think I'm food!
Subaru acquired!
Huh? Have you gotten tan, Subaru-sama?
Wait, this isn't Subaru...
Whomst'd've?!
Oh, found you, Subaru!
Gah!
They're gonna get me this time for sure!
Ah!
Looks yum.
Can't we just make hotpot out of this?
I'm starving, am I.
Let's have sitting duck hotpot
with leek tonight.
Don't just forget about me!
And here we have a 2nd Gen hotpot.
If you enjoyed this,
please subscribe for more!