Disclaimer:
This video has been self-censored
to limit its boundless sexuality.
I'm going to go full tilt now, okay?
There you go, blowing your load again.
I blew my load early.
Are we not doing phrasing anymore?!
Starring:
Aki Rosenthal
Yuzuki Choco
Yozora Mel
This show is brought to you by Aki Rosenthal...
...Yuzuki Choco...
...and Yozora Mel.
Hitting the perfect spot
and taking a load off your mind,
this is the very first
"Sounds of Rapture Championship"!
Sounds of Rapture Championship
Yeah!
I ask you!
Do you like feeling good?
Love it!
Are you game for taking the lead
and doing something that would feel good?
Huh? That sounds like [REDACTED], A-sama.
What are you implying with that look?!
Are you offering [REDACTED] to me?
Are you actually looking forward to this? Gosh!
Listen! Let's keep this PG!
This isn't members-only content, okay?!
So, I believe we've asked each of you
hololive 1st Gen:
Aki Rosenthal
Yozora Mel
hololive 2nd Gen:
Yuzuki Choco
hololive Staff:
Friend A, a.k.a A-chan
to bring whatever you think
will produce pleasant sounds.
Rules: Whoever produces the most pleasant sounds using
the items at their disposal will be declared the winner
Okay.
I see, I see.
I'm going for the win.
As for the judging,
it will be thoroughly deliberated by
the International Society of Pleasure Review.
I have never heard of this society!
Where did you even find them?
If you win, you will be declared the Rapture Queen,
so go all out, but make sure
this doesn't end up being rated R-18.
Oh, so R-15 is fair game?
R-15?!
Can you please stop trying to
figure out where to draw the line?
Yuzuki Choco's Sounds of Rapture
So, what will you be going with?
I'll be using a pear.
Sounds of Rapture Using a Pear
Oh, a pear? Nice.
That does look good.
That looks yummy!
Yuzuki Choco's Pear-Shaped
Sounds of Rapture begin in...
Three...
two...
one...
Rub-a-dub-dub...
Note: She's just eating a pear.
Whoa, that sounds really nice.
*slurp*
Oh, I hear something
being sucked out.
She did suck on it a little.
Water content.
I guess this is one juicy pear.
Yeah.
That's all it is.
Yeah, yeah!
Nothing more.
Yeah, nothing more.
Yeah, yeah.
*om*
[REDACTED]
She went in a little harder this time.
Is it good?
Oh, very good.
Cute!
I hate to admit it,
but that made my heart skip a beat.
Cute.
I'm going to go full tilt now, okay?
Go for it.
*om*
Love that look.
She's making the perfect expressions.
[REDACTED]
Mm...
Mnn!
Mm...!
You okay over there?
Are you okay?
Hnnn!
Fin
Okay, that's that!
I got a little too [REDACTED].
Thank you for that passionate performance.
Uh, things got a little hot
under the collar over here too.
After careful and thorough deliberation,
the International Society of Pleasure Review
has awarded you a score of...
9.6 out of 10!
What?
Awesome!
Congratulations!
So they enjoyed the [REDACTED], huh?
Aw, I went and nailed it!
A super-high score!
You missed out on the last 0.4
because they wanted it to keep going.
Some of the Judges Wanted More
But our time is limited, so...
Ah, I see!
So leaving them wanting more is good.
So I could've kept going...
Kept goin—
Next up is Mel-san. Are you ready?
Yeah!
Ready as ever!
Yozora Mel's Sounds of Rapture
I brought with me, well...
Some body soap.
Oh, body soap? Great idea!
Sounds of Rapture Using Body Soap
Yozora Mel's Bodaciously Soapy
Sounds of Rapture begin in...
Three...
two...
one...
I sure worked up a sweat.
Ah, she's taking it from the top.
I need to wash up.
Wait, what? That sounds good!
Note: She's washing with body soap.
Wh-What's that sound?
Foam?
Work up a foam...
You can hear it.
*foamy*
Sure can.
*bubble*
You know, what POV are we
supposed to take here?
Oh, right...
But you know,
You know, what POV are we
supposed to take here?
she's washing herself...
in the [REDACTED].
Just think of yourself
as a bathroom wall.
Okay, so a fly on the wall.
That foam all over you? It's me.
Hello? Why's she joining in?
This is you, Choco-sensei?
It's all me.
I will take you all in.
You're so soft... it [REDACTED].
The sounds are getting rhythmical.
They sure are, huh?
I wanna be enveloped in this scent forever.
That scent? It's mine.
That's some talkative foam.
But what happens to it in the end?
Good question.
Will it be washed away?
Okay, all this washing has
made me sparkling clean.
No, this isn't enough.
Huh? It's not?
Are you sure you haven't missed anything down here?
Oh, I forgot to wash [REDACTED].
Okay, hold up...
Wait, timeout!
No... not so hard!
Okay, that's that!
Fin
I washed up nice and good.
Nice and good?
You sure, uh, kept going faster
as you went along.
After careful and thorough deliberation,
the International Society of Pleasure Review
has awarded you...
a score of 9.2 out of 10!
Ooh!
You lost points because
they couldn't figure out where to end it.
Couldn't Figure Out Where to Stop
Honestly,
even I had no idea where to stop.
Last but not least, Aki-san! Are you ready?
Will there be a new high score?
Aki Rosenthal's Sounds of Rapture
I'm going to go with a combination of things.
Oh, a combination?
G-Give me a bit.
Take your time.
I hear that rustling!
As do I.
Are you sure you haven't started already?
Well?
It just happened...
There you go, blowing your load again.
I blew my load early.
Are we not doing phrasing anymore?!
Now, for what I brought...
Yeah?
Handcuffs!
Handcuffs?!
Sounds of Rapture Using Handcuffs
Seriously, handcuffs? Cutting right to the chase?
And what will you use in combination with it?
Well... all in due time.
Due time?!
AkiRose's Cuffed Sounds of Rapture begin in...
Three...
two...
one...
See?
This is what you get...
for trying to run away all the time!
I need to keep you under lock and key,
Note: She's putting on handcuffs.
or you just won't get it, will you?
*click*
Oh no! We got cuffed!
Not so tight! No! Ahh!
Wait, she's talking to you two?!
You're in this?!
I mean, you can't...
leave Melty Kiss alone for one second,
or they'll start [REDACTED].
She's the crazy girlfriend!
You see?
You need to pay more attention to me!
Or you aren't getting out of these.
Let's all [REDACTED] together, then.
I didn't know you liked being cuffed so much.
But I know how it is. This always happens.
You act like you have eyes only for me,
and then start talking about somebody else.
So I'm going to seal off your mouth with this.
A new challenger!
*fwip*
Time to shut up.
No!
With this...
You can't take anyone else's name
or think about anyone but me.
Uh... Wait, Aki-sama!
But then I can't call out your name either...
Wait, wait, Aki-sama!
I want to [REDACTED] with you, though!
You're so needy.
Fine, I'll take off the tape... using this.
*creak*
Nn...
Hmm?!
Is that a box cutter?
*creeeaaak*
This is dangerous territory!
Aki-sama... wait...
*fwip*
[REDACTED]!
[REDACTED]...
Don't resist!
You'll get hurt!
Fin
You just brought out all these things
like you always carry them around.
Yeah, that's why she had them ready.
I do carry them around, yes.
You do? So I was right!
Standard loadout.
I bet she does this all the time.
Definitely. She was so used to it!
After careful and thorough deliberation,
Give me a good score.
the International Society of Pleasure Review
has awarded you...
What's it going to be?
10 out of 10!
Congratulations!
For real?
Actually?
I knew it. People want to be under lock and key.
I see.
So that's the kink.
The fact that you used three items
Used multiple sounds and noises
to create a crescendo of pleasure.
and had the other two
playing their parts to perfection...
I think that impressed the judges a lot.
Results
So there we have it! Our very first Rapture Queen...
is AkiRose-san!
Rapture Queen
Aki Rosenthal
Congratulations!
Congrats!
Thank you very much.
This...
This proves that the world loves **nd**e.
It's clear now.
If you enjoyed this video,
If you enjoyed this video, please subscribe to hololive's
official YouTube channel and smash that like button.
please subscribe to hololive's official YouTube channel and smash that like button.
If there's ever a second edition of
the Sounds of Rapture Championship,
we hope to see you there again!
Bye-bye!
Starring:
Aki Rosenthal
Yuzuki Choco
Yozora Mel
This show was brought to you by Aki Rosenthal...
...Yuzuki Choco...
...and Yozora Mel!