Whoa, hang on, Robocosan!
You're glitching out!
Um, it's the afterlife?
Wha...
That's horrifying!
Drawing with Control!
The Holo Master Artist Test!
Y-Yay...
Yay?
#HoloMasterArtistTest
We have with us today
three of hololive's most esteemed
master artists.
Take it away!
Pleasure to be here!
Self-Portrait
hololive's resident doodler,
Natsuiro Matsuri here.
Gen 1: Natsuiro Matsuri
How cute!
So cute!
Adorable!
That's quite the beautiful drawing.
Would that happen
to be me on the right?
It is!
I thought I'd try to
get on the judge's good side.
Hey! That's cheating!
The game hasn't even started yet!
Self-Portrait
Hellobo!
Gen 0: Robocosan
Here's my drawing!
It's very round and cute!
Feast your eyes on my art!
I see a hand holding chopsticks.
So cute!
Are you about to be eaten?
Yeah, I just stole some food, see?
How adorable.
That's so cute!
Om-nom-nom-nom.
And last but not least,
the master among masters.
Let's hear it!
Self-Portrait
From hololive 1st generation,
Gen 1: Aki Rosenthal
with artistic talent
envied the whole world over,
the impressionist
Aki Rosenthal, AKA AkiRose.
Okay, hold on a sec.
You're wearing socks and gloves,
but none of the most important parts
are covered up.
You're right!
Aki-chan, are you naked here?
Any more, and we might
uncover some dark truths,
so let's leave it at that.
Huh?
Holo Master Artist Test!
The Rules
Our contestants will have to draw pictures
while controlling their art skills.
They will each be assigned
a target ranking, from 1st to 3rd.
If you're assigned 3rd,
your goal is to draw the worst picture.
If you're assigned 1st,
your goal is to draw the best picture.
I get it!
You need to draw with control
to get the desired ranking.
I see.
The ranking will be determined by myself,
Friend A, and my infallible artistic eye.
If everyone gets their
assigned rank, it's a success.
But if even one is off,
it's a failure.
So good luck, and try your best!
Okay!
Holo Master Artist Test!
1st Piece
Your first prompt is:
Dog!
Doggie!
This should be easy.
Dogs are so cute!
Next, you'll be assigned
your target rankings,
but I'm not allowed to see those.
So I'll be waiting in another room,
finishing up some
of my backlogged work...
Always the company slave...
Don't mention that
in front of the audience!
Anyway, let me know
once you're done drawing.
Goodbye.
Let's see our assigned ranks!
Right!
Give it to us!
Okay!
I see.
Well, we're screwed.
I just need to draw something worse than that.
"That"?
As for Roboco-shenpai,
just draw something that
can barely be considered a dog.
Got it.
Hang on!
I object to this treatment!
Let's get right into it!
Start!
I just gotta draw
the best picture, right?
Boy, this is terrible.
Oh dear, I may have drawn something
better than I even imagined.
Are you sure?
Well, that's what
we're hoping from you.
Of course! I've got this covered.
Now to spice it up a bit.
Spice it up?
Spice?
Learn to stop
when you're ahead, AkiRose!
No, see, this part is essential!
Are you sure?
Looks like we're all done,
so let's get A-chan back in here to judge.
Okay!
Right.
Oh, A-chan!
Is everyone finished?
Yep!
We're finished, A-chan!
Uh-huh!
We gave it our best shot!
I can't wait to see
how they all turned out.
Let's start with Matsuri-san's drawing.
Here it is!
Ta-dah!
Whoa! Um...
It's a dog.
Yes, I see.
The dog says hi.
Yes, yes.
Next up, Robocosan.
Ta-dah!
Whoa, hang on, Robocosan!
You're glitching out!
You can't keep skipping
your maintenance like this!
You can tell what it is, right?
Whatever it is, it's scaring me!
See, I received a transmission
from outer space...
Huh?!
I think it's pretty good.
Isn't it?
People will question my sanity
if I compliment this,
so I'd rather not.
Things are getting pretty strange here.
AkiRose-san, what does
our master artist have for us?
Have a look!
I see.
Ah... how should I interpret this?
It kinda looks buff.
No, come on!
Like it could stand up on two legs.
It's obviously a very fluffy doggo!
But Robocosan's looks so unholy,
I'm not sure how to interpret this.
Gosh, how do I judge this?
Why are all of your pictures so disturbing?
Even when Aki-chan isn't trying to...
What about this masterpiece is disturbing?
But I'm guessing Aki-chan is 1st place.
The other two are clearly doing it on purpose.
Now, Matsuri-chan decided
not to draw a background at all.
I'm not sure if that makes her 2nd or 3rd.
As for Robocosan's, I have no idea.
What is this thing?!
Here's my ranking, starting with 1st.
1st: AkiRose-san.
2nd: Robocosan.
3rd: Matsuri-san.
Does it match your target ranking,
or is this a failure?
Let's see their target ranking!
Friend A's Ranking
Target Ranking
Ahh!
A-chan!
Which makes this a failure!
Failure
You big dummy!
How could you not tell?
I was channeling my inner Aki-chan!
This was inspired by Aki-san, was it?
I don't think you could draw this badly
if you held the pen in your mouth.
Cut me some slack here!
Holo Master Artist Test!
2nd Piece
Your next prompt is:
Robot!
I see.
We've got the perfect model
right next to us!
That's true.
Of course, it's up to you what
kind of robot you want to draw.
Next, you'll be assigned
your target rankings.
I'll go to another room so I don't see.
Maybe I'll catch up on
some anime I've recorded.
Goodbye!
Okay, let's see what
our target rankings are this time.
I see.
I see!
Wait, 1st place is kinda hard.
This is looking pretty bad for us.
Oh, we'll be fine.
We've got this in the bag!
Piece of cake!
This game is so hard.
It sure is.
Really? I haven't felt that at all.
You should.
This is on your shoulders, you know.
Miss Master Artist.
Well, let's get A-chan, then.
Please, A-chan! Come back to us!
I'm here!
I will get it right!
I will get it right! x2
I will get it right! x3
I will get it right! x4
I will get it right! x5
Let's start by taking a look
at Matsuri-san's drawing.
Here it is!
Ah, that's a robot all right.
I see what you're doing here.
This contains something else.
You've added some
AkiRosenium, haven't you?
That's my impression.
Looks good to me.
I injected it right in!
It's spreading!
Next, let's see Robocosan's.
Here it is! Ta-dah!
Oh! How cute!
It's a self-portrait!
That's right!
That's very cute!
I can imagine a game in this style.
I'm a robot, after all.
Now the biggest question:
What does AkiRose-san have for us?
I'm super proud of this one.
Here it is!
Right!
Oh! That's quite good!
A bit old-fashioned, though.
Old-fashioned?!
But it's quite good for you, Aki-san.
The lines are straight, for one.
Right!
Yeah, for sure.
Great effort!
Now, time to decide on my ranking.
I think this one's pretty easy.
Oh?
1st: AkiRose-san.
2nd: Robocosan.
3rd: Matsuri-san.
How about it?
Let's see their target ranking!
Friend A's Ranking
Target Ranking
A-chan!
A-chan?
A-chan, look at my smug face there!
No way!
Seriously?
Look at how I'm sparkling!
See, Roboco-shenpai expresses
her feelings through her art.
I see.
Aki-san's threw me off!
I couldn't―
I can't tell what expression it has!
Well, robots don't have
facial expressions.
Isn't that one of their selling points?
Unfortunately, we've failed once more!
Failure
Ahh!
Holo Master Artist Test!
3rd Piece
Your next prompt is:
Friend A in 100 Years.
I see.
Okay...
That's tough!
Especially since it's a person.
In 100 years?
Do we get to decide if
you're still alive or not?
I'd be about 120 years old.
I see.
A-chan, are you human?
Yes, of course I am!
I'll be doing some work in
another room, so I don't see.
Let me know once you're done drawing.
Goodbye!
Okay!
I'm afraid to see the ranking,
but here we go.
Give it to us!
Ahh...
I had a feeling this was coming.
Gosh, why do I never
get assigned 3rd place?
The staff clearly has it out for us.
I guess we should start drawing.
Let's draw!
100 years from now...
So either she's all wrinkly...
We could have her look exactly the same,
or make her all elderly.
Right.
Aki-chan being 2nd
is the biggest hurdle.
That's for sure.
But Matsuri-chan,
if you draw the best one,
then as long as I don't do better...
That's true.
I have faith that there's no way
AkiRose will draw better than me.
Darn it!
Don't say that part out loud!
Let's get A-chan back in here.
A-chan!
Here!
Are you A-chan from
100 years in the future?
That's me.
My, how exciting.
Gosh, I sound like Dor*emon.
Let's start with Matsuri-san's picture.
Here it is!
Ah! I look the same.
That's so good!
Oh!
Very well drawn.
So good!
Since A-chan is virtual...
I'm eternal.
Right.
Forever young and
forever productive.
A true asset to the company.
Oh gosh, I'm practically a robot!
100 years later,
and still a company slave.
This is very well drawn.
I have high hopes for...
It's so good!
Indeed.
Mine came out pretty good,
too, so I'm excited.
Oh, really? Then let's have
a look at Robocosan's.
Please do!
Wha...
Is this a horror piece?
I'm scared!
That's terrifying!
Since when is this your style?
Um, it's the afterlife?
Wha...
That's horrifying!
I'm scared!
You don't have to zoom in like that!
In other words, I'm dead!
That's dead me!
Oh my gosh!
I'm leaving behind shadows!
There's a trail of something behind me!
You're walking forward, bit by bit.
<- Past
Future ->
The years of your youth are that way.
How deep.
Finally, hololive's problem child.
Let's see what Aki-san drew.
Okay.
Here it is!
Ah, I see!
I have to ask,
why are your people always naked?
Life exists on a plane that
transcends mere clothing.
I'd rather not transcend
my clothes while I'm alive!
Don't kill me yet!
It looks like a post-apocalyptic
scene or something!
What's the deal here?
See, you've grown so old
that your hair's turned all white.
But I've got a lot of it!
That's like an afro!
You need a cane,
but you're still standing.
Aki-san, could you please
take this seriously?
But I drew that
as seriously as I could!
Sheesh.
We should have had
an advisor for this game.
Here's my ranking, starting with 1st.
Please be right!
Okay!
1st: Matsuri-san.
Oh!
2nd: AkiRose-san.
And 3rd: Robocosan.
Ohh!
That's gotta be it!
Are you sure about that?
Huh?
Very interesting.
What'll I do if I get this wrong?
I might have to shave my head.
Let's see their target ranking!
Friend A's Ranking
Target Ranking
1st: Matsuri-san, 2nd: AkiRose-san, 3rd: Robocosan!
Yes!
You did it!
Congrats!
Which makes this a success!
Success
Yay!
Congrats!
I finally got it!
This game wasn't a complete failure!
We did it!
I think A-chan got all of mine correct?
That's right!
I always felt confident with Matsuri-san's.
So much for our shared bond
as Robovitan A!
Yours looked like something
from a horror movie!
Maybe you're mentally unstable.
You're one to talk!
Wait, why?
Please like this video
and subscribe to this channel
and the participants' channels!