Yo, lamb chops, go buy an umbrella.
Why me?
What does that mean?
Fine, I'll make do.
Why this?!
You know I don't carry those foldable thingies with me.
Not what I'm asking!
Oh?
Scawy!
I see nothing but skirt!
Quit wobbling! Flex 'em abs!
Yo, yo, yo!
Fourth Chairman of the Kiryu Group
Kiryu Coco
Uh, Kiryu-chan?
I gotta stay still while this thing's onscreen.
No... I can't believe she's graduating...
Kiryu Group Member
Tokoyami Towa
Waaah!
Whaaa?!
You gotta freeze for this thing!
Kiryu Group Member
Tokoyami Towa
But I'm just so sad...
It'll be okay if you collect the Seven Balls.
Don't cross that copyright line!
Prepare to pass on!
Which gang sent ya, punk?
I just... I just wanted to make you
graduate with my own hands.
Listen, you keep yer law-abiding ass outta this!
Not a word more outta you two!
Phew, close shave.
You're pwetty cwazy yourself.
What's with the lump on her head?
She got wan over earlier.
Call a damn ambulance!
She's built like a tank. A wittle hit-and-run won't hurt her.
But she's been dis-armed!
I crossed my pain threshold earlier.
But I don't wanna waste a second
of the time I have left with y'all.
Cococha...
Some spit'll fix it up.
Like hell it will!
Lick it.
Okay...
Huh?!
Chairman, with your arm as good as new,
is there anything you wanna do?
Can't you see it written on my face?
All I see is that you're a looker!
What are you, a scratch card?
I wanna save Nishinari
Well, it's time for me to go
to the promised land.
Cococha...
How'd you like the year and a half
you spent with me?
It was the best.
I had so much fun.
I wasn't bored for a single moment.
Coco! 😭
Good!
We'll never forget you,
Coco!
Cocochi!
Cococha!
Good morning, everyone!
It's time once again
for Morning Coco LIVE!
And we're joined right away
by one of our reporters.
Uh...
Here's Coco-san, live on the scene.
Reporting
from outside the hololive office
Hi!
Wha?
Guys, come look! She's here!
We're in this together, right?
Right?!
Right!
Then you're all graduating with me!
Hell nah! That's a different matter entirely!
Take this!
Gaa!
Hey, these are counterfeit!
Parting gift from me. Cherish it.
We don't need this trash!
Live strong, you guys.
And have a good morning, motherf*ckers!