Hey, a camera.
These things still exist in 2021?
Uh, yeah?
Time to try it out.
Whoa!
Watame just metamorphosized!
Halp!
Man, that's scary.
Watame-chan?
That camera, duh!
Look, just put it back.
...
Okay, I bet she got some crazy idea!
She's up to no good!
A-chan! KanaKana!
Oh, Mel-senp...
Cheese!
Yikes! My eyes!
It's rude to take pics of people
without permission.
You okay, Kanata-san?
Love thy neighbor.
Holy moly!
Where'd Mel-chan run off to?
…
Wha?
Evil hath taken over thee.
Divine maintenance ye require from me!
The heck?
In death do salvation be!
Judge, jury, and executioner?!
And why am I included?!
Mel! Try taking another picture!
Okay!
Huh? What was I...
Prepare to die, Ookami Mio!
Why single me out?!
And why did you take another?!
Fun things are fun, okay?!
Gonna kick yer candy ass!
So much for divine!
Then you know what Omarun did?
I spy a lion passing by!
Go, Mel!
On it!
Help us, queen of the jungle!
Meow.
Aww, how adorbs! ♡
Don't just leave m—
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!