Get this, get this!
I got a pet for myself!
A pet?!
A doggo? A kitty?
Show me...
Yikes.
What do you make of it?
Well, a cactus is technically a living thing,
so I hesitate to say it can't be a pet...
Not that part! I mean Aki-chan.
I feel like she's the same as ever...
The Aki-chan I know wouldn't complain to a fidget spinner.
So I told them,
I want no part of your bread-and-butter sob story!
Okay, she is acting weird.
Hmm?
What's that?
"The Steam and Eat hololive Members'
Pillow Covers Syndicate"
Uhm...
Now that you've seen it,
you can't escape the White Death!
Shirakami!
"The Steam and Eat hololive Members'
Pillow Covers Syndicate,"
or "The Steam-and-Eat Cover Syndicate,"
can't be stopped!
Syndica-ha-ha!
What a misleading short form.
Look what you've done to Aki-chan!
Radish...
What did you put her through?
We put her on night duty turning pillow covers inside-out.
Ah...
No! Aki-chan's trying to eat her cactus!
💚
That's not food!
Hup!
Nice receive!
The Syndicate needs AkiRose!
We'll be taking her back!
No! What do you mean, you need her, anyway?
She can stuff her mouth with meatballs
and cry into her pillow
while chanting "Pillow Book" over and over...
What?!
That's too much for her!
No, she can handle it.
I know she has the potential!
Give it a shot!
Urk... Pillow Book...
・_・
See! You can do it!
Man, she's too good.
And so, AkiRose rejoined the Syndicate
and became Chief Officer.
Congratulations, Aki-senpai!
The Syndicate is forever!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!