hololive IDOL PROJECT - Suspect
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Kyota.
Vocals: Roboco san, Aki Rosenthal, Nakiri Ayame
I didn't keep an eye on you for no reason
itazura ni kimi o zutto miteita wake janai
Try to figure out what's on my mind
boku no kangae o atete goran yo
Your quirks, your gaze, down to your wink
sasaina shigusa shisen mabataki
I already have you in the palm of my hand
kimi wa mou tenohira ni
I won't fall for such an open trap
mukidashi no torappu nante kakaru wake nai wa
Nor would your sweet words lure me in
amai kotoba ni mo madowasarenai
The innermost depths of your heart are an open book
kokoro no oku no oku no oku made misukashichau yo
(Looking Thinking Touching Feeling,)
Why you know?
I know it
(Looking Thinking Touching Feeling,)
Understand?
(Meaning, meaning of love)
“Are you Ready?”
As I thought, you really have no idea
jikaku nai deshou ne omoidoori ni
that you're being played with!
kimi wa ugokasareteiru koto!
I'm not that simple, so be careful
tanjun janai no kakehiki no hinto o
not to miss any hints
subete miotosanai de
(meaning of love, meaning of love)
The throbbing of our hearts
kasokushiteku
(meaning of love, meaning of love)
is just getting faster
futari no kodou
(meaning of love, meaning of love)
Let the mind games move on
shinrisen wa
to the next stage
tsugi no suteeji e