Oh hey, an apple!
Dibs!
Aah...
Wait, don't!
Blech!
Matsuri-senpai!
Crayons?
Yes, believe it or not!
Anything drawn with these crayons...
...materializes in real life?
How could you tell?
Well, it's a familiar setup.
Basically...
...Sora-senpai drew this apple
that I bit into?
How could you tell?!
I'm sorry, okay?
It's all my fault
for drawing a sand apple.
Why sand?
But hey, this seems fun.
Why don't we use these to battle?
Sounds good!
Let's do it!
Begin crafting your weapons!
Done! Behold my Knockout Paper Fan!
I'm done with my Hammering Hammer too!
Mine's done too.
Lemme see!
Ta-dah!
She's way too into it.
I need to test its strength.
She's completely lost it!
I'll distract her!
Knock her out with your fan!
G-Gotcha!
Aight, Sora-senpai! Bring it...
Menacing
Mommy...
She lost to her sheer aura!
Ma. Tsu. Ri. Chan...
Hold up. It could just be a toy sword.
Okay, yeah, no. It's the real deal.
Hello! Y'all seem to be having fun!
Run away, Kanatan! It's not safe!
We have a killer in the house!
Eek!
Huh?
Wait, what was I doing?
In the nick of time!
These scribbles go away
after a certain amount of time.
Is that so?
So it's time for us...
Close shave, huh?
Look who's talking.
Huh?
Where... am I?
What's going on?
Am I gonna disappear too?
And that's the story
I was planning to draw.
Too scary!
Less talking, more drawing.
Sometimes, Sora unleashes her mischievous streak.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!