KAAA
MEEE
HAAA
HAAAAAAA!
Wow, Lamy-san,
that's the first time I'm seeing that face.
You're that mad, huh?
I'm not wearing any underwear at all right now!
Hype Meter
Good morning, girls!
Morning!
Good morning!
I found this on the floor in the office.
Did any of you girls drop this?
I didn't drop anything, no.
No, I don't think so.
I've got all my stuff on me.
What is that?
First time seeing such a thing.
What is it?
There's a dial on this thing.
I'm gonna try giving it a spin.
The number's changed.
Do you girls maybe know
what this is used for?
I've got no clue at all.
No clue.
Nope.
No idea.
What makes you think we'd know?
The heck are you on about?
I'm really sleepy here.
You all seem a little down in the dumps.
What happened?
Don't tell me this dial
has something to do with it?
Let's try resetting it back to 50%.
Crank it up to 50%...
Okay. It's back to 50%.
What're we doing for today's episode?
Yeah! What're we doing?
What's the plan today?
Yeah!
I'm so excited!
Ah! So that's what this does!
What're we gonna do today?
Wait a minute. This dial
can control the hype levels
of people nearby, can't it?
This is gonna be good!
Girls!
For today's plan,
I'll be asking you all some questions!
Today's Plan
Answer A-chan's questions!
Huh? That's it?
Yeah!
Is it really okay to do such a thing?
Yeah! It's perfectly fine!
This is a perfectly valid episode!
Let's get started, shall we?
Let's crank the dial up to 100%.
100%!
All right! Gimme 100% energy, girls!
Go all out
and give us your best self intro!
Knock,
knock,
goes the fox!
I'm from hololive Gen 1 & GAMERS!
I'm your super cute & lovable fox,
Shirakami Fubuki!
WHAAAT?!
ABSOLUTELY ADORABLEEE!
The first and probably
last time I'm ever doing this!
I'm from hololive Gen 3!
Shirogane Noel! Happy to be here!
WHOOO!
Hey!
You came, ta!
My USP is my 50 kg grip strength!
*Currently still updating her record.
I'm gonna crush you... with LOVE!
Warning!
The angel of hololive Gen 4,
Amane Kanata here!
YEAAAH!
My head's a liver!
'Cuz I can take a drinking!
Yukihana Lamy from hololive Gen 5 is here!
LET'S GOOO!
Okay! Calm down!
All right!
LET'S GOOO!
That's enough!
It's like I'm in a jungle.
Questions from A-chan
Favorite Food
So, girls!
What were your favorite foods again?
Let's see... well,
it'd have to be drinking snacks.
Oh!
I like stuff that goes with sake.
That sounds nice.
As for me,
I like salmon roe.
Ah!
They're really delicious!
I always love eating salmon roe rice balls!
That does sound delicious!
It's super good!
It's obvious what my favorite food is!
It's beef rice bowls!
Uh-huh.
Obviously!
I love my beef rice bowls.
I like Salisbury steak!
That's so cute!
Now let's crank the dial down to...
8%.
Let's try asking them again.
What was your favorite food again, Lamy-san?
C*lorieMate.
Pretty straightforward.
That's all you'll ever need.
It doesn't go well with sake, though.
Is that okay?
Who the heck drinks in the mornings?
Yikes. She's scary.
Nobody does that, right?
Sorry for making assumptions.
By the way, Kanata-san! What do you like?
Hmm...
Salted rice balls, I guess?
Plain salted rice balls?
As long as it's edible, I s'pose.
As long as it has flavor, huh?
How about you, Noel-san?
Bean sprouts.
Bean sprouts? Ah...
They work well for vegetable hotpots.
'Cause it's cheap.
As long as it's edible.
Basic Criteria
[As long as it's edible]
I see.
As long as it's edible.
As long as it's edible, I see.
Uh...
You're staring at the floor, Fubuki-san.
Are you okay?
Do you need anything like your favorite food?
I'd like some dried baby sardines, then.
Dried baby sardines? Uh-huh...
They're pretty good.
Are you...
They are.
They're delicious.
Are you okay without meat?
Baby sardines are the best.
Don't bring up anything but baby sardines.
Baby sardines are the best, huh?
Yeah. Agreed.
Baby sardines are life.
It's delicious and chewy.
Questions from A-chan
Embarrassing Secrets
Do you have any
embarrassing secrets you're hiding?
I'd love to hear stories like,
"Truth be told, I'm hiding so and so." if you have them.
Secrets, huh... let's see...
I've been watching my own VODs lately
Uh-huh.
and I noticed that I have
some habits in my laughter,
Ah, I see.
so I looked up
"How to laugh cutely" on YouTube
You really dug deep, huh?
and tried to mimic them...
Laugh for us!
How do you normally laugh?
I normally laugh like
Hah.
Haha.
Heh
Hold on.
Pfft.
Hah.
Haha.
Heh.
I can't just laugh on command, okay?!
As for cutesy laughter, it'd be something like...
You sound like a doll from a horror game.
Is that even a cute laugh?!
I'm working on it, okay?!
Uh-huh.
Let's try this!
Noel-san.
Yeah?
You got any recent
embarrassing stories to share?
Whaaat?!
Like in your private life.
Are you really asking me that?
Well, as per a certain wolf senpai
who revealed it on her stream,
I'm testing something out.
Uh-huh.
Oh?
I'm trying out the
"No underwear health act."
Whaaat?!
Seriously?!
The feeling of liberation is just insane.
What?!
Really?
You recommend it, huh?
How about you, Lamy-san?
I'm gonna do the same starting today!
Today?! That's big news!
Phew!
Two out of the four of you
are now going commando.
All right, Kanata-san!
It's all for your health!
Hmm, let's see...
I'm not wearing any underwear at all right now!
We have a 3rd one!
Please put some on. Right now.
We weren't looking for commandos
for this episode, though.
But since you're at home,
it's perfectly fine to go
without underwear, right?
Yeah! Totally!
Everyone's taking off their underwear
just from the hype.
The ones wearing clothes
are the strange ones, right?!
Who wears clothes?!
Just go au naturel!
Okay. Let's drop the hype meter down.
Let's lower it down.
Oh. Everyone clammed up.
Come on girls, tell me
some embarrassing secrets!
Wow, Lamy-san,
that's the first time I'm seeing that face.
You're that mad, huh?
How dare you ask idols such a question.
Yikes. She might sue me for harassment.
She's talking nonsense.
Yeah! Sorry!
Just being here is an embarrassment.
Aaah!
An official rejection!
She actually did an official rejection!
Yeah.
Suggestion from A-chan
Let's try playing Shiritori
Let's start from Fubuki-san!
The "Ri" from Shiritori!
Go ahead!
Ring, ring ring ring ring...
(Riii, riririri)
Done.
Pause.
Hold on (lol)
What?
You're gonna end on that? Really?
Yeah.
Okay. "Ri," then.
I'll go with a different approach.
"Squirrel (Risu)," I guess.
"Squirrel," huh. Okay.
Sounds pretty normal.
"Watermelon (Suika)."
Ah. Okay.
How about you, Lamy-san? "Ka" next.
What're you gonna go with?
"Fin (Kan)," the end.
"Fin—"
It's over.
Suggestion from A-chan
Let's try playing Shiritori: Round 2
I wanna do one more round.
Yeah!
One more round!
Okay, please start us off, Fubuki-san!
Starting with the "Ri" from Shiritori!
Uh... let's go with
"Ring Fit (Ringu fitto)!"
Ooh, that's a nice one.
Yup!
"To," next!
Okay, continue the chain, Noel-san!
Uh...
"Ibis (Toki)," I guess?
"Toki"?
"Toki"? Which one is that?
The bird?
Yeah, the bird.
Toki from F*st of the North Star?
Oh, the bird one?
Okay, Kanata-san!
Continuing from the "Ki" from "Ibis (Toki)"!
"Ki..."
"Ki."
"Tree (Ki)."
"Tree," huh?
Okay, understandable.
I see. You're going with "Tree."
Nothing more, nothing less.
Okay.
Moving on, it's your turn, Lamy-san!
"The Golden Bat of Gold (Kiniro no Ogon Batto)"
The Golden Bat of Gold
Ooh!
"The Golden Bat of Gold!"
I heard you like gold
so I put gold in your gold!
Okay, Fubuki-san. Please continue with "To"!
"Tomato!"
Tomato! Nice!
How cute!
Do you like tomatoes?
I like—
I don't really like them!
What a picky eater!
But whatever! Cute is justice!
Okay, Commander! "To" from "Tomato"!
"To" again?!
Dammit!
"Topp*'s sticks are full of chocolate inside!
(Topp* wa naka made choko tappuri)"
"Ri" next!
"Ri"!
That's a very unique choice.
Oh, well! Let's roll with it!
Kanata-san, continue from "Ri"!
"Apple juice, yo! (Ringo juice da ze)"
"Apple juice, yo!"
The next letter's "Ze," I guess?
It's "Ze," yeah?
Lamy-san! "Ze"!
"To all the hololive fans in the country...
(Zenkoku no hololive fan...)
YOU WATCHING?! (Miteruka?!)"
Okay!
WHOOHOOOO!
Arriba!
YAAAY!
WHOO!
Okay.
What was it again?
YEOW!
"To all the hololive fans in the country..."?
"You watching?!"
Last round!
Start us off, Fubuki-san! "Ka"!
KAAA
MEEE
HAAA
HAAAAAAA!
Nice one! Noel-san, your turn next!
"Ha"!
"Humming is... (Hamingu wa...)
"Amazing! (Suteki da!)"
IS IT?!
You've really been going
with some unique choices.
Okay, Kanata-san! "Da" next!
"I told you, didn't I...?
(Dakara itterudaro)
I... (Ore wa)
CAN FIRE THE BLACK DRAGON WAVE!!!"
(Kokuryuuha o uterutteee)"
Whaaat?!
Okay, Lamy-san! Finish it off!
"My hand... it trembles...!
(Te ga... te ga uzuku!)
"My arm is going out of control!"
(Ore no kataude ga uzuite yarareruze!)"
Okay.
That's enough.
Let's see...
"Let's see..."?!
Yeah.
Feel free to drop the acting from now.
Hold up. This episode was really
pushing it a bit too much, ain't it?
That seriously scared the heck out of me!
It was scary, wasn't it?
The script's even got a note going
"When you're hyped to the max
you'd say stuff you never would normally.
That helps release stress, doesn't it?
That's horrible!
Actually, we're more stressed now
just from the things we spilled!
It's mentally scarring!
Yeah!
Exactly!
Anyways!
If you enjoyed the video—
Stop right there.
"Anyways" my foot.
Yeah!
Yup!
Exactly!
Now, now...
Someone here hasn't been hyped yet!
An eye for an eye!
Hand that over, A-chan!
This is the gadget, right?!
Lemme crank this up! Let's do 100mil!
You should have a taste of it too!
Here! 100m!
100m!
Now let's not get hasty!
Sure!
100m!
A gazillion then!
Wha?
IF YOU ENJOYED THE VIDEOOO!
WOWOWOWOWOW
DON'T FORGET TO SMASH THAT LIKE BUTTON
GO TO THE HOLOLIVE OFFICIAL YOUTUBE CHANNEL
AS WELL AS OUR TALENTS' CHANNELS
AND HIT. THAT. SUB. BUTTON!
SEE YA!
Bye-bye!
Don't forget to like & subscribe!