Bloopers and Cuts Special
Game Shop Maruyama is back!
Today's episode will be a bloopers and cuts special!
Towa Kiss...
You may be able to see new sides of the girls!
Let's get on with it! Start!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
The beginning of everything!
Cut interview scenes!
These are from the interview scenes
in the Grand Opening episode.
There were actually quite
a few scenes cut from here!
Q: What do you do?
I...
uh... live!
Wait, I messed up!
Q: What made you want to work here?
The pay looked good!
Can I scratch my nose?
Super relaxed
Subaru-san, try to be more formal
during an interview.
Q: What is your strength?
My strength is...
um...
I can enjoy anything!
Q: Do you have any work experience?
I've worked numerous part-time jobs!
Let's see...
I delivered newspapers,
and...
carried around milk,
hmm...
worked in service,
yelling out "Welcome!" and stuff.
Q: What made you want to work here?
Well, I'm a pirate, an outlaw.
Since I've, like,
stopped being a cog in the wheel,
I've started losing sight
of what's considered "normal."
So, by becoming a
productive member of society again...
Do you follow?
I'm trying to regain my common sense.
Q: Do you have any work experience?
I have never done part-time before,
but I've been a full-time employee for 5 years,
so you won't regret hiring me.
Q: Are you a dog person or a cat person?
I'm a cat person!
I love cats.
Q: What would you do with 1 million yen?
Buy anti-aging products, probably.
Q: When can you start?
Well...
If you wish for it,
I'll rush to your side... anytime.
You may be seated.
Ah. I'm sorry.
I'm Tokoyami Towa the Great
from the 4th Gen!
Q: What do you do?
I'm a devil.
Q: Do you get paid doing that?
Well...
uh...
We have a few backroom dealings. (What?)
Q: What are your hobbies?
Anything you enjoy lately?
What I enjoy lately?
Uh...
Let's see...
messing with humans, I suppose?
Q: What is your strength?
My strength is that I can sing songs well.
That, and...
What else?
That I'm the lively sort? Am I?
I can hype things up, yay!
Man, even in their interviews,
these three were true to themselves.
Moving on...
You got this! Boss's flubs compilation!
Marine the Perv and Word Master Noel Arc
We're accepting requests for advice from you.
Yeah!
If your request gets featured, you get this!
Oh!
A completely uneep—
Let me try again!
Boss?!
Offense is the best defense!
From @mikino_holololo on Twitter!
Thank you!
Let's see...
Hello, everyone!
Hello!
I've taken on a stark raving
mad persona, and it's stuck,
Uh-huh.
and now I have to live
while wackt—acting nout—
Can I go again?
From the Twitter name.
Marine the Perv and Word Master Noel Arc
We sell a wide variety of games here,
Mm-hmm.
but we are not a normal game shop.
Yeah.
We recommend a game to a troubled customer,
and resolve their wurry bleh, bleh, bleh.
Yup!
Oh?!
Boss?!
We recommend a game to a troubled customer,
Yup!
and resolve their wurry bleh, bleh, bleh.
Oh?!
Pose on point
That's a fantastic pose,
but you're still flubbing your lines!
Let's move on!
Resident Evil Village
Scream Ranking
Time for a sudden
Resident Evil Village scream ranking!
Of Angels and Luck
This was a very chaotic episode,
and now, we'll be showing you
a ranking of whose scream was the loudest!
4th Place
Starting with 4th place!
Kanata-san is playing with
Subaru-san backseating her.
This is the scene where
she's being attacked by bugs.
There should be a prompt. Back off for a sec.
Get back a little.
Walking back.
That! That!
I'm tearing it off!
Now go straight! Go!
OK!
And to the left.
Okay, nice!
Eeek!
And to the left.
Scream Ranking
4th Place: Amane Kanata
In 4th is the guest for that episode, Kanata-san!
3rd Place
Now, time for 3rd place!
This is the scene where Kanata-san
runs from the boss, Dimitrescu.
Yikes! Go around here!
The lever! Go back to the lever!
Wait, wait, wait.
Isn't that way bad?
Ahhh!
Wait, wait, wait.
Isn't that way bad?
Ahhh!
Scream Ranking
3rd Place: Oozora Subaru
In 3rd is the backseating Subaru-san's scream!
2nd Place
There's still more!
Time for 2nd place!
Towa-san is looking out for enemies.
She has a knife in hand,
but she's freaking out quite a bit.
L2.
This is scary!
Eek!
They suddenly appeared!
This is scary!
Eek!
Scream Ranking
2nd Place: Tokoyami Towa
In 2nd place is Towa-san,
who was on the verge of tears.
1st Place
And finally, 1st place!
Captain Marine's scream
in the heat of the moment!
Hol' up. Hol' up. Give us a break.
What now?
Do we just keep running?
Give them a moment to rest.
Where are you going?
Give us a moment.
There it is!
They've raised the lever again!
Ooh!
Please! Please go up faster!
Dimitrescu will come if they don't hurry.
Open the hell up already!
Why are you so damn slow?!
Open the hell up already, you idiot!
Scream Ranking
1st Place: Houshou Marine
In first place is Marine-san's heated exclamation!
Cut scene!
By the way, this episode
had this happen as well.
Captain Marine and Towa-san's team
took the lead!
However, maybe she was
concentrating too hard...
Captain?
What is it?
I think I'm about to miorf.
Towa in trouble!
Towa's about to miorf!
Really?!
H-Hang on...
Attention, everyone!
O-Our Tokoyami-san is about to miorf.
I feel just...
Is Towa's towaste going to come out?
a little unwell.
Her towaste is coming out!
Her towaste!
I was so confused.
Is she feeling sick?
And this person too...
Wait!
Oh no!
It stopped at one heck of a shot.
Um... excuse me.
Kanata is, uh...
about to puke from the shock of dying.
Please be careful not to stare too intensely
at the screen or overexert yourself!
We'll get rid of the towaste first!
Towaste clean-up time.
Cut segment!
"The Three Saleswomen!"
Now for a first-look!
Cut segment!
"The Three Saleswomen!"
Boss presents: The Three Saleswomen!
Yaaay!
This segment is one where I'll have the three girls
learn the know-how of marketing games
by designing this store's advertising,
slogan, and illustrations
in anticipation for the day
they become our poster girls.
Yaaay!
Ooh!
This sounds tough. Out of nowhere.
Our topic for today is this!
Oh?
Make an advert for Monster Hunter Rise
to further increase its sales.
Let's start drawing!
Okaaay!
Okaaay.
The people who are good at this make them in a jiffy.
Really?
There's that one famous general store
called VILL*** VAN*****.
That's super obvious!
I'm done!
Ah!
Good going, Subaru, yo.
Subaru's Advert
My advert is this!
This will chainge your life!
"This will change your life!"
There it is!
Wow!
This will sell like hotcakes!
This is...
quite the bold claim.
I'm sure they'll think about how
their life would change after seeing this...
This will chainge your life!
Right.
and want to buy it for sure!
This is genius.
It just exudes confidence.
I feel like I've seen that claim before.
True.
I've seen it a few times.
Whoever's done next!
This might not be a good idea...
Marine's Advert
@c*sme Cosmetics Awards
#1
1st place on the c*sme cosmetics awards!
So much censoring!
This might not be...
This will definitely boost sales!
Especially if they're a woman!
This is wrong on so many levels!
Well, the * could be anything.
Honestly,
the fact that they're about to buy
Monster Hunter is...
Don't market Monster Hunter
with a cosmetics award!
Last up, Towa-chan!
Okay!
Towa's Advert
Buy now, and you can get it at half the 2x price!
Buy now, and you can get it at haf the 2x price!
Isn't that just the usual price?
This might be good!
Really?!
I was tricked for a sec.
I got tricked for a moment!
Yeah.
Make them think it's half-off,
Buy now, and you can get it at haf the 2x price!
but still sell it at full price.
Wow.
That's the plan.
This is quite the technique.
Right?
Definitely a technique.
Someone will definitely file a complaint later.
Right.
"Huh? But I bought it
because it said it was half off!"
"Please double-check next time."
Please double-check the prices
when buying at Maruyama!
And for the second season,
maybe we should have them brush up on their spelling...
chainge
haf
Cut Openings!
They were talking about this
kind of stuff as well before opening.
The Three Girls' Cunning Conversation
The Three Girls' Cunning Conversation.
Nothing to do today, either.
Do you think
this place will really get customers?
It'll go bankrupt. (confident)
What?
Well, Boss asked me to do some cleaning,
Oh.
so I'll get started on that.
Okay. See ya.
Make sure not to slack off while I'm gone.
Of course. (blatant lie)
OAAAA!
Ah! Subaru-senpai!
Why you slackin'!
I'm not!
I'm working hard!
Where's the energy?
Fully charged!
Good!
Where's Towa?
She's cleaning up the break room.
Oh, really?
Now's my chance!
Hey Captain,
are you free this Saturday?
Hmm?
What? Is she asking me out...?
Nah, there's no way.
She must be trying to
make me take her shift.
No way in hell!
Hmm...
I wonder...
So? So? So? So?
Are you? Hey, are you?
Hey.
I'm free af,
but with the way she's asking,
I'm not helping until hell freezes over!
Knowing you, you're free af, aren't you?
What do you know, it's Towa-sama!
Good work with the cleaning!
Good timing!
It's Towa-chan!
Say, Towa-sama,
are you free this Saturday?
Wait a sec...
That came out of nowhere.
Are they perhaps trying to get me to take their shift?
I almost fell right into their trap!
I'm not completely free.
I've got some things to
take care of in the afternoon.
Oh, you're not getting away that easily.
Do you have anything, Captain?
I don't! I don't have any plans!
I'm completely free this weekend!
What do I do? How do I respond?
Um... Uh... Hey...
Hey,
on Saturday... Saturday...
Shut up for a sec!
AHHHH!
These guys...
are such a pain.
Legendary Subaru Line
No-cuts Reveal!
Since the Subaru Line became
somewhat of a legend in the show,
Towa too
we'll show you the full version
of how it came to be!
This isn't looking good!
I've never played before!
Just erase them as they come.
Go!
It's started!
You're going fast!
Keep 'em coming!
Wow!
Fast!
Looking good!
She's not too slow!
I've always got Urokodaki-san
by my side on my stream.
Fast decisions!
I can make decisions fast!
1-chain!
Okay!
A chain!
What is this one?!
You erased a ton of them!
No 2-chains so far
Nice!
A chain would be nice.
Your current score is 152.
Keep at it!
You need 20,000 points.
20,000 points!
20,000?!
2,100 points so far.
Get past 20,000, Subaru-senpai!
20,000?
You can make it if you chain!
30 seconds left!
Crap, I have less time than I thought!
This is looking bad.
You got this!
This is bad!
You still have only 2,000 points!
This is looking bad!
You got this!
I don't know how I'm supposed to place these!
You're doing fine, I think!
Looking good!
Faster! Faster!
You're going fast, good!
For this...
You're keeping good speed.
This one's no good!
10 seconds left!
For this...
No time to think!
Snap decisions!
Almost time!
5 seconds left!
4!
This is bad!
3!
2!
1!
Time's up!
Wait, the total score is...
2,516...
Wait, what's with that best score?
It's insane!
20,000?!
How do you even hit 20,000?
That's crazy.
You have to get some chains, I guess.
There's our total score!
2,516 points!
I'm only a tenth of the way there!
Dang.
Her longest chain was... 1!
This is how the Subaru Line came to be.
Towa-san's was also cut short,
so please enjoy the full version!
Off to a quick start, I see.
Yeah.
I'm... I'm stacking early.
Oh?
This is looking good.
Looking good.
Place this like this...
She's intentionally delaying it!
So that's how?
How do I position this?
She keeps them on!
So she's stacking them first?
I see!
Stacking them up.
I see.
Ah, she messed up there.
I have no idea what to do!
You have at least some idea, right?
It looks good.
This looks good!
Do this...
This looks great for a chain!
Whoa!
Ah! I messed up!
Her controls are getting sloppy!
You can do it!
This doesn't look good.
But she can still do it!
This is worth a lot!
Go! It's in!
Ah! There!
Go!
Wow!
Oh! 8,000 points!
She got a ton of points for that!
This is looking great!
So chains are where it's at.
You're doing great!
Wow!
Wait, I messed up again!
You're great at this!
She's about to reach 10,000 points!
Like this...
Ah, I didn't mean to do that!
10 seconds left
Doing good!
Stack them up.
You can do it!
That's amazing!
Whoa!
5 seconds left!
Go! Go!
5!
4!
3!
2!
Hurry! Hurry!
1!
Yeah! You did it!
Amazing!
Time's up!
Hey, hey, hey!
Yaaay!
This is pretty good.
This is...
So, Towa's points,
her total score is...
Is...
10,400 points!
Heck yes!
Amazing.
Cut Openings: Part 2!
Battle without Honor and Humanity: XXXXX War
Let's both say which one's better on one.
Worrying about where to order pizza from
Okay. Ready? I'll count us down.
Okay!
Ready?
3, 2, 1!
Pizza Cap!
Yay!
What is Pizza Cap?
You know them for being "Fast! Delicious! Cheap!"
Hugely popular with city people.
Yaaay!
Of course.
Next up, the dough!
Yeah?
Pizza dough!
The dough?
I have my preferences.
The fluffy and filling hand-tossed crust
Uh-huh.
or the crisp and light Thin n' Crispy crust?
Captain?
Hey, Captain!
I don't mind either!
Who cares about that?
Help me with this work!
Taking stock by herself
No way in hell.
Ah, crap, it just slipped.
Let's just shout it on one!
Okay!
Yeah.
Ready?
3, 2, 1...
Hand-tossed!
Hand-tossed FTW!
Perfect match
I could tell from the way you jumped.
You did? These big motions give it away, huh.
Lastly, what kind of pizza?
3, 2, 1...
Super Korean Bulgogi!
Teriyaki Chicken & Mayo!
Unbelievable.
Unbelievable?
Don't you dare cross this line!
Divided
What?
You don't come over here.
How about you don't come over here?
What is that pose?
What was that?
Oi.
Step outside!
Help, Captain!
Just order half-half.
Marine-san, nice idea.
Great idea
Finishing Move
Full Set
Finishing Moves Full Set!
We'll be showing every finishing move so far.
There are even ones we cut out, so check it out!
Ready?
Marine the Perv and Word Master Noel Arc
Tick-tick-tick-tick—
Uh...
Hnnn...
Why I Can't Stop! Miko's Adult Hobbies Arc
Elite Destroyer!
Pew, pew, pew!
Mood Destroyer 💀
Huh?
Swolenthal Is Born!
Take my finishing move!
AkiRose☆Alona☆Sexy!
First I've heard of it.
Boss, look at just how unfazed Towa's stance is.
My greeting is actually "Hello-robo,"
I swear I'm not an airhead!
but if I say the "bo" part strongly, it becomes...
*inhale*
Hello-
BOOO!
Thoughts?
Wait, what's with this mood?
I don't understand you anymore!
Roboco-senpai...
Retorting
Frozen
Disappointed
You weren't like this
three years ago, Roboco-senpai!
Boss-sama...
All Else Fails, Suck Subaru's Life Force
Choco Kiss❤
*mwah*
ARRGH!
Press F to pay respects
Are you okay?!
First reveal of cut Finishing Attacks!
It's finally time for the never-before-seen scenes!
All Else Fails, Suck Subaru's Life Force
Towa-san was actually made to use
Choco-sensei's finishing move as well.
Shouldn't Towa do it too?
Towa should do it too.
Wai—Oh! My heart!
It hurts!
Are we getting Towa Kiss?
That's the one thing I won't do!
Try it! Towa Kiss!
One Towa Kiss, please.
Towa Kiss...
Arrgh!
She's about to die.
That was just... that veggie juice ad.
I can't! I can't!
Who taught Towa-sama? They suck!
Finishing Move: Smile of the Lamy.
"I Only Trained Towa-senpai!"
Yukihana Lamy Leadership Arc
What is that?
What? Lame.
Never heard of it.
What do you mean by "smile"? Lame.
Did you always have that move?
Actually, around my debut,
Uh-huh.
the viewers gave me this finishing move.
Huh.
She's insisting that
she didn't come up with it.
Show us!
I said then that I won't do it again
because I can only do it once every 6 months.
Once every 6 months.
We're seeing it today?!
Oh!
Then that means...
You can do it today?
Yeah.
Oh!
Will you do it here?!
For real?!
Please show us!
3, 2, 1...
Smile of the Lamy!
Time to leave.
Botan-chan, it says here
that you have a Finishing Move.
Offense is the best defense!
I do!
Really?
I yell "Shishiron Kick!" while punching them.
Scary.
That's a total feint.
Could you show us how it works?
On Subaru-chan, of course.
Why?! Why me?!
Take one for the team.
No way! Why are you making a legit stance?!
Aren't you the manager
of a mixed-martial arts club?
Well, yeah.
She looks experienced.
Shishiron... Kick!
AHHH! It's scary!
You've got a great straight.
Really?
Tough Love & Mental Training
Those movements are hilarious.
Super Nenechi's...
Love-Love Beam❤
I got the chills just now...
You're all my kind seniors, aren't you all?
Rising Sun
Full Set
Let's not miss a beat!
Rising Sun Full Set!
Weather?!
Stormy
Rain
Cloudy
Clear
Rising Sun!
Here we go!
Your answer, please!
Ready?
Three, two, one!
Rising...
Sun!
Stormy
Rain
Cloudy
Clear
Rising Sun!
Rising... Sun!
Stormy
Rain
Cloudy
Clear
Rising Sun!
Rising... Sun!
Stormy
Rain
Cloudy
Clear
Rising Sun!
Rising... Sun!
Sun!
Well. There you have it.
Uh...
Okay. Let's bounce.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That was new.
If everyone stinks it up, nobody stinks it up
Thank you very much.
She wanted to try it.
We wanted to do something
about this mood.
We wanted to help.
Why are you all talking
like I stank the place up?!
No! We all stank the place up!
Rising Sun
Sealed
And so, the painful Rising Sun
was sealed for eternity.
The End.
Game Shop Maruyama
Exterior Design Reveal
Now for a tour of
Game Shop Maruyama's exterior!
Please enjoy the parts of the store
we didn't have a chance to show before.
How did you enjoy this episode,
the Game Shop Maruyama
Bloopers and Cuts Special?
For the upload schedule for the next episode onward,
please refer to the hololive official Twitter account for updates.
Next episode will be the start of Season 2!
Who will our guests be?
What games will they play?
Please look forward to it!
I'll do my best with the narration!