Spot the Fake Picture Diary Championship!
Yay!
Yaaay!
All right, we've started!
It's time for the Spot the Fake Picture Diary Championship!
August is drawing to a close,
and we're entering summer's endgame.
How's everyone doing at this time?
Any memories of rushing your
summer homework at the last minute?
I did do mine,
but evewyone bets it on that
last minute adrwenaline, wight?
Is that even an adrenaline rush?
I also do everything on the last day, but
then I remember going,
"Shoot. I can't finish X and Y."
"What do I do?!"
and use my secret skill: Forget everything.
What?!
Ah, happens.
You forgot?! Did that even work?!
I'm the type that makes a schedule
as soon as summer break starts.
Really?!
That's amazing!
That's so like you!
It really is!
I would create the ultimate summer
schedule down to the last minute
and then scrap it.
That defeats the purpose.
You scrapped it?!
Well, summer memories is part of our agenda today,
but we're here to do battle.
Oooh!
All right, bring it on!
Let's go straight into it!
We'll be doing a team battle this time!
It'll be Roboco & Luna vs Botan & Lamy.
Yup.
Sure.
Hold on, the odds are stacked high!
We're doomed!
They have a stacked team!
I can awweady feel the pwessure.
Both of us ARE from the same gen.
We might walk home with the trophy!
I feel like we're gonna lose just based on that factor.
Why would you think that?!
We did Anpontan together, didn't we?!
(Anpontan: A group formed by Roboco, Luna, and Akirose)
For this battle, each team has drawn four instances
of a summer homework classic: The Picture Diary.
However, one of those four is a fake,
and the aim of the game this time is to spot that fake.
Here are the picture diary titles!
Lucky Me
Tummy Trouble
Watch Your Back
Luna & The Bee
Yakitori Skewer Bonus
Overslept & Overshot
NePoLaBo's Online Nagashi Somen
NePoLaBo's Online Test of Courage
Oh?
What?! What are theeese?!
I'm interested!
What's with Luna & The Bee?
It sounds like a new movie title.
Yeah, what is that?
What's up with that?
It's definitely a tearjerker.
A tearjerker?
Yeah. It'll make you cwy a wiver.
As for our end, NePoLaBo refers to
us 5th Gen girls collectively,
and we have 2 entries for NePoLaBo.
The fake's definitely one of those two.
Whaaat?
I wonder.
Maybe it is? We don't know!
Are you setting up a fall?
Whaaat?
Are we starting awweady?
Battle Begins!
Picture Diary Reveal
The one I'm curious about the most is...
Which one?
The one called "Watch your Back."
I really wanna know what's that about.
Okay, let's go with that for our first pick!
We'll pick "Watch your Back."
That's so cute!
It is!
"Watch your Back."
By: Himemori Luna.
Gosh, that's so cute.
I went with mommy and daddy to the zoo!
When I fed the wabbits cawwots,
Mr. Goat munched on my hair
from behind and scawed me!
The end.
It's so adorable. This one's real.
It sounds plausible.
If this is the fake,
you can find me in my bed for the next three days.
Uh, Lamy-chan, you need to riff
on this entry and poke it for holes.
Right. The absolute adorableness put me off guard.
You can't let it trick you!
Still, do goats actually munch on hair?
So, wike...
Honestly, the goat just
appeared behind me out of nowhere.
Like, I was wondering "What's tugging my hair?"
and turned around to see my hair being munched
and that's why my hair's short now.
So THAT's how it happened!
YEAH!
Mr. Goat the Stylist
That's how it happened!
Still, were there any other animals?
There was Mr. Bunny, Mr. Goat...
Who else was there...?
Uh...
The drawing sure is cute.
Oh! Mr. Horse was walking around in another area.
Oh!
There were a lot of hewbivowes.
I wonder... this one's tough to tell.
Yeah.
I really can't tell!
Picture Diary Reveal
Don't either of the NePoLaBo ones look sus to you?
Yeah.
They could be twicks, but let's pick one of them.
Hm... how about the Test of Courage?
Test of Couwage, pwease!
Good choice.
Okay, let's go with that!
Okay! NePoLaBo's online Test of Courage!
By: Yukihana Lamy.
We did a midnight Discord watchalong of Inagawa J*nji's
horror stories for some summer memories.
Ooh, that sounds nice.
It does, yeah.
It was scary as heck and made for an
unforgettable summer in more ways than one.
By the way, I recommend watching Living Doll.
"No more, stop! It's so scary..."
Well then...
First off, that's some high-quality picture diary right there.
That's not even a picture diawy.
That's basicawwy the weal deal.
That's weird.
It's fully colored.
What time was it?
Uh, I think it was around 12.30 AM.
Yeah.
How long was the watchalong?
Huh. I think the watchalong itself
was like 30 to 40 minutes.
After that...
Yeah, it was about 30 to 40 minutes.
We did chat like usual,
but the Inagawa J*nji watchalong was about 40 minutes.
Who bwought up the idea?
I think it was me...
Actually, who WAS it? I don't remember.
What?!
I think it was you who brought it up.
It probably was, yeah.
This one's tough.
Still, it's really plausible,
even if you consider the fact that Lamy suggested it.
I wonder?
So you recommend Living Doll.
Yup.
But you said, "No more, stop! It's scary!"
Picture Diary Reveal
Okay. I pick Lucky Me.
Title: Lucky Me
By: Robotaro.
Who the heck's Robotaro?
Robotaro? Who?
WHO IS THAT?!
Isn't it you, Roboco-senpai?
I'm a good robot so I started self-cooking.
However, I was lazy to go out,
so I ordered eggs off Amazon.
I cracked one open and it was
the first double yolk egg I ever got!
I recommend buying eggs off Amazon.
This legit happened.
Why the heck would you buy eggs off Amazon?!
Don't be lazy! Just go out and buy them!
The store's just nearby!
Infighting?
I do buy them from convenience stores lately,
but isn't it amazing?
Getting double yolks from eggs bought off Amazon.
How much did they cost?
Uh... hold on.
They were cheap for sure.
Oh?
They were really cheap.
Lamy-chan, this is a little...
She doesn't remember the price!
Oooh, I see.
She can't answer!
Gimme a minute! I'll check Amazon Fresh!
No, you won't! Not now!
YOU'RE CHECKING NOW?!
You can't check it now!
Seriously?! You're looking it up?!
You don't know the price of the eggs you bought?
I'm noticing this now but they're actually breaking up!
The level of derp in this sailed way past the "D" in "Derp!"
I can't help but riff on it.
That's not twue!
Are you mocking me?
By the way, what were you trying to make?
Huh? Just my daily meals.
What?
Self-cook— Huh?
I really can't tell if Roboco-senpai's faking it.
Yeah, it's hard to tell.
Picture Diary Reveal
I'm cuwious about the Overslept & Overshot one.
Let's pick that one, then.
Overslept & Overshot, got it.
What happened?
Okay, let's take a look.
Here. Overslept & Overshot.
Why the heck is—
I can't help but look at the picture. What the heck?
It's an actual photo.
It's an actual shot.
It's real.
That's such a power move.
I reached for what I thought was toothpaste
and got facial wash instead.
That was a big mistake.
Be careful not to do the same, everyone.
Ah... that hits hard.
That's totally possible.
You could totally do that.
Totally possible when you just woke up.
Yeah.
How did it taste,
brushing your teeth with facial wash?
So... okay, hear me out.
It was so... it's an eye-opener.
Huh? What? Eye-opener?
Okay, hold on.
I was expecting the taste of toothpaste in my mouth,
but when I tasted something that wasn't toothpaste,
my brain just got shocked.
Ah... true.
That's true.
You get what I mean?
Like, when I realized it was facial wash...
Well, it's not soap, but, like...
the taste was like, "Yikes!"
Were there bubbles?
No, it didn't froth.
It didnt?!
It didn't, huh.
'Cause I didn't brush yet.
Still, I feel like I might do the same myself these days.
Whaaat?!
The possibility of doing this in the future isn't zero.
The chance of me doing this in the future...
Well, I'll at least make the facial wash froth.
Why are you competing in that aspect?!
The heck is that supposed to be?
Picture Diary Reveal
I wanna learn more about this
new summer movie called Luna & The Bee.
The movie of the summer! It's very nice.
You wanna watch the movie?
Okay!
The art is so cute!
It's overflowing with emotion.
Title: Luna & The Bee
By: Himemori Luna
I ran around in my grandma's garden
and cwashed into Mr. Bee!
It hurt so much and I cried a lot.
Grandma brought me to the hospital
and they pulled out Mr. Bee's needle—
I mean stinger!
The end.
That's just so darn cute it can't be anything but real...
That's so adorable!
This actually hurt for real.
You were running...
You mean you got stung?
Yeah! I was running and suddenly felt a sharp pain.
I wondered what it was because it hurt a lot
and the swelling kept growing.
That's painful.
Yikes...
I realized that it was a bee
and cried a lot but they removed
the stinger when I went to the hospital.
Apparently, the stinger was stuck in my arm.
What?! That's so scary!
That's scary!
Did you realize it was a bee
when you ran into it?
I didn't.
I wike running awound
and I just dash around wildly when I run,
so I didn't wealize it was Mr. Bee in front of me.
He just came outta nowhere.
I also got stung by a bee before in the past.
What?!
They sting you before you notice them, right?
Yeah...
I see...
So when I asked just now and
you said you didn't realize you got stung,
it does seem credible
since I've also experienced it before,
but I wonder...
Did it really happen?
Did it?
Picture Diary Reveal
Robo-cha-senpai, you pick.
Let's go with the Nagashi Somen story!
You wanna wash them away?
Let's do it!
NePoLaBo's Online Nagashi Somen!
We bought some tools that can make nagashi somen.
This was also done on Discord, by the way.
We did an online nagashi somen.
What? How does that work?
We enjoyed watching videos of
Azumino's scenery on YouTube
while all of NePoLaBo slurped away at our somen.
It really gave that feeling
and was a great summer memory.
What the heck is "That feeling" supposed to mean?
Yeah, what's it mean?
We played some beautiful 4K videos of Azumino
What?
and there are actually tools
you can make nagashi somen with.
There's one where you just put the noodles
into the container and it'll let you do nagashi somen.
Yeah.
There's one that automatically flows
the somen down in a spiral
and we were like "Let's try this out!" and did just that.
Wow! But someone didn't get the memo
(to buy the tool), did they?
Who?
The somen!
Chowing down on a dried somen bundle.
Well one of us prefers her somen hard.
She's eating them like that?
She might be the type that likes dried noodles more.
Yeah.
She probably likes her noodles tough.
That really looks fun.
Yeah.
Both the Test of Courage from earlier
and this one are totally plausible,
but I also feel like one of these two is the fake.
Still, seriously?
I mean, we were like "Let's do it"
and actually did it for real,
but it was pretty surreal.
Right?
That is pwetty suwweal, doing it online.
Well, in reality, all of us were eating alone in our rooms.
Yeah. Do it on stream!
Picture Diary Reveal
Now we've each got one left.
Tummy Trouble.
Tummy Trouble!
Let's see it.
The heck is this?
Just what is this swoppy dwawing?
It looks pretty cold.
Tummy Trouble.
By Robocha.
Wrong name!
Who's that?
Who is it?
It's Robocha. Robocha wrote this.
When I was taking a nap,
I dreamed that I was trapped in a refrigerator.
When I was about to freeze to death, I woke up!
I was sweating so much because
I had thought I was going to die.
But the AC wasn't even on...
This one is hard to make fun of.
Since it was a dream.
The title is Tummy Trouble, so did your stomach hurt?
My stomach hurt so much that I was stuck
in the bathroom for about three hours.
Did you have an upset stomach?
Yeah, I did.
So the sweat from thinking you were going to freeze
to death was actually from your stomach pain?
Like a cold sweat?
A cold sweat?
Yeah.
Are you for real?
Uh oh, I made fun of it after all.
I'm touched!
So basically you had a nightmare while you had an upset stomach.
Right.
So you had a nightmare due to stomach pain.
Yeah, I think so.
Well, to be blunt
this seems more credible than the egg story from before.
Why do you say that?!
Picture Diary Reveal
The last one is Yakitori Skewer Bonus.
And the writer of that one...
is me!
Okay!
Okay.
Yakitori Skewer Bonus.
By Shishiro Botan.
When I bought 10 yakitori skewers just before
they closed up for the night, they gave me 15 more for free.
Sounds like a math problem.
I got more for free than I actually bought.
I enjoyed them very much.
Wow, you ate 25 yakitori skewers?
Yes, all 25.
Wow!
You got that many?
I mean, not all that night.
Okay, yeah.
It was a nice old lady.
She was like "I'm gonna give you a little bonus."
That's nice.
So I told her thank you.
But I didn't look, and when I got home, I was like,
"Wait, this is a lot of bags!"
When I counted them,
the freebies outnumbered what I bought.
That actually happens?
How much was it?
About 150 yen each?
Oh, she can name the price.
Oh, she can name the price!
Sure I can!
The credibility is rising!
Weren't they on a discount since
the store was about to close?
They were 150 yen?
Yeah, like 150 yen.
The place I went to didn't have one.
Hmm...
What kinds of yakitori did they give you?
Well...
I mean, there were a bunch of different kinds in there.
Chicken and scallion...
Those are good.
Chicken skin...
Chicken tail?
Nice.
Stuff like that.
Hmm...
Sounds good.
Salted? Or tare sauce?
Tare sauce.
Tare sauce?
Tare sauce, huh?
That's yummy!
Okay, ding ding ding ding!
Awww, it's over!
Which picture diary is the fake?
Discussion Time
I think it's weird she was able to name the price right away.
The yakitori one.
Wight! I thought so, too!
I thought it might be the yakitori one, too!
First of all, awound cwosing time
they'll generawwy go on sale and give discounts.
I bought yakitori wike that, too!
They'll give you a discount on however many!
Right! You'll see them for like 80 yen quite a bit.
I thought 150 yen sounded weawwy steep!
For both of Luna's stories...
I hope they're true.
A wish?
Honestly, the one I think it might be is
Lucky Me?
The one where she bought eggs from Amazon.
I mean, Roboco-senpai even said
she's been buying her eggs at the convenience store.
If so, why didn't she just buy them
from there in the first place?
She did.
Prediction Time
Ready, set...
Yakitori Skewer Bonus!
I see.
The pwice of the yakitori...
being 150 yen is weird!
You think?
I see.
A pwice of 150 yen late at night is weird!
You thought we didn't share any bonds...
...but we grew them at the last second.
We both agweed on that one!
You agreed? Really?
Prediction
Ready!
Lucky Me!
Why?
Why don't you believe me?
Shishiron, do the honors.
Luna-senpai and Roboco-senpai
were saying that 150 yen is expensive,
but on the other hand
here she was saying she doesn't know how much she paid...
Why?!
Isn't that a little weird?
Why is it weird?!
And...
On top of that, she said she bought them online
but now she's buying them at the convenience store...
Why didn't she just buy them
at the convenience store in the first place?
I can't help you here...
Watch here
I'm so sad my outfit changed~
Real?!
Or Fake?!
Let's find out!
Lucky Me
Yakitori Skewer Bonus
It was true!
Huh?
Really?
Are yakitowi skewers weally 150 yen?
They are!
Yakitori skewers are wittle more expensive wately.
Was Lucky Me really true?!
It was!
You got a double yolk egg!
A double yolk!
Amazon weally was wegit.
Yeah, they were.
I think I'll try buying eggs on amazon too.
Seriously?!
See?!
Prediction Time
Round 2
Weady...
NePoLaBo's Online Nagashi Somen
(NePoLaBo) All get along really well,
so they probably think they can
just make up a story and it'll fly.
Yeah. They pwobabwy made it up.
Prediction
Round 2
Ready!
Lu―
Watch...
Ah... Is that what we're going with?
Wait, what?
You had diffewent answers?
Ready!
Watch Your Back
Was that okay? Like...
Was that okay?
It's fine.
We were out of sync. Sorry 'bout that.
Are you guys alright?
Why pick that?
My bad.
But really, I kind of chose this one
by process of elimination.
Yeah.
I see.
Real?!
Or Fake?!
Let's find out!
Watch Your Back
NePoLaBo Online Nagashi Somen
Sorry! I was wying!
Sorry! I was lying!
They were both fake!
No way!
Wow!
Nagashi somen was kind of like...
That just sounds too widicuwous.
We really did invite everyone though.
You were actuawwy going to do it?
Yeah, we were.
Weally?!
So it's something that you still plan to do?
I see.
Yeah.
Luna-senpai, how did you come up with this story?
Was it based on something?
Or is it completely made up?
Appawentwy, this is a twue stowy...
It happened to someone in hololive.
Really?
I see!
I wonder who it was?
It'd be someone with long hair, right?
Maybe Watame-senpai?
Then I choose Akirose-senpai!
What's your answer?
Then...
Okay, wet's go with AkiRose-senpai then.
Is that okay?
Yeah!
You're right!
Were we right?
Wow!
You guessed right!
We got it! Yay!
So AkiRose senpai really had her hair eaten by a goat...
Yeah, she did.
She did.
Why don't you guess who came up with NePoLaBo's Online Nagashi Somen then?
It'd definitely be
either Polka or Nenechi...
But, honestly, it could be either of them.
It could be someone unexpected though?
Lamy-chan!
Was it you?
No! Lamy doesn't lie!
Yeah, yeah!
Yeah, it could be someone right here!
We choose Nenechi.
I see.
You're right, but there was another person!
Polka!
It weally was them!
That's not fair!
So there were two people?!
Thanks for the spoilers.
There were two people!
So the first Fake Picture Diary Championship! champions are...
It was a tie!
It's a tie?!
So we don't have a winner?
Let's do this again another time.
This was fun!
That about wrap things up,
so that's all for today.
Please like and subscribe to the hololive official channel!
Please like and subscribe!