hololive IDOL PROJECT - SHIJOSHUGI ADTRUCK
(Ad Truck of
Supremacy)
Lyrics: Haru
Composition, Arrangement: Kisaragi Yunna
Vocals: Natsuiro Matsuri, Ookami Mio, Shiranui Flare
Eye contact - so begins the product evaluation
meawase hajimaru shinasadame
Words communicating without understanding
fusokushita mama no ishisotsuu
Meaningless compliments and satisfaction
muimina shousan manzokuge
A marked bankrupt in more than one way
hihei no mihonichi
Paper adorned with hollow phrases
utsuro ni kazaru shimenjou
Deception spread on uneven lines
dekoboko ni furikazashita kiben
Scrape away at the deformed faces
hishageta kao o tsutsukarete
The mask begins to peel off
haritsukerareta kao ga hibiwareteiku
The chess game is lost. How to recover?
kanpunaki made ni tsubureta ko no ban kaesu te wa?
Face carved with wrinkles, shoes worn out
kizamareta shiwa suriheru kutsuzoko
Ahh, tell me the answer!
aa kotae o
Driving day and night in the ad truck of supremacy
shijoushugi adotorakku de shirokujichuu o kakemawaru
It's just a throwaway consumable, you say?
shosen tsukaisute no shoumouhin da to?
Whoa, don't go criticizing just yet
otto iiki ni naruna yo
Shoot up the fireworks and light up the night
patto uchiagete yare yoru o nomikomu hoshi no hana
Crumple up the piles
mata sumi ni tsumikasanerareteiku
Of prayers and throw them away
inori marume nagehanatsu