Ah... Aah...
No more...
Shoot, I'm stuck!
Wait, I'm stuck!
Hell yeah!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Yay-a yay-a!
It habbened! It habbened!
What's "yay-a"?
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Starting off in high spirits
Oh, right!
I've been meaning to ask something.
What? What is it?
Uh-huh.
You know how there's summer homework?
Mm-hmm.
Are you guys the type to plan it out
or the type to do it at the end while in tears?
Knowing us, it's pretty obvious.
You already know.
Yeah.
Do you really have to ask?
I do know you guys don't plan ahead.
What gave you that impression?!
If you know, don't ask.
She found us out.
Since I'm the most put together out of us, I will say...
I shirk it off pretty often.
What do you mean by that?
Sh-Shirking it off...
It's like, "Oh, that... I did it, buuut..."
There it is!
The type to give excuses
You see people doing that often.
That's so cheap.
I'm also the type to shirk it off, but...
You're one to talk, then!
That much was obvious.
I'm a rank above Subaru-senpai when it comes to shirking.
The heck does that mean?
Forbidden technique
A lecture on the trick to
shirking off summer homework
Don't try this at home!
To start off, you'll always be let off on the first day back.
"I forgot!"
Makes sense. Makes sense.
They let you off.
On the second day, they'll be like,
"You forgot again?!" But they'll still let you off.
Uh-huh.
"I forgot! I'm so sorry!"
By the third day, they'll start to be fed up,
so you skip school once.
Hey...
Reset the situation.
And then, on the day after,
You're just scum!
once you arrive to class,
you say, "Ah... I was absent because I was sick, so I forgot!"
Then, you say you forgot one or two more times.
You're absolute scum!
You can finish it in time if you delay it that long.
The only thing I learned was to avoid being your teacher.
What? Don't be so cold.
As for me, I say something similar, like,
Is anyone here responsible...
"My dog ate my homework."
It's too obvious a lie!
Be more realistic!
Settle down, class.
Oh, shoot!
Crap, the teacher's here!
Yikes!
I can't overlook that.
Today's customer:
Yuzuki Choco
How lascivious...
It's so real compared to
Captain's fake sex appeal.
It's not fake!
It's totally different.
Boss!
So Captain's was a sham...
She's the real deal!
I have lost...
She's been defeated.
Yuzuki Choco
Personality: Likes sweets.
The nurse at underworld academy.
Hobbies: Eating!
MENT
LUCK
Today's customer, who's already charmed Boss, is Yuzuki Choco!
Yuzuki Choco
Finishing Move: Choco Kiss
(Effect: Makes you fall head-over-heels for her)
She's the underworld academy's nurse who likes sweets!
Her low physical stats stand out.
Boss, despite how she looks, Choco-sen's quite extreme.
In what way?
She's overexaggerating!
A reliable(?) tip from a genmate
I think you'll see when you listen to her.
Please enjoy seeing Choco-sen when she's on edge.
Moreover, it says you have a finishing move?
Oh!
What is it?
Yeah, I do.
It's a move that makes you fall head over heels for me
called "Choco Kiss."
I LOVE YOU!
Too soon! She hasn't used it!
She hasn't used it on you yet!
She hasn't done anything yet!
Choco Kiss...
Take one, Boss. For science.
Oh? Sounds good.
We'll get out of the way.
Oh, can I?
Thanks.
You're sure about this?
Taking shelter
Then...
Excited...
Boss-sama...
Choco Kiss❤
*mwah*
ARRGH!
Press F to pay respects
Are you okay?!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Anyway,
Calmed down by listing prime numbers
let's see what problem Choco-san wants solved!
I've never had much stamina to begin with,
but because I've only been going
to the streaming room and back,
I've gotten even further out of shape.
I feel you!
Leave it to us!
And there we have our request!
We have just the thing!
Choco-wenwei's request is, in short,
"I want a fun way to exercise!"
Yaaay!
The game we recommend for today is...
Mario Golf: Super Rush!
Yaaay!
Nice shots made easy with simple controls!
Play as your favorite Mario characters
and enjoy some authentic golf!
That's what Mario Golf: Super Rush is all about!
Fill your power gauge to take the shot
while taking wind and terrain into account.
Moreover, you can use motion controls
to use your Joy-Con as a golf club.
You can experience how it feels
to play golf using your whole body.
It's the perfect game for getting back into shape, but...
there's some worrying info.
Let's see...
By the way...
Your grip strength is nonexistent.
MENT
LUCK
Oh, what's it like?
"Right: 12kg and Left: 13kg.
I can't hold anything heavier than a phone."
Is this gonna be okay?
Can you hold a controller?
Seriously.
Well,
I can do most things, despite how I act,
so I'm sure I can have fun swinging today!
Stop acting tough.
Eek!
Stop bullying her!
You know she has no endurance!
Oh, I forgot!
Sorry!
You might break something!
Are you okay?
I'm fine. I can just suck some strength out of Subaru later.
Why me!
Lewd.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Now then, Towa, please explain the rules for today!
Okay!
Today's project is...
the Maruyama Open Speed Queen Championship!
Yaaay!
They'll be competing in Speed Golf today,
which scores both strokes taken and time taken.
The members will start at the same time
and run across the course,
where they can take another shot
as soon as they reach the ball.
However, being fast isn't everything,
as 30 seconds are added to your score per stroke.
In other words, the goal is to finish
as fast as you can with the least amount of strokes.
Off to a practice match
to get our players used to the controls!
Who are you guys picking?
Hmm... You know, like,
First off, selecting a practice character!
the bigger characters hit harder.
You can see how far they can hit on the top right.
Oh, you're right!
Yeah.
So characters like Bowser,
and...
this, uh... gorilla?
Donkey Kong, yeah?
Yeah, Donkey.
Don't call him a gorilla!
He's Donkey Kong!
Donkey is a heavy hitter.
Mm-hmm.
I see.
Characters selected! Now off to the course!
Now that they've chosen their characters,
we're finally off to the course!
Motion controls with the Joy-Con!
In Round 1, they'll be using motion controls
to swing their Joy-Cons as a club.
Can they pull it off?
First, change your aim.
Change your aim.
Nice!
Choco-sensei, you're doing well!
Nice shot, Choco-sensei!
Now, let's run to the ball!
Towa! I can't hit it!
Look!
Towa!
Teach me how to do it!
Then,
lower it.
Now press the button.
Hold it...
Hold it down and swing.
Nice! Just like that!
Ah! So it's like that!
All right! I got it!
Just like that!
Ruuun!
Whoa! She's doing something!
You can dash by shaking the Joy-Con.
Push L or R while dashing
to move even faster by activating a Special Dash.
This is so tiring...
Ah... Aah...
Choco-sensei, should you be
running so hard in the practice round?
No more...
I think this might be my limit...
Shouldn't you just shake the Joy-Con?
Already tired in the practice round!
Huh?
How does that work?
Overcome the struggles of training...
This is hard...
Practice time is over!
And now, finally,
I'd like to start the
Maruyama Open Speed Queen Championship!
I'll beat all of you!
Wenwei, you can do it!
Thank you!
Why are you only cheering for Sensei?!
Aren't you being biased?!
Wenwei!
Please choose the character you'll be using in the games!
Towa-chan's going with her look-a-like.
Nah, nah, nah.
I don't look like a gorilla!
I have a gorilla in my gen—
I mean...
Gorilla in your gem?!
She's not a gorilla, but...
I thought I'd...
What does "gorilla in your gem" mean?
Remember that gorilla, Amane Kanata?
Ah, I do.
She's basically Donkey Kong.
Gorillanata, I choose you!
It's finally time for Round 1!
Ah! It's time! It's speed matches, remember.
It's starting!
It started.
Sensei, it's starting!
Yeah.
There.
Speed.
Line this up...
Wait, what?
Now then, we're off!
Nice shot!
Run! Run!
Huh?
Subaru, you got this!
Subaru is nowhere to be seen...
Wait, this might be bad!
I want a heart to recover my stamina...
Ah, you can do that?
Yeah, you can.
So you can grab hearts.
I did it!
Mm-hmm.
She's finally off!
Run! Run!
Let's go!
This thing is in the way!
All right! Go! Go!
I messed up!
The obstacles are annoying.
This is bad.
Holy moly.
Marine, that looks bad.
I'm in a bad position.
Oh, geez.
Go! Go!
Let's shift it this way first...
Aw shoot!
Getting it out is important!
Faster... Faster...
There... Oh?
Donkey Kong is walking very, very slowly.
My stamina...
Towa-sama ran out of stamina!
Towa-san is currently in the lead!
Subaru-san and Marine-san had a late start...
Shoot, I'm stuck!
Here I go!
I want to get out of this...
Wait, I went past my ball!
Wait, this looks bad!
Crap, crap...
Craaap!
Hell yeah!
There.
Towa-sama holes in 4 strokes
I got a par!
Ahhh! Stop!
Choco-sensei finishes next.
The amount of strokes is a little concerning.
Choco holes in 8 strokes
I did it!
Oh! Nice!
Wait, what?
Captain looked to be in great shape during practice, but...
Those obstacles were devastating, after all!
Captain was struggling with obstacles.
Go in!
Nice!
Captain is the third to finish!
Marine holes it in 8 strokes
Now then...
Last to finish, it's Subaru with a bogey.
Subaru holes in 5 strokes
This looks bad...
In terms of points,
first is Towa-sama,
second is Subaru,
and third is Choco-sensei.
Yeah.
Every swing adds 30 seconds.
That's crazy.
Speed isn't everything.
Let's start hole 2!
Hole 2, start!
What's that in the distance...
What is that?
Is it bad if you hit that bird?
Yeah.
All right!
Run! Run!
Nice shot!
There!
Subaru's doing pretty well this time!
Watch your stamina!
Owww!
Choco-sensei gets blocked!
Interference from Subaru
My stamina's running out!
Subaru-san appeared to be doing well this time, but...
Crap, I hit it too far!
She's going at it 120 percent as always.
Crap.
There.
They're running about.
An intense battle on the green
Run...
Get out of the way!
Choco-sensei—Ah!
"Get out of the way."
Get out of the way!
There's Subaru's "Get out of the way!"
Scary.
Calm down a bit.
Okay! It went in. Nice.
Marine holes in 3 strokes
All right!
The first to sink her putt is Marine-san—Ah.
Captain Marine.
Choco-sensei chips it in!
Choco holes in 4 strokes
Impressive.
Bogey?
Towa-sama holes in 4 strokes
Will it go in?
Oh?
Towa-sama holes out!
Nice!
Nice.
You can do it!
That was bad...
Bogey, huh...
Subaru holes with 6 strokes
A triple bogey...
Oh?
A triple bogey.
First is Towa-sama, second is Choco-sensei,
third is Marine, and fourth is Subaru.
The positions keep changing, except for Subaru in last.
Consistently fourth.
It's time for the final hole of Round 1!
Can Towa-san keep the lead?
Wait, where's the goal?
Ah, it's over there!
Wouldn't it be super impressive to hit a hole-in-one?
It would!
They have an ocean—
I mean, a pond.
Nice shot!
And they're off.
Choco-sensei's going too.
All right!
Run! Run!
I'll hit it at this angle.
Okay!
Nice shot!
Run! Run!
Here I go!
Wait, that angle is...
It's going towards the water!
AHHH! It's gonna splash!
Oh shoot, it might go in.
Wait, you can make that?
Is this possible?
Just as planned.
She's going for a shot that can cross the pond?!
She's lining up a shot that can cross this pond!
Take that!
Is it going?
GOOO!
You can do it! Go over the pond!
Subaru...
lands in the pond!
Go over the pond! Please!
It fell in the pond!
It's right in there!
Regret
Master Subaru has landed in the water.
Hey, if it falls in the pond—
Ah! I fell!
Marine falls in the pond too...
Like this?
So if you fall in the pond here,
Towa-sama fell in.
How?!
Donkey fell in too!
Towa-sama falls in the pond too...
If you fall in here, you get stuck.
Ah! Wait! Wait!
Sensei also fell in.
Everyone's having a nice splash in the pond!
It's like a Thing here, is it?
Subaru-san is in last place,
but she's catching up while everyone's taking a dip.
All right.
How's that?
Oh? Captain... Nice.
It landed at a really good spot!
Oh? Subaru gets to a good spot.
Yaaay!
Everyone is now within reach of the hole!
Round 1 is now approaching its conclusion!
Yay!
Choco holes in 4 strokes
Captain!
Ah, Sensei made it in first!
Seriously?
The one most out of shape here
somehow made it in first.
Huh?! How'd that miss?
I'll watch you all from first place.
How?
She's already announced her victory!
Ah! It went past!
This is so hard.
All right!
I hit it so many times.
Towa-sama holes in 6 strokes
Towa-sama finishes second.
I hit it so many times.
Now it's just Subaru-san and Captain Marine.
Go in, please...
Oi! That one should've gone in!
Six whole strokes...
Marine holes in 6 strokes, Subaru in 8
Marine, I'll be leaving first.
Darn it.
The final results are in!
Subaru-senpai's fourth.
In fourth is Subaru,
and Towa-sama and Choco-sensei are tied in first!
Are these the bonds of the devils at work?
Yeah!
Quite impressive.
Yaaay!
It's a tie for first!
Was it manageable even without stamina?
For that... I made up for it with luck.
So it was luck?!
Luck. I see.
So you used your luck, like a devil.
So it was a fluke.
I see.
You know,
I'm a late bloomer,
so I'll be zooming past everyone,
including the granny that's calling herself a temptress,
to grab first place.
There's only one granny here.
Oh?
Nah, nah.
I'll show you how good grannies are at golf!
Don't grannies play croquet?
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Well, then, everyone.
I'd like for us to start the second half, Round 2, now!
Let's start!
The scoring rules for Round 2 will stay the same,
but we'll be changing from motion controls
to the button controls!
Okay!
Yeah.
And another thing about button controls
is that you can use Special Shots unique to each character.
Round 2 will be held with button controls.
You can use Special Shots
once your Special Shot Meter is full.
You can even come back from a late start for a surprise win!
Check it out, yo!
Without further ado, Round 2, start!
Whether you like it or not,
the Maruyama Speed Queen will be crowned soon!
Let's get pumped!
Yaaay!
Heck yeah!
And we're off!
Yes!
Let's get going!
The first stroke!
Nice shot!
Choco-sensei makes a clean shot.
I want a nice shot too!
Nice shot!
For now...
Ah! Don't go that way!
Ow!
Looking good.
Take that!
Ow!
You can apparently hit a bob-omb!
Captain Marine blew up!
That was close.
I could hit a bob-omb.
Wait, you can hit them?!
What?!
Seriously?
That's right!
Bob-ombs can be used to disrupt other players!
I want to get to my ball!
I'm sure you've all noticed,
but Choco-sensei shuts up when she's focusing.
Choco self-destructs!
Now that you mention it.
Wait! Wait! My...
I'm surprised you noticed.
My coins...
Everyone's at the green!
Now then, everyone's gathered on the green.
Wait...
Whoa, it landed at a nice spot.
This is the key moment.
Oi gorilla, get out of my way!
"Get out of my way."
Go in!
Ah! That was really close!
Please stop the profanities!
Subaru-chan has such a foul mouth.
I don't!
Nice shot.
What a foul mouth.
Marine holes in 4 strokes
It just barely went in.
I don't...
Captain Marine holes! Amazing.
Seriously?! I messed up...
That was fast.
It just barely went in.
Captain Marine scored fast.
Well done.
That was good.
Towa-sama holes with 5 strokes
It's a bogey...
The gorilla's in the way...
Towa-sama holes!
Will Sensei make it in?
Ooh! Just barely.
Did it go in?
Did Sensei miss it?
Ah, it went in.
Yay!
Congratulations!
Choco holes in 7 strokes
What about Subaru-senpai?
She's still going?
Is she not being allowed to score?
I'm putting it in right now!
You can make this.
I'm doing it...
Just a little more.
This is an easy hole.
You got this!
Go! Go! You got it!
It'd be perfect if you made this.
The ball hates you.
How do you miss that?!
That wasn't for real.
See?
Nice.
Subaru holes in 6 strokes
Well, not bad.
Double Bogey, huh.
Well, this is just a warm-up.
It's still the first hole.
The true battle starts here.
Aren't you all a little too on edge?
We don't know who'll win yet.
Of course.
Subaru is in last by a huge margin.
But she's not giving up!
Let's move on to the next hole!
There's a thwomp.
Isn't that a bad spot?
I guess we have to match the timing.
It's a little dangerous.
This is...
So we can't hit the way we've always been?
This might be hard.
This could prove difficult.
Wait, isn't it hard to hit past that?
Is it a timing issue?
This seems hard...
Can we make it over?
Three of them can use the Special Shot.
Want to use it?
Hit it to the moon.
Go! Go!
Nice shot, Towa-sama.
Let's gooo!
That looks cool! But will it land?
That was cool!
Nice!
♪♪
♪♪♪
Is someone singing?
Captain Marine's in high spirits!
My singing was on point.
Now then.
Has everyone noticed?
Captain Marine, in her excitement,
forgot to charge her power meter,
so the ball didn't fly far at all.
One more time.
Wait, where's my ball?
Marine-san ran all the way to the green,
but the ball is, of course... nowhere to be seen.
This is impossible!
Wait, what?! Why's it all the way back there?!
Wait up!
Backtracking to the starting point
Wait, the ball went back!
Darn, that was close!
Did it hit a thwomp and bounce back?
Marine-san, it was your fault...
This makes no sense!
Hey, hey, hey.
Meanwhile, on the green...
Yay!
Oh? Choco-sensei has holed!
Choco holes in 4 strokes
I got it in!
Wow!
Choco-sensei's really good!
The gorilla's in the way.
Gorillas deserve love, too!
Like this...
Meanwhile, Subaru has holed!
Subaru holes in 6 strokes
Subaru has finished.
Now, it's a one-on-one!
It's a triple bogey.
Please...
They're messing up quite a bit.
How does that happen?!
They're using a lot of strokes.
Keep missing!
Wait, but
Captain Marine
Marine holes in 6 strokes
has fewer strokes.
Captain Marine gets a triple bogey!
This is seriously bad!
Towa-sama holes in 9 strokes
This is seriously, horrendously bad.
This is just embarrassing.
I don't want to lose to Subaru.
Why do you have to say that?!
I also don't want to lose to Subaru-senpai.
Why do you all have to say that?!
Now then, it's time for the decisive, final hole.
The decisive, final hole!
Start!
I got this!
There're so many thwomps...
Which way...
They're everywhere.
Isn't this overkill?
Wait...
How do you do this?
I know, right? Where do we hit?
Th-This way?
Hup!
Nice shot!
Go! Go!
Run!
Nice.
Owie!
Hell yeah!
Nice job!
Towa-sama!
Hoping for a comeback victory,
Towa-san goes on a ferocious offence.
How could you do this to me?!
Shoot, Captain's on my tail!
Oi!
Take this!
Get back here!
Captain's so scary...
Oh, shoot.
Hup!
This can work.
Wow!
Choco-sensei shot that straight at the flag.
Marine-san is within reach of the green, but...
Crap, it's gonna go in the pond...
That was close!
Right on the edge.
Wait, how do I get this out? Am I stuck?
The worst place possible!
Marine, that looks bad.
What do I do?
Sucks—
Gah! I fell!
Hey, Subaru-senpai,
how do I...
Marine, that looks bad.
Can I even hit this back up?
While they're panicking...
Meanwhile, they're having an intense battle for first.
Choco-sensei's seconds away from scoring!
Can she finish or not?
Choco holes in 6 strokes
All right! I did it!
Choco-sensei has holed out!
That was fast!
Wait, I'm in serious trouble!
That looks quite serious!
Subaru's wandering around in a weird place.
Boss!
Where are you?
While they're doing that, Towa-san also holes the ball!
Towa-sama holes in 5 strokes
I tried to make fun of Marine when I fell
and now I can't get back up.
Wait, you were what?!
I'm seriously stuck at this wall!
Let me out!
Marine... It's over for us...
Marine-sama, you can do this!
Try changing your club?
Meanwhile, Subaru-san escapes the bunker!
Where's Subaru right now?
Ah! I found my ball!
Ah, there she is.
You're really close, Subaru!
Subaru-san's on the green.
Marine-san is still in the bunker.
Will Subaru end the match?
It went a little far.
It's looking pretty good.
Just a little more!
Wait, "Your meter isn't full"?
What?
Just a little more!
Shoot! Not enough power!
It's looking good.
Ahh!
This bunker's bad news!
How's Captain Marine doing?
All right!
Subaru!
Subaru holes in 6 strokes
Subaru has holed!
Wait! Don't roll back down!
Captain, you're lacking sexiness!
Sexiness?!
Wait! Wait!
Make it in time!
You got this!
Choco-sensei has given her some advice!
She's lacking sexiness.
Please go in! You know you can do it!
Nice!
That bunker was seriously bad.
Marine holes with 9 strokes
Plus 4!
And so!
We'll now reveal the results of those 2 rounds!
Okay!
We have a tie for first place!
Towa-sama and Choco-sensei!
Yay!
I knew they were gonna win...
Not surprised.
In third place is...
Please!
Captain Marine!
Of course.
Whaaat?!
And in 4th is... By, unbelievably,
Really?!
a 1-point difference, Subaru!
I'm done for...
Who would've thought.
The Maruyama Speed Queen title
Sad.
goes to Choco-sensei and Towa!
Yaaay!
The devilish speed queens.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
And that's all we have for today's demo!
Have we solved your problem
of wanting to raise your stats
with a fun way to exercise with
Mario Golf: Super Rush?
Geez.
You've solved everything!
Yaaay!
Is your body okay?
It's starting to hurt.
That was fast!
It's starting to hurt now.
Where's it hurting?
My hips and arms are all...❤
I might not make it...
Why does she sound so lewd...
What's gonna happen to her hips and arms?
It is lewd.
What's with her?
U-Unless Boss gives me a massage, I-I...
I want to massage her!
I might not make it back home today!
Oi, stop seducing her!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
I have one last question for you.
Please tell us the member who shined the most,
the Twin-crew for today!
*drum roll*
Something's habbening!
This feels nostalgic!
Okay!
The Twin-crew for today is...
Of course, it's the devil
who showed how devilish she can be,
Towa-sama!
I knew it was coming!
Today's Twin-crew
Tokoyami Towa
What about our sexy crew's bonds?
Choco-sen, did you forget our 2nd Gen's bonds?!
Shut it!
What was that for?!
Since Towa-sama got selected as a Twin-crew,
we'll give her a star!
Continue doing your best
to become the brightest star in the sky!
Sparkle!
Ya!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Challenge From the Boss: the Maruyama Championship!
Yay!
This season's minigame is...
Puyo Puyo Tetris 2's Endless Fever mode!
Yay! Let's go!
At the moment, in first place is
Marine with 57,726 points.
That's right.
Seriously?
Seriously.
Choco-san, how confident are you?
Well, uh, I've never played Puyo Puyo before.
Oh, a first-timer?
But I'll use my devilish powers to win this one!
The devilish power known as "luck."
Useful devilish power.
Then let the game begin!
Okay!
Now, it begins.
It's starting!
It's over in a flash, so do your best!
Show me how to be an exemplary devil.
The game is timed.
An exemplary devil?
Yeah, you only get a minute.
Oh, really?
Yeah, you only get one minute.
Hey, she's actually stacking!
It looks like she knows what she's doing.
Yeah.
Oh?
She's being very precise with placement.
Choco-sensei is good at Tetris.
Oh, she's good at Tetris?
That's right.
Then maybe she's good at this too?
Wow, she's really stacking!
But if you look closely, it won't chain.
Ah! Wait a second!
Really?
She's stacking, but it won't chain.
Oh, I see.
The game is still her oyster.
You have 30 seconds left.
Huh?
Wait, wait...
She might join us at the Subaru Line!
2nd Gen's Spiritual Connection
Subaru & Ayame Line:
2,516 points
No, no, no, no, no.
The Subaru Line's pretty bad.
Yeah, pretty bad.
Oh, if you put it there, it won't chain.
Ah!
This one—This one's a 2-chain.
You can do it!
Marine knows the chain right away!
That's right!
What a girl!
There.
5 seconds left!
5 seconds?
It's almost over! Your max chain so far is 2!
Wait...
It's too soon!
And it's over!
What are the results?!
Now, let's see that final score.
8,981 points!
That's awesome!
Yay!
Did I beat Subaru? Did I beat Subaru?
Subaru's power level was 2,000.
Power level 2,000.
Oh, good!
I was so worried I might lose to Subaru!
You trying to pick a fight?!
Come on, let's be friendly!
Well, will a monster appear and beat the high score?
Tune in next time and see!
Look forward to it!
Yuzuki Choco
Thank you for your patronage!
Look forward to it!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
After Closing
How did you enjoy this episode of Game Shop Maruyama?
I've asked Towa-chan to stay back this time.
Bonjour. How do you do?
Uh, you seem very...
Choco-sen's influence?
...cultured today?
I like this.
Now, let's give our viewers some advice with their worries.
Yes.
From @shiotan031010 on Twitter!
Shio-tan?
Pfft.
When I have to present in front of a crowd,
my voice and body always quake.
I grow nervous and start trembling,
even in front of friends and family.
Do you have any suggestions to deal with this?
That's our viewer's worry.
Tokoyami...
...would scream.
Tokoyami would scream?
Correct.
When I feel nervous,
I can't control my body whatsoever.
Oh, I see.
Yes.
Mhm.
And so...
When I do...
I sound my loudest voice...
Sound your loudest voice...
...and release myself.
...and release yourself.
Could you give an example?
Eeeyyyaaauuuggghhh!
I'm so goddamn nervous!
What have we released?
Someone save me!
Oh, I see!
That is my method.
So you lose your head for a moment.
Yes, yes, yes.
So if you let it all out before you go on,
you won't lose your head again, is that it?
Yes.
Thank you.
You freaked me out a bit.
And now, we're accepting requests for advice from you.
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique,
personally signed request fulfilled sticker!
So please send in your submissions!
Please do send them in as... as... as it suits you?
You're acting the part right to the end?