Kabaddi!
Huh?
Where am I?
Dunno... I just woke up here for some reason.
It won't open! We're locked in!
I see you're all awake, ladies.
Fubu-chan?
Th-That's "Moderator" to you!
Ahem.
You shall all participate in
a game of Health Mafia.
The heck?
Find out who's the least fit of you all.
The door will open if you answer correctly.
But why?
Because we have
medical checkups next month.
Emergency meeting! Go!
What a pain...
Aqua basically screams "unfit."
What?
You don't go outside.
Yeah, you know what they say
about sunshine and vitamins.
Huh?
I agree.
Sorry, Aqua-senpai.
Okay, yeet Aqua.
No!
Yuck!
Medicinal Tea
Yikes.
Okay, that should get us out...
Or not.
It's Watame, then.
Wh-Why?
You do so many late-night streams.
Staying up late's bad for health.
And for your skin.
So unhealthy.
B-But I did nothing wrong... right?
Wrong.
No!
Hey, this is nice and warm!
Good things can happen too, huh?
I've got an unbalanced diet, you know.
Hey! I eat nothing but beef bowls!
You're not unfit.
You're just unfit for kids.
True... Wait, no!
I bet I'm more unfit than you two.
I mean, I'm purple!
So?
The color itself seems so unhealthy.
That makes zero sense!
Step in, Moderator!
Hmm... Okay, Commander Noel.
Yippee!
Ye Primal Massage:
Go Beyond the Pain
(You get hurt? It's on you.)
Hmm?
Wait a second...
Gah!
That leaves two.
You mean three.
Oh, right.
Hey, Moderator!
Oh?
Come on out.
You dare come at me?
Very well!
We'll decide things with this:
Longest Kabaddi Wins!
Stole it from Shion, huh?
Kabaddi, kabaddi, kabaddi...
Kabaddi, kabaddi, kabaddi, kabaddi...
Kaba...!
Damn it!
Kah!
Oh, come on!
Heck yeah!
Wait, what?
Why?!
And Then There Were None Fit
Get your checkups done!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!