We have a recording session soon.
Geeky Rosenthal
That hangover needs to go, now.
Moshy Rosenthal
This'll do the trick.
That only made things worse!
A sound mind in a sound body.
Aki Swolenthal
Pumpin' it up!
Pump...
in'...
it...
up!
╹༝╹
Stop that!
No more strain on the body!
Fall is for craving!
Hungry Roseinfall
・ﾍ・
We have enough to throw up!
Rozen B. Jack
Pumpki Rosenthal
...
How about this, then?
A-Tea Rosenthal
Whoo, this tea so tastea!
Uh, yikes. What?
I fished up a yellowtail!
It's you! NeneRose!
Yay, yay, yay!
Yel-low♪ Yel-low♪ Yel-low♪ Yel-low♪
Ugh, this fishy smell...
Huzzah! Huzzah!
Huzzah! Huzzah! Hu...
And here we have...
Pukey Rosenthal
PukeyRose!
Can we all agree that it's still fall?
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!