It's gonna blow, you know!
Oh crap!
Aren't you two overreacting a bit?
Aim for the Limit!
Master of the Last Minute!
Your resident high performance, last minute—
Wait, that's not right!
Hellobo, I'm Roboco!
A-quality day to you all! I want to stay home
and not get up until the very last minute!
Let's have fun today!
Good afternene! I'm hololive 5th Gen's
Orange Ranger, an idol VTuber,
and I've been chipping minutes away
from my health lately. Nene here!
That's worrying!
Nene...!
You all often push the bounds of the last minute,
maybe even crave for that last minute,
but which one of you can push
that last minute out the furthest?
Today's program will identify
our Master of the Last Minute!
That's a lot of last minutes.
I guess so.
Time for: Last Minute Balloon Chicken!
Woohoo!
Do you all have an electric air pump
and balloon in front of you?
Yes!
In this game, you'll state for how many
seconds you'll inflate the balloon
and compete for the very last second
you can go without popping it!
It's a very simple to understand,
yet nonsensical game.
That's absolutely frightening.
First Round
Robocosan's Attempt!
How many seconds will you try, Roboco-san?
Mhm!
Hm... Maybe four seconds?
She's already on her toes!
On my toes?
She's wimping out!
Okay, how about six seconds?
Yeah, six seconds sounds good!
Since my name has six letters!
Okay! Roboco-san's starting us off
with six seconds!
But I'm still scared!
Three, two, one, go!
Oh crap!
Is she okay?
Robocosan, are you okay?
My god.
I can hear my heart pounding.
She's thunderstruck.
It got to like, two, three, four, no—
FIVE times the size of my head.
Huh? In just six seconds?
I thought I was going to die.
You thought you were going to die?!
First Round
Minato Aqua's Attempt!
It's Aqua-san's turn next!
Well...
I think Robo-chan's totally wimping out, no?
Why don't you try it for longer, huh?
Yeah, go for it, Atishi-senpai!
How many seconds will you try?
Seven seconds.
Seven seconds for me, please.
Huh?
Seven seconds, please!
Aqua-san will attempt to go for seven seconds!
This is really scary!
I'm sure seven seconds is fine.
Three, two, one, go!
The timer has started!
Three,
Oh crap!
four...
I told you, didn't I?!
Okay, stop the pump!
Oh my god!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god!
See?
It got even taller than me!
It seriously might catapult
the furniture around it.
First Round
Momosuzu Nene's Attempt!
So, Nene, you're totally not scared, right?
Pfft, I wouldn't wimp out
at something like this!
8 seconds sounds kinda lame, so...
I see!
Uh-huh...
Yeah?
I'm gonna go for 10 seconds!
Oh!
So, Nene-san's going for 10 seconds.
You're supposed to stretch the balloon
like this first, you know?
That's unfair! But it makes sense!
What kind of technique is that?!
Nene-san will be attempting 10 seconds.
Three, two, one, go!
One,
two,
three,
four,
five,
six,
seven,
eight,
nine,
teeeeen!
It's over!
Whew!
What a sound!
10 seconds is doable?!
You weren't scared at all.
You've got some guts.
That was a snooze.
Whoa...
Really?
Aren't you two overreacting a bit?
You're kidding me! Really?!
Oh? Is this the mettle of
Nene the Troublemaker?
Second Round
Robocosan's Attempt!
So, Robocosan,
it's time for your second attempt.
Maybe...15 seconds?
Teary Face
That sounds more like it!
How's 15 seconds?
It's gonna blow, you know!
It's time for Robocosan's attempt!
Three, two, one, go!
I'm already at my limit at this point!
The timer isn't running!
Wow. Um, it sounds like she's vanishing.
We can't hear anything anymore.
She vanished...
(This was recorded remotely.)
Mic Failure?
Is she still doing it?
Robo-chan vanished...
Oh, looks like she is.
We can't hear anything, though.
Did it pop?
What happened? Robocosan!
The microphone might've flown off.
Roboco-san, are you back?
Nene...
Tell me it isn't true, Nene...
Management...
This must be...
Did it perhaps...?
Did it perhaps blow up?
Unfortunately, we couldn't hear it
or your voice at all earlier...
Heeey! Why me?!
I'm guessing everything
got noise canceled, maybe.
This is the worst!
Robocosan loses!
I can't believe it!
And that marks the end of...
Wait!
Won't you have another go, Aqua?
What, why? It's over, you know?
15 seconds!
It'd be nice to find out if the balloon
would actually pop at 15 seconds.
I guess it is open to debate.
Then, if mine doesn't pop at 15 seconds,
does that mean Nene-chan will try 20 seconds?
Well, my balloon's got to stretch already,
so 20 seconds should be a cinch, I think?
I see!
By the way, a word from your senior.
The balloon went absolutely bonkers.
Second Round
Minato Aqua's Attempt!
This is Aqua's attempt at 15 seconds!
Three, two, one, go!
One,
Okay, I'm doing it!
two,
And we're off to a start!
three,
four,
five,
six,
seven,
eight,
It's so big!
nine,
Oh no!
ten,
11,
12,
They're behind.
13,
14,
15!
There, 15 seconds!
It didn't pop!
It did not pop!
Hey, management!
Can you believe it? It survived!
What went wrong with Robocosan's balloon...?
Give me an explanation, management!
We're going to have a talk later, you hear?
Which leads us to...
Second Round
Momosuzu Nene's Attempt!
At this point, doesn't
25 seconds sound doable?
Nene, should be a cinch, right?
Are there any wimps in the crowd?
Not at all! Sign me up for 25 seconds!
Alright, let's aim for 25 seconds!
Three, two, one, go!
Will it make it to 25 seconds?
The limit was 20 seconds after all!
And that's a wrap!
Since the balloon popped, Nene-san loses!
That's ridiculous.
This really sucks...
Aqua-san is the Master of the Last Minute!
Congratulations!
Yay!
My balloon's in a million pieces...
Alright, let's have the Master of the Last Minute,
Aqua-san, wrap up the show!
Okay!
You're going to inflate the balloon
as you do it, by the way, Aqua-san.
Let's gooo!
You can do it!
I really had fun with everyone today!
I can hardly hear her.
What? What was that?
What? Huh?
Save me!
I'm not hearing your voice!
I can't hear anything!
What was that?
What?
This is too much!
Huh? Where's your goodbye?
Where's your goodbye?
Like this video
and subscribe to this channel
and the talents' channels!