They're pig panties, right?
It's a bear!!
Ahahaha!
My bad!
Hahahaha...
Time to move on to the next segment!
'Kay!
Waaah!
Sketches Speak asLoud as Words?!
So this is my segment for the show!
In this segment, we'll take turns drawing
Rules
Secret Situation
Please draw "Shiranui Flare
falling asleep during a stream"!
a picture of a set topic, and the first one who can
convey what the topic is with their drawing wins.
Nenechi, Watame, and I,
Thinking...
and of course everyone watching too, will be guessing.
It's me falling asleep!
'Kay!
A: Momosuzu Nene making the smuggest face
So now, it's my turn to guess.
Draw
Answer
So now, it's my turn to guess.
Let me know when you're done.
Topic: Shiranui Flare performing a quick-draw slash
Ahh!
I see.
This one will need some creative thinking.
I see how it is!
This will be hard.
Well then,
please start now!
'Kay.
Ding!
I wonder what it is.
Like,
Noel seems to be coming up
as the topic a lot lately,
but surely they wouldn't put her
as the topic three times in a row!
I wonder what it is.
Done!!
Okay, Nene-chan!
Let's take a look
at Nene-chan's drawing!
Please do!
Here it is!!
Who?
Eeeeekkk!
You're asking who?
Is this me?
Huh?!
So that thing over on the right,
is what...
W-What―?
What's that thing on the right?
That thing's
a hint!
Flare-senpai...
Really?
Uhmm...
Shiranui Flare making a circle with her hands.
That's not it.
Nope!
Though actually,
I think I might have
misread the words
on the topic!
You read it wrong?!
Hey, can someone from the staff
tell me how to read this, please?
Please continue drawing then.
The both of you should obviously know
what the topic is if you're drawing it.
That's a weird thing to ask now.
I just read it wrong!
But they kind of mean the same thing.
Kind of.
I'm done!
Okay!
Let's take a look at Watame-san's drawing!
Please show us.
You should be able to guess this, right?
What's this supposed to be?
This is―!
This is super easy to understand.
It kind of looks like "Shiranui Flare
and the Tale of the Bamboo Cutter".
Am I cutting something?
Huh, did I get it wrong?
Did I?
Maybe I didn't really understand what this word meant.
Shiranui Flare cutting bamboo
No?
Well then, keep drawing please.
'Kay.
So like,
the comments are
starting to get a little busy too.
Done!!
Okay!
Nene-chan!
Please show us your dr―
Huh?
What's this?
Combine them!
Is it a quick-draw slash?
A: Shiranui Flare performing a quick-draw slash
Ding ding ding!
You got it!!!
That was so
hard to get!
Wooow!!
Is a quick-draw slash actually
used for fighting people?
...That's what I thought, but
you guys tried a lot of different things that were
kind of close, so I got it.
I got confused
and drew "sword catching" at first.
Anyway, I figured it out from
Nene-chan's drawing, so
she gets 1 point.
Hooray!
So what actually is a quick-draw slash?
So up next―
Uhmm...
Well,
it's time for that.
That problematic segment.
Can I leave now?
Huh, why?!
Love Letters From Nene!
I want to leave too.
So in this segment,
I write love letters to other hololive
members that I really, really wuv.
Rules
Then, we turn the replies I get
to those love letters into a quiz.
I see.
This letter will form the quiz!
Then Watame-senpai, Flare-senpai,
and all the viewers will guess what's written,
Fill in the blanks!
so please go all out with some bold answers.
So, on the last―
During the
last episode of holo's Bonjour,
Here it comes...
I'd already told Towawa-senpai
that I'd be sending her a love letter,
so I took the chance to go wild
and wrote whatever I wanted.
I feel sorry for her...
And Towawa-senpai
just went with it and wrote
whatever she wanted for her reply as well.
Now, let's first look at the love letter that I sent her.
Momosuzu Nene
Tokoyami Towa
Okay!
Okay.
Here it is.
"Dear Towawa-senpai,
What's with that drawing?
There's a strange picture on the letter!
What's this drawing?
♥Nene's Panties♥
"You are the senpai that I feel closest to,
and you were my first collab partner as well.
You're so easy to talk to and so cool
and I wuv you!!!!
Please send me a barrage of Towawa-beams.
Let's continue to have lots more fun together!
Also, this is a present from me."
Nobody wants that!
Hahahaha!
I gave her my panties as a present.
U―U―
Used?
Of course! After I used them!
And before I washed them, too.
What do you mean by "of course"?!
I gave her fresh ones
that I took off just before
getting in the bath.
What an amazing present.
Huuuh?!
What are you on about?!
Old Man Watame is turning into a pervert,
so please show us the―
Please show us the reply to this letter.
'Kay, this is the reply.
That's a lot of line breaks.
"Dear Nenene,
Reading Out the Questions
I really love your
(1) ??????"
(1) makes everyone..."
Ah...
U-Uhmm...
"Makes everyone happy"?
"Makes everyone happy"...
"I really love your...
They heard nothing.
your bright smile and laugh,
and your (2) ??????
as well ♥.
'You're the biggest, brightest star in the sky!'
is what I thought at first,
but I'd actually rather you
stay here in on the ground,
and work hard to become the
biggest pervert in hololive.
(3) ??????...
Thanks for the stinky present as well.
Here's something in return...
Love, Towa"
She just up and decided that my panties stink.
So―
Okay,
so we have to guess these...
Yes, please guess what they say!
"Makes everyone happy"~
Please erase that from your memories!
"Makes everyone happy"...
This picture of me kind of looks like a jellyfish.
It does.
But, actually (1) and (2) are pretty hard...
I have no idea about (3) either though.
Don't zoom in on that!
Please zoom in on my panties too!
No, don't!
Stop that!
They're pig panties, right?
It's a bear!!
Ahahaha!
My bad!
My bear turned into a pig...
For (2), please write something
kind of...
a little harsh and scornful please?
Flare-senpai.
Pfft.
Okay then, please show us your answers now!
Here they are!
Tada!
Ahh!!
I see.
Mmhmm.
Let's start with Watame-senpai.
Please read out the sentences
with your answer.
What's up with your (2)?
Watame Reading Her Answers
"I really love your
(1) cheerful atmosphere that makes everyone happy,
your bright smile and laugh,
(2) and the fact that you like to drink
from the flowing springs of the armpits♥
*cough*
*gasp*
... Work hard to
become the biggest pervert in hololive.
(3) The three perveteers...
Bwahaha...
That's a pretty iffy reaction.
65... points, maybe?
65 points!!
I got 65 points!
You still got more than half of it right, huh?
That's true.
Okay, next.
Flare-senpai,
it's your turn.
'Kay.
Flare Reading Her Answers
"...Your (1) cheerful vibes that makes everyone happy,
your bright smile and laugh,
{2) and your sexually suggestive remarks are also great♥"
Bffft.
Mmhmm?
That's good.
"...work hard to
become the biggest pervert in hololive.
(3) Good grief...
Ooh!
That's good.
That's what I had.
Ahh!
I see!
I see it now!
I see.
A little lower,
at 60 points!
A 5-point difference!
What's the 5-point difference?
Is it the degree of perversion?
Is the amount of perversion?
Haha.
Hahaha!
Bwahahaha!
Well then,
I'll read the answer out now and
do my best to convey
Towawa-senpai's feelings.
Yes, please.
Reading Out the Actual Letter
I really love your
(1) cheerful singing that makes everyone happy,
your bright smile and laugh,
(2) and your slightly creepy masochistic side as well ♥
I see.
Oh my...
...Work hard
to become the biggest pervert in hololive.
(3) You've got lots of competition though...
Ahh!
She really went there!
... is what she wrote!!
You'd have to be a pretty big pervert to take #1 here...
Hehehe.
I see it now.
We certainly do!
You know...
I'm a bit frustrated.
Frustrated?
You are?
Yeah, a bit.
The next one...
The next letter will be going to you, Flare-senpai!
Really...?
Moving on!
We've got a new segment this time!
Ooh!
Yay!
Old Man Watame's Best Pictures Quiz
So, what's this mysterious quiz about?
This is Watame's section,
so Watame, can you introduce it to us?
Sure!
In this segment, we'll have four images
Rules
Pick an image from A to D.
and everyone has to guess which one
that would've made Watame think
"Damn, this is a nice picture..."
I thought was like, "Oh yes, very nice!"
Correct answer
I see.
I see, I see.
Out of the four images,
one of them will be chosen by me.
That one's the "Best Picture".
The other three images
will be chosen by the staff.
Ah, okay. I get it now.
Yes.
Today, you two are Old Man Nene
and Old Man Flare.
Old Man Nene
Old Man Flare
Leave it to me...
Heeheeheeheehee
Let's move on to the next one.
Nene: A: Lewd thighs ♥
Okay!
Surely the next one isn't... Oh, wow.
Aah...
You put some effort into this one.
You sure did!
I did, I did!
Which one do you think it is?
I'm pretty sure it's this one.
Thinking time starts now.
* It is a widely known fact that Old Man Watame starts her day with a generous helping of cute girls' armpits.
There's really only one that it can be...
There's pretty much only one,
maybe two at most...
If we were
picking two it'd be those,
but pretty sure it's this.
Oh?
Well then!
Please show us your answers!
Pfft!
Flare: Armpit
Nene: C: Boobs (Lamy's "snowballs") and pit
You didn't even write the letter!
Flare: Armpit
So,
I think people that choose D
would probably be normal Yukimins.
That seems right.
Normal―
Normal Yukimins would
probably pick D,
but as we know,
Watame is
only interested in armpits,
so yeah.
That's how you see it, huh?
Her eyes are locked on
to the pits and boobs.
Her "snowballs"are
in the picture too after all...
So both of you choose that one?
Yeah.
Yes.
Like,
if you were going for A,
I bet you would have gone for
an even lower angle
than that one.
Yeah!
I think you would have
found a
picture where you can
see more.
This kind of seems
a little half-baked.
Yeah, this just doesn't really quite
feel like Old Man Watame.
Yep, yep.
Same.
I see.
I guess I'll reveal the answer now...
Okay.
The answer is...
A!
Correct answer
WHAT?!
Watame?!
I expected more of you!
This is as low as it gets!
I actually watched it a bunch of times to check...
Are you sure it's not C?
There weren't any
lower shots than this.
Aaaaahhh...
Are you really sure it's not C!?
I wanted to choose C too, you know?
But A's like,
you'll understand if we can
get them to zoom in for us,
the way they pinch...
those thighs...
and like,
the way you can just almost see,
like, "Please just go down a little bit more!"
That kind of feeling.
You'd want to stick your hand in there, right?!
Yeah.
I'd want to squeeze myself in there.
You'd what?
I feel like...
I feel like the staff win this time.
This is a bit frustrating.
I was just taunting you before and now...
A-ha-ha!
But still, don't you think C
is up there as Best Picture as well?
I do!
I really had trouble deciding.
Actually, I was the one that asked her
to do this pose right?
What did you think?!
You really know what people want Nene.
It was the best.
You know what I want.
I guess we should call you
Old Man Nene from now on.
Thank you for your kind words!
I wanted to collab with Old Man Nene too.
Thank you very much!
Nenechi,
when you have your 3D debut,
Watame will probably start exploring
your body with her eyes.
Why stop there?
She can always cop a feel if she wants.
You sure?
Nene-chan really is a huge pervert, huh.
Got 'em!
BONUS
Q7: If you were to choose other hololive members to be your family, who would you choose?
I would pick Choco-sensei to be my mom
and my dad would be
YAGOO.
Wha—?
Is he in hololive?
Is YAGOO actually a hololive member?
You're so good!
You're so good at drawing hands!
That's what you're praising?
I might be receiving
a love letter next week...
I'll write you something
hot and heavy,
Please make it really juicy.
so look forward to it.
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub channel
on NicoNico for the full stream archives!
— P l e a s e
m a k e
i t
r e a l l y
j u i c y .