Cool and Composed White-Lion Girl
Shishiro Botan
*yawn*
Perfect day out today.
Maybe I should go for a stroll.
Senpai?
Gulp!
Why are you avoiding me?
Because you have a frickin' gun!
Oh, please. You've got it all wrong.
Look, I'm a pessimist at heart.
Wha?
I always prepare for the worst!
I was just... holding it in place
until the glue hardened...
Plastic Model
Towa-senpai!
Uh, everything okay up top?
Do you have any pwoblems that need fixing?
Well, one showed up just now.
Wely on your seniors more, Botan-chan.
I'm here for you.
Uh... In that case...
I think Towa-senpai has the wrong idea
about me, and I'd like to fix that.
Take a wook outside.
Do you know what she must be thinking
as a piwate widing a twicycle?
Not a damn clue.
She thinks that's her piwate ship.
That's what it means to have
the wrong idea about something.
I just wanna go home and play games.
You'll understand once you wide it too.
No, I...
I would rather not, honestly.
Take a wook outside.
Well?
I'll do it.
How am I supposed to deal with this?
Sorry, Shishiron!
Thinking about it,
there's no way that's a real gun.
Towa-senpai!
Sorry I freaked out...
...
Gotta tweet this out.
Please! You've got it all wrong!
She's a hunter by nature!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!