A devil! There's a devil in the house!
Eek!
Huh?
Help, Towa-chan!
Help, Towapi!
We don't crawl out like bugs.
Wow, there really is one.
Guess I'll try talking to him.
They seem to be having a convo.
Is that the devil's tongue?
Looks like he's here to see
if I'm doing my job right.
Oh, so like an inspection?
Let me at 'im.
Uh, Fubuki-chan?
Seeing small, cute things
makes you wanna touch 'em, y'know?
Foxy d...
...
No way, really?!
What is it? What's he saying?
He demands to be treated
with the respect he deserves.
And... why do you look so happy about it?
Okay, then. I present to the li'l devil
the doll I bought at the bazaar yesterday.
Wow, I'm impressed you have that on han...
Have this buzzing orc!
I worry about your spending habits.
Here you go, li'l devil.
Borc!
She even gave it a name...
Grumble grumble...
But he is kinda cute, to be honest.
Aki-senpai, no!
Here, Devil-kun.
Oh, he fell for me.
Too easy!
It seems he has a gift for you, Aki-senpai.
What is it?
Wow! A bouquet!
It's so pretty!
Will you please date and eventually marry me?
That's how he sounds?
It's time for him to leave.
Oh, really? Guess it's bye-bye, then.
A devil only leaves when
pacified with an offering.
An offering, huh?
A doll would be perfect for a kid like him...
Ah.
Huh?
Jerry!
Why'd the name change?!
A bouquet of roses for a present.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!