Hey, listen up.
I made a new magical item.
It's a sticker, and if you put it on someone,
you can control their every move!
Awesome, right?
You don't believe me, do you?
I'll have you know it's real!
In one of the office drawers!
Oh?
Come forth, Shion Mark II!
Whoa, a spitting image of me!
Next up...
Amazing! I'm a genius!
Wow, anything goes.
Lastly, to transmit my voice...
Gimme da fingers!
Hmm?
Eureka!
'Ello, Shion-chan!
'Ello, Korone.
Hey, don't copy me.
That's rude!
Heh. She has no idea.
Korone's such a simpleton.
She doesn't know that's a fake...
......
This is fun.
When will she catch on?
Wow! Wow!
So cool!
Damn, she's slow.
I'm getting bored of this.
Think it's time...
......
...to reveal my hand.
Whatcha gonna do next?
Ta-dah!
You've Been Prank'd!
You've been Prank'd!
What d'you mean?
You've been interacting with a puppet I made!
Huh? What the heck?!
Aren't I awesome?
My magic skills are the best in town!
Surprisingly small-scale.
Cool.
I gotta tell this story on stream.
I won't reveal my hand just yet.
That one's a puppet too, y'know.
Duping your friends is not cool.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!