Hiya-peko, hiya-peko, hiya-peko!
From hololive's 3rd Gen, I'm Usada Pekora!
Huh? Nobody home?
Hmm?
What's this?
"Peko Note"?
I don't pekall releasing any merch like this.
"Something funny will happen
to whoever's name is written here.
Erasing it will revert the change.
Once you've fried the beef and onions,
add the roux and boil to a simmer."
Uh, the last bit is just how to make curry!
Hmm?
Nya-hello!
Guess I'm first in today.
Time to explore.
Sakura Miko
Oh, hey, cake-o!
Wait...
...what?
What...
What the pek did I just say?
Not again!
What's happening? I'm in...
...shock-o.
I get it now.
I can force them to have my verbal pek.
So if I write down a bunch of names,
I can rule over them as their pekogenitor!
I will...
pekome the god of a new world!
What the pek is happening?!
Desk-o: -1 HP
I am so pekish right now.
How do we pektify this?
...
The Pekofied
Pekekekeko!
The Pekochan Empire is pekspanding its borders!
Okay, everyone calm down.
There's no use crying over spilled milk-o.
We should just...
suck-o it up and stream like this!
Peko?!
I'm sure the fans will like it.
It'll be a new peksperience.
Agreed. It'll be a nice change of pace-o.
Yeah. I wanna pek a crack at it too.
Wait, this goes against my pekolicies...
All right, gang,
let's do this thing-o!
Well, that was unexpected.
But I like it.
I should tune in and see how they go.
Breaking News!
What do you want
to see Pekofied
Miko do?
A Peko is fine too
Hiya-peko, hiya-peko, hiya-peko!
From hololive's Gen 0,
I'm Usada Miko!
Who died and made you Usada?
How are the others doing?
Ask us anything!
Something Crazy Happened!
I'm Usada Noel!
I'm Usada Rushia!
I'm Usada Luna...
W-Well, I don't know how to feel about this.
What do the fans pek of this?
nice
cute af
better than the OG
"Better than the OG"?!
Rude!
I'm the absolute best at this...
Wait a sec-o.
If this keeps up...
No! That'd be a disaster!
I'm cancelling this project this very second!
Peko is mine, and mine alone!
What game should I play nyext?
Huh?
Well, this game is over!
I weally don't understand...
Oh?
We can talk normally again!
You're right!
*pant*
Now...
With this, my unique identity is safe.
I've propekted it.
Urk.
Huh?
Usada Pekora
Was... Was I being made to talk like this?
We would love a Peko Note!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!