How confident are you on a scale of 1-100?
2.
What?!
For me...
20.
You're one to talk about being afraid!
'Sup! I'm Oozora Subaru
from hololive 2nd Generation!
And with me is...
A-quality day to one and all!
I'm Minato Aqua!
Next is...
'Sup, groupies!
I'm Tokoyami Towa-sama!
And finally!
Good afternene!
I'm Momosuzu Nene!
Thanks for having me!
Now then, we had Towa and Nene
participate in a little program of ours!
Right!
Please say the title together!
Ready, set...
VS!
One-Take Live Dubbing!
Yay!
For this program, we're going
to have both Towa and Nene each dub
some live narration over
some pre-recorded footage.
Aqua and I will watch the footage
and judge who did better!
I'm a little excited for this...
How? How?
How's it going to turn out?
Before the recording,
there was like a warning message.
It said,
"Don't record more than once!"
So it's a one-take?!
Yeah.
The real deal...
How confident are you on a scale of 1-100?
2.
What?!
Just 2?! Are you really that afraid, Nenene?!
Really?!
Are you freakin' serious!
Fine! 500!
O-ho?
What about you, Towa?
For me...
20.
You're one to talk about being afraid!
Aq-tan, seeing this is causing
a little nervousness for the judges, too.
Yeah, will this actually come off well?
If you were doing it, Aqua-chan...
you'd be like "Well... well... well..."
Excuse me!
She's making fun of you, Aqua!
Yeah, now I'm getting excited
for Towa-chan's turn.
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
(pressure)
Getting excited!
Let's get into it and have a listen, shall we?
Nenechi, give us a cute and funny
transition to the clips!
Well then, it's go time to showtime!
Sparkle sparkle sparkle!
I feel like I've heard that one before.
Nom Nom Animals!
Our first Nom nomanamaiamal! Hippo!
Hippo!
You flubbed it!
Its full English name is the hippopotamus!
Hippos are a regular feature in zoos!
They're a giant animal that can grow to over
five feet long and weigh more than two tons!
Length: 3~5m
Weight: 1~3t (adult)
Very passionate.
Next! Next slide!
Footage provided by Nagasaki Biopark
Now take a look at some
excellent footage of
this big hippo enjoying a meal!
Let's go!
It's showtime!
What do we have here?
Oh, this is what it's like?
Chomp! Nom nom!
REC
Whoa! That's incredible!
Mmm, mmm! Yummeh! So yummeh!
Who's that?!
Sorry, I made a little mess.
Now, they toss a watermelon
into the next hippo's mouth, and...
In just a second here!
And, wow, he swallows it in one gulp!
That's amazing!
The inside of his mouth is bubbly.
He should... Yes, that's right.
Bubbly?!
He should probably brush his teeth
a little more, don't you think?!
Thank you!
Now I, Momosuzu Nene, will tell you my own
special little piece of trivia about the hippo!
Actually, the hippo is...
(Script) Please provide
your own piece of trivia.
Huh?
Uh... um... uh...
Actually, you see, the hippo is...
Uhh... umm... well...
Hold on a sec! Hold on!
Oh no, we're out of time!
Our next Nom Nom Animal is the raccoon!
Raccoons prefer to...
inhibit areas near the water,
Inhabit*
Feature
Very dexterous fingers
and they have very dexterous fingers!
Inhibit?!
Poor kanji skills!
Time to take a peek at
a very unusual scene of raccoons eating!
Let's head over there!
In 3, 2, 1...
This is something else...
Go!
Now, what's happening here?
REC
A bamboo pole has been split in half here,
but it's not soumen that's being slid down it.
Cute!
What could it be? Beans, soybeans, what exactly?
What's coming down the slide?
Just what are they munching on?
Well, let's see, it's... ahh...
Oh, that sucks...
I want outta here...
What's sliding on in? Maybe it's natto?
They're washing the natto in water
and eating it.
Wow, wow!
Raccoons are, in fact, very clever.
One of them is stopping the flow.
This is a technique people
use for soumen quite a lot.
They stop it with their chopsticks
and then eat from there.
That's certainly one way to do it.
Oh, looks like it's really packed
down at the end!
That raccoon at the top is...
Oh, wait, time to read!
Now I, Momosuzu Nene, will tell you
my own hilarious piece of trivia about the raccoon!
Actually, the raccoon is...
Nice reading!
(Script) Please provide
a hilarious piece of trivia.
"Please provide a hilarious piece of trivia."
Actually, the raccoon is... uhh...
apparently a relative of Momosuzu Nene!
And that's all for today's episode of
Nom Nom Animals!
Now we've got some capybaras here. Oh!
Next time, we'll be showing you
some capybaras chowing down!
Make sure to tune in!
We'll see you all in the next episode!
Nom Nom Animals was brought
to you by Momosuzu Nene!
Which animal do you see
when you look at Momosuzu Nene?
What the heck was that at the end?
Which animal do you see
when you look at Momosuzu Nene?
That was a lot of ego
popping up at the end there.
That was some serious
Momosuzu Nene promotion.
I mean, I had leftover time to fill!
Okay, then.
All the extra stuff you threw in was great.
Like adding "Thank you!" in there.
Yeah, you were really vibing with it,
so it was easy to listen to.
It was, honestly.
Good Review
Really?
The more I watched,
the more confidence I lost.
Okay, next!
Shall we take a look at
Towa's exciting footage...?
It's the same video, but...
But the important question is,
will it be full of Towa's charm?
Okay, I see. That's what it's about, huh.
Now, Towa-chan!
Give us a cute and funny transition to the clips!
Ahn! Uhn! Let's roll the clip! Uhn!
This is cute?
Nom Nom Animals!
Yep! Guess they'll be eating!
Okay! Uh!
Our first Nom Nom Animal! Hippo!
Read backwards, that's Oppih!
Its full English name is the hippopoPOtamus!
Hippos are a regular feature in zoos!
They're a giant animal that
can grow to over five feet long
Length: 3~5m
Weight: 1~3t (adult)
and weigh up more than what's called,
uhh, two tons, it is said!
Called?
5 tons is pretty freakin' huge!
Now take a look at some excellent footage
of this big hippo enjoying a meal!
And now we've got this weird silence.
It's asking me to provide
some ad-lib voiceover here.
REC
Mmm, this is so yummy!
Yeah, becoming the hippo here
is the natural option.
There's lots of juice dripping out of my mouth,
but I guess that don't got
anything to do with anything!
This, it's just, it's just so tasty.
That's what he's saying, but it seems like none
of that melon is actually getting in his mouth!
Mmm, this combination of juice and seeds
is just so good that... that...
Oh, I spilled a lot there.
I hope that was okay.
Okay.
Now I, Tokoyami Towa, will tell you
my own special little piece of tribbera...
trivia about the hippo!
Actually, the hippo is...
Oh?
(Script) Please provide
your own piece of trivia.
"Please provide your own piece..." Oh!
Actually, the hippo is really dangerous
because it's got such a strong jaw!
It's dangerous,
so be careful, everyone!
Towa's IQ where?
The following... Oh, that's not right.
Our next Nom Nom Animal is the raccoon!
Raccoons prefer to...
inhibit, inhabit areas near the water,
and they have very dexterous fingers!
Feature
Very dexterous fingers
I knew it!
Yep.
Time to take a peek at
a very unusual scene of raccoons eatin'!
What was that silence?!
Don't all of them crowded back there
look like people at a bargain sale?
REC
So, here we have, um, wow, well...
A hotspot only the locals know.
Oh, raccoons!
This is well...
She's playing along.
If you stay here, you can eat all of it!
Take a look behind me.
All those guys behind me are so dumb.
All o' them back there.
I can just get up on this thing
and use my body to stop the food.
Well, that'll happen, too...
falling down and stuff.
The heck did you fall down for?!
Okay. "Provide some ad-lib..."
Oh, yeah, right.
Using my hands to stop it here,
I can get all this...
All of it, so much, so much that
it's spilling over my hands, spilling so much.
Oh, right. Oh!
Now I, Tokoyami Towa, will tell you my own
hilarious piece of trivia about the raccoon!
Oh crap! I don't know nothin'!
I wanna hear it!
Trivia...
Actually...
(Script) Please provide
a hilarious piece of trivia.
Actually, the raccoon is...
Umm...
Apparently, if it washes its body too much,
it will completely disappear!
Just kidding! (star)
Just telling lies.
Okay! No!
Nom Nom Animals...
ThatsallforNomNomAnimamu—
Next time, we'll be showing you
some capybaras chowing down!
My goodness, his face is
covered in that. Is he okay?
We'll see you all in the next episode!
Please give a closing line.
"Please give a clo—..." Oh!
Right! Uhh...
Next time...
Next time:
Nom Nom Animals D*es
See you next time!
Duel, standby.
What the heck?!
Nom Nom Animals is done for!
That was hilarious!
Yeah, it was funny.
"Nom Nom Animal D*es."
What was all that about?
I mean, when it says "next time,"
that's what it's gotta be, right?
The ad-libbing part was really funny.
Right?
It was really...
Wait, Aqua-chan, can you do it too?
Uh... yeah?
Wait, what?
The two of you could, like, be a bit
calmer while talking, right?
Huh?
Are you really saying that?
Did you hear that, staff-san?
Bring it.
We have one available
for dubbing over.
Oh, they have one more.
Do you wanna try it?
Wait, what?
Aqua-chan, that means you think
you could do it better than us, right?
Crap
You were talking about how easy
it was, right, Aqua-senpai?
Crap
Hmm?
Aq-tan's Nom Nom Animals starts in 3...2...1...
Start!
Uh...
Wait, "Nom Ngkohgdrgs Animal!"
Wait, we're starting so suddenly?!
Seriously?
Let me get some popcorn.
"Today's Nom Nom Animal is the capybara!"
Wait, wait, wait.
There's like, no—Where's the script?!
"Not capipara, nor cabibara,
it's a capa—capybara!
Let's give them a call! Capybara!"
All together now!
Footage provided by Nagasaki Biopark
Capybara!
"I wonder what they're eating!"
Seriously, what is that?
"Here is a cute scene of the capybara eating!"
What are they eating?
They're all eating it together.
It's one big family.
Mmg om mm mh ommh omm mm mm...
She sounds like she's dying.
Everyone ends up becoming the animal.
Mm mmg omm mh...
Someone call 911,
she's drowning.
Capybara (CV: Aqua)
Blrg mmg om mmh mm...
Time until next part:
7 seconds left.
6 seconds.
Mdgsjgsfu Delish! Delishush!
Delishush... Delicious!
5 seconds.
Delishush?
"And now, I, Minato Aqua,
will perform a one-shot joke."
Excuse me?!
The capybara is... capyba-dum tss
Alright. Moving on.
Why you gotta do that to me?
You got this!
"On the next episode, we'll be doing
a special coverage of kangaroos fighting!
There's more.
It'll be called... Energetic Animals!
Don't miss it!"
Oi, you tryna fight, mate?
Fight me. FIGHT me!
Yer always on your high horse, mate.
"Please say something to close it off."
Bye-bye!
I'm so off.
When it went to the capybaras,
you were going "Omdfjoghghuhd"
the whole time and not talking!
The way Aqua-senpai went from
"Hmm? I can totally do this, though?"
to her just making noises...
No one told me it was that difficult...
What the heck are you talking about?
There's no way that was in one take.
Stop lying!
No, we actually did!
It was actually one take.
So this means that
Next time:
Minato Aqua D*es
"Next episode: Aqua D*es"
Yeah.
It was foreshadowing.
Moving on, before we leave,
let's pretend Aqua's commentary
never happened,
and vote for whose commentary
was better between Towa and Nene.
Aqua and I will reveal
our choices at the same time.
Ready? Go!
Nene-chan?
Towa!
Oh? We're split.
Which part of Nene's did you like, Aqua?
The way she was unfazed even when
there was silence in-between the ad-libbing.
The "Thank ya!"s and "Let's go!"s kept it flowing.
Right!
I thought that was great.
Thank ya!
I feel like Nene's was better too after hearing that
Oi!
For me, "Next time: Nom Nom Animal d*es"
was just so funny.
Next time:
Nom Nom Animals D*es
That was great.
Now that I think about it,
Nenechi's was better.
And so, our winner today is...
Nenechi!
Yaaay!
Whoo!
I'm
the queen
of hololive!
The scope just widened.
Please close us off, Nenechi!
Okaaay!
I urge you to smash that like button
and subscribe to the hololive official channel
as well as our personal channels!
Who will challenge my throne next?!