chiheisen o suiheisen ni shitara...
Give up the high road and sail the high seas
ra Sea ra Sea
Le sea, le sea
ra Sea 4 (shi) shi!!!
See the seas of ecstasy!
WAHHH!!!
Wahhh!
(Aw yeah)
shin! shoku! Sing! Shock! shin! shoku! Sing! Shock!
Sing! Shock! Sing! Shock!
harou de minna ni HELLO HELLO
Upon the waves, we wave hello
shin! shoku! Sing! Shock! shin! shoku! Sing! Shock!
Sing! Shock! Sing! Shock!
shinsui shinkai Swing & Sweet
Sincerely sail and don't sink, enjoy the Swing & Sweet
fuffuuu
Woohoo!
tomii❤ meiyo❤ seiso no shougou!
Wealth, fame, symbols of pure
yon nin de kassaracchattaro
The four of us will take it all
saa saa saa saa
Na-na-na Na-na
(saa saa saa saa)
(Na-na-na Na-na)
chikyuu o shinryaku TAKODA"CHkyuu"zou.
Take over the world, the Takodachi run amok
InaIna ii naa Ina ii naa
Ina, Ina, I-na, Ina, I-na
e kore de kaizoku honshokuka!?
Wait, am I a real pirate now?
datsu kosupure tte koto jan!!
No more cosplayer!
kimitachi mo "honmono no aji" shiritai no?
Would y'all like a taste of the real thing too, mateys?
(kitsui zo!!)
(That's a yikes...)
kimitachi mo "honmono no aji" shiritai no?
(kitsui zo!!)
(kusa desu)
(lol)
kimitachi mo "honmono no aji" shiritai no?
(kusa desu)
(kowa...)
(eep)
Shrimp, to salman, same zenbu tabemasu
All the shrimp, all the salman, sharky eat it all
(eat shrimp...
we eat every shrimp on the earth...
oh mic's on!)
A
zen jinrui jousen
All mankind on deck
hahanaru umi e to
To the all-encompassing sea
mizu ni otosan de...
No one goes overboard
hahanaru umi e to
mizu ni otosan de...
saikou no Deep blue
Take in the great deep blue
mizu ni otosan de...
saikou no Deep blue
watashitachi no umi e goshoutai
This is our cruise line
(Our showtime!!)
(Our showtime!)
(humu-humu.)
Uh-huh, uh-huh
son ja
Okay, let's roll
(1) Depart the harbor
(2) Launch our marine jet
(3) Start a sharkventure
(4) And TAKO-over the world with sea
Here we go
issee no
A-one and a-two
Here we go
issee no
(Hi hi hai!!!)
(Hi hi up high!)
oushan🌊🌊🌊oushan🌊🌊🌊
Ocean🌊🌊🌊Ocean🌊🌊🌊
Lovely ocean
mizu bita shin sekai
This inundated new world
aoi hoshi o urutoramarin ni somete
Paints the planet a deep ultramarine
ieei ieei ieei!!!
Yay, yay, yay!
oushan🌊🌊🌊oushan🌊🌊🌊
Ocean🌊🌊🌊Ocean🌊🌊🌊
Epic ocean
rikukaikuu zenbu kai kai kai!!
Taking over both land and sky
AQUA manpai Bluest Planet e susume
Destination: A bluest planet full of AQUA
yo-soro-!yo-soro-!
Keep 'er nice and steady! Steady as she goes!
kono hoshi o hitoshizuku ni shitara...
Turn the planet into but a drop in the bucket
ra Sea ra Sea
Le sea, le sea
ra Sea 4 (shi) shi!!!
See the seas of ecstasy!
WAHHH!!!
Wahhh!
rettsu ra oushan!!!
Let's ocean!
hai! kono fune no namae nani ni suru no?
Kay, what are we naming this ship?
"Nice boat gou" de ii n janai?
How about SS Nice Boat?
sore saa wakai risunaa wakannai yo...
You know the zoomers aren't gonna get that
uhh, "Uncontrolled gou" wa dou desu ka?
Uh, how about Uncontrolled?
nn... nande? douiu imi?
Why? What's that mean?
kono gyosen wa...
It means steering this ark is no walk in the p-ark!
"dare mo seigyosen" no imi desu!!=w=)7
e... mata dajare...
Oh, wow, so punny...
That's amazin-guh! same wa sore suki desu!!
That's amazin-guh! Thumbs up from the sh-ark!
senchouteki ni wa sore... "bacchiguu"
You have the captain's stamp of approval!
That's amazin-guh! same wa sore suki desu!!
senchouteki ni wa sore... "bacchiguu"
ano...
Er...
senchouteki ni wa sore... "bacchiguu"
That's amazin-guh! same wa sore suki desu!!
ano...
senchouteki ni wa sore... "bacchiguu"
That's amazin-guh! same wa sore suki desu!!
("nori" de zenbu susunderu...
(They're all going with the flow...
That's amazin-guh! same wa sore suki desu!!
("nori" de zenbu susunderu...
kore ga "komyuryoku"... tte koto!?)
Is this the gift of gab in action?)
oushan🌊🌊🌊oushan🌊🌊🌊
Ocean🌊🌊🌊Ocean🌊🌊🌊
kore ga "komyuryoku"... tte koto!?)
oushan🌊🌊🌊oushan🌊🌊🌊
waarudowaido komyu kyou, kowai...
Global smooth talkers, so scary...
oushan🌊🌊🌊oushan🌊🌊🌊
waarudowaido komyu kyou, kowai...
Here we go
issee no
A-one and a-two
Here we go
issee no
(hai? hai? Hi hi hai!!!)
(Hi hi up high!)
oushan🌊🌊🌊oushan🌊🌊🌊
Ocean🌊🌊🌊Ocean🌊🌊🌊
Lovely ocean
mizu bita shin sekai
This inundated new world
aoi hoshi o urutoramarin ni somete
Paints the planet a deep ultramarine
ieei ieei ieei!!!
Yay, yay, yay!
oushan🌊🌊🌊oushan🌊🌊🌊
Ocean🌊🌊🌊Ocean🌊🌊🌊
Epic ocean
rikukaikuu zenbu kai kai kai!!
Taking over both land and sky
AQUA manpai Bluest Planet e susume
Destination: A bluest planet full of AQUA
yo-soro-! yo-soro-!
Keep 'er nice and steady! Steady as she goes!
kono hoshi o hitoshizuku ni shitara...
Turn the planet into but a drop in the bucket
ra Sea ra Sea
Le sea, le sea
ra Sea 4 (shi) shi!!!
See the seas of ecstasy!
ra Sea ra Sea
Le sea, le sea
ra Sea 4 (shi) shi!!!
See the seas of ecstasy!
(wah...)
UMISEA - Domination! All the World Is an Ocean
Music/Lyrics: Camellia
Illust: namo
Vocals: Minato Aqua, Houshou Marine,
Ninomae Ina'nis, Gawr Gura