hololive 1st Generation - Plasmagic Seasons!
Lyrics: Ren Morimoto
Composition, Arrangement:
Ren Morimoto, Yoshinobu Takeichi
Vocals: Yozora Mel, Aki Rosenthal,
Akai Haato, Shirakami Fubuki, Natsuiro Matsuri
In the twinkling night sky, the seasons turn
kagayaku Yozora shiki megutte
The spring breeze will carry you
harukaze kimi o nosete
Until the summer is in sight
Natsuiro ga mukaeru yo
The colors of fall will give you a little push
iromeku Aki ga senaka o oshitara
Into fluffies, blizzards, and sparkles
mofumofu Fubuki kirameki
Your dizzy, giddy heart
meguri meku Haato
We didn't know where each step would take us
nannimo wakaranai ippo susunde
And now we've finally made it here
yatto koko made tadori tsuketa ne
We've been waiting for so long
machiwabiteru
(Too long)
(zutto)
To be on this lovely stage
sutekina suteeji
You'll be the first
ichiban ni
To see us put on a show! (Yeah!)
zettai misete ageru yo! (oo!)
Let's go! Smile! Smile! Catch up, future!
ikou Smile! Smile! Catch up, future!
The innocent seasons keep turning
mujaki ni mawaru kisetsu ga
Running around the world, making every day a dream
sekai o kakemegutte yume no youna hibi e to
Shine! Bright! Bright! Light up, future!
hikare Bright! Bright! Light up, future!
We're the brightest stars there are!
bokura ga ittousei!
That's right! Keep that light shining!
sou sa! terashi tsuzukeyou
The spotlight has only just been lit
supottoraito wa tsuita bakari
Red cheeks glowing like holiday lights
akaramu hoho no irumineeshon
Hearts in each and every color
kokoro wa irotoridori
All dancing at this festival
hajike mau fesutibaru
A rose-tinted glass filled to the brim with happiness
shiawase ippai sosogu rozegurasu
Ring it, and with a sparkle, it'll fill with color
narashite kira tto someru yo
All your pure white feelings
masshirona kimochi
Let's forget about the stroke of midnight
juuni ji no kane nanka wasurechatte
And cast a spell that will never be broken
zutto tokenai mahou o kakeyou
We'll make your heart flutter
tokimekashite
(Softly)
(sotto)
We'll give you a good time
mune odoru jikan o
Your heart'll dance
okuru kara
So you'd better keep up with us! (Yeah!)
zettai tsuite oide yo! (oo!)
Do it! Spark! Spark! Pop-up, future!
todoke Spark! Spark! Pop-up, future!
Living for the moment, these five stars
ima o kakeru itsutsuboshi
Let's get the whole world in here and make some noise
sekai mo makikonde nigiyakashiku asobou
Forever! Flash! Flash! Make up, future!
zutto Flash! Flash! Make up, future!
In a blindingly bright situation
me mo kuramu shichueeshon
You still haven't danced enough, right?
mada odori tarinai desho?
Keep going long, long after the curtain call
kaatenkooru no zutto zutto saki made
Anyone can be the star of the show
tanoshimu kimochi sae mottekitara
As long as they're ready to have some fun
kitto daremo ga shuyaku ni nareru yo
Show the world your wings and tail and smile
hane mo shippo mo egao mo sarakedashite
Step bolder!
motto Step!
(Step!)
Jump higher!
motto Jump!
(Jump!)
You only live once in this world
matatonai kono sekai o
So let's enjoy it all we can! (Yeah!)
issho ni asobi tsukusou! (oo!)
Sing it! Clap! Clap! Let's sing, future!
hibike Clap! Clap! Let’s Sing, future!
Even if this melody has to end
kono merodi ga owatte mo
We won't let it just be something you heard today
kesshite kyou dake no omoide ni wa shinai yo
Let's go! Smile! Smile! Catch up, future!
ikou Smile! Smile! Catch up, future!
The innocent seasons keep turning
mujaki ni mawaru kisetsu ga
Running around the world, making every day a dream
sekai o kakemegutte yume no youna hibi e to
Shine! Bright! Bright! Light up, future!
hikare Bright! Bright! Light up, future!
We're the brightest stars there are!
bokura ga ittousei!
That's right! Keep that light shining!
sou sa! terashi tsuzukeyou
The spotlight will never go out
supottoraito wa owaranai