Ooh...
Ugh, it's so hot!
Inari-san, what is the matter?
It sure is.
Oh, Touka-san...
It's definitely summer.
It's just, I've noticed
a lot of people are absent lately.
It's so hard to work up the energy
to study when it's this hot.
And more and more students from the class
next door haven't been heard from.
Can't it be summer break already?
I know!
Yes, that seems to be the case.
Camping in the mountains,
swimming in the pool...
Perhaps a summer cold is going around.
A summer cold...?
There's so much I wanna do
during summer break.
Yes, a summer cold.
As it gets hotter,
people start to lose their appetites
For me, it's the festival!
or have trouble falling asleep at night.
I just can't wait for it!
That disturbance to the body's rhythm
They're holding it this year, right?
can make one more susceptible to summer colds.
You bet they are!
I-I see.
Oh man, I'm excited too.
A summer cold...
That would be a relief...
I hear they're pulling out all the stops
for this year's festival.
I am unsure if that could be considered a relief.
Really?
I hear that summer colds can be quite stubborn.
How come?
Is it a special year?
Indeed, last year,
too many late nights studying for exams
Like the festival's 50th anniversary?
I dunno, actually.
ended with me bedridden for three days.
How I feared that
I would simply miss my exams.
I might have missed that part.
I think there was something to do
with the god that the festival celebrates?
That must have been awful...
I'll take care.
Final exams are coming up.
Oof, sounds complicated.
Are you staying up late studying?
You know what, forget I asked.
Yes, somewhat...
Not worth the energy.
Hey, now, are you sure?
I'm sure you have a lot to study for,
but be sure to rest.
You should respect the god,
or it might punish you.
Without you,
our class would turn into a zoo,
even during school hours.
It might double your summer homework!
Eek! That would suck!
Ah-hah-hah...
Thank you for your concern.
I respect you, god!
I'll take care of my health.
I'll celebrate the heck out of your festival,
so please don't punish me!
I know! Let's all go to the festival together!
Our combined celebration
will definitely please the god!
Great idea.
Let's all go together this year.
We can invite the new kid, too.
Yeah, let's!
I hope they enjoy it.
I'm sure they will.