Okay, hang on.
Noel's being scary!
Noel scary!
I feel like I shouldn't take this one!
Who're you calling a cat?!
Pre-Bloom, Streams Roundup
From 2021/01/05 Stream
"Want to Be a Flowery Idol!"
Floriography Concentration Game
AkiRose's favorite number, seven!
Seven? Lucky seven!
Noe-chan!
Wow, that was quick!
It's Noe-chan's flower!
It's Noel-san's motif...
Flare-chan's going to kill me...
Number 15.
Shirogane Noel's Floriography Keywords
Number 15 is Noel-san's.
Yikes.
I gave away a huge hint.
Next up is Choco-sensei.
Oh no...
Oh no!
What am I supposed to do?
I feel like I shouldn't take this one!
And she scores Noel-san's cards!
Man, that's crazy.
I had to score that one,
or I'd get stabbed later.
We're all...
From 2021/01/29 Stream
"Taking On New Challenges In Our Everyday Lives"
Daily Challenges!
overwhelmed over here!
Are we gonna be okay?!
You know...
You get nervous with the concert
right around the corner.
Okay, hang on.
Noel's being scary!
Noel scary!
As for me,
I took over Oozora Subaru's Twitter
and ran it for one whole day!
Here's one of the tweets.
Okay, Subaru-senpai.
ha ha ha
Read it out for us.
I'm a girl too, you know...
Hmm?
That's a lot of retweets and likes!
62,000 likes?
That's an all-time high for me.
It's the most buzz I've ever had,
and it was created by someone else.
To Sakura Miko
Challenge:
"Record yourself sleeping for a week!"
From Sakura Miko
It's from Sakura Miko!
Why'd you pick your own topic?
Temperence...
Temperence?
Tem...
Tempest...
I wanna eat adfhasldnc...
Dun!
From 2021/02/06 Stream
"holo's Extreme RPS Tournament"
Scissors! I get the points!
Gah!
I lost!
O Roboco, win this in my stead.
You got it, Kitty.
Huh?!
Who're you calling a cat?!
What will you play, Shishiro Botan?
What do you want me to play?
Paper.
Sure.
Dun!
Yeah!
You're... pretty straightforward.
It's cute.
They don't call me
Straightforward Shishiro for nothing.
By whom? When?
Talk about having the wrong idea.
My viewers!
Oi.
Don't you dare mock my viewers.
Wha!
You're gonna talk to me like that?!
Cry into your pillow and wait.
:sob:
Towa-senpai's bullying me...
Stop saying that! This is why...
Towa-senpai's
bullying me.
You moron!
So, these boards...
From 2021/02/13 Stream
"9 Weeks Straight Recap! Song Quiz!"
Floral Circlet Quiz
Question
From Hyakkaryouran Hanafubuki
Nikko's Irohazaka Winding Roads
The road uphill
has 20 characters set up.
How many does the downhill section have?
Wait, wait, wait.
Okay, I just got it.
Oh, you did?
Well, I got the question.
I dunno the answer.
Iro ha nihoheto, chirinuru wo
You're saying it out loud!
Yikes, yikes, yikes.
It's Asaki yume mishi, wehi mo sesu.
Oh, uh...
Could you repeat that? Slowly.
The answer was 28!
By the way, Lamy-san,
did you understand the question?
If I did, I wouldn't answer with "5"!
Let's take a look at the next
submission from our viewers.
"I pump myself up for important days
by making some Japanese-style carbonara!"
Yeah, it's good to eat something that fills you
with power and energy the day before.
Right?
Well, we're going to be singing and dancing,
so, uh, I don't know about
eating that much garlic.
hahahaha
Let's all eat garlic the day before.
Make it impossible to tell who
the garlic stench is coming from.
Let's all reek of garlic.
That'll leave only the staff
holding their noses like, "ew."
Let them eat garlic too.
That's crazy.
I'll be a Garlic Concert.
lololol
Bloom, Highlights I
All Talents Have Their Own Flower Motif
Okay, AkiRose-san's first up.
Aki Rosenthal's Flower
Rose/Red
"I love you"
Affection
Wow, how passionate.
That's me.
"I love you so very much."
Thank you!
Yuzuki Choco's Flower
Rose/Pink
Graceful
Stylish
It's perfect for me.
It's missing the lewd part.
It fits my image perfectly.
I keep getting distracted by the boobs.
Don't you guys have anything better to say?!
Shiranui Flare's Flower
Kalanchoe/Orange
"Many small memorable moments"
"Harbinger of fortune"
Oh, now we have Flare-san.
Aw, how cute.
Very adorable. Do you have some kind of
special connection with kalanchoes?
Nope.
No?!
Didn't see that coming!
So I can make many, many memories
together with Flare-sama?
Sorry, I already have Noel.
Towa-san.
Tokoyami Towa's Flower
Forget-Me-Not/Violet
"Don't forget me"
"True friendship"
Huh?
It's your turn!
Huh? It is?
Were you asleep?
Wake up!
Forget-me-not?
Forget-me-not!
Yeah, forget-me-
Bloom, Highlights II
All Songs Original, a First for hololive
From 2021/02/06 Stream
"holo's Extreme RPS Tournament"
Bloom, Songs Introduction
In Candy-Go-Round,
we'll be moving all over the place.
In Bloom, that is.
It's a song where we're truly being idols.
Please look forward to it.
Fubuki-san, talk us through
Hyakkaryouran Hanafubuki.
Okay, so this song...
It's a really cool Japanese fusion rock track.
It's a song with really fun calls and stuff,
so it'd be great if you could listen to the full version
and learn all the calls, like the "ooo hai" and stuff.
Next up, Towa-san.
Tell us about STARDUST SONG.
It may be all bright and stuff,
but it's also a song with these cool vibes.
Keep an eye on our dance moves
during the concert.
And finally, we have Botan-san.
Talk us through BLUE CLAPPER.
It's an uptempo, hype,
and dance-like track.
And during the concert...
You know how the song title has CLAP?
So it would make us very happy
if you could all clap along with us.
Bloom, Highlights III
A Concert Put Together by Both Management and Talent
From 2021/01/29 Stream
"Taking On New Challenges In Our Everyday Lives"
Recording Tidbits
Do you have any anecdotes to share?
Like what happened in recording?
When we recorded the song,
I was the last one up.
Your voices were already in the backing track.
I get to second verse,
and I hear Noel's backing vocals
going all like, "lmaooo."
Y'know, I recorded that several times.
And that was the best one.
That particular "lmaooo."
At first, I recorded my line like, "banger!"
But then we decided I'd match Noel's,
so it became "bangeeer!"
Lastly, let me advertise
the Bloom, concert.
hololive IDOL PROJECT 1st Live "Bloom,"
will be held on February 17.
Only three days left now!
Streaming tickets are on sale for 6,000 yen
on both niconico and SPWN.
It's a no-audience, streaming-only concert,
so I hope you will all cheer
our performers on from home.
For more details,
click the URL in the description
and check out the special website
for hololive IDOL PROJECT 1st Live "Bloom,"