Caw caw!
"Caw"?
Yikes! It's evening already!
What's this, then?
'Sup!
Whoa!
Yo, Subaru.
Ya doin' all right?
Ayame? What's with that getup?
New outfit reveal.
I was more wondering
when you got your PhD in Thuganomics.
Wait, did you read this?
Aye. 'Tis my bible.
Talk about easily influenced.
S-So cool!
Make us your soldiers!
Now listen 'ere. I'm a lone wolf.
Gangs ain't my style.
Please!
Let us call you "Boss"!
"Boss"...
Fine. Do whatever.
Yay!
On one condition.
If ya wanna roll with me,
ya gotta have some drip.
M-Rod NayNay
T-Bone Watameh
Have you guys lost your minds?
Yer startin' to look the part.
Thank you, Boss!
Next up, practisin' yer stink eye.
Whoa!
Give it a shot.
Aye!
Damn, that looks kinda fun.
Why do you have to freeze me out like that?!
Okay, forget that little drive-by.
Ya got it down pat.
Thank you, Boss!
Now for the finishin' touch.
Let's hit the road!
Hit the road? On our beasts?
Aw yeah, the wind feels hella good.
You guys feelin' it too?
A... Aye.
I-It feels great.
Aight!
Floor it!
We're goin' beyond the horizon!
Y-Yeah!
Now also manager of the Gang.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!