'Tis...
'Tis.
'Tis?
'Tis!
'Tis We!
Summer is here, and 'tis a sizzler!
But the heat, it makes me suffer.
It's so hot, I've split into many others.
If this keeps up, I'll melt like butter!
That's where the talk of the town...
...this special cooling material, comes in!
It shall OHKO the summer heat!
And 'tis time for show, not tell.
Sally we forth!
Aye!
Ugh... Another hot day.
Summer has you hot and bothered, does it?
Eek! Why do you have four heads?!
Since you're having such a hard time...
I present to you my special cooling material.
What? Really?
Here!
That looks hazardous!
Wait, "material"?
Isn't this just food?
Listen to yourself!
'Tis most efficient to cool down from the inside.
Y-You may have a point there.
Furthermore, I gave some to
Watame and Fubuki-chan earlier.
And it worked really well.
Too well!
No... Am I the only survivor?
Indeed. The last woman standing.
Join the other two in the land of permafrost!
Why the sudden heel turn?!
Anyway, it's too hot in here.
Let's continue this after a shaved ice break.
Ah...
No! The Third! The Fourth!
How dare you!
Uh, that was entirely self-inflicted!
Fine. I, the true self, will take you on personally.
Hold it! I'm the original!
Excuse me? I'm the real one.
No! 'Tis I!
I!
Talk about an I for an I.
Actually, Ah'm the real 'un.
Huh?
'Tis I, pray believe me.
Wha...
I!
Gah!
Try this on for size!
You're going down!
I'm I!
Why, you little...
Wait, did I eat breakfast?
There is no "team" in I!
Take this!
Yikes.
I do be the real one, believe it!
Who?!
She sometimes multiplies over Obon.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!