The story so far!
Armageddon is upon us.
Where did we go wrong?
How did this happen?
I can't just sit around
and accept this cruel fate.
I need to take a look back at past events
so I can figure out the cause.
So let's roll the footage!
Top 10 hologra Scenes
Likely to Cause Armageddon starts now!
Number Ten!
The Need for Speed
Suisei... Train?
You! The Kanata over there!
Ah, the scene where Suisei-chan makes like a train.
How would you like a ride on the Surly Suisei Train?
Looks like a fun time, but beneath the surface...
That was you being surly?
Armageddon Triggered In:
Weren't you singing and stuff?
No mood lasts forever, okay?
Scariest look ever!
Yeah, her rage does have the potential
to cause world destruction.
Anyway, you should give it a shot. Come on.
O-Okay.
Get it now? That's how this episode is gonna go!
What the...
Number Nine!
The Difference Between Coffee and Mud
I will become a sheep who can drink coffee!
It's the scene after Watame
Apologize to me first.
spits black coffee all over Subaru-chan's face.
My, my. Can you really, Watame-sama?
Armageddon Triggered In:
I can! I know it!
Then you'd do well to start by
grasping the situation you're in.
I tap! I tap!
I hear a Great-O-Wrestler started using
this move in his matches!
I tap! I tap!
Time to step out for a strategy meeting!
Let's go, Subaru-senpai!
But kids, don't try this at home.
Eh, I don't wanna... go?!
Number Eight!
Really Wanna Eat You-Know-What!
Get your PolPols in, okay?
I know my way around hell, thank you!
The scene where they have a run-in with the forest gang.
Owie!
Armageddon Triggered In:
Alarm Clock! No!
I'll miss you.
Hmm?
At that moment, the clock's raging spirit took over.
Rise and shine, kids! Wakey-wakey!
If only the alarm clock's raging spirit
hadn't taken over...
Goonigh!
Number Seven!
You Won't BELIEVE What These Two Did!
Koro-san?
The scene with the Korone-chan startup!
Armageddon Triggered In:
The Korone Company is born!
Yay!
The Korone Company would eventually go public.
Koro-san's grown so big...
Number Six!
Buried in Wall. Send Help
Why are you stuck in the wall?
I don't think I need to explain this one.
Well, I was practicing teleportation,
Armageddon Triggered In:
and I messed up.
So pekoolish.
Hey, you've got carrots stuck in your hair too!
Unlike you, Shion-senpai,
these come pekout easily!
Maybe Shion-chan wouldn't have gone berserk
if she hadn't been relentlessly trolled this way.
Number Five!
No wait time in this one!
Armageddon Triggered In:
Help! I'll be Burned!
'Tis I.
The tidal wave of tweets after this
It's gotten quite chilly lately, huh?
shook the world to its very core.
Right?
You agree, don't you?
Number Four!
Watch out, no wait time here either!
Armageddon Triggered In:
Polar Bear vs. Noble Girl
Vroom!
Thwack
What in the world is Lamy-chan doing?
Mimicking a lawnmower because she's bored, apparently.
This led to landmowers flying off the shelves,
Of all the things to mimic...
erasing all greenery on Earth...
Okay, time for a break.
Number Three!
Let's Form a Band!
(＾ ‿　＾)
Matsuri-chan?
Her heart is so pure now,
she has a smile on her face 24/7.
Matsuri-chan gets her hands on a magical triangle.
Scary!
But the triangle should sound beautiful now!
Its tone changes based on
how pure your heart is!
Armageddon Triggered In:
Try playing it!
One, two...
(＾ ‿　＾)
The Negative Ion Vacuum Sisters
became a huge deal at the time!
(＾ ‿　＾)
That sound led to the completion of
Negative Ion Vacuum Sisters.
Number Two!
In Spring, w00t!
...I am the goddess of spring.
Oh, hey, Miko-senpai.
Hey! No breaking that wall!
Running around in search of Spring,
Nene-chan finds herself in a strange portal.
To ye, who believes in spring,
I bestow these spring powers.
Spring powers?!
Show them who's boss.
I'll try, Miko-senpai!
Armageddon Triggered In:
I told you, I'm the goddess of spring!
Oh, she's back.
Behold Super Nene,
now with new spring powers!
My headache's gone!
Huh?
*hack*
The concept of ever-changing seasons died here.
The first spring breeze!
Thanks, Nene-chan.
You're a lifesaver.
Perennial spring was comfy living, though.
A goddess! The goddess of spring!
Number One!
Survival of the Fittest
Haachamachama!
The scene where Haato-chan escapes Subaru-chan
and returns to the gang in a foul mood.
Armageddon Triggered In:
Desk: -100 HP
What did I do to deserve this?!
And thus, the Cretaceous period came to an end.
hololive had been active since the Cambrian explosion,
but it would go on hiatus here.
Oh, so that's what brought about Armageddon.
The next time hololive resurfaced
was at the beginning of the Cenozoic period.
I didn't realize because I slept through it all.
Fiiin.
Yikes! Even this place won't last much longer!
See you next week!
Production Is Disaster.