Oh my god, Nene!
Wait, this doesn't look good!
Why?!
It's already over!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
You know how today...
Yeah?
is August 19th?
I hear that's Haiku Day.
Oh!
Really?
Since it's Haiku Day and all, let's make some together.
Why are you suddenly trying to torture us?
How about we don't?
Suddenly hell
Don't do this.
I don't wanna.
Marine, you seem raring to go.
Please no!
You're gonna traumatize us!
If you want to go that badly, be my guest.
Uh...
How about your goals for today?
I'm...
My goals?
My dear Subaru
Her dear Subaru.
Can I address you as such
From this day onward?
Ew, no!
Eww!
Will she give her a response?
Marine-chan, you see
Marine-chan!
That might be a little bit
Cringe coming from you
Oh my!
She got rejected!
My dear Subaru
Then I will personally
Kill you here and now
It's a haiku bloodbath!
No! Help!
Someone hasn't gone yet.
Oh yeah, Towa-chan!
End it with a bang!
That's your last one, Subaru-chan?!
Yeah, that's it.
Towa has strict standards for friends
But...
That's...
You didn't even get the format right.
That's it for me.
You suck at making haikus.
Oi! Then you try it!
Stop it!
Blow our minds with your galaxy brain.
Zoom in on her please, Cameraman!
Our dear customer
Our dear customer!
Here we have a lot of the
Ah.
No, wait.
Let's-hip-hip-hoo-ray!
Yaaay!
You suck!
Don't force it!
At least make sense out of it, you dolt!
What the heck was that hip hip hooray!
Relax a little!
Let's relax
and open up the store!
Hip hip hooray!
Hooray!
*spin*
Welcome!
Ooh! She's here!
She's so full of energy.
Today's Guest:
Momosuzu Nene
This is one cute customer.
Today's guest is Momosuzu Nene,
who's currently into making slimes.
Momosuzu Nene
Hobbies: Going outside! Dancing! Singing! Drawing!
Skills: Moving around...
Finishing Move: Super Nenechi's Lovey-Dovey Beam❤
MENT
LUCK
Compared to her insane LUCK, her MENT's a little low...
Which gen is Nene-chan in?
I'm in the 5th Gen!
Oh! So you're the newest one here?
She is.
She's our little newbie!
That's pretty rare.
I'm scawed! My seniors are so scawy!
I knew it! You guys are bullies!
Nene, we always treat you well, don't we?
Nene-chan, was that true?
Right, Nene?
We take such good care of you, don't we?
They're harassing her!
They're all such angels towards me.
They're making her say that!
Good girl.
They're totally making her say that.
While we're on the topic, who's the scariest senior here?
Towa-senpai has the sharpest tongue.
Ooh, I see.
Go stand in the corner!
You don't have what it takes to be a good senior.
Yeah!
It's not what you think!
She always acts like a brat towards me.
Like a brat?!
This is what she's talking about.
Bratting in progress
*distraction dance*
Nene-chan seems like
the most carefree existence in the world,
Free of any cares.
but I'll ask anyway. What are you here for today?
I'm super confident in my luck and physical abilities,
Uh-huh.
but my MENT is a little...
weak.
Seems kinda sus
Is it really?
Really?
Nene's surprisingly...
She seems strong-minded...
You're absolutely unfazed by everything, you know!
When I get told something, I end up accepting it as is
and feel down.
Ah, I see. So you end up
taking people's words at face value.
Yeah.
I see. Leave it to us!
And there we have our request!
We have just the thing!
Momosuzu-san's problem is, in short,
"I want to have a mind of steel!"
Yay!
It's already steel, ain't it?
But leave it to us!
The game we recommend for today is...
this!
SUPER BOMBERMAN R ONLINE!
Yay!
The latest installment in the Bomberman series,
SUPER BOMBERMAN R ONLINE.
The biggest selling point
in this installment is the Battle 64 mode!
You can play with 64 people, cross-platform, online!
On top of that, you can enjoy customizing your character
by changing your outfit and your bomb's skin.
And of course,
the other Battle modes are available as well.
Train your mental strength through some tense battles!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Nene-san, I hear you've played
a Bomberman game before
but your skills are around average. Is that right?
Yeah.
I played it once with the 5th Gen,
but I still haven't really grasped the rules.
Ah, I see.
Wait, but wasn't your INT maxed out...?
MENT
LUCK
Now that you mention it.
That's 'cuz I was just so smart
that it couldn't keep up with me.
Too smart, huh?
I was thinking too fast.
Ah...
So Bomberman couldn't keep up with your inputs?
Yeah, Bomberman couldn't keep up.
Ah...
Happens.
Like hell it does!
We've prepared a little something
so you'll want to win no matter what.
Oh? What is it?
Yeah, we did!
And its title is...
"You lose, you boom! Maruyama Bomber Survival!"
"You lose, you boom"?!
What does that mean?
That sounds scary.
Now then,
we'll have the four of them duke it out!
You lose, you boom!
Maruyama Bomber Survival!
Last place will have verbal bombs
that can break their heart
dropped on them from the other three.
You're all familiar with Bomberman's rules:
The last man standing wins!
The people with 2 wins get to leave the match,
and the person who can't get two wins
by the end loses.
Nene-san, overcome these odds to seize victory
and attain a mind of steel!
You can do it!
Game 1: Start!
Without further ado, game 1, start!
Round 1
Time to win!
The stage is random!
Time for an easy win.
And so it begins!
Whoa, what's this?
It's so big!
Yeah, it is.
Can I do this?
Whoa.
Just keep calm and carry... Keep calm!
Got me an item!
I'll have this...
Keep calm!
Calm!
Nice.
Good stuff.
Hey, Blue has a ton of items!
What?!
Huh?
Wait—
Wow, you're good at getting items.
Ah!
Louie (Egg): A powerful item that gives you a second chance.
Gotta make it work somehow.
Hey, my egg—
Oh my god, Nenechi, you idiot!
Gah!
Oh, bye-bye!
Oh my god!
Oh no, there goes one of you!
Subaru Out
Oh no! No!
Nice!
You have to get back in!
Bad Bomber: Allows other players to attack from outside
the map. Hitting someone gets you back in the game!
I can win this now!
Oh god, you can't be serious!
Ah! Ah!
That was so close!
You can get back if you hit someone!
What's your problem?!
Come over here, Marine!
C'mon, Subaru-senpai?
No! I screwed up...
Towa Out
Two left.
Marine and Nene's One-on-One
I wanna get back in there!
Nene-chan's still there!
Ah! Oh my god! Get me out!
Nice one, Nene-chan.
Nene-chan's dodging at the last possible second.
Just die already!
Oh no, this isn't good.
No!
Take that!
Nooo!
Skull Item: Applies a random debuff.
Effect may spread to other players.
Oh?!
I've got this, Nenechi!
Hold on, Marine!
I feel so loved!
Wait, why aren't you cheering for me?!
Why am I so slow?!
You can do it, Nene-chan!
Die!
Ow!
Wait, no!
Nene-chan wins!
What a win!
Yay, yay!
What do you mean? You were amazing!
Round 2
I did it!
You suddenly got so good.
I've awoken my potential.
There are a lot more rounds to go!
That's right. We're just getting started!
Let's do this!
Okay!
Nice.
I'm amazing at anything once I get how it works!
Oh!
Wow, listen to you.
You sound confident.
Are you starting to get it?
Oh, oh no!
Nenechi? Nenechi!
Ah!
Instant Karma
She blew herself up!
Huh?
Nene-chan got too cocky and blew herself up.
Nene Out
"I'm amazing at anything once I get how it works."
You just trapped yourself in there with that bomb.
That's some foreshadowing.
Yeah, didn't make sense to me.
Nenechi?
You're aiming at the wrong person here!
Nene-chan's being threatened by her senior.
Right, Nenechi?
Didn't I help you earlier, Nenechi?!
Nenechi?
Bad Nenechi, bad!
I wanna get back inside.
Hey, Nenechi...
Anyone will do...
"Anyone will do."
Switch places with me.
Nenechi's turned into a terrorist.
How could you do this to me?!
Oh no!
Stop screwing with me, Nene.
Nenechi...
You can't help someone who bullies you—
Wait for me!
Nooo!
Oh no!
Subaru Out
Oh my god, no!
And now Subaru is out!
Let's screw with them together!
Let's do it!
Stop it! Stop!
Ah!
Marine died in the same place!
Towa wins!
Yay!
Nice!
No...
Round 3
This could still go any way!
You don't know yet.
It's so much less stressful after you win one game.
Yeah, the stress is gone.
Definitely.
True.
Nene-san was desperate for a victory but dies instantly...
That's too bad!
Nene-san needed just one more win to be done,
Nene-san was desperate for a victory but dies instantly...
Nene Out
but she blows up immediately!
Let's see if she can get back using the Bad Bomber!
Nene-san was desperate for a victory but dies instantly...
You're a stubborn one.
Marine joins the fray from the outside.
I wanna get back in...
Huh?
Look at them scurrying around.
Oh god, look at that!
Is this it?
That was so close!
Looks like the game is about to be decided.
Aren't you good at running away!
Oh my god, Nene!
Nice one, Subaru!
Come on, Nene!
Ah!
Nice dodge, Subaru!
Subaru's too good!
Subaru's inhuman dodging skills
Subaru's waiting!
How did you—
She's a genius!
Easy game!
Come on!
What's this?
Hurry!
Whoa.
Is it speeding up?
There's one minute left!
What?
Wait, something's happening.
Look at the stage! It's getting smaller!
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
You've gotta survive!
Is this the most exciting match so far?
It's a one-on-one.
Wait, no!
Yes, yes, yes, die!
Ah!
Yes!
Subaru wins!
That was a bomb sandwich.
Yeah!
Come on...
Hey, now...
Marine's the only one left without a single win!
You're kidding?!
Round 4
Seriously?
That's right,
everyone has one win each.
I always come in at least second, though.
Yoink.
Nah, you gotta win at least once.
Everyone's too good at this.
Why...
It's way too hard to come first in this!
I feel like I have to play really carefully here.
Uh, Nene-chan?
Deja vu...
Nenechi?!
There goes Nene-chan.
What's going on here?
What the heck is this? Oh, come on!
Can she return?
Towa Out
Towa-chan is out too!
Here we go.
It's down to Marine and Subaru!
Look at all those items!
Come on, now!
What's going to happen?
That was too close!
Stop that already!
Hold up...
Marine's slowly being driven into a corner!
Nice one, Marine.
Can she survive?
I'm so slow—
Towa-sama blows Marine up from outside!
Now that's devilish!
Towa-san's bomb takes Marine out!
Now she's back in the game!
Oh yeah, let's go!
That's going to bring Towa-sama back in!
Yes!
I did it!
Wow!
The resurrected Towa-sama wins!
Towa-sama finishes first!
Come on!
No way!
Nice one!
Who's the next winner?!
Towa-san's win resets the scoreboard!
Who's going to be next to two wins?
What is this place?
This is so cute!
This stage is so cute!
Wait, we're so close together.
We're too close!
Wait, I can't, I can't, Ican'tIcan'tIcan'tIcan't!
It's so cramped in here.
No!
Nooo!
Wait, this doesn't look good!
Let me out!
Why?!
Hell yeah!
It's already over!
Subaru wins in an instant!
Yay!
What was that?!
That was a quick battle.
Everything ends in an instant on this stage!
Ah!
This is what you do.
Wait a second!
Ah!
Subaru Out
Someone just got blown up! Subaru's out!
What the hell are you doing, Subaru-chan?
Who's going to win this?
What's going to happen?
Pay more attention to your surroundings!
Come on now, calm down a bit.
Nenechi?
Ah!
Wait, you drew...
What are you doing?!
Come on, now!
There are draws in this game?
This might take a while.
You sure you don't just all suck?
Let's stop all dropping bombs
when it starts and gathering here.
Yeah, let's not!
No, no, no!
Let's not!
Let's be nice!
Ah! C'mon, be nice!
Nooo!
Subaru wins!
That was over in an instant!
Yeah!
Thank you, thank you!
Subaru finishes second!
Subaru's second!
Yay!
And now, the biggest loser will be decided!
Oh no!
Oh man, this sucks.
I won't lose to you, Nenechi!
I'm not gonna lose to you!
Good luck to the two of you!
Loser's Final!
It's time for the loser's final!
Can Nene's overcome this pressure
with a mind of steel?!
Final Round
Let's see who the true loser is!
Let's go!
Oh god, I'm so nervous.
Oh, we're in opposite corners.
Wow, you're in a corner.
You have to get to each other first.
Okay, calm down.
I'm not gonna blow myself up anymore.
Right.
The bombs look kinda cuter too.
Your bomb has some logo on it too.
Customization: Character and bomb skins and effects can be changed!
Wait, I don't have that...
You don't?
Sorry 'bout that, Captain!
Oh man.
It's not like I need those skins...
They're cute after they explode too!
The color after the explosion changes too!
I don't need them.
Yeah, they turn pink!
That's so cute!
Why—Come on!
My bad, my bad!
Uh, Marine...?
Marine?
I'm not gonna blow myself up anymore.
They're all very good at eating your own words!
Can you hear me out?
What did you just say?
You're just screwing around!
I just...
I just heard Nenechi's explosions were pink,
so I was really curious what they looked like
and took a peek...
You got caught in my honey trap!
That looked like suicide to me.
I just wanted to see what that color looked like!
Yay.
I'm finding a safe spot.
They're about to meet each other!
Save it. You're one loss away from being crowned loser.
Right?
Yeah, she'll just blow herself up anyway!
Don't come over here!
Don't blow yourself up.
I blew myself up!
Captain!
Marine blows herself up again
You suck way too much!
Nene avoids the verbal bombs!
Nene-chan wins!
So I thought the explosion
was already over, so I walked down—
Nene-chan is our winner!
I did it!
Congrats!
I'm the winner!
Thank you, thank you!
What this means is...
Marine will be the one getting verbally bombed!
No!
Please spare me...
Time to drop the verbal bombs
Subaru drops the bomb in
All right then, Subaru, drop the bomb in...
3,
2,
1!
Hey, Marine!
Off-stream, you're always like,
"I can handle anything thrown my way just fine!"
but you gotta stop that!
What are you talking about?
Everyone knows you actually feel really hurt!
U-Ugh!
A-Ah...
Ah...
It actually hurts her a lot!
It doesn't hurt me at all!
Moving on!
It's not hurting!
Next, we have...
Towa!
Here!
Three,
Towa drops the bomb in
two,
one!
Hey, Marine!
Huh?
Stop moving like a boomer!
Ha!
My moves are forever seventeen!
Now that's a burn!
That's a burn.
My movements are really cute!
I-I move the exact same way Nenechi does...
It's true that something about her does feel outdated!
Finish her off!
Here comes Nene-chan!
Three,
Nene drops the bomb in
two,
one!
Hey, Marine!
She's so bratty.
Try and move like me if you can!
Oh!
What a burn!
Who saw that one coming?!
Oh no!
She's in despair mode!
I'm Nenechi!
It's a monster!
A monster!
Ah! Oh no!
Hey, Nenechi!
The bombs were too powerful!
I can't tell if those movements
are supposed to be young.
Captain!
Ah!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
And now,
let's do a team battle in pairs!
Yay!
How do we split into teams?
Yeah, you all will be split into teams,
I wonder too!
but worry not, Marine!
Oh?
Because you will be together
with the first to win, Towa-chan!
Ah!
Towa-sama will protect me!
Can I? I...
I'll do it. For sure.
She does need help.
And Subaru and Nene-chan
will be in the other team.
I knew I could rely on you!
Next up is team battle!
In team battles, you compete in score.
In this mode,
each player starts with six lives,
and their teams will be scored on
how many times they blow the enemy up.
The team that has
the higher score after two rounds wins.
Of course, the losing team will be
showered in verbal bombs!
Be careful not to blow your partner up!
Well, at least our team has no dead weight.
Yeah, we both did well!
Dead weight?
Could you possibly be talking about me?
Aw, they're bullying you.
Are you roasting me again?
Oh no, the roast...
You said "dead weight," didn't you?
No, nothing of that sort.
You get much worse on a daily basis.
Deal with it.
And so, the team battle begins!
Round 1
Okay, so, remember to replenish your lives.
Let's go!
Where should I place the bomb?
Maybe here?
Let the games begin!
Don't rush ahead too much.
Sure.
Where should I—
It's a bit dangerous to place one here...
Oh no, it makes me actually think now, not good.
I get you so much.
Your partner's bombs can blow you up too.
You're right!
I'll put one here...
Ah, nice one.
And one here...
I put one above.
Gotcha.
I'll put one here, then.
Ah, sorry!
Huh? What happened?
Marine's alone! Go get her!
Hold on, don't do it!
Come here!
No, don't!
Ah, Towa-sama is back!
You will be revived as long as you have hearts
I'm back!
Towa-sama!
Save me!
Ahh! No!
This is no good!
This is bad!
They flew away one by one. The score is 2-1!
They'll respawn here, right?
Let's try to get a spawn kill.
Don't you dare!
Stooop!
Oh no!
Both teams are on par with each other.
Both teams are on par with each other!
What a heated battle!
No one wants to get roasted!
Don't give up, girls!
Towa-sama... Protect me, please...
And time is slowly running out!
You're tied right now.
That's bad, Towa-sama...!
Oh no!
Eat this!
The bombs are all over the place.
I'll do the best I can, so...
Whoa!
No, no, no!
Ah, no!
Dammit!
That was so close!
Oh, Nene-chan!
You have only one life left!
That's no good!
What? Only one life?
Don't come any closer!
Are you going to finish her?
I'm outta here.
You won't catch me!
Nenechi?!
Nene out!
Nenechi, are you kidding me?
Nene's done for?
Only Subaru with 4 lives left—
Me and Towa-sama together—
Let's go!
Oh no!
I'm still alive!
There we go!
Nene, worry not, I'm still good to go!
Roll the replay!
With just a few seconds were left on the clock
Marine-san blew up both herself and Towa-san,
which led to a draw!
Unforeseen draw!
I still had lives left, all good!
Did we win?
Wow!
Round 2
It's a draw!
A draw?
A draw!
Okay, let's start from the bottom.
And now, the second round.
Right here!
Nice battle, everyone!
Going good!
Nice battle indeed.
They're backing each other up.
I'll place one here, okay?
Go for it.
Here should be fine.
Yup.
Looks fine.
Close one!
I'll make a way out above.
I put one in the top right.
Ah, sorry!
No way!
Nice!
Way to go!
This is bad!
This leaves Nene-chan and Marine...
I'll wait for the respawn.
Go for it!
Kill them at the spawn!
No spawn kills!
Go, go, go!
Don't even think about it!
Got you!
Oh no, she trapped me...
Towa-sama!
That's cheating!
Oh no, she got me!
Did you see that?
Everyone's gone...
Marine was blown away twice already!
Towa-sama was blown away two times too!
Can you get away?
Crap, Nene's here.
Marine, sorry! I am so useless right now!
Towa is down to one life!
Towa-sama, you okay there?
Got Nenechi, nice!
Go for blue! Go for (Towa) blue!
Yikes.
Hmm?
Put it here!
Oh no! I'm stuck!
This is really bad!
Nice!
Towa-sama, you have only one life left...!
It's fine!
Nene-chan has only two left as well.
This is bad...
Nene-chan, it's fine, calm down!
I'll make a run for it.
We have to blow up Subaru-senpai somehow!
Subaru still has five lives left!
Crap!
She's so good!
No good.
Five lives?!
We just have to blow her up!
Oh no!
Leave it to me—
Nene!
I'm so sorry! I messed up!
It's okay!
Just stay alive, Nene!
Just stay alive!
Got it! I'll run away!
Far, far away.
Nice, that's nice.
I won't allow it!
No! Don't come close! I'm scared!
Oh no, Towa-sama...!
Towa out!
I'm so sorry!
Here we go!
Marine!
Dammit!
Just leave it to me!
Oh no!
This is bad!
Captain Marine giving it her all!
It's okay! Just hold on, Nene!
Nene! Run away!
Dammit...!
Nice, nice!
The winner is...
We did it!
Winners - Subaru & Nene's Team
Team Subaru and Nene!
Hell yeah!
Yay!
How could it be...
That means
that the ones getting bombs dropped on will be
Captain Marine and Towa!
Verbal Bombs for Team Marine and Towa
Ahh!
I'm sorry, Marine!
Time to drop the verbal bombs
Starting with Subaru!
Drop the bomb in...
Subaru drops the bomb in
Hey, Marine!
What do you want?
Going for Captain!
You...!
You always have those dead eyes
during the latter half of Maruyama recording!
That's right!
Get some rest!
Tell her!
Don't burn yourself out halfway through!
I'm not tired at all...
I'm still young...
Then why's your voice trembling?
A piece of cake...
Stop that! You're really hurting her!
It doesn't hurt me one bit...
It's super effective!
Looks like it works, after all.
Moving on, Nene-chan's turn!
Got it!
Here we go!
Drop the bomb in...
Nene drops the bomb in
Hey, Towa!
Huh?
You...!
Show your juniors more love!
I show you maximum love already!
Damn, she's scary.
You messin' with me?!
The pressure...
She's a scary senior.
At the very least, I always send you nice messages!
The pressure...
Don't give me that crap!
It's terrifying...
She just countered back fivefold.
Work on your mind and spirit!
She's tough...
Indeed...
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
I have one last question for you.
Please tell us the member who shined the most,
the Twin-crew for today!
Sure!
The Twin-crew for today was...
Who's it gonna be...?
Oh?
Who?
Captain!
Marine?
Huh?
Me?
Yup!
You blew up so many times,
you were shining like a star!
Oh no, Marine?
Ugh
Agh
A pity prize?
Marine...!
Get a hold of yourself!
Agh
Argh
Ahh
Ah...
The poor thing...
*sparkle*
Anyhow,
Since Captain got selected as a Twin-crew,
we'll give her a star!
You'll be the boss at 100 stars,
Nice.
so keep doing your best!
Yay...
"Yay"!
Yay!
You okay, Captain?
Work hard for the promotion!
Ahoy...
She's done for...
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Challenge From the Boss:
the Maruyama Championship!
Yay!
This season's minigame is...
Puyo Puyo Tetris 2's Endless Fever mode!
At the moment, in first place is Marine
with 57,726 points.
Right.
So, Nene-chan, how confident are you?
I'm gonna get 60,000 points!
Do it, if you can!
This episode...
This is the last episode of the season.
Huh?!
What?!
So if Nene-chan can't change the rankings,
Captain Marine will win this season...
I'm gonna change those rankings!
Hey, Nenechi, you'd better beat her.
You're not gonna get 60,000.
I've got this!
Then let the game begin!
You gotta keep clearing them, Nenecchi.
Yeah, you don't have much time.
It's starting! Let's slap 'em on down.
I've never played this game before.
Gonna be okay?
You'll be fine. Just fine, Nenecchi.
Will you get 60,000 points?
That's a 1-chain.
People who start with 1-chains never end well!
They don't? It's bad?
You can spin them.
Beware of the
Subaru and Ayame Line!
You need to build chains.
Spin this...
Oh, so close.
Yeah, that's pretty good. That's pretty good.
This is a 2-chain.
Nice!
Nice! You got a 2-chain!
But you need to get up to 57,000 points.
Shoot!
It's a long ways off.
Just keep stacking them up!
You just need to get 50,000 points from here.
You can do it!
Speed, speed!
Just come from behind!
This looks pretty good.
Looks pretty good!
Oh, I see.
You have 20 seconds left!
That was fast!
You haven't chained much at all so far.
Your current max chain is 2.
Are you just gonna take that, Nenechi?
Just keep clearing them for now.
10 seconds!
10 seconds left! 10 seconds! 10!
Go! Go!
Don't lose to this loser, Nenechi!
10 seconds!
Who's a loser?
No, I don't wanna lose!
Not to this hag!
2! 1!
I don't wanna lose!
0! It's over!
Your final score is 8,853 points!
Hey, that's pretty high!
Huh? Nenechi, weren't you going to get 60,000?
Yeah, that's right. You were going for 60,000...
*whispering*
Shut up! Quiet, you old hag!
Hey, kid! Get off my lawn!
Nene-san is...
in 8th place!
That's pretty good.
Is that good?
8th place!
It was your first time?
You're right above Lamy-chan.
Ooh!
You beat Lamy!
And you're below Choco-san. Mhm.
Yay!
Unfortunately, that means no new high score.
Right.
How do you feel about the game?
It was super hard.
I'm going to practice hard, so next time...
If there is a next time—
There's no next time!
I'm gonna wreck you so bad!
Just try me!
Well, honestly, 2nd place was 34,255 points,
Final Ranking
so 1st has a lead of over 10,000...
Yeah!
So the winner for this season's minigame,
Puyo Puyo Tetris 2's Endless Fever mode,
is Captain Marine!
Dammit!
I did it!
Congrats!
I'm the best!
That's crazy.
Noel-chan came in 2nd.
That's right.
Frankly, you dominated the competition.
Like, you know, the challengers kept coming,
and they were like,
"It's my first time playing Puyo Puyo!"
You could see the age difference.
It's like, none of you guys ever played it?
Like, I was surprised that none of you's ever played it.
Anyway, like we promised, Marine-chan's the winner,
so we're giving you
a Special Maruyama Championship Trophy!
What?
Seriously?!
Yay!
Put it on your streaming table!
Wow!
I will, thank you!
Look forward to next season's minigame!
Look forward to it!
Momosuzu Nene
Thank you for your patronage!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
After Closing
How did you enjoy this episode
of Game Shop Maruyama?
'ow did 'oo lake eet?
I've asked Subaru to stay back this time.
'ello ebrywran. Aim Ohzra Zoobaroo!
Hello, everyone. I'm Oozora Subaru!
Let's give our viewers some advice with their worries!
You're on fire, Subaru-chan! Nicely done!
I'm not on fire! I'm cold sweating so hard!
Since you're on fire today,
here's our viewer and their worry!
From @SERUTASU3 on Twitter!
@SERUTASU3!
I play basketball for club activities,
but despite practicing more than others,
recently, I haven't improved as much as I'd like.
What do you do when things
don't go the way you planned? Please tell me!
Oh, I see.
So, let's give some advice for this worry!
Okay! So basically!
Imagine you've got a gun pointed at your head
and practice like your life's on the line!
Yeah!
That's a totally awesome idea!
Right? I thought so too.
Then, like,
you can work really hard like that.
Your life's on the line!
Like, actually.
So, anyway...
Yeah!
We've resolved the problem, so...
We're accepting requests for advice from you.
Resolved the problem?!
What?!
Yay!
If your request gets featured, you get this!
This!
A completely ugeek,
personally signed request fulfilled sticker!
"Ugeek."
So please send in your submissions!
Send 'em in!
Yay!
Woohoo!
Well then, everyone. Bye-bye.