A 1st Gen!
Today, on Game Shop Maruyama:
Yeah, I'm a first gen!
Oh! She's senior to y'all, huh?
The OG!
The OG of OGs!
She's the biggest shot here!
Looking good!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
We're open for Season 2!
You girls been well?
Yaaay!
Season 2
Finally Open!
Whoo!
It's been a while, Boss!
Yaaay!
It's been a while!
Long time no see!
Long time no see, girls!
Yup!
How have you girls been?
Y'all had a good break?
It went by in a flash for me.
Yeah, time sure flew by.
Right?
What did you do during the break, Boss?
Me? I've gotten a bit too big,
so I've been hitting the gym.
What?
I just got here from the gym, too.
What kinda workouts
have you been doing?
Well, uh... squats.
The Basic Workout
Squats
Do a squat now!
Yeah, do it!
That's pretty hardcore.
Let's all pop a squat.
Here's how you do it.
You really did it!
They praised my form a lot!
Wow!
They said my form was really good.
Really?
You weren't lying.
Yeah, the Boss was actually serious.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Oh? I sense a customer approaching!
Oh?
Th-This aura!
A Guest Approaches?!
You wearing a straightjacket or something?
She's trembling weirdly.
Here, little one.
Here, here!
What's with you girls?
Here, foxy!
Hey, the heck's wrong with y'all?
What's with the calls?
Here, foxy!
I hear something!
Here, foxy, foxy!
I hear something calling me.
She's already here!
Someone's here!
What's going on?
I hear something!
What's with you girls?
What do I hear? Oh?!
Beep be-beep beep!
You actually appeared!
Huuuh?
Hmm? Oh my.
Did you summon me?
I'm guessing she's your acquaintance, girls?
Yeah! Hello!
Yup!
I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
Welcome, Fubuki-chan!
Thanks for having me!
Our first guest for Season 2
Shirakami Fubuki
Speciality: Fantasizing
MENT
LUCK
is the white-haired, animal-eared otaku fox,
Shirakami Fubuki!
Finishing Moves:
1. I am FOX (Finger snap)
2. Sharing douchechills with fellow otaku!
What sort of concerns lie
underneath her fantasies?
What's the hierarchy between y'all?
A 1st Gen!
Yeah, I'm a first gen!
Oh! She's senior to y'all, huh?
The OG!
The OG of OGs!
She's the biggest shot here!
She is? The Don's finally here!
Shirakami Fubuki (hololive 1st Gen)
The biggest?!
The Don? I s'pose I am!
She's the big Don!
Your MENT is a surprising 5 stars!
What?!
Yup!
That's a pretty big claim.
Well, I'm super tough mentally!
She is, yeah.
Super tough mentally, huh?
Yup!
Even after the last episode of an anime,
I just look forward to what's next.
Uh-huh.
I don't get down in the dumps.
I even buy merch and stuff.
Whoa.
Even if my fave character dies in the anime...
Yup.
Oof. You can take that?
Yikes!
Even if they die,
I just vent and move on. That's how tough I am.
Wow, you're tough all right.
She is.
Yup, I am.
Fubu-chan's the type that gets a kick
outta seeing her faves suffer.
Yikes, that's messed up!
She's a hardcore sadist!
She really IS a sadist!
I get all tingly from it.
I love watching Subaru-chan
getting her butt kicked in games!
❤️
Yikes!
You're scaring me!
She's scary!
Her sadism's leaking!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
All right. Tell us what issue
you'd like us to help resolve, Fubuki-san!
Sure!
I think it'd be great if hololive
gets an anime or a game in the future,
Yeah!
Ooh! That'd be awesome!
but if we get a game of us,
That sounds nice.
I'd need to do my own SSR pose, right?
Whoa!
Ooh!
I see!
I've been fantasizing
'bout what'd be a good pose,
Uh-huh.
but I just can't decide!
I can't decide on an SSR Pose that suits me!
I see.
I'm hoping everyone from Game Shop Maruyama
can help me resolve this issue!
Got it!
And there we have our request!
We've got just the thing!
Fubu-chan's problem is, in short:
She wants her own perfect SSL Card…
It's "R"!
"R," yeah.
She wants her own perfect SSR Card pose!
The game we recommend today is this!
Just Dance 2022!
Yaaay!
A game you can play with up to six people!
Each song comes with
its own unique choreography,
and players have to copy the dance
shown on-screen in tune to the music!
The more accurate you are,
the higher your score!
Furthermore, there are Fever Time and
Pose mechanics that give you bonus points,
so the better your dancing,
the higher your score!
If you dance with passion and strike your pose,
your issue will be solved then and there!
All right, then. Everyone together now!
Let's dance!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
By the way…
Raise your hands if
you've got experience dancing!
Doom and gloom? I didn't ask for this!
The two in the back are sus!
You misunderstand!
You two are lying!
Wait. Hold on.
No, I don't!
These two dance!
They totally do!
Do we have liars among us?
No, I'm not lying.
These two.
Hey! You dance too!
The two of them are learning how to dance!
Yeah! They are!
Yeah, I'm learning.
You're taking dance lessons?
I am an idol, after all,
so I'm learning how to dance.
Honestly, though,
it's wracking my nerves now.
It's doing the reverse
and pressuring you instead.
I'm sweating buckets here.
How about you, Towa-chan?
Do your usual dance steps!
Yeah! Do your usual dance steps!
Yeah! You always do it!
She's always doing it!
The usual one would be this.
Those are moves from a real dancer!
What the heck is that?
This is the only thing I've been practicing!
Yeah!
I can't do that at all.
Amazing!
All right!
Please reveal our episode
for today, Towa-chan!
Got it! Today's episode is:
Maruyama Dance Festival 2022!
Yaaay!
We'll be doing 3 segments in
Maruyama Dance Festival!
The first one is a Solo Dance!
Yaaay!
Nooo!
All of us here will dance to 2 songs!
And, of course,
Boss will be taking part as well!
Oh boy...
Wow!
Let's all dance together!
Yaaay!
The person with the highest score
after we dance to 2 songs is the winner!
Got it!
I see!
Okay!
I won't lose!
Everyone ready? Let's start!
Yaaay!
What's this?
Wait, we're starting already?
It's started!
It's a cat!
Boss, you're a cat, so...
Yeah, I'm good at this one.
Meow. Wait, we're jumping straight in?
Meow!
Oh, shake our hands!
This is one funky song.
What's it called?
It's cute!
It's a cat dance!
Oh, you just keep doing this move, huh?
This is so cute!
Meow!
♪ Tulikitakata ♪
It's this song?!
♪ Tulikitakati ♪
♪ Tulikitaka ♪
What is this song?!
What is this dance?!
This is so cute!
This sure makes you move!
Phew!
Do we stop moving? Oh, we do.
This is a tiring one!
Wow, this is rough.
I can't do all these moves.
This is surprisingly hard.
It's so cute!
There's the big cat!
When do I breathe?!
There's no room to talk!
Agh, we need to hold the pose again!
We need to hold again!
And stop!
Stop!
Whoo!
What's this?! It's a new move!
Towa-chan, you can use your moves!
This is tough!
This is a little...
You can use your dance steps on this!
I don't even remember how!
You can use your moves here!
I hardly have the headspace to!
Use your dance moves, Towa-chan!
My legs are giving in!
My body's hurting too!
Ah!
Phew, okay, it's looping back.
This is the surprised cat pose!
Oh, I know the rest from here!
Lift your legs up!
This is long!
I'm getting tired!
Keep it up, girls!
Boss?!
What're you taking a break for, Boss?!
I'm doing squats!
Boss!
Hey!
You said you were good at this!
Do your best, girls!
No more!
How long does this go on for?!
No clue. It's just too freaking long!
We're not done yet!
It's not over yet?!
There's still more!
This is really tough!
How do you move your head here?
No clue.
Meow.
Huh?
Oh, we need to sit.
That was intense!
That was tough!
I'm ready to call it quits.
What're the results?
Girls! The next song's starting!
Stand up!
Get up!
Wait, no breaks?
Coach! Please, give us a break!
No breaks!
It's one after another?!
The next song's Chiwawa!
I can't!
Do we really get no breaks?
We don't get any breaks.
We're walking the dog!
Coach... Coach, what the heck
are these moves?!
Walk it!
What the heck's this, Coach?!
We're walking the chihuahua in this!
Walk the chihuahua!
Is this a chihuahua's workout?
It's walk time!
This is insane!
They're going "Bow, wow!"
They're going "Bow, wow!" that's cute.
They are, yeah.
We went from cat to dog!
What the heck's this move?! I can't tell!
This is tough!
What'd she say?
She's saying, "Stepped on the dog!"
That's plenty messed up!
Stepped on the dog!
She stepped on the dog, not the cat!
These dance moves are tough!
I know, right?
Yeah, they are!
This is hard!
It's really hard!
This song's making us work up a sweat!
Hold on! Wait a minute!
This is brutal!
Time out!
Whoa!
Huh?
This is intense!
Hold on, wait, stop!
Stop, stop! Give us a break!
This is insane!
I can't breathe!
Yikes!
What is this move?!
Please stop!
What the heck is this?!
This is insane!
This move's a nightmare!
This is torture...
This move is torture!
My knees are breaking!
This is madness!
This is really bad for my knees!
This is brutal!
No more!
Please stop!
Stay strong!
I'm so tired...
I can't keep up!
This is rough!
The dancer's amazing!
This is painful!
Time out!
There's no end to this!
This is pain.
Did someone nail a Superstar?
The screen just lit up hard!
You're right! Whoa!
It's over!
Woo-hoo!
Thank god, it's over...
It's over!
I'm so tired...
Holy...
That was insane.
That was brutal!
Hey, Boss!
You didn't even dance near the end!
A-Anyways...
How are you so dead?!
Only two of us survived!
What the heck?!
Anyway, the person with
the highest score in the 1st Step is...
Subaru-san!
That was some epic dancing!
Yay, yay, yay!
Whoo!
The song was really fast
Yeah!
so my hands and feet had to move pretty fast too.
Yeah, it was so fast.
Wow, those were some
really nuanced dance moves.
It was so hard!
But there were a lot of parts that repeated,
so it's a lot of fun once you learn those.
Once...? So you've already
remembered everything?
There's a certain pattern to it,
like how this part goes after this.
What?
Oh, you're right!
It was really hard, but a lot of fun!
Right?
Yeah!
The dog-walking was cute.
Fubuki SSR Pose Check
Oh, that was really cute!
What, the very beginning?
You look great doing that!
What about this part?
Remember this pose?
Oh, right!
Oh yeah!
That was really cute.
That was so cute!
It fits you really well.
This was so cute.
Yeah.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
And now part two of the show begins,
where we're now dancing in pairs!
Let's go!
Pair dances!
Let's ask Fubuki-chan who
she wants to pair up with!
Yes?
Oh!
I see!
We'll hear you out, at the very least.
What?!
You wouldn't abandon me, would you?
Wait, I can...
Fubuki-senpai...
Who should I pick?
Don't abandon me...
State each of your cases!
Yeah, I'll hear you out!
Tell her why she should pick you!
I'll hear you out!
Here!
Okay, Subaru.
Fubuki-senpai...
What is it?
Compared to those girls,
Marine and Towa,
Huh?
I've known you for a lot longer.
Oh.
That's true.
You little—
Ahh!
That's true, though...
Fubu-chan! You might've known her for longer,
but you've seen me the most, right?
Yeah.
True.
We're on that radio show together!
Out of the way! I started calling you
"Fubu-chan" the other day, didn't I?
"The other day"?
Yeah.
Ah!
We've been getting so close!
Oh, she's getting closer.
True.
Stop acting all lovey-dovey!
Subaru just calls her "Fubuki-senpai"!
Can I start calling you "Fubu-chan"?
Let's just, let's just...
Oh, uh, okay!
She's being such a brat!
Can I call you Fubu-chan?!
Hey, ow!
Please stop fighting over me!
Oh, wow.
She's been dying to try that line out.
I'll be going with...
Subaru!
Hell yeah!
What?!
Fubu-chan!
She picked the winning choice!
I knew it!
You've been blinded by your desire for victory!
She's going for the win!
Of course she'd rather pick
someone who can dance!
That's right!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Here's the song I'll be
dancing with Subaru-chan!
Only...
...You!
Oh, come on!
Yay!
C'mon, pick something harder!
That's so easy!
We came to win!
That's right!
They're chickening out!
Hey...
It's starting already!
Wow, they're already starting.
Excuse us!
What are they doing?
♪ Only... you! ♪
Now they're holding hands.
Fubuki-senpai!
Now they're spinning!
That's backwards, Fubuki-san!
Wait, is that backwards?
Oh no!
Is that backwards?
That's backwards!
Oh no!
That's not allowed!
Huh, what?
Isn't this part backwards?
Who's doing which part here?
We're backwards!
Fubuki-senpai!
They're switching places?!
They're swapped around.
Fubuki-senpai!
Wait, so who's the alien here?
Is Subaru-senpai the alien?
Oh, spin! Spin!
Who's the alien?
Oh, Subaru's the alien.
Wait, we switched places!
Subaru's the alien, then.
Alien Subaru.
I'm an alien.
I feel like they're not
gonna score very well now.
I think we can win this!
Right?
There doesn't seem to be
a lot of scoring moves.
It's actually harder because it's slow!
Fubuki-senpai!
Fubuki-senpai...
Look at them spin!
♪ You... ♪
This way!
They need to get the
rhythm down since it's so slow!
It's so relaxed.
Ah, we swapped places!
We're backwards!
Why do we keep swapping?
Why do you keep
switching places during those?
Fubuki-senpai!
My fingers are gone!
Fubuki-senpai...
My fingers!
Fubuki-senpai!
What are they doing?
No!
We've already won this.
Oh, shut up.
They're a complete mess!
And a spin!
Look, Towa-sama, they're a mess!
Oh, that's the wrong way!
They're switching places way too much.
Yeah!
We just got a "Yeah!" though.
They're rubbing butts now.
Oh, okay?
They're rubbing against each other now!
What's going on?!
What's happening?
What now?!
They're rubbing butts.
They won't stop rubbing butts.
What's happening?
And now a spin...
Ah...
And they swap places again.
They're expressing their love.
This way!
A spin here...
Nice.
I have to come this far?
And now... yeah! Third time's the charm!
Oh, nice!
Let's go!
They're getting better.
They're starting to get the dance now.
They're getting it now.
Never mind.
They're all tangled up.
Fubuki...
Fubuki-senpai...
Please grab my hands.
Please grab my hands...
Subaru-senpai's arms look—
Fubuki-senpai!
What are they doing?
Hey, something is going on, on that screen!
What is this?!
Hang on!
This way!
Whoo!
Who knew this was a thing?
What the heck is this?
Interesting.
What is that?!
They're kneeling down!
They're kneeling now!
Kiss, kiss, kiss!
It's this way!
We're backwards again!
Fubuki—
You're all over the place!
Why do you keep switching places?
Why?
Now they stand up...
Fubuki-senpai!
That's it, nail the ending!
Now hug!
Ah, Fubuki-senpai!
How romantic!
Anything is acceptable if it's cute.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Next up, we have the Marine & Towa team!
We'll be bringing out the passion for this one!
Exactly!
What song did you guys pick?
EZ DO DANCE!
Dance, dance, dance, dance...
Dance, dance, dance...
EZ DO DANCE, yeah! What a classic.
The reverb...
Let's start!
EZ DO DANCE... Good luck!
Whoo! Let's go!
Those are intense moves!
Damn.
Good! Very good!
It goes so hard!
Great moves!
You're doing fantastic, Captain!
You can do it!
What is this?!
Marvelous, Towa-chan!
Towa!
Towa's so damn good!
Towa-chan's absolutely great!
She's killing it!
Good! Great! Perfect! Marvelous!
Towa! You go, girl!
Oh crap!
You're amazing, Towa!
This is frickin' hard!
They're doing really well!
Passion! Passion! Add more passion!
Passion! Passion!
They can do it! Passion! Passion!
Yes! Keep it up!
You two are doing pretty well, somehow!
Oh man...
Yeah!
They're getting it!
I... I can't...!
Great!
Towa-sama, I'm sorry!
You're doing fine!
I might just die here!
Hah! We've only just started!
Marine's arms!
Don't die on us.
Do your best!
Hang in there!
Don't stop!
Go! You can do it!
Aaahn...
Whoa, it's gotten lew―
It's the Marine pose!
Excellent!
Those are the Marine moves!
Marine-chan!
It's the usual Marine pose!
It's the Marine pose!
That's so Marine!
In her element!
It's Captain's Lucky Time!
Lucky Time...
Lucky Time!
It's her Lucky Time!
This is unfair!
Fantastic! Towa, let's go!
Move! Towa!
Over there?!
Gotta move here...!
Keep it up, Towa!
Three more seconds!
Ma-ri-ne!
Marine!
Marine... Captain Marine!
Marine's really lucky here!
This must be fate!
No fair, Captain!
This is her fate.
Whoo! Let's go! Lucky Time is over!
I'm tired!
Keep going!
I'm dying!
Agh!
Now move that body!
Save me!
I'm dying!
Slap it, Marine!
The chorus is coming!
Psych! Not yet!
Fight on!
Please end this!
It's like watching a marathon.
Chorus!
Chorus now!
The chorus might be the easiest part.
What...?
Seems like it!
Yeah!
♪ EZ DO DANCE! EZ DO DANCE! ♪
Help me!
Not whoo, not whoo.
Doing great!
I'm not gonna whoo! I'm not gonna...
Whoo!
Whoo! Aagh...
Oh man...
I'm so tired!
Please end me.
Push yourself!
I'm so done...
You're doing great!
It's coming!
Marine! Hold out until it comes!
That easy one...
Lucky Time's starting again!
Lucky Time might be close.
Wait...!
Okay, it isn't.
It ain't time yet.
Keep those feet moving!
It's unfair, I say!
Go for it!
It's time! It's time! Let's go!
It's here!
Why does she get the easy moves!
Marine Time!
It's Marine Time!
Marine Fever Time has started!
Time to take it easy.
I want to do that!
Time for her to go full Marine.
Look at that bright and beaming smile!
So unfair...
Keep going, Marine!
Spectacular.
Towa-chan nailed
Sam's moves perfectly!
What the―! How do I do this?!
Why do I have to do these moves?!
You practiced this, didn't you?
No, I didn't!
Towa's doing Sam's moves here, right?
Sam's choreo is serious stuff!
You're doing great, Towa-chan!
Keep going!
I'm hearing something else here too.
Let's go, chorus time!
It's the chorus!
Okay, guys! Time to ramp it up!
My arms!
Last spurt!
We're at the climax now!
My arms are...!
Yeah!
Keep it up!
♪ EZ DO DANCE! ♪
Woo-hoo!
Whoo!
You've got this!
Let's go, Marine!
I think I'm gonna pass out.
Don't give up! Push to the end!
Whoo!
We're like an aerobics class!
Yeah.
Fight!
Don't make me laugh, please!
Go on! We're at the last stretch!
I don't have much breath left in me.
I can't... talk anymore!
Pose! Pose! The ending pose!
Yaaaaay!
Whoa! So cool!
Now that was inspiring.
Absolutely awe-inspiring.
You guys were great!
That was really rough.
I'm touched by your performance!
I can't talk anymore!
All the viewers are probably tearing up in joy.
The ones with the higher score for Step 2
are Marine-san and Towa-san!
What a passionate performance!
I knew it!
Yeeeah!
Amazing!
We did it!
MarineTowa team wins!
Marine-chan!
Yaaay!
"Power of love," my ass!
Damn it!
Yeah, baby!
We lost!
Damn!
Do that pose again!
Those moves during Marine Time...
Next round...
Marine Time...
I was doing this the whole time!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Finally! In order to pull an SSR-worthy pose,
we'll all be dancing together!
Yeah!
Woohoo! Dance!
In order to resolve Fubu-chan's problem,
we're going to make use of what we learned today
Oh!
and dance it up to
discover her SSR pose together!
Woohoo!
The song will be Da Pump's U.S.A.!
Whoa! This is my first time dancing it!
Whoa, nice!
Oooh!
I pick yellow!
Red for me!
I'm picking pink!
I pick blue!
Let's go!
Okay!
Okay! Our colors match us perfectly!
Right?
Yeah!
Nice!
I-It's starting!
Looking good!
Oh, I have to be behind you.
Oh, sorry!
Oh, oops!
You guys are doing great!
Your formation is on point!
♪ U! S! A! ♪
Hey, this is the part where we go one by one!
One by one!
Woo!
♪ U! S! A! ♪
♪ ...S! A! ♪
One by one!
Dang, this is hard!
Next up is Subaru! Go, Subaru, go!
Is Marine next?
♪ U! S! A! ♪
♪ S! A! ♪
Oh, it is me!
It is! I got it right!
Do your best, Marine!
Whoo! Towa-sama!
♪ U! S! A! ♪
It's nice that each of you
get to show off here.
Like this?
What even is this?
Dang, this part's hard.
Wow, your formation is
changing left and right.
Wow!
Right?
It's time for the chorus!
There it is!
What is this?
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
♪ America! ♪
♪ Ame— ♪
Looking good! You guys tired yet?
Very!
They are tired!
This is really intense!
Looking good!
America's coming up!
This way?
♪ America! ♪
Nice! Time to relocate!
This again?
Your formation's turning out great.
Dang!
And—Oh! They're doing slow-mo, neat!
Oh, it's this way?
What is this?
You guys were great!
That was wild!
Okay, so you wanted to figure out
which pose would be perfect for your SSR card...
Oh!
Yeah!
I made my pick!
Oh! What is it?
Oh, she already decided!
Which part did she pick it from?
I've made my decision!
What kind of pose is it?
*drumroll*
Ta-dah!
There it is!
SSR Pose Set!
Huh?!
She picked it!
I thought this was pretty cool.
The U.S.A. bit?
And with that, Fubuki-san's SSR pose
has been determined!
When the day comes,
be sure to use this pose, Fubuki-san!
Can I have you all do it, too?
Like where it makes one pic if you get all four.
That looks really good!
Cards?
Like this?
Like everyone's doing a dab.
If you line up like that—
*dab*
Quadruple SSR Pose💛
Oh, when Marine raises her arms up like that—
Oh, this looks great!
I have one last question for you.
Please tell us the member who shined
the most, the Twin-crew for today!
Okay!
Today's Twin-crew title goes to...
*drumroll*
the one who gave it her all,
showing us all her slick moves,
Towa-sama!
Ah! It's Towa-sama!
Congratulations!
Yay!
What about me, Fubuki-senpai?!
You two had a chummy dance together, too...
Right? Haha, she's doing the wotagei dance.
Sorry!
You're so hyped up!
I'm sorry, Subaru!
Huh? Why didn't you—
Dang it!
But Towa-sama was really mesmerizing!
Yaaay!
You were dazzling out there!
Damn it!
You looked really cool!
You were amazing.
Since Towa got selected as a Twin-crew,
we'll give her a star!
Give it your best to
become the number one star!
Yay!
Congratulations!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Challenge From the Boss:
the Maruyama Championship Season 2!
Yay!
At this point, we'll have our customers
try their hand at a minigame.
Okay!
The one who finishes the season
on top will receive a trophy!
In Season 1's Puyo Puyo Tetris 2
Endless Fever mode,
Marine ended up winning the trophy.
That's right!
It's lonely at the top.
She completely dominated.
The undefeated.
This episode marks the start of Season 2.
This season's game is
SEGA AGES Sonic the Hedgehog.
Yay!
Players will compete in
Green Hill Zone Act 1's time attack mode.
Yay!
By the way, our show staff's
best time is 35 seconds.
Is 35 seconds good?
Is that fast or slow?
You'll have to find out yourselves!
Is that fast?
No idea if that's impressive.
Right?
So, Fubuki-chan, are you good
at minigames like this?
Well, I am part of GAMERS,
unlike the other three!
GAMERS, I see.
So, you know...
That's true!
So, who wants to go first?
Me!
Oh? Subaru?
Oh! Subaru!
The Subaru Line.
I've gotta lay down the
Subaru Line, you know.
You sure?
First and foremost, huh?
I see, the Subaru-chan line.
You sure you've got this?
Way to go! We need that Subaru Line.
Gotta first lay the Subaru Line.
Everything's relative to the Subaru Line.
Way to go!
Here I go!
Go for it!
Three! Two! One! Go!
Go get 'em!
Let's go, Sonic!
Start!
How's this work? Let's go!
Looking good!
And off she goes! Not bad!
Good so far!
You've got it! You've got it!
Oh crap, oh crap!
There are lots of obstacles!
And jump...
Nice! Doing good!
And run...
Oh, crap! Should I run?
Keep running!
I would imagine so!
Yes, you should run. Oh, nice!
That's right! Sonic's gotta go fast!
Is that how it works?
It's all about speed!
Sonic's about sp—Oh no!
Augh!
This part's hard!
But you're still alive!
You need those coins for safety!
That's right! The rings!
Coins?
Those rings.
Make sure you get the rings!
If you have no coins when you hit an enemy...
Rings?
Wah!
Boing!
What now?
Whoa!
Close call!
Nearly fell there.
I'm sweating!
My eyes can't keep up!
Come on, you can do it! Make that loop!
She can't get up the hill!
How do I do this?
She's stuck!
I can't get up!
You need momentum!
Build some momentum and...
The slope! Use the slope!
...still can't make it!
I can't get up this thing!
A bit more, use the slope... Nice!
Just a little more!
She's got it this time! Build momentum...
Keep going, keep going!
Go!
Nice!
I get it—
Just needed a running start.
Whoa, whoa!
Oh, wow!
What a jump!
Oh crap, oh crap!
Looking good!
Doing good! Ah!
Oh, no! Not good!
Augh!
She lost them all!
This is tough!
Nice!
Oh, nice!
Oh, that's the goal.
Hey, 52 seconds!
Oh! 52 seconds!
Well, well.
Hey, that's not bad, is it?
That's pretty good!
So that's the Subaru Line.
I think I might be the winner.
Any slower, and you're just
a walking embarrassment.
Is that how it is?
Don't say that.
Geez, that's harsh!
You might be the next embarrassment yourself!
Have we seen the bottom route before?
Wait, why is Captain...
She's doing better. This is good!
Am I?
So fast!
Ooh! Which means...?
This'll be a good time.
And we have Captain Marine
with 41.25 seconds!
Dang!
Well, gosh.
She's faster than I expected!
Losing to Subaru-chan is embarrassing!
It's looking like she's gonna...
Don't be embarrassed! Come join me!
Unfortunately...
Ahh!
Towa Line! Towa Line!
And there we have it!
Towa-chan with 1 minute, 3 seconds!
Oh my, could it be?
Seriously?
Finally, GAMERS' Fubuki.
Man, I'm getting nervous now!
Next up, Challenger Fubuki.
She's representing GAMERS, after all.
I'm in it to win it!
Are you, now?
Victory will be mine!
Here I go!
You've seen everyone else's
perfomance by now.
Yeah! Should be a piece of cake!
I think she's got this.
Start!
Go!
Yahh!
Start!
She makes sure to get the coins!
Doing well so far.
Whoa, what?
What's that?!
Wait, what's that?!
A hidden item?!
The heck?!
What did you get?
She's all sparkly!
It's all...
That's not fair!
Hey, that's not fair!
What's happening?!
What is that?
She's in invincibility mode!
Yay! I've got invincibility!
You're invincible!
No fair, no fair!
No fair!
I didn't get that!
Oh, I fell!
She's invincible!
Oh crap!
That part's hard!
Oh! You survived!
Spikes don't hurt her!
Dang, this invincibility lasts forever!
Yay!
You can stand on spikes!
I'm invincible!
This is big! Spikes don't hurt her!
Oh, wait, what?!
Can she?
I got stuck for some reason!
That's what I like to see!
Stuck here again!
Crap! Why did I get stuck?
This part's hard!
It's always this part!
It was so random!
Everyone gets stuck here.
Why?!
Nice!
Okay, keep going!
Ahh!
You bonked there!
She still has the effect!
Not good, not good!
Get stuck!
Ahh!
Wait, augh!
Don't jump!
Hang on!
Wait!
Ahh!
Can she do it?
Keep going!
You're almost there!
This is not going well!
And jump!
Wait!
My powerup ran out!
Oh no!
Come on! One minute!
Oh crap!
Oh no!
Go, go, go!
Don't do it, Fubu-chan!
Augh!
That was pretty slow!
Which makes Fubuki's time
49.38 seconds!
Ack!
Meaning the best time of the four
Oh?
goes to Captain Marine!
Seriously?!
Dang it!
Shucks, I win again?
I lost!
On top again in Season 2, huh?
You were supposed to save us, GAMERS!
Augh! I lost!
Cheer up, Towa. Being a
walking embarrassment ain't all bad.
Shaddup! I swear!
A walking embarrassment.
Sonic was lots of fun!
Yeah, it's a cool game.
It was so fun! Can... Can we play the next level?
The next level? You'll have to play that at home!
Aw, we can't?
It's pretty addicting.
I will!
The new season's started,
and more exciting battles await!
Look forward to it!
Thanks for stopping by!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
After Closing
How did you enjoy Game Shop Maruyama?
I've asked Towa to stay back this time.
Let's give our viewers
some advice with their worries!
It's been a while.
Do you remember the ropes?
Surely.
Okay, let's start!
This one is from @moyuruinu.
Whenever a show, like a radio program,
accepts letters,
I want to submit something
that'll get selected
whenever my favorite segments
or guests are being featured.
But it's always on those occasions
when I never have any worries or anecdotes to share.
Do you have any ideas
how I could deal with this?
Great question.
Quelle chance!
You have been le selected!
Where did that sound come from?
Do you mean to say that they
passed the selection process this time?
Le indeed.
And with that, le worry of yours
shall continue to remain your worry for le ages.
So basically, they may be happy
that they got selected now,
but it's possible they
may never get selected again, huh?
Le indeed!
Exactly, huh?
Wasn't there a time where
you spoke while walking around?
Walking?
There was, wasn't there?
Yeah, you did it just like that!
Ah, yes.
You dodged a question like that before, no?
Yeah! Your moves were really nice!
Absolutely lovely.
Le worry of yours shall continue
to remain le worry,
and there may be someone who will le select it!
Que c’est beau!
We're accepting requests
for advice from you.
If your request gets featured,
you get this!
A completely unique,
personally-signed request fulfilled sticker!
So, please send in your submissions!
We look forward to them!