I won tickets for a space tour!
No way that's not a scam.
Let's just give it a shot, okay?
It was for weal!
Look, you can see the planets out there.
Hey, Okayu's out there!
She's seeing things awready...
That girl's brain needs dissecting.
I brought us something to play around with.
Put this near a window, and...
L-Like that music video!
Let me have a go...
I haven't sang anything yet, so no.
Gah!
Gaa!
Oh no! The engines!
Owwie...
Lucky us! We crashed into the office!
But, uh, something's off.
Welcome back, ye all.
Fubuki-senpai?!
She's aged like fine wine.
Our spaceship must've warped into
a different point in time!
You're right!
Fubuki-chan even has four ears now!
I always have.
By the way, we have some
futuristic tech here.
Thanks, Fubu-chan!
This is a big welp!
It's wike we're flying!
We can make it back to our office!
Look, we can see the exit now!
I forgot to say this was
hololive Egypt HQ.
Hope they made it back okay.
Non-stop across the Milky Way!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!