Absent
I can't! I can't! I CAN'T!
You can do it if you try!
This is so cute!
Yummy!
Hot!
Spicy!
Sweet!
Yummy!
Starring:
Nekomata Okayu
Nakiri Ayame
Uruha Rushia
This program is brought to you
by me, Nekomata Okayu...
...Nakiri Ayame, and...
...Uruha Rushia!
Who's the word association queen?
It's the Imagination Queen Contest!
Yay!
Our usual host A-chan
isn't here with us today,
so I'm taking over instead.
This almost never happens, huh?
I know, right?
Mio-chan usually takes over
the hosting duties for us...
Right?
I know, right?
I'm super nervous about this.
Are you feeling okay? Can you do this?
I can't! I can't! I CAN'T!
You can do it if you try!
I can't...
This is so cute!
Don't worry, you've got this!
You can do this!
Oh, I just got a cue card or something.
Whoever comes up with
the most related words
to the prompt they're given within
30 seconds will be declared the winner.
I see...
Oh!
Related words?
For example, say your prompt is an apple.
Prompt: Apple
Red, round, healthy.
Bleeding from your gums. Wait, what?
What, because it's red?
What?!
This cue card's messed up!
The winner is bestowed the
title of Imagination Queen.
Ayame-senpai got the
title last time too!
The winner of the Imagination Queen title
will be bestowed with a lavish extra prize!
I'm so excited for this!
What would you two want, by the way?
A TV.
A TV?!
How many inches?
About 70!
Absolute unit.
That's huge!
What about you, Rushia-chan?
What I want?
Love.
Love?!
Let's start off with Ayame-chan!
Wow, I can start it off?
Nakiri Ayame's Imagination
Here's your prompt!
Prompt: Body pillow
Who picked this photo?!
Why this photo?
What the...
This is a pretty unique photo...
You have 30 seconds to
come up with related words!
30 seconds?!
30 seconds? I'll do my best!
Ready?
Yeah!
Three!
Two!
One!
Go ahead!
Uh, big!
Fluffy!
Comfortable!
Uh...
Soft!
Good for sleeping!
I need one more!
Bleeding from your gums.
Bleeding from your gums!
Uh, uh...
Fix neck pain!
Fin
Time's up!
You came up with so many!
The first three were easy
but it got tough after that.
By the way, what was
"fix neck pain" all about?
Well, I thought it might support your neck,
and it's really soft so it'd fix your neck pain.
I see.
Yeah!
You sounded really cute saying,
"Fix neck pain!" though.
What, why?!
The Imagination Queen Deliberation Committee
will announce your results now.
You have...
six points in total!
Oh, nice!
So many!
So they all passed?
They all passed.
Nice, thank you so much!
So now we have to
come up with at least seven?
Yeah, you need more than
seven answers to beat Ayame-chan.
That'll be hard...
Going for at least seven points
Uruha Rushia's Imagination
Let's go!
All right.
Go!
Here's your prompt!
Prompt: Curry
Okay!
That looks good.
Okay, okay, okay!
That curry rice looks so good.
Can you do this?
Okay.
I can!
Let's go!
Three!
Two!
One!
Go ahead!
Yummy!
Hot!
Spicy!
Sweet!
Yummy!
She just said "yummy" again.
Uh... Super delish!
She's mentally regressing!
Super delish?
Uh... cook it!
Stew it!
Cut vegetables!
Cooking!
10 seconds left.
Okay.
Cooking... pot!
Five seconds!
Uh...
Yummy.
Spicy.
Fin
I just heard some things again.
Just so you know...
Rushia said "yummy"
four times, apparently.
* Each word is only counted once
She also said "spicy" twice.
She's repeating everything!
And Rushia-chan receives...
nine points!
What?!
Wow!
That's amazing!
I got nine?
That means you're in first for now.
Yeah, she's in first now.
Let's see if Okayu takes it up another level.
hololive NEWS
We interrupt this program
to inform you of an anchor change.
Replacing Nekomata Okayu
from hololive GAMERS
is hololive 2nd Gen's Nakiri Ayame.
Nakiri Ayame-san?
Here!
Breaking: Nakiri Ayame takes over host position
Ayame-chan's taking over?
I, Nakiri Ayame, will be your
new host for this program.
Ah, #$%(&@#(, I'll do my best!
Thank you for coming out.
I'm counting on you!
10 or more points for the win!
Nekomata Okayu's Imagination
We'll now announce Okayu's prompt!
Here it is!
Prompt: Dog
Dog!
Won't this be pretty difficult?
Yeah, it will be!
Let's get started!
Imagination Start!
Um...
Cute ears.
Uh, long tongue.
Sharp teeth.
Drinks lots of water.
Eats dog food.
Cute eyes.
Furry.
Wags tail.
So many...
Has lots of fur.
Wet nose.
Pretty eyes.
Has toenails.
Has paws.
Likes walks.
Wears a collar.
Fin
Time's up!
That was a lot!
How was that?
You had so many.
I think that was a lot.
I came up with a bunch!
Yeah, you had so many.
Nekomata-san receives...
*15 after a recount
16 points!
Oh wow!
Wow!
That's so many!
Oh wow!
So apparently you had 16 in total
and they all passed!
Really?
Awesome!
Wow.
Wow!
Results
The one who truly dazzled as an
Imagination Queen today was...
🥁🥁🥁
Nekomata Okayu-san!
Imagination Queen
Nekomata Okayu
Congrats!
Congratulations!
There's a prize you get for winning.
What do you think it is?
Oh, right.
The prize for the Imagination Queen
this time is...
a Planetarium!
That's so romantic!
Yay!
That sounds so nice!
I'm so happy!
You better make sure I get it.
If you enjoyed this video,
please subscribe to hololive's official
YouTube channel and smash that like button.
And also!
Please do!
Please check out Okayu's channel,
Rushia-chan's channel,
and my channel as well!
Please!
Please check them!
Starring:
Nekomata Okayu
Nakiri Ayame
Uruha Rushia
This program is brought to you
by me, Nekomata Okayu...
...Nakiri Ayame, and...
...Uruha Rushia!
See you again!