Huh?
Wasn't I about to do something?
What... was it?
I swear there was something!
I was just thinking about it!
How could I forget?!
Seriously, what was it?
Pancakes, coming right up!
What was I even doing here, anyway?
No! The pancake!
M-Mikochi?
I ate some taiyaki, drank some tea...
Nice catch!
Just your run-of-the-mill stuff, eh?
Ugh, I can't stop thinking about it.
Uber Tight! Can only be opened by the elite!
Mikochi, help.
I'm too distracted to do anything!
When this happens...
Gah!
Baseball outta nowhere!
Force yourself to remember someway!
Wormhole Generator
N...
Nay, I can't do it.
I feel lost, astray in my galaxy brain.
O God, please,
pray gib me strength!
Man, I might never remember,
even when I'm old and gray.
With my elite powers,
I thought nothing was impossible,
but maybe I was wrong.
No, wait.
I'll remember for sure someday!
After all, I am so elite,
I bring people to their knees!
I should get ready to stream...
Ah!
Lava bucket in the kitchen!
Gas spill on the floor!
Fireworks and bombs right there!
Didn't lock my apartment!
Forgot to turn the TV and AC off!
Left my smart card in the charging machine!
And!
I was supposed to meet Sora-chan now!
Sora-chan!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!
Been a while since the office last blew up, huh?