Are we doing it?
Let's do it!
Ah! What is this?!
Owie!
Will they use that move on this big group?
It's here!
Oichi is also cute.
Let's unify the country!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Gyaru or not, it's gotta be tea.
You got that right.
Sodas? Please no.
She's not even!
Oh yeah,
What is it?
July 15th is NES day!
Oh.
This is related to that... Were you guys
born before the NES?
I wasn't!
Denial
Denial (Sus)
What's an en-ee-ess?
Press X to doubt.
I don't knyow what that is.
You don't knyow?
Isn't that your generation?
I know what the SNES is.
Ah, so you were born then.
To➚u-chan used to play.
Oh? You did, Towa-chan?
To➘u-chan (dad) used to.
Ah, your dad, huh.
Not me, not me.
Sorry,
I thought you were lying about your age too.
Nooo!
Don't lump me in with her!
I thought she sounded old.
Well, enough teasing.
We already have a customer!
Coming in!
Welcome!
It's Ayame-dono!
Today's guest:
Nakiri Ayame
Good afternoon!
My genmate!
That's right!
2nd Gen gang!
It's the 2nd Gen!
Yeah!
Today's guest is Nakiri Ayame, who's currently
addicted to collecting cute gaming gear.
Nakiri Ayame
Hobby: Collecting cute gaming gear
What are your most attractive features?
Appearance: Horns, fang
Personality: Free-spirited
MENT
LUCK
She's got nimble fingers and excellent luck.
She seems good at games.
Why did you give yourself 4 stars on DEX?
I'm actually pretty good at sewing.
How girly!
Stop showing off how girly you are!
You also put 4 stars on your luck.
That's pretty high.
Right?
I had a Minecraft stream a long time ago.
Mhmm.
It was an endurance stream until
I fished up an enchanted book,
and I ended up fishing it up on the first catch.
That's amazing!
The first one?!
She's got it.
That's how much luck I have.
She's got it all.
And it seems that she has a problem
she wants to fix, so please tell us!
You know how it's been pretty hot lately?
It has!
Because of that, I haven't been able to sleep well.
Not sleeping well!
I want to get heated by playing an intense game
so that I can sleep soundly.
And there we have our request!
Thank you!
We have the perfect game for you, Ayame-chan!
Oh? What is it?
The game we recommend today is...
Samurai Warriors 5!
Yaaay!
Our enemy...
is in the Honnoji!
Samurai Warriors 5 is the latest game in
the largely popular Samurai Warriors series,
which will celebrate its 17th anniversary this year.
The biggest selling point of Samurai Warriors is...
that you can become a samurai warrior
and beat down large numbers of enemies
in an exhilarating hack-and-slash battle.
Moreover, SW5 features flash arts, a new battle mechanic.
You can switch out your moveset
to match the battlefield or your playstyle.
Moreover,
you get to experience Oda Nobunaga
and Akechi Mitsuhide's story first-hand.
The turbulent era from Nobunaga's adolescence
to the Honnoji incident
is depicted in all of its glory.
You can try the game out in this store,
so would you like to play?
I want to play it!
Play Samurai Warriors 5
to participate in the Sengoku rivalries, and...
One, two...
Let's unify the country!
Yaaay!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Have you played any of the games before, Ayame-chan?
No, I haven't.
Ooh! It's your first time.
Yeah.
So, are you as aggressive as your name implies?
Does my name affect how aggressive I am?
I'd say I'm gentle at heart.
You're gentle at heart.
She's got some deadly items in her backside, though.
Yeah!
Deadly items
She fits this episode so well.
Right?
By the way, is there anyone in here
who's played Samurai Warriors before?
I have!
Oh!
Subaru!
Subaru: Has played
the Samurai Warriors series before.
Won't she get another star today, then?
Will I really get another one?
I won't let you!
Me neither!
As the tutorial,
we'll play the "Imagawa Raid" chapter.
I'm thinking Ayame and I play the first one.
Let's play together!
There are a ton of characters.
Can you choose whoever you like?
I know who Oda Nobunaga is,
but I didn't know he was this hot.
Mitsuhide's seriously good-looking.
Whoa! He is.
WAIT A SEC!
HE'S SO CUUUTE!
Oh no! He struck a chord with her!
HE'S TOTALLY MY TYPE!
Crushing on Ieyasu
He's really good-looking, after all.
Ayame-senpai, let's use him!
Marine-san had a request,
but Ayame-san went with Akechi Mitsuhide.
Towa-san went with Oichi.
Let's save Tokugawa Ieyasu for Marine.
Oh?
It started!
Nice!
The screen's actually split!
We can see both your perspectives.
Go! Go! Go! Go!
I'm gonna start!
Mow them all down!
Ah! It's Ieyasu!
Ieyasu's here!
Ieyasu appeared!
Wait, is this...
Ah. What? Uh...
That's...
Do you need help?
It's square to attack.
Square?
You can charge forward with triangle, too.
Doin' good.
Oh, we got a mission.
Mission!
"Eliminate the enemy soldiers"
Let's do it.
Kill all the enemies!
Ayame-chan, let's do this!
You can use your arts by holding R1
and pressing the face buttons.
Whoa!
This...
Oichi's throwing some talismans or something.
Right?
That was so cool.
Oh, what? That was super cool.
We got to use the art.
Amazing.
He's quite cool.
I'm going on ahead!
Go! Go!
R1... this one.
What's this move?
Whoa, look!
Cuuute!
That was cool!
Amazing.
It's like, hovering.
What is this?
I bet you plebs can't get close now!
Let's go on ahead.
It's an AOE.
Oichi's here!
Yoohoo~
Nobunaga-sama is here too!
Lookin' cool.
Advance by making full use of the flash arts!
There's an enemy in there!
There was an onigiri.
Onigiri?
A new mission.
"Defeat Honda Tadakatsu"!
Okay!
They aim for Tadakatsu's head.
There he is.
Where is he?!
He's right there.
There he is! There he is!
It's easy to tell where he is. They attack him together.
There. There. There. There. There.
Congratulations!
There it is!
That's so cool!
Whoa! Amazing!
It's here!
Honda Tadakatsu, defeated!
That was amazing!
Nice!
I'll try pressing triangle.
Whoa, she's so high up.
That was cool!
How violent!
That was cool.
This is so satisfying.
She split the ground.
You have to go towards the bottom-right area.
Ah, you're right. Is it this way?
Is this way right?
Yeah, that's the right way.
Let's go! Go! Go!
It's a straight road until the boss.
It's Tokugawa Ieyasu!
Hold on! Ayame-chan!
Hmm?
Charge your gauge with R1.
OK! One sec.
Wai—
I'm charging!
All right! It's charged.
I charged it!
Will they use that move on this big group?
It's here!
Lookin' good.
Nice!
Wonderful.
Ieyasu's talking!
Time to mow down some enemies!
Ah! Wow!
That was so good!
This is really refreshing.
So cool!
Using that feels good. Also, Oichi's cute.
Oichi's seriously cute.
This is so fun.
Let's take down Ieyasu-san!
Boss Ieyasu found!
You're really hammering him.
Ah! There's Ieyasu.
He's there.
They're pushing him into a corner.
It'd be cool to beat him with a Dual Musou.
Will they be able to finish him off with the joint attack?
Ieyasu has quite a lot of HP. He's hella tanky, isn't he?
Fill it with R1+O.
Yeah, like that. Nearly there.
Okay!
It should charge with a little more damage.
It should fill up soon.
Crap, Ieyasu's gonna die first!
I'm ready when you are!
Don't die until I fill this up!
Don't die yet!
Ieyasu's gonna die!
Don't die yet!!
Oh no!
Oh no, he's...
Oh no!!
AHHH!
Ieyasu surrenders!
Oh no!
Ah... he's so cute.
"I have lost. I will humbly follow you."
He surrendered...
Ah, but we won, at least.
She's scaring me.
Victory!
There's a dangerous person loose.
Nice!
That felt so good.
The gameplay isn't that complex.
It's an S!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
I had a lot of fun,
so I'll let Captain play next.
I'll be playing! Yay!
Let's do it!
Let's show them our bonds!
I think the one that's two chapters over would be good.
Ah, this one?
Okay!
"Inabayama Riot."
Please go ahead!
I played a male character in the last chapter,
so I'd like to play a female character this time.
Sounds good!
Sena, huh...
Sena's cute, isn't she?
Can you play her?
Can I?
Ooh!
You can!
Then, should I...
Should you...?
go ahead and play Ieyasu?!
Your excitement's scary.
Ieyasu's probably crying in his grave.
Now then, we're off!
It started!
We're in a castle!
You're right!
We're inside.
It's a castle!
This feels great!
This is really nice.
It's so fun!
The objective is to clear a path out of the mansion
and reach the escaping point.
Go! Go! Go!
Let's use some arts too.
Look! Look! Isn't he super cool?!
Nice!
He's spinning so much!
He's so cute!
We got a mission.
We did.
Defeat 50 enemies.
It seems Sena's good with aerials.
Which button is jump?
Jump is... X?
Yeah, it is.
You're right! I can jump.
Wow!
I didn't know that!
Captain has her gauge filled, so Ayame-chan, fill up yours,
then we can see that amazing move again.
The one that they use together, right?
That move is so cool.
Ah, so that's a nata.
Yeah! It is.
So it's a nata.
It's really cool.
I see.
She's running around quite gracefully.
It might be good to defeat the named enemies.
Roger that!
Defeat the named enemies, noted.
Yeah.
I want to see you guys do a joint attack
on a big group of enemies.
I want to see that too!
You both have your gauge filled!
There's something there!
One of the named enemies is here!
A commander found!
Let's do it here!
Ready?
Together!
Okay, okay!
Ayame-senpai, ready?
Ah, sorry!
They're ignoring the mission.
Ayame fires early!
I'm sorry!
Our timing didn't quite match there.
It didn't.
Ah, but you'll be able to fill your gauge with another R1.
I have one gauge now!
Are we doing it?
Let's go!
Let's do it!
AHHH! What is this?!
Owie!
You can do it now!
You can do it!
Ayame-senpai, ready?
Ready?
Aaa...
Ah...
Your ties are so frayed...
They're making it quite hard to use the finishing move.
And she's used up her gauge!
It's fine. It's fine. It's fine.
It's fine. It's fine. It's not the boss, yet.
Right. Right. Right. Right.
We're still only halfway through.
Did we get Toshimitsu?
Nice!
We got—Wait, he's still alive.
He's almost dead.
Nice.
Okay!
Saito Toshimitsu, defeated!
Nice!
Filling their gauge again
Let's do the...
The joint attack?
Let's do that.
OK, let's do it.
Ready?
Ready, and...
We got it!
So flamboyant.
You guys finally got the timing down!
We're quite glad.
Ooh! Doing joint attacks feel amazing.
Sena's pose at the end is so cute.
It's cute!
They seem to be approaching the boss battle.
Oh? Nice.
Will they be able to handle it?
Let's keep forging ahead!
Go get 'em!
Let's move forward!
Let's use the charge move here.
Lookin' good.
Nice.
There he is!
He's here!
Ayame-senpai, would you like to use it?
It's the boss!
It's a boss!
My gauge is full!
Let's do it.
Ready, and...
Now!
Nice!
That's so fun.
Nice.
Wonderful.
Ayame and Marine's cooperation leveled up!
It's impressive to succeed on a boss.
Right?
It's working!
Nice!
The last attack missing kinda hurts.
All right.
Hold on...
"War drum soldier"
Ah, it's the person with the—
Do you see him?
He was behind you to the right.
Oh, on my side?
Over here?
Yeah, the one with the war drum.
Ah! This one!
He's a buffer!
Yeah!
Marine-san goes for the war drum soldier
to lower the enemy's morale!
He's in charge of a war drum?
He's giving everyone buffs.
They've got a war drum buff.
They sure do.
You're really beating him up!
Swish!
Oh? Enemy general, defeated!
Nice!
The boss is almost dead!
All right!
Nice!
They're running away!
They're running away! Kill them all!
This is so satisfying.
I want to see how all the other characters fight.
Right?
They seem unique to the character.
Their movesets and weapons are different, after all.
Oh, nice!
Nice!
Nice, nice.
How was playing Ieyasu?
Oh my god,
I'm infatuated!
Infatuated...
He was so cool.
He looks so innocent and cute,
but he was fighting with all his might,
Marine can't stop talking about her crush, Ieyasu.
and he looked so cool and brave.
You're scaring me.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Lastly,
Subaru-chan's already played the game before,
Yay!
so I'd like for her and Ayame-chan to play
the historically famous "Battle of Okehazama."
I didn't get to use Nouhime earlier,
so I'd like to try her out.
Oh? Sounds good.
Ooh! Nouhime.
What about you, Subaru-chan?
Who should I play...
I'm curious about Hanbei...
What, do you want me to use Hanbei?
I wonder how he attacks.
Though, I'm curious, too...
I'll use Hanbei, then!
It's Nouhime!
She's cute! And shiny.
So that's Hanbei.
She uses a bow!
Wait, he's smaller than I thought.
He is!
He's playing the hand drum!
Baaam!
He's using the shockwaves from hitting it!
That's amazing!
Amazing.
Hanbei's so cool.
Ooh!
Nouhime's amazing.
Hanbei's throwing something.
Ooh!
It seems like he's releasing shockwaves.
Nice.
Wow!
With such a nice instrument...
Okay!
There are targets.
Let's push forward! Ayame, follow me!
Take this!
Oh wow!
This is so satisfying!
This is crazy.
Ah, there's the target!
Enemy commander found!
Subaru-senpai, can you fill it up?
I filled it!
A little more.
Ah, I've got a little left.
Will she be able to fill it?
Just a little more!
Let's fill and fill and fill it up!
Fill and fill and fill it!
It seems almost filled... And it is!
It's filled! Ayame-chan, I'm ready!
Oh! Let's do it!
Where are you?
Get close to her...
Behind you.
Stop for a sec.
Let's stop for a sec.
He's chasing me!
Subaru-san, stop for a sec!
Subaru-chan?
Ow, ow, ow.
Okay! Ready, and...
Ow.
When you take a hit and get stunned,
Stunned
you won't be able to use the Dual Musou attack,
so keep that in mind!
And now...
What?
Huh?
Wait, I can't move.
A-Ayame-dono?!
I couldn't...
She might've been stunned.
Unleashing their Musou Ougi separately
Yeah, yeah. I was.
So you were stunned.
Doin' good.
Whoa, what is this?
There are named ones down there.
Yeet!
All right!
Hanbei jumped down!
There are so many down here!
Ayame-senpai already has her gauge filled.
Nouhime's so cool!
Imagawa Yoshimoto found!
I'm ready whenever!
Wait, the boss is here!
Seriously?
She's not lying! Go! Go! Go!
Can I just kill him like this?
That was fast.
"Eliminate the supreme commander
of the Imagawa army, Imagawa Yoshimoto."
Ooh!
So I can just defeat him!
Can I really use it here?
Go get 'im!
Nice!
He's regretting being conceited.
This is looking good.
Subaru-chan, use the R1 moves too!
Oh, right!
Ooh!
Whoa! That was cool.
All right!
That was an imposter?!
What?! That's...
They said that was an imposter.
I see.
It was a substitute.
The Imagawa Yoshimoto they thought
they defeated was a body double!
The battle continues!
Za Warudo.
Ah, it's Honda Tadakatsu!
Ayame-dono, Honda Tadakatsu is here!
Ah, I see him!
You're right!
Crap! I'm taking a ton of damage!
Do a combo attack!
Let's do a joint attack, Ayame-dono!
Where are you?
I'm... Wait.
Ah, I see you!
Let's see...
Do this...
It's a joint attack!
Let's go!
Without any callouts!
Without saying it!
Nice.
No way.
Tap! Tap! Tap! Tap! Tap! Tap!
How does that happen?
It's the power of the 2nd Gen!
Yeah! It's our 2nd Gen bonds!
It waits for you to let you use it easier.
Yeah, it does.
Yeah, that's really helpful.
It even shows you when to press the O.
They're quite considerate.
We've taken down the war drummer!
Subaru-chan, don't forget to R1!
Right!
There we go.
She's taken the onigiri!
Nice.
I took all of it...
That's fine.
Ah, there's Sena!
Sena's here!
Let's kill Sena!
Take this!
Use your arts. Nice.
It might be good to target her.
Hi-yah!
She's so far back.
What's with these guys?
Like this!
All right!
Nice.
Nice, nice.
Sena, defeated!
Okay, nice.
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Charge!
Boss Imagawa Yoshimoto, found!
All right!
Ooh!
He's here!
Yoshimoto's flailing a hammer around!
He's swinging it!
We can't let him out-swing us!
We gotta get one over him!
For real!
Let's get the war drum buffers first!
Subaru-san goes for the war drum general!
Subaru attacks the war drum general!
She's got a knack for war.
Let's get those drummers!
She's smacking them with her hand drum!
Take that!
Nice!
Mine's charged!
Ooh! Here we go.
It's charged?
Yup.
Let's let loose on Imagawa!
Ayame-senpai's right next to the boss.
I'm pushing him into the corner.
I'm chasing him to the corner.
Nice.
Ready?
Yeah.
Ready, and...
Nice!
They did it!
Ah, the other way.
Please drum on the other side.
The other—
But we can control it.
Yeah.
You can turn.
Wait, that was perfect!
Wait, he's still full.
He's still at full HP!
This guy's tanky!
Let's do it one more time!
One more time!
Give me a sec.
Okay!
Okay, okay!
Ready?
Yeah.
Ready, and...
Now!
Ooh!
We did it!
Will it kill him?
Tap! Tap! Tap! Tap! Tap! Tap!
Take this! And this! And this!
And this! And this! And this!
You're hitting him this time.
Ready?
Yeah!
There!
The hand drum sounds are so funny.
And now,
once you clear the "Battle of Okehazama" chapter,
you can watch a special cutscene of
Imagawa Yoshimoto and the young Oda Nobunaga.
Please give it a try as well!
So cool!
I was using close-ranged weapons before this,
and this time, though I used Nouhime,
I was just shooting at melee range.
It felt really good, though.
And have we solved your problem?
Have we?
I'm fully refreshed, so I think I'll sleep soundly today.
Yay!
Yeah.
That's good to hear.
Problem solved!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Please tell us the member who shined
the most, the Twin-crew for today!
The Twin-crew for today was...
Subaru...
*drum roll*
Bam!
Oozora Subaru-san!
Yaaay!
Seriously?!
Today's Twin-crew
Oozora Subaru
Wait, I'm so happy!
You were all amazing,
but Subaru was the easiest to do joint attacks with.
We even did one without a callout.
Right?
We could do them together too by the end!
It's all in our 2nd Gen bonds.
Since Subaru got selected as a Twin-crew,
we'll give her another star!
I'll get to 100 in a jiffy!
Subaru will be the boss at this rate!
She's at 3 now.
Yeah! I'll be at 100 in no time!
You'll be the boss at 100 stars,
so keep doing your best!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Challenge From the Boss: the Maruyama Championship!
Yay!
At this point, we'll have our customers
try their hand at a minigame.
Their results will be ranked,
and the one who finishes the season on top
will receive a Special Maruyama Trophy!
This season's minigame is...
Puyo Puyo Tetris 2's Endless Fever mode!
Yay!
At the moment, in first place is
Marine with 57,726 points,
and in last is Subaru with two mill-oops, 2,516 points.
Not two million, two thousand!
Huh?
That's right. Thank you very much.
I'm very sorry.
We call this the Subaru Line.
The Subaru Line.
How confident are you?
I've never played Puyo Puyo before.
She's never played!
Oh?
Ayame has never played Puyo Puyo!
Can you beat the Subaru Line?
Are you joining me at the Subaru Line?
I might make a Nakiri Line.
She might have a talent for it.
A Nakiri Line.
I might make a new record with a Nakiri Line.
Maybe not. She might have a hidden talent for it.
Yeah, she might awaken a hidden power!
Then let the game begin!
Do your best, Ayame-chan!
Do your best!
You only get 60 seconds, so slap them down fast.
Huh? It's that short?
Right. Just keep slapping them down.
One minute, that's all.
Slap 'em!
Yeah! Good speed, good speed!
Just keep slapping them down.
Yeah, yeah. Good, good.
Yeah, good.
I can smell the Subaru Line cooking!
You're doing great.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's fine.
You can clear it.
Nice!
1-chain!
So she cleared it.
Nice 1-chain!
She's almost past the Subaru Line already.
How?! How?! How?!
How does someone even get lower than the Subaru Line?
She is?! No way!
Good question.
How did you make the Subaru Line?
What happened on that day?
Let's go back over that game.
I don't know!
Am I doing this right?
Yeah, you are!
Wonderful!
Ayame-chan, why aren't you a Subaru Line person?!
I don't really want to be like you.
Why not?!
20 seconds! 20 seconds! 200 points, Ayame-chan!
Nice, nice, nice!
You have 13 seconds left.
This isn't a Subaru Line game?!
What? No, I don't want that!
Your score isn't rising very well.
Not enough chain.
Yeah, it's not rising. 5 seconds!
4! 3!
2! 1!
Wait, wait!
Shoot!
Go! Go! Go!
It's over!
The Subaru Line!
Let's see the results!
Your final score is 2,512 points!
Yes!
Amazing! Oozora Subaru's Subaru Line has been beaten!
No!
Yesss!!
It's the Ayame Line!
The Ayame Line has been born.
Ayame Line
No!
This episode is one for the books.
I guess I didn't get a big enough chain.
Your max chain was 1.
You didn't need to mention that!
Will a monster appear and beat that score—either one?
Tune in next time and see!
Look forward to it!
Nakiri Ayame
Thank you for your patronage!
Look forward to it!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
After Closing
How did you enjoy this episode of Game Shop Maruyama?
I've asked Towa-san to stay back this time.
Now, let's give our viewers
some advice with their worries!
From @languedegyat on Twitter!
My problem is that my shoulders
and eyes are extremely fatigued.
Do you do anything to relieve your fatigue?
I'd appreciate it if you told me!
That's the problem.
What do you think, Towa-sensei?
This is a very good worry.
Who are you supposed to be?
Tokoyami... When she is le tired...
Third-person?!
She goes to have le massage?
That is what she le does.
What do you do when you're tired, Boss?
When I'm tired, I just go to sleep, I guess.
Oh, I see!
I roll up and sleep. Yeah, I roll up and sleep.
That is very good.
I sleep too. Sleeping is good, isn't it?
Yeah. You aren't saying anything enlightening,
but you're making up for it with the presentation?
And also...
There's more?
Sometimes...
Looks like there is.
I move my body about at home.
You mean you exercise, or like some routine?
Um...
Do you really do it?
I do.
I do do it.
And I also take hip baths.
Oh, hip baths!
So demons take hip baths?
I seek to be le beautiful!
I see...
Yes.
You're being very condescending.
So yes, you can sleep and
take baths and go to le massage?
Okay! So, anyway,
thank you for the answers you'd get
at the top of a Google search.
Excuse me?
And now, we're accepting requests for advice from you.
Excuse me?!
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique,
personally signed request fulfilled sticker.
Yay!
So please send in your submissions!
Send them in!