It's habbening! It's habbening!
It's habbening!
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey!
It habbened!
It habbened! It habbened!
Starting with a Mysterious Dance
Heeey!
It started! It started!
HEEEY!
Heeey!
I can hear something.
Hey!
It took three minutes
Ah.
for you guys to quiet down.
It's hasn't even been a minute!
Same as Always
Please quiet down.
Sorry.
Quit rounding up.
You're all so full of energy today.
Yeah!
We're all here,
so let's practice some greetings!
Sounds good!
Ready?
Welcome!
Wel-the hell-come!
What are you looking for?
What the hell are you looking for?!
That's some intensity.
Very Unique Greetings
Please don't smash the B button!
Don't you dare smash the B button!
That's a card machine, not an NES!
That's not an NES, dammit!
It's a goddamn card machine!
Perfect! Work hard today!
Okay!
Hello.
A customer appeared!
Oh?
Welcome!
Nice to meet you all.
Hello everyone!
Today's Guest: Shirogane Noel
It's Commander!
I heard there was
a peculiar game shop in this area.
Yes. Too peculiar.
Oh? You heard well.
There we have it!
Our guest this time is Shirogane Noel-san!
Shirogane Noel
About Her: Laid-back Muscle Knight
Hobbies: Eating!
Finishing Move: Muscle Metronome
Effect: Ruins target's rhythm
MENT
LUCK
A soft, musclebrained female knight
who solves everything with brawn.
Oh, and check out her finisher!
"Finishing Move: Muscle Metronome"?
Finishing Move: Muscle Metronome
It's here!
What's that?
What's here?
What's here?!
Oh, you haven't seen it?
Can you tell me what that is?
Ah.
This might be my first time doing it in 3D.
First time in 3D!
Oh!
Here I go.
Ready?
Tick-tick-tick-tick—
Uh...
Trust me, it's hilarious in streams.
It's hilarious in streams
Ah, so it's popular in streams.
I-It really is funny during streams!
Don't say it like it was lame!
Right.
It wasn't lame!
Moving on, Noel's worried
about her insane appetite recently.
That's right.
Recent Worries: Insane Appetite
Ohh, I see.
It's the spring of cravings.
What sort of cravings?
I've been eating tendies a lot recently.
It's so good, right?
Recent Worries: Insane Appetite
Tendies? I know, right?
But hey.
Boss, take a look at those huge pecs.
They did catch my eye.
Chest muscles!
She's got two huge tender ones on her.
Hey!
They're pretty big.
I'll eat 'em up!
They're pretty nice.
Isn't that sexual harassment?
Sorry.
Please stay on track
Apologies.
I'm getting a bit scared.
Let's see what Noel wants to fix.
What worry would the customer like resolved?
Yes.
Please go ahead.
Yeah.
Here's my problem.
I'm...
as you can tell, I'm pretty confident
in my physical strength.
Right.
However, I want to improve my vocabulary
to become a more eloquent knight.
Current worry: I want to be an eloquent knight!
She wants to become an eloquent knight.
I do.
And there we have our request!
We've got just the thing!
We have the perfect game for you!
Maruyama's game recommendation is...
this!
Ta-dah!
Kotoba no Puzzle: Mojipittan Encore!
Moji-Mojipittan! Mojipittan!
It's Mojipittan!
This latest version of the popular
intellect-stimulating puzzle game
is now available on four platforms!
Connect the letter tiles to make words!
Its simple but deep gameplay is certain to get you hooked!
The latest version includes the latest slang!
Over 130,000 words in the dictionary!
You'll never get tired of playing it!
Would you like to give it a try?
Yeah!
I'd love to try it out!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Let's give Kotoba no Puzzle: Mojipittan Encore a run!
Yay!
Here we go! Start!
Yeah!
Let's try solo first.
"Solo."
Go!
There're a whole bunch of options.
There's a section for "New Stages"
Yeah.
Oh? These seem good.
It has a time limit and all that.
It's a set of practice stages.
It's two minutes, which is perfect.
The donut stage seems all right.
Should we try it, then?
Let's!
Here I go.
Will the word donut come full circle?
I want some!
Let's do it!
The time limit is pretty strict.
Two minutes go by pretty fast.
"Donut," huh.
Time limit: 2 minutes! Fill in all the stars to clear!
"Fill in all the stars."
Fill in the stars?
You have to fill in the stars.
Ah.
Then, maybe "o"?
"ō (o)."
Ah, "o," huh?
I just have to fill them in, right?
English words count too!
From the English alphabet.
Uh, this is "kittsu (hard)."
Doesn't exist.
Don't say that!
You got this!
Then, "ketsu (butt)."
Oi!
Noel?!
That's not it!
That's
It's "butt" as in the butt of a joke!
It was defined as "the thicker end of something."
Like that, huh?
"Tsuse"?
"Tsu..." "tsu..."
Tsuki (moon)! Moon! To the moon!
"Moon" for sure.
Ah, "moon" should work.
Do I have "ki"?
Do I?
Ah, I do.
"Moon," nice. Once you use a letter, you can't use it again.
Oh, so that's how it works.
It uses it up.
Each letter can only be used once!
You have to be strategic!
That's right.
It's completely viable to keep your versatile letters.
Exactly.
"Kushi (master)."
Alright!
Good pace so far!
Nice!
You still have a minute and a half left!
"Kusa (grass; lol)."
You're so good!
It's that thing people comment a lot!
That thing...
Yeah, that thing people comment a lot!
You gotta bridge the gaps between the stars too.
"Sasa..." "susu..."
Nice!
"Susa"?
"Suso"? Ah, I can do "suso (hem)."
Hem.
Whoa!
Maybe "sechi (gumption; stingy person)."
Let's see...
One minute left!
Wait!
"Kase (reel)."
You're doing great!
Go, go, go!
1 star left!
"Doe."
Nope.
"Do..." "do-do-do-dotsu..."
"Do-do-dotsu..." "dotsuka (*dokka, to skim)."
What's a "dotsuka"?
What the heck's a "dotsuka"?!
How does that exist?
Lastly, "tatsu (to be built)."
With that,
I've cleared the stage!
Stage cleared!
Stage clear!
Congratulations!
It was really forced, though.
It was quite a powerful playstyle.
Like, words happened to exist.
Have you figured out the game?
Yeah!
Next: Pittan Queen Championship!
Perfectly.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Guys!
Have you gotten the hang of Mojipittan yet?
Yeah! We have!
I have!
Since we all know how the game works,
we'll be seeing who has the biggest vocab!
Pittan Queen Championship!
Who has the best vocabulary?!
I won't lose!
I'll make you all cry!
This person's scary.
Let's improve our vocabulary!
Noel and Captain will be Team Gen 3!
3rd gen!
Yay, our bonds!
We got this!
It's all in our bonds!
VS!
Let's show them! Icarus Rollercoaster!
Yaaay!
It's the Icarus Rollercoaster team!
We won't lose!
The winner...
Yeah?
...gets to challenge
the Vocabulary Beast, Boss!
I'll wreck all of you!
That's our Boss.
Quite the comedian.
Without further ado, let's get started!
Let's!
Let's go with the "go board."
The first to 25 points wins.
45 seconds per move. First to 25 tiles wins!
Okay!
I don't wanna lose!
Give it your all! Fight!
Let's win!
Here we go!
Which team will go first?
Which one? Which one?
Which will it be?
"First move..."
Yay! We go first!
I see.
We go second.
Subaru and Towa team first?
Ah. We go second...
We're Player 1.
Ah, the 3rd gen team is Player 1. I see.
Let's start with the less versatile letters.
3rd gen team, you have 30 seconds!
How about "sukutsu (den)"?
Ah, yeah!
"Den"!
Nice. Nice.
OK, OK!
Here we go.
The music's really nice, too.
A three-letter word...
Maybe "chiyose (a name)"?
Go for it!
Do they have it?
They have it, right?
Yeah!
So they don't.
It fit, though.
It had "chiyo (very long time)" and "yose (endgame)."
I see!
"Sugita (common surname)."
"Sugita"!
Shoot!
Let's go!
"Hora (look)"!
Look?
Look.
"Su..."
Ah! Ah!
You can make "chibusa (breast)."
"Breas—" Hey! Stop that!
Just had a divine revelation
"Ra..." "Ra..."
Right there!
"Look"!
Good move.
Go for it!
Uh... Where is it?
To the right.
There? Oh, up.
Up. Up.
Right there. "Breast."
"Breas—" Haha.
Not there!
Huh?
It's "breast"!
Where?
Huh? Where?
Ah. It's a "z."
You just have a dirty mind!
Sorry, sorry.
Jeez.
Nice!
Crap, crap!
Hey, wait!
Three-point difference!
We don't have "i" anymore.
You can make "Takechiyo (a given name)"
and "chiyo (very long time)"!
Is "Takechiyo" valid?
What?! "Takechiyo"?!
Does "Takechiyo" exist?
What?
"Chi" for "Takechiyo..."
What's a "Takechiyo"?
But they've already used a "chi" earlier!
Oh?
They found it! They still had one!
Ah! It fits!
"Takechiyo" has been put on the board!
What even is "Takechiyo"?!
It was just "kechiyo."
There was a sumo wrestler named that!
Takechiyo sumo
Not found.
This game has surnames too, surprisingly.
Yeah.
"Kura (saddle)."
Ah, "kurai (dark)."
Nice, nice!
That was good.
So "gira" doesn't exist...
It seemed like it would.
But it didn't.
"Saku (to bloom)."
"Sa"?
"Sakura (cherry blossom)"!
Where? Where?
Uh...
Next to the "ko."
It's to the bottom-right from the "gi."
Maybe we can also get the surname, "Sakurai."
Is that the plan?
I feel like that would exist.
Can we get "Sakurai"?
"Saku..."
"Sakura"!
"Sakurai"!
Ooh!
Good one.
"Sakurai"?!
Let's try "i."
Where?
"Gi... gitai (camouflage)"?
Maybe "Ise (a city)" too.
Ah.
"Camouflage."
Here?
Okay! Got it.
"Camouflage"! And "Ise"!
"Ise"!
You're both doing great!
You're tied in points!
Three-point difference!
Neck and neck right to the endgame!
Wanna risk it on "bubu"?
Let's do it!
Please!
"Buru (bourgeoisie)"!
"Yobu (to call out to)"!
AHHH!
Team 3rd Gen's in trouble!
Three points to victory!
"Bubu" doesn't exist!
"Sakin (gold dust)"! "Gold dust"!
"Gold dust"! "Kin (gold)"!
Ah... Still a one-point difference.
Five more points to victory!
It's currently a one-point difference.
This is bad!
"Ono (axe)..."
"Ohiza (knee)"!
"Thine honorable knee"!
"Knee"!
Slap it on there!
Two more points to win!
However, the 3rd gen team has a chance to turn it around!
"Tsuna (tuna)," "nami (wave)..."
It's not enough.
Ah, but I feel like "nachi" is also a word.
Unless they choose the best spot, they'll be in a pinch.
Oh?
Ah, it's not a word!
This is bad!
Three more points!
Will this clinch it?!
Is there a word like "kannami"?
If they can get those tiles...
I feel like that exists!
I think we used "ka" already, though.
What the heck's a "kannami"?
What is that?!
Will the 3rd gen team win?
We don't have "ka"!
"Ke..." "ku..."
"Kunna (Stay the hell away)"!
"Stay the hell away"?!
Huh?! There's no way that exists!
"Kun (-kun)" exists, at least!
So this one?
What?! You're actually going for it?
You sure?
There's no way...
GOOO!
There's no way!
"Kun"!
"Kaoku (house)." "Oku (to place)."
They won!
And the winner is...
the Subaru and Towa team!
Winner: Team Icarus Rollercoaster!
I know why we lost.
Marine misread one of the letters...
Ah. To explain,
I saw "bre" and "st" and thought,
"YOOO! Let's make 'breast'!"
And it ended up being a "z" instead.
It was a "z."
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
And now, it's time for
the Mojipittan Queen match between
Team Icarus Rollercoaster
vs
the person referred to as the "Vocabulary Beast"
due to the nature of her job, Boss!
Boss!
But she's a bit scared on her own,
so she's with Noel!
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm not scared.
Hey.
Noel-chan insisted on playing more,
so I said okay.
I see.
Mhmm.
I'll be more useful than her!
What are you getting at?
So Captain's been temporarily laid off.
Thank you for your service.
I'll help your side, then, Subaru-senpai.
I don't need your help!
How could you?!
The final begins! Who will be the vocabulary queens?!
Friend or foe?
We'll be using this stage!
Let's go!
Four-by-four.
45 seconds per move. First to 9 tiles wins!
This match will be pretty fast.
Yeah.
It'll be over in a flash!
Wait, this is so small!
Can you even make "breast" on here?
You gotta stay on the attack.
Which team will go first?
Ah, it's us!
It's us!
Wait, it's your team!
Let's see...
How will they start?
Darn.
Maybe "oi (old age)" and "kai (story)"?
But shouldn't...
Shouldn't we save the vowels?
Ah, right.
That's true.
What will they use?
"Oku (to place)"?
"Kaku (to write)" exists, right?
Yeah.
Wanna do "place" and "write," then?
I think that's fine.
Okay!
I see.
"Place" and "write."
Makes sense.
I feel like these are easy to steal.
Yeah.
How about "ao (blue)" and "aka (red)"?
Uh-huh.
Ah, the corner, huh?
Or... "kaoku (house)"?
But that's still just three letters,
so I think it's better to take the center!
Oh!
Take that!
Let's go!
I see, I see.
That's our Boss.
That was clever.
It was.
2 colors, just like me.
Truly a beast.
"Aka..."
How about "akago (baby)"?
"Baby"!
"Baby."
It exists, right?
Yeah. If it's that...
"Kago (basket)"!
Nice!
The "red" is pretty easy to steal, though.
What should we do?
Uh...
But we have to make it
with that letter!
They wouldn't...
That letter...
is all we have left!
We'll leave
our legacy ("br") here!
Inherit...
Inherit our will!
Go!
Could it be...
Is she trying to complete it?!
That string of letters...
Can't stop smiling
This is a joint effort!
This...
What?!
Is she really gonna do it?!
And now it's time...
Hey!
Nice joint effort! (not the point)
We...
Let's place it down!
Yeah! Let's do it!
Boss, it's time!
Is she gonna do it?!
All right!
Are you really fine
with letting us do the honors?
My hands... They're shaking!
Breas...r?!
My hands are shaking too much!
Calm down!
Boss! That's an "r"!
That's an "r"!
Ah! Close one.
I had the wrong letter.
Boss, your hands!
Boss's natural airheadedness
That was close!
Wait this is a "z"!
Boss!
Darn!
Where is it?
It's further up!
It's up!
How much time?
Ah!
Boss!
My hands!
I'll be ending it now!
Chibusa - breast
GOOO!
It's "breast"!
This is our victory!
Victory!
We've lost...
It's our victory!
We haven't lost yet!
We have!
Please wait while Boss and Captain's emotions run down.
Back to the game
"Chi..."
"Chichibu (a city. 'Chichi' means tits)."
She's good at finding those.
Please exist!
If "breast" is taken, we'll have to take "tit"!
We'll have to take "tit"!
They've taken the "tit"!
Wait, "Chichibu" exists!
Of course it does!
Why did you think it didn't?!
Hey, what's the plan?
We should do a counter tit.
Chaos
Wanna do a counter tit?
How about "to"?
We can take "tochi (plot)" and "tooku (far away)."
Are you ready?
Do it!
That's a good move!
"Far away"!
The bottom
next to the "sa" looks good.
Wait, they can do "tookuhe (far, far away)"
"Far, far away."
How touching.
Wanna try it?
Do you wanna try?
That'd be miraculous.
No way.
Far,
far away...
Will they do it?
Will they go far, far away?
Do ittt!
Yeah!
Not an Emopittan...
It didn't work!
Why doesn't it exist?!
It wasn't placeable.
Yeah.
"Go..."
What starts with "go"?
Wait we only have 10 seconds!
Crap!
"Okubi (thine honorable head)"!
Does that work?
Nine! Eight!
Trust me!
Seven! Six!
Almost out of time!
Where's the "o"?
Five! Four!
We need "bi"!
Ah, "bi." Right.
Three!
Two!
Faster!
One!
Time out!
When the timer runs out, the player passes.
The opponent gets a turn.
I was too busy taunting to think.
Crap.
Wh-What's the plan?
Let's take something we can take for certain.
When you're in a pinch, this'll make it a cinch!
English!
"Go (go)."
Ah, they took that spot.
Nice.
Wait.
"Ya..." Can we put a "ya"?
In the bottom left.
Hey, this is bad.
"YAGOO" you say?!
We're gonna lose!
There's no way "Yagoo" exists!
He could be one of the 130,000 words!
Oh no!
We'll make it happen! Go!
Don't be rash!
"Yago (Dragonfly nymph)."
So "Yagoo" does exist.
What should we do?
This could be a big move!
Yeah, yeah.
This is a difficult choice.
Do you have something?
Ah! Maybe with a "shi"?
Oh? "Shi."
I'll use it here, okay?
Yeah.
NOOO!
Oh no!
It's "shikaku (assassin)"!
GG!
There's the finishing blow!
That's Boss for ya!
We got "breast" as well, so that's 2 wins in a row!
So this is the Vocabulary Beast.
Winner: Team Boss & Noel!
The Vocabulary Beast's true power...
That was amazing!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
The demo for today ends here!
That was so fun!
She's increased her vocabulary through
Kotoba no Puzzle: Mojipittan Encore.
Or was supposed to. What did you think about the game?
Let's see...
It was extremely fun.
I've learned something at least!
What?
Thanks to you guys,
I'll be using "Breast" and "Tit" from now on!
Yay! Commander!
But Noel's been calling her breasts
"pecs" this whole time,
so maybe her vocab's gotten worse.
We would prefer not to have such open indecency...
Could you hold yourself back?
You were the one who taught me that!
It's your fault!
Friend or Foe?! Boss & Noel
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
So, Noel-san, you said you wanted
to increase your vocabulary.
Current worry: I want to be an eloquent knight!
Did we manage to fulfill your request?
Bring out the weather scale!
The floor is yours!
Stormy
Rain
Cloudy
Clear
Rising Sun!
Rising... Sun!
Not this again...
Oh...
It's the best option, isn't it?!
I heard it was!
Huh?
Oh...
Did you hear that from Lamy?
That it was a huge hit?
Yeah. She said you guys loved it.
She said I should do it too.
Um... Uh...
Noel... You fell for her trap.
Trickster Lamy's trap
I can't believe you've done this!
What good friends.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Challenge From the Boss:
the Maruyama Championship!
Yay!
At this point, we'll have our customers
try their hand at a minigame.
Okay!
Yes!
Yeah!
Their results will be ranked,
and the one who finishes the season on top
will receive a Special Maruyama Trophy!
Oh, I see! Want, want, want!
I want it.
I want that!
This season's minigame is...
I want that too.
Puyo Puyo Tetris 2's Endless Fever mode!
Yay!
Aw yeah!
The current high scorer
Yes.
is Marine with 57,726 points.
Hey, that's high!
But, you know...
It's one heck of a high score.
I want Noel to beat it,
so I taught Noel the orthodox strategy
of building stairs earlier.
That was five minutes ago.
Was that some pro jargon or something?
What are stairs?
A strategy for creating chains by
stacking each color vertically with 1 block
of the adjacent column's color on top.
Yes.
Can she build stairs like she was taught five minutes ago?
Noel-chan can do it!
I hope so!
Well...
All right.
I want to see that!
Okay, then!
Are you ready to play?
Let the game begin!
Start!
Wait, is it start-
It's starting!
It starts right away. You get 60 seconds.
Seriously?!
Do your best! You can do it!
Okay, okay.
There's a countdown,
and it starts!
It's starting!
And there!
Go!
This is an easy stack.
Nice, nice.
But this...
That's a good start.
Like this?
Yeah, yeah-
Ah! Ah!
You're okay.
Can she build stairs from this?
Nice, nice.
What do stairs look like?
Nice.
No, wrong-
Oh, like this? Is this right?
You're okay, you're okay.
Put that...
Okay, okay...
She's learning. On the side-
Wait, like this?
Oh, so close.
On the side.
I messed up?!
So close, so close.
Someone just said she messed up?
So close?!
I don't know! What do I do?
Why not just play the way you want?
Let's watch her from the sidelines.
Go my way!
I wasn't supposed to do that?
Noel... Noel...
Do I do it like this?
Oh, I shouldn't?
Noel...
Ah, Noel!
Just let her play the game!
Huh? Wait! Wait!
Let me just-
Just let her play the game!
Ah! (wailing)
Was that bad?
What do I do?! What do I do?!
I'm just going to keep stacking.
Just do your best and stack them.
Good! Good! Good!
Nice!
You can get a chain with that.
Nice! Nice!
With this?
Good, Noel!
There!
2-chain! 3-chain!
Chain! Chain!
Good, Noel!
Yes! Chain!
4-chain!
A 4-chain! Nice!
You can do it!
Okay! Okay! Okay!
Now, with a max chain of 4!
There's 10 seconds left! You can do it!
You can get a 3-chain!
You can get a 3-chain, Noel!
Her score keeps rising!
Wait, but time-
Yellow! Yellow!
Five seconds left!
Four!
Noel!
Gah!
Three!
Noel!
Two!
Ah! Noel!
One!
No, it's over!
It's over!
So close!
I panicked at the end!
But look at that score!
And your final score was...
Wow!
What are the final results?!
Noel!
Wow! Wow!
Is it, like, the chain?
Yeah, you get a lot of points from chains.
I panicked at the end there.
We have a final score!
No, like, you were awesome!
34,255 points!
Awesome!
You got a 4-chain! 4-chain!
Really?
I got a 4-chain! I'm so satisfied.
Unfortunately, that's not a new high score!
Nice!
She's just too good!
That's it!
But you got a good score.
It was your first time.
How do you feel about it?
It was my first time playing,
That's right.
so I'm really satisfied with getting a 4-chain.
Awesome!
Discovered an unexpected talent?
I'm so happy!
Impressive. A 4-chain on your first game?
I taught her five minutes before.
Thank you!
She learned all that five minutes ago.
I mean, you're a pro.
That's crazy!
Five minutes before.
Wow!
Well, then...
Will a monster appear and beat that high score?
Tune in next time and see!
Look forward to it!
Shirogane Noel
Thank you for your patronage!
Look forward to it!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
How did you enjoy this episode of Game Shop Maruyama?
We helped our customer with her worries.
She must be very pleased.
Yeah!
I've asked Subaru-san to stay back this time.
Yay!
You're an energetic one.
Yeah!
We'd love to give our viewers advice regarding their worries,
Yeah, yeah.
but due to reasons, we haven't received any submissions yet.
Still?
But...
Yeah, they still aren't in.
Sorry.
It's okay!
So, Subaru-san,
is there anything bothering you?
So, like...
Yes?
I don't know if this is something I should ask you...
Huh?
What?
This is really bothering me.
Okazu Club's
YuiP-san's
channel thumbnails are way too unique.
Everyone says I'm really bad at making thumbnails,
but, like, I have to say
her thumbnails are like three levels higher than mine!
Below: Okazu Club's YuiP's very unique thumbnails
They're so-
Cut it out already!
Huh?
I think...
Crap!
I think I'm hearing things!
Crap! Crap! Crap! Crap!
Like, I wanted to know how she made those.
I see.
Current worry: I want to make some nice thumbnails!
Well, actually,
I should've told you earlier,
but I'm friends with Okazu Club's YuiP-san.
Boss's Secret 1: Friends with Okazu Club's YuiP?
That's right.
So just now,
How good of friends are you?
I got mad like you were talking about me.
Well, like, we're basically always together.
Except when working.
Like, one body and mind?
Basically one body and mind.
Boss's Secret 2: One body and mind with YuiP?
Oh?
Oh, I see!
You were curious about those?
Yeah, I was!
She says that no one ever says anything about them.
What? Nothing at all?
No one ever says anything,
and no one expects anything either.
Well, that's...
The saddest possible truth
What does she use to make them?
Well, like, something like...
Something you can swap out
rectangular text and backgrounds?
It's really simple.
Isn't that PowerPoint?
Yes, that's right.
It really is. But it's super useful.
Really?
Are your thumbnails really that crazy?
Well, like,
I always use red text on a black background.
Subaru's works of art
They say my thumbnails look like ramen restaurant billboards.
I can see it.
But, like,
YuiP-senpai's thumbnails have this feel like
a mixed-use building.
Mixed-use building
I don't mean that in a bad way!
What?
Comparing those thumbnails
to a mixed-use building?!
Why?!
How dare you?!
I'm sorry!
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Boss's Secret 3: Extremely sensitive
to remarks about YuiP?!
I'm calm. I'm calm.
You okay, Boss?
So, like, right.
Let's try copying Marine-chan.
Hey, yeah! Let's copy her together!
Yeah, yeah.
Let's steal Marine-chan's.
Yeah! Steal it! Steal it!
Right.
Marine-chan's good at drawing,
so why not ask her to draw them?
Oh, that's an idea!
Yeah!
Marine-chan's good at drawing, so she'll
draw something for you, probably.
Boss's Answer: Get Captain to draw them!
And she's over there.
Is that—
You'll draw some, right?
Will you draw some, Captain?
Like hell, I will!
She snapped!
You'll raise your blood pressure!
Why not?!
Oh shoot!
With that done...
We're accepting requests for advice from you.
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique,
personally signed request fulfilled sticker.
Yay!
So please send in your submissions!
Send in your submissions!
Stupid thumbnails!
Stupid—
It's not the thumbnails' fault!
Right?!