Rushia-chan's got that laser focus going.
How can she choose sewing over us?
Let's distract her!
What?
Frog behind you, Rushia-senpai!
A-Actually, it's me, Amane Kanata...
I'm so sorry, Kanatan!
I didn't know frogs freaked her out...
A-Anyway, I'm trying to focus. Keep it down.
You've picked up sewing?
No sewing. Just threading the needle.
But... why?
To attain heightened concentration and dexterity,
and become an all-powerful girl!
I think you're broken enough already.
Heh, I can do it with my eyes closed.
Excuse me?
Just watch me!
stab
What is wrong with you?!
Wah, it's bleeding a little.
Ugh!
Aren't you a vampire?
But man, this is hard.
You gotta put yourself in the thread's shoes.
Pre-ci-sely!
Excuse me?
Thread yourself through this supersized needle.
You want me to become thread incarnate?
We'll help you out, too.
Yeah, we've got you.
You guys...
Aight, let's do this!
Hi-yah!
100/100
You look thrice as threadening!
That was needless.
Be sure to put in work that makes sense.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!