July 25
It's Tanabata time!
July 7!
That's bamboozling. It's late-July now.
Got your wish strips here.
And the bamboo?
Noel-chan should be here with it soon.
Delivery for you!
Perfect timing!
That's yuge!
The bigger, the better!
How is this gonna fit?
Art is a loop...
of creation and destruction.
I gotchu!
Nngh! Nnngh!
She actually split it into pieces!
I made this.
Okay, time to put it together.
Can we?
With Noel-senpai's help, it'll be a cinch!
Muscles are the answer to everything.
Now I'm worried.
We're done!
What even?!
Now to enter this in the bamboo creations contest.
It'll win for sure!
That's one weird contest!
From the top!
Yikes, I messed up!
We have no somen!
I bought some.
One more time!
Piece of cake. Piece of cake.
I'm beat...
Okay, write your wishes, girls!
Yay!
And so we wrote our wishes...
For each and everyone to get better
at the things they love doing.
Through the Milky Way...
Er, uhm...
How do I read this?
I dunno!
Way to ruin it!
Uh, it's getting cloudy outside.
Our wishes won't reach the sky!
Okay, I'll get them there!
Hi-yah!
Waow.
"Who's Fubuki-chan? I'm Fububoshi."
Wishes from Earth, delivered in the flesh.
Let's see...
"I wanna eat somen! - Nene"
...Then why don't you?
It's been two long years.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!