Help!
Guys, help!
Ahh!
F!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Game Shop Maruyama
Ready.
Interviews In Progress
Q: Could you give us your name?
Sure!
I'm Oozora Subaru!
Q: What do you do?
I spend my time managing an MMA team
and an e-sports club!
Q: What made you want to work here?
I saw the poster outside the station.
The pay looked good,
and I figured it'd be fun,
so here I am!
Ahoy!
Q: What is your name?
Captain of the Houshou Pirates,
Houshou Marine here!
You may be seated.
Q: In-your-face much?
Oh... I wanted to show off
my boundless energy.
I can move!
Look!
I'm fit as a fiddle, so rest assured!
I can move!
I can work!
Whoo!
Please remain seated.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry about that.
Really.
'Sup, groupies!
Q: What is your name?
This is your Tokoyami Towa the Great
from hololive 4th Gen!
I spend my time, uh,
Q: What do you do?
playing a bunch of FPS games—
Wait, sorry! Scratch that!
I'm a devil!
Q: How did you get here?
Huh? "How"?
Like, just now?
I, uh, er...
I came flying, obviously.
Like, zoom.
Maruyama Theater: Part I
Chance Meetings
Q: If you had a time machine,
would you travel to the past, or the future?
Uh...
The future!
I'd like to see the future!
Q: And why is that?
Because what's done is done.
I don't care about that.
Q: What do you do?
Oh, as you can see...
It's obvious, isn't it?
I captain a pirate crew!
Q: And you still want to work here?
Oh!
It could be a side hustle...
Ah!
Look, honestly speaking,
I don't actually engage in piracy.
That said, I do have a large crew.
No ship, though.
Huh? Work experience? Well...
Q: Do you have any work experience?
Back in my old world,
I worked at two sushi places at once.
Sushi squared.
Oh, right. Nearly forgot.
I worked at one over here, too.
Uh...
Q: What if you know the world
was going to end in one hour?
I seem to have lost...
lost my voice all of a sudden.
So...
My guardian angel will
read out my answer.
'Cause I lost my voice.
I'll put my entire life's savings
into the stock market!
Wait, what does that even mean?
Q: What would your funeral poem be?
Oh, it's a haiku?
Where'd that... Fine.
From this day forward
I will do everything
To live a good life.
Wait, that doesn't work!
Q: What is your strength?
My strength?
Sex appeal.
My sex appeal... will bring...
It will bring about world peace.
And liven up the workplace.
Q: Do you have any questions?
Well...
I've been wondering, Boss.
How exactly...
are you moving?
Whatever the job, you can count on me!
Oozora Subaru: "What's done is done.
I don't care about that."
Hired
I have a crew to feed.
As their captain, I'll work for them.
Houshou Marine: World peace
through sex appeal.
Hired
I can get paid to play games?
When can I start?
How about now?
Tokoyami Towa: "I'm a devil!"
Hired
And so begins Game Shop Maruyama's opening day!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
I'm gonna work my butt off
and $^!#%$*!#$!
Oh, and the other employees
are gunna show up today.
Who's it gunna be?
Hello!
I'm Tokoyami Towa the Great.
I start here today...
What? Fur real?
You're working here too, Subaru-chan?
Yeah, I'm gunna werk here!
You gunna werk 'ere too?
Wait...
Have you always talked like a redneck?
Let it go!
You're gonna work here too?
Yeah, I'm gonna work here too!
All right.
Hello there.
Now...
Did you hear something?
There.
It took three whole minutes
for you to stop talking.
It's a school teacher!
Morning Assembly Tropes
We're sorry!
It's a school teacher!
Sorry!
Boss
I look forward to working with you.
Same.
Likewise!
But who the hell are you?
Suddenly Rude
Seriously?
I'm your boss.
Oh, right. Sorry about that.
It's fine. Just don't forget it again.
Thanks for hiring me.
Me too.
My pleasure.
Huh? Where's the last one?
Here!
I apologize for being late!
I'm thowwy!
Get out if you're just gonna goof off!
Kids, don't try this at home.
You okay?
Y-Your arteries holding up?
Be careful with your heart.
My bad!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Now that we're all here,
let's bring you up to speed.
This is a shop selling
a huge variety of games.
Solving customers' problems
using video games
is our USP.
Say what?!
First, when someone walks in,
have them fill out our questionnaire.
Customer Questionnaire
(Check @hololive_EN for translated version!)
Think of it as something like
a checklist of questions a doctor might ask you.
Mhm.
We don't have any customers yet,
so let's have you three fill it out.
Makes sense.
Okay by me!
Let's start with Subaru's.
Got it!
Okay.
Great.
"What's your biggest appeal?"
Yeah!
"Loud voice!"
Heck yeah!
They say she sounds like a duck.
You disagree, right, Boss?
Uh... a duck?
I don't sound like one!
I've never heard a duck speak,
so I couldn't say, really.
Well, duh!
Yeah, duh!
If you had to pick one,
funny man or straight man?
She says straight man!
Yeah, I'm the straight man.
Really?
But...
Yup!
Has she done that at all so far?
She's been, y'know...
Okay, listen.
I'm playing the role this show needs right now!
Understand?
Man...
You're so loud today.
Really...
Yeah.
Really hyper!
But seriously,
Stop that. I'm...
I'm doing my best here!
in her usual streams,
when she's more relaxed,
she does play the straight man more.
It seems she has a question for me.
Oh?
Oh!
She asks, "How do you make
your stream thumbnails?"
What's this about?
Well,
I suck at making those.
I kinda wanna see your thumbnails, Boss.
Can we, like, put 'em up?
They look like this.
There...
Wow, Captain!
There you have it.
Wait, not "Captain."
You're mixing up "Captain" and "Boss."
It's "Boss," okay?
I just change the text each time. And colors.
How long do you take to make yours?
Huh?
Q: How long does it take you
to make thumbnails?
How about you, Captain?
How long?
At least thirty minutes, I'd say.
Th-Thirty minutes each time?
Yeah.
And you, Boss?
It takes me... five.
Five?
Five minutes.
Five minutes before the stream.
What?!
Yeah.
What a way to act shocked.
How about you, Towa-chan?
Personally,
pretty close to yours. Five minutes.
What?!
Why, you...
I thought you were one of us!
Uh...
Around fifteen minutes.
You all put in effort—
Fifteen minutes for those?!
Wears heart on sleeve
Did you just hear that?
Look, I...
Boss! She's bullying me!
"For those?" Pfft...
She's a bully!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Next up, Marine's questionnaire.
Oh!
Be gentle.
Go, Captain.
Let's go.
"What's your biggest appeal?"
"Sex appeal."
Well, what you see is what you get.
Fair enough.
Look at me.
Not everybody puts themselves out there like that.
Stop it.
Hey, that's a cute pose.
Oh, really?
I like it.
I'll do it too.
Stop that.
Cute!
You're so cute, Boss!
Let's form a duo.
We can be "Captain Boss."
Don't even think about it!
Sorry.
Stay far away from this girl!
Yikes.
I nearly went over to the dark side.
Need to be more careful.
Your impression of me is...
Yeah?
"Probably eats a lot."
Yep.
"Probably a really good shoulder to cry on."
Indeed.
I see.
I don't eat that much, though.
Well, you look like you do.
I really don't eat that much.
Uh, my bad.
I was thinking of the wrong person.
Don't cross the line!
Sorry.
I'm on the slimmer side, aren't I?
You are, you are.
I just mixed you up with someone else.
This is the average cat build.
You might not have a job tomorrow, Captain.
Only you two come in from now.
Woohoo!
Boss!
C'mon, Boss!
Just kidding.
Hey, Boss?!
She's done for!
She's already dark side.
Hello, we are Boss Captain.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Lastly, Towa.
Yeah!
Okay.
What are you hooked on lately?
Your cat, Toratarou?
Wait, no!
It's Kotarou!
Oh, Kotarou?
Kotarou!
Kotarou, huh?
Sorry.
So, what's this about?
I have a Munchkin.
Oh, a pet cat?
Yeah!
My little Kota at home.
So cute, I could die!
But hey, the boss is a cat too.
So what do you think?
Who's cuter? Boss or your little Kota?
Who's cuter?
Depending on your answer,
Whoa?
you may get a raise.
I might consider it.
You, Boss.
Very good.
Correct Answer
You get 1k an hour.
Seriously?
Woohoo!
Is this how...
Is this how you do things?!
Welp.
You went and said it first.
I don't know what to do now.
I just wanted to try it.
I've always wanted to say that line.
Yeah, me too.
Wait, hang on. What is this?
Your impression of me is "sumo wrestler"?
How could you?
Whoa, whoa, sorry, no!
That's so mean!
I don't look like one at all.
No, no! I-I just...
Apologize!
Like I got hit by lightning.
Bzz!
I-I just made a mistake.
Did your eyes deceive you?
What do you make of her answer, Boss?
Look at how cute I am! And you call me...
a sumo wrestler?!
Wh-What's wrong with you three?!
Is this how you do things?!
Whoo!
The OG
I knew you wanted to do it too!
Wahey!
I'm amazed we managed to stay quiet through it all.
We did it.
I was thinking that too!
Waited for the quote
Like, "Wow, they're all waiting silently."
Real mature. You know what's up.
Thank you.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Okay, so after you go over
the information provided by the customer,
you ask them what's bothering them
and recommend a game to make it go away, like now.
Yay!
Cool!
This time,
let's try solving Subaru's problem.
Okay!
Subaru, what's on your mind?
See, the thing is...
Yeah?
people always make duck soup
out of me and eat me!
That's the sad world we live in!
There are hunters and there is prey.
And I wanna feel like a hunter for once!
Okay, makes sense.
Makes sense.
You seem frustrated.
Oh, yeah, I'm sick of it.
Once we get the request,
think of a game that can
solve that issue and recommend it.
Got it.
In order to prevent buyer's remorse,
every game in this shop is
try-before-you-buy.
Whoa!
To lead by example,
I'll recommend a game to Subaru this time.
My recommendation is...
this:
Monster Hunter Rise!
Hooray!
So, this game.
Play whenever, wherever, and with whoever you want!
The latest entry in the super-popular
hunting action game series, Monster Hunter.
Right.
Move around freely with your Wirebug!
Choose from fourteen weapon types
and hunt monsters,
collect material, craft better gear,
and aim even higher!
What's more, in this game,
you have Silkbind Attacks, performed using Wirebugs
and unique to each of the weapon types,
widening the scope of the action.
Right.
And if you keep landing Silkbinds,
use the environment,
or intrude in a turf war between monsters...
Under these conditions,
you can bind a monster and control it.
It's called Wyvern Riding.
Uh-huh.
You can even use monsters to
engage in monster-on-monster action!
Whoa.
It feels so good, huh?
It's awesome.
Yeah.
And everyone's favorite Palicoes are back,
and they're joined by aggressive buddies
who let hunters ride them
and aid in coordinated attacks, Palamutes.
They're a new addition.
They're so adorable!
Oh, and not to forget...
The monsters to be hunted
feature brand-new ones based on yokai
and all of the popular series regulars.
Wow, yokai?
Yeah. Rise is kind of Japanese-y.
True.
Pretty, actually.
Yeah, that's right.
Whether you're a beginner or a veteran,
go on a hunt with Monster Hunter Rise!
You can try it out here,
so would you like to?
Yeah!
Let's do it!
And that's how you'll recommend a game.
Keep that in mind.
That was amazing.
Awesome!
What a sales pitch, huh?
You know, Subaru-senpai
is basically one of the only ones among us
not to touch Monster Hunter at all.
What?
Subaru: Monster Hunter Beginner
I had no idea.
Why is that?
Well...
It's popular, so I don't wanna.
She's just a hipster.
She's a contrarian.
It's not like that!
But now I can try it.
You were interested, though, right?
Honestly? Yeah.
Oh, that's good, then.
This is your chance.
Let's actually give Monster Hunter Rise a shot now!
Yeah!
Let's do this!
Let's go!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
So now...
Subaru, acting as "customer,"
will play Monster Hunter Rise
right from the opening.
Yay!
Whoo!
👏👏👏
Yay!
New game!
Let's go!
It's happening!
I can't start it.
What button is it?
We have to start there?
Is this gonna work?
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah.
Oh, wow!
You can pick between Type 01 or 02
Character Creation First
Mhm.
to choose your gender.
Oh!
Right, right.
What're you picking, Subaru-chan?
Gotta go swole!
Loves the Swole
Well, that is her goal.
Be careful with those buttons.
Now...
Wait, this is me?
Damn, looks strong!
Choose one.
Oh, the face.
Pop star?
Looks smooth.
Huh...
I really want that specialist hunter vibe, you know?
Right, right.
I'm going with this.
He looks ancient.
An austere base
Yep.
This owns!
And strong.
Very cool.
That's a lot of options!
Create your own unique character!
Yeah, there's a lot.
Anything in particular
you're looking for?
You know,
I want him all wrinkled
but buff as hell.
Of course.
Default skin.
Wow, he's 95.
Whoa.
There's that muscle bar.
Wise old sage.
All right!
He's ripped now.
He sure is.
Hair.
Hairstyles, huh?
Hairstyles?
Hairstyles.
Wow, cute!
Stop it! I'm not doing that!
Might look stronger with longer hair.
Whoa?
It's like wool! Adorbs!
Adorbs...?
Oh, I think you can leave it white.
Swole + austere + afro = adorbs?
Uh...
Looks strong.
It's like he's wearing a wool hat!
It can look like he's blocking
attacks with his wool.
What's that supposed to mean? With his head?
The squishy stuff.
Crazy!
Okay.
Oh, how about facepaint?
Paint?
Oh, you can have facepaint?!
Yeah!
Awesome!
It looks fresh.
Freshly Scarred
Are we sure his brain's not gonna leak out?
This is where Subaru's story begins.
Like, crack. Just happened.
We might see some red here.
Go with that.
This is good.
Look at it!
Right out of Harajuku.
It's perfect.
Oh, the feels!
Man, what a badass.
Incredible.
The clothes are, well...
You'll get armor later.
Yeah, yeah.
So just pick whichever you like.
Wait, diaper?
That's nice.
Diap—
No way!
Looks like a sumo loincloth.
Nice.
Very nice.
Awesome!
Yeah.
I mean it. Seriously awesome.
I know, right?
You can pick a voice too.
Really? Wow.
Heya!
Pick one that's gruff.
Let's have a fun time.
"Let's have a fun time."
You can preview the animations.
Are these the animations?
Yeah.
Wow!
Look at him swing his hair around!
It may fly away, like wool.
I like how it sways.
Looks fluffy.
Very fluffy.
Oh, expressions.
Scary! Is he mad?
He snapped!
Hella Mad
His face snapped in two, too.
😊
Snapp—
😔
He looks sad!
Sad.
😄
Now he's all happy.
He's having fun.
Let him be hype.
He must be living a fun life, huh?
Oh, you need a name now.
A name, huh?
It's gotta be Su...
Subao, maybe?
Suba.
Subao?!
What?
Subageezer.
He will soon be a star
on Fashion Street.
He will lead from the front.
I'm sure he will.
A star is born?!
Folks will run from him.
He's shining!
Whoa!
This is it. The new Palamutes.
Isn't it adorable?
It'll give you rides, Subaru.
Oh, it'll give gramps a ride?
Right. This dog will take gramps.
Cute.
So white!
And the silver jives well with the geezer.
I'll go with this one.
Oh...
By the way, in this game...
Yeah?
You can have cats, dogs, and owls.
And if you're gonna have a cat,
That's a lot.
make the Palico the boss here.
Good idea.
Huh?
Oh boy.
But if one's the boss,
I'd like a captain, too.
Woof!
Boss&Captain Joins the Fray!
Okay, gonna do this.
Woof!
"Captain."
Aww...
Subaru-senpai made me her dog.
Shut up. I know you're happy about it.
Oh, ooh!
Don't berate me like that. It's too much.
Wow, tell me how you really feel.
Hey, I do feel that way.
Scary!
Captain.
Coworker romances aren't banned here.
She's egging us on.
Hell nah.
A romance with Subaru-senpai, huh?
In Captain's Case?!
In Captain's Case!
What a fancy name!
One Unique Name
Too fancy, almost.
I really want to see where this goes.
"In Captain's Case: Another Story."
I'll make this one "In Boss's Case."
Ah, nice.
In Boss's Case...
The Obvious Choice
Oh, no space?
No-space version?
Had to be.
Oh, nice.
He's shining!
So awesome!
Let's get going, then.
He's shining bright.
Let's go.
It's time.
Okay, time to play.
It's habbening!
It's happening!
It begins!
👏👏👏
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Now for the best part of the Monster Hunter series.
Let's work together
and take down a large monster!
Yeah!
Let's go!
It begins!
The quest we'll be attempting
is 1* urgent hub quest, "Dead Ringer."
Our target is Tetranadon.
Everyone's in the hub,
so let's set out!
Let's go!
Yeah!
It begins.
The Hunt Begins!
Here we go.
You all here?
We are.
Wow!
It's one per person, okay?
Subaru-senpai, here you have to
pick up your supplies.
Right.
Okay.
Subaru-senpai, here you have to
pick up your supplies.
Come here,
and pick up this potion
Good idea.
and the rations.
You can have mine.
We have our own!
Leave some for your crew!
Why are you panicking?
What, playing the victim again?
Stop that.
I am not playing the victim!
Nice, you all got yours.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah?
Let's go.
Let's get going.
Let me...
Houshou Marine
Slow down, Captain!
Oh, sorry.
I apologize.
Faster than the boss!
Over here.
I'm just...
Boss!
Boss
Wait, Subageezer. Did you pick up this Spiribird?
I did.
Very good.
Nice, nice.
I picked up some nectar, too.
Oh, you did?
Whoo, this is like a picnic!
Yes, yes.
It's a picnic!
Follow me.
It feels really nice to ride the Palamute.
Yeah!
It's the best.
Picnic Doesn't Last Long
It's coming into view, everyone.
Don't tell me...
Whoa?
Huh? Already? Awesome.
Boss!
This is our target.
Let Subageezer land the first strike, then.
Go, Subaru-senpai.
Are you sure?
Go for it! Attack!
Oozora Subaru
Go, vanguard.
I'm going in!
He's running from real far away!
Subageezer Charges In!
En garde!
She really ran all the way.
Oh!
Eat this!
Yikes.
It knows your face now.
Okay.
There!
Help! Guys, help!
Let's get it.
To the back!
Ow, ow!
Look at 'em go.
Do I press Y here?
Guys!
Aah!
You okay?
You guys!
I'm...
You can press B to dodge, roll, and stuff.
Aah!
Subageezer! No!
Subegeezer Wiped Out In a Flash
That was fast! Gotta be a record.
Guys! Subageezer, he...
Okay, Senpai.
Subageezer, come back!
Okay, Subaru-senpai. From there...
Uh, are you listening?
Uh...
If you press in the, uh, right stick...
Yeah.
You can set a waypoint.
Should I come pick you up?
I'm good.
I can make it there myself.
Really?
Check the map for locations
Of course!
We'll believe you.
We're waiting.
I'll be there soon.
Tokoyami Towa
We may finish the hunt without you.
Yeah, yeah!
Hold it!
Yeah, Subaru-senpai, get here quick.
Hurry up!
Or it'll be too late.
She's not here yet.
What do I do now?
You can do it!
Subageezer Rejoins the Battle!
Go, go, go!
Go!
There you are.
You got a buff, too.
You see...
This hunting horn can apply buffs.
Is that so?
I see.
Its notes will wrap your body up.
Bask in it.
By playing it, you can support your squadmates.
I see.
Okay, how are we looking?
Whoa, whoa!
Watch out!
Dodge!
Dodge it, Subageezer!
Dodge, Subageezer!
Subaru-senpai, use B to evade.
B? Okay.
Subaru-chan, are you using your bugs?
Huh?!
What's that all about?!
Suddenly, "use your bugs!"
Using your bugs?
I'm using the glaive.
Oh, she's just...
using the glaive to beat it to a pulp.
Now! Beat it up!
Now!
This is our chance!
Go!
Now! Pummel it!
Beat it to a pulp now!
Looking good.
Scary!
Hey!
Ah!
It ran, huh?
It ran away.
Are you all here?
Yeah!
Make it quick,
or I'll hunt it myself.
Here I am!
Eep!
Close.
Wrong button.
Dun!
Let's do this.
Let's go.
Ow!
It's down!
Now! Now!
Go, go!
Make it count.
Uh oh, hang on.
You're actually beating it up with your horn?
I am.
The horn's good, you know?
Music is universal.
I'd like to apply some buffs.
Take this!
Looking good.
And this!
Nice, we're really pummeling it.
But, hey, couldn't Insect Glaive
fly around and stuff?
It can, yeah.
Got it!
Fly, Subaru!
Did you?
Subaru-senpai...
Hold ZR and press X.
ZR!
Oh, nice!
Gonna hit it with a good one.
Let's keep going.
You're getting the hang of it.
This is it.
Uh oh, it's raging.
Keep going.
Oh?
It ran away!
Sure did.
You're not getting away!
Uh, did two of you go the wrong way?
Huh?
You're right.
Marine?!
Okay.
Wyvern Riding! Nice, Captain!
Hup. Now, then...
Wyvern Ride that monster
Hmm... What's a good place?
Whoa, awesome!
Go!
You're riding it!
One, two, one, two,
bam!
Cool!
Nice.
One, two, one, two...
Very cool.
It ended!
I wanted to do that thrice.
Let's go.
You can do that thrice?
It'd hard, but you can.
That's great.
Hmm...
Whoa!
Oh, that was good.
Wait, Insect Glaive can double jump?
Go, go, go, go!
It's a hard weapon to use at the start.
Until you get used to it.
Yeah!
Oh, yikes.
Oh, it bloated.
You need to observe the monster's moves.
Well...
It's about time to finish this!
Yeah.
Whey!
There.
Whoa!
Not good.
It's almost done.
Oh, it ran.
There it goes.
Hold on, can I heal up?
Sure.
Yeah!
Do you want to join me?
Oh, sure.
Not coming?
Me too.
You're good?
Got it.
Heading over there.
Coming.
There's Subageezer.
Here I am.
You all seem fine, though.
Here I go.
Okay.
Got it.
Thanks, Vigorwasp!
Healing!
Together!
That hits the spot.
Really does.
You see the monster face on the map?
Yeah.
You see the blue, uh...
The blue and the tired face?
Yeah.
That means it's totally beat.
Wait, does the monster heal this way?
A little, but not a lot.
Seems like it recovers a little if it eats.
I see.
Some even sleep.
This one might be sleeping, actually.
Really?
Is it sleeping?
Wake it up!
It's asleep.
It's asleep!
Sleeping Tetranadon ZZZ
Go for it, Subaru-senpai.
Wait, I'm still walking my dog. Hold on.
Get off.
Do it!
Here I go!
Show it what Insect Glaive can do!
Wake up!
You're just hitting it?
Musclebrain Subageezer wakes it up with a smack
Use your damn bugs!
Use your bugs!
She never did.
You don't know how to, huh?
Yeah, I don't.
Right.
I don't know how to get off.
Boss!
You see, the captain...
I don't really get this controller.
Did she just call herself the captain?
She did! Her brain fried!
Wait, which is the real one?
Wait...
Did we switch places?
Like hell you did!
Did we switch—
We did it!
Yay!
Nicely done!
Your first hunt...
Congrats on finishing your first hunt!
Subageezer's First Hunt!
Congratulations!
Hooray!
So, what did you think of your first hunt?
At first...
Yeah?
I was like, "Is this gonna work?"
Figures.
But it's a game where you work together to hunt,
so I really enjoyed the sense of pride and accomplishment!
Oh, nice.
Yeah, that's exactly it.
Like...
It was fun learning on the go, too.
Glad to hear it.
You really loved it, huh?
Happy Subaru
I did, I did.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Lastly, we ask the customer for the results.
This time, Subaru wanted to feel strong.
Yeah.
That was the issue.
Did we manage to make it go away?
Tell us how you're feeling, on a weather scale!
Weather?!
Stormy
Rain
Cloudy
Clear
Rising Sun!
Here we go!
Your answer, please!
Ready?
Three, two, one!
Rising...
Rising Sun!
Sun!
What was that?
That's what I wanna know.
Rising sun?
You got all hype by yourself.
Hold up. It's not like that.
R-Rising...
Look at you.
You might have to do it next week, you know?!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
And that's it for your training.
How do you feel?
Think you're up for this job?
Subaru!
Okay!
At first, I didn't know if this trio would work,
but I hope we can build our teamwork
and do our best!
Nice.
Yay!
Marine?
Well, I, uh... don't know about the "Rising Sun" bit,
but other than that,
Just that?
everything else was Rising Sun!
Towa!
This was my first shift,
and I was too nervous to talk properly,
so I want to try harder from next time!
Who?
Huh? I was sure we'd see it now.
Damn, I got my hopes up.
Suddenly Asking for the Impossible
Rising Sun!
Gah! Too soon!
Too soon!
Way too soon!
That was traumatic.
I went all "gah"!
What was that?
Do your best from now on to
make this the #1 game shop in the biz!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Okay, so as we wrap up,
Viewer Consulting Segment
we'll be running a mini-segment
where we solve the viewers' issues for them.
Oh!
Whoo!
Mini-segment!
However, we haven't received any yet,
so I asked my friends.
Who is it?
"I find it hard to play the comic in front of people.
I find it hard to play the comic in front of people.
How do I fix this?
How do I fix this?"
From Okarina-san of Okazu Club.
I find it hard to play the comic in front of people.
How do I fix this?
Okarina (Okazu Club)
What?!
Why?
It's a mystery.
That surprised me in more ways than one.
The Most Unexpected Person
Why Okarina-san?
This settles it.
She totally knows her, doesn't she?
Our boss really is...
really...
"Friend," she says.
This is all I have to say:
Yeah?
Harden your heart!
Boss's Answer: Harden your heart!
That's tough!
Real tough!
So, yeah, Okarina-san,
good luck.
Do your best!
Jingle!
Jangle!
Jingle-Jangle