Cardboard boxes arrived at our doorsteps outta nowhere.
OUCH!
*BZZZ*
Whoa!
That's lewd!
*BZZZ*
Is it a lewd device?
IT'S NOT A LEWD DEVICE AT ALL!
Pay attention to their reactions!
What's inside the
black boxes
they received?
What's inside~?
Uh, I'm hololive's mysterious fox,
Shirakami Fubuki!
Noon-nui!
I'm hololive's mysterious half-elf.
Thanks for having me!
Thanks for coming!
I'm hololive's sheep of many mysteries,
Tsunomaki Watame!
Are you really full of mysteries?
Don't say that!
Cardboard boxes arrived
at our doorsteps outta nowhere.
Yeah, they did.
And we were like, "What are these?"
Mysterious packages arrived at your doorsteps.
This time, we want you to guess
what's in the others' boxes
by playing a word association game!
I, the chairman of the
international black box deliberation committee,
will be scoring you, uh...
So in other words...
She's the chairman this time, huh.
...fair and impartially,
so let's have a fair competition!
Will she drill it home?
Tsunomaki Watame steps up!
What's in the black box? Challenge
starts now!
Hi-yah!
Ooh! That's a nice sound.
She's going hard at it!
Nice acoustics.
That's a high score for artistry.
That's a really nice sound.
What is it?
I can open this, right?
Yup!
Wh-What is it?
It's rattling a lot.
It sure is.
Opened it!
What's inside?
This is...
"This is..."?
This is... uh...
Please give the others information like
the item's color, shape, size, and so on.
Info, please!
What's it like?
It's odorless.
Odorless.
It has no smell. Got it.
That's good.
It's black, but...
It's black, but?
It's... oh!
It's actually easy to grip!
It's easy to grip. Okay.
Easy to grip. All right.
That's a pretty good hint.
Easy to grip?
I got it!
It's a rice ball.
It's...
Well, they ARE easy to grip.
It's not a rice ball.
Let's check how comfy they are to use.
Oh!
The comfortability, huh?
Comfortability?
Yeah.
Comfortability...?
There's a spot I can press.
OW! OUCH! YIKES!
Huh?
What?
Ah! Are you okay, Watame-san?
Huh?
What?
Did someone just zap me...?
Huh?
What?!
Did someone just zap me?
That's...
It zaps you?!
It's one of those zapper thingies?
There's a spot I can press.
*Click*
Here. I'm pressing it.
Ah. That sound.
*Click*
What the heck IS that?!
I'll press it, okay?
That's a nice sound.
*BZZ*
Ow, ow, ow!
*Huff*
So Watame-san was sacrificed
Wait, what's it...
What's it called again?
for the sake of the hint.
What IS that thing?
My thumb's numb!
This is normally a writing tool.
Oh! Okay!
What?!
It's one of those pen-shaped buzzer toys
that you use for pranks!
You're correct!
Oh, I actually got it right!
That's the correct answer!
So that's what it was!
This just shows how much
the staff members want to eat me!
That's undeniable.
So these—
So these kinds of items
could be in the box too?!
That's scary!
I'm starting to get scared now!
It really is!
Well then, who's going next?
What do we do...?
Okay, I'll go next.
Oh!
Flare!
Crazy things in the box?!
Shiranui Flare charges ahead!
What's in the black box? Challenge
starts now!
It's amazingly small.
It's small?
Got it.
It's about the size of my palm.
I won't know what it is 'til I open it, though.
Ah!
I know what it is now.
Oh! Okay.
What is it?
It works differently from how it feels, right?
This...
This can be spun around.
You can spin it in multiple directions.
Huh?
Uh-huh.
That's quite a hint.
I'VE GOT IT!
Oh?
WHAT?!
Go ahead, Fubuki-san!
It's a Rubik's Cube!
That's freaking fast!
Is that the correct answer?
It is!
All right!
That was fast!
That's REALLY fast!
This just proves how well I know Flare!
I know you too well!
You just love me way too much, don't you?
Since Fubuki got it immediately,
Flare gets one more try!
What's in the black box?
Round 2, begin!
LET'S GO!
Oh.
Phew, she's going hard at it!
Ooh, opened in one go!
She unboxed it in one go.
What's inside?
Aaah...
So? What is it?
Ah.
What is it?
It's like, uh...
It's sorta like a suction cup.
A suction cup?!
A suction cup...?
You attach this somewhere
and pull it with a "Plop!"
Ah. Right.
What?
Are you happy you got it, Flare-san?
Just for the record.
Not at all.
But if I had to say,
it feels like it'd be convenient
if you had one of these lying around.
It's convenient?
Wait, this is brand new, right?
Um... probably.
I was thinking of sticking it on somewhere
and letting you girls hear the sound it makes, but...
It's probably...
Uh...
I definitely don't wanna do that
if it isn't brand new.
That's also a hint.
I can't tell at all.
You'd hate it if it's not brand new.
Just for the sake of it,
I'll stick it on something now.
*Ploop*
That's how it sounds.
Plop, schuck, yoink!
It's something you attach, right?
Is it one of those S-shaped
suction cup hangers?
An S-shaped suction cup hanger's...
Nope.
the wrong answer, yeah.
By the way, it reeks.
It does reek, doesn't it?
It smells?
Does it have that rubber smell?
Do you have any hints on its shape and such?
The tip is round.
It's kind of a big round circle.
Uh-huh.
It's also got a handle attached.
You don't stick this onto walls.
Yeah. You probably don't stick it onto walls.
What?!
At least conventionally speaking.
You use it when something's stuck.
Ah.
Yeah.
Ah!
Oh?
It's a... plunger?
OH!
That's correct!
IT'S A PLUNGER?!
That's what it's called?!
But that IS true.
You'd hate getting a used one.
You definitely wouldn't want a used one.
I seriously wondered what the heck was up
when I had a plunger delivered to my house.
Well then...
Yeah.
Oh!
You're last, Fubuki-san. Let's get to it!
It's finally time!
Crazy things in the box?!
Shirakami Fubuki leaps right to it!
What's in the black box? Challenge
starts... now!
Okay!
Let's first get rid of the wrapping...
It's kinda tough to open this box.
Oh.
Ah! Opened it.
Ah, you got it open?
The box is—
HAH!
She just laughed.
I'd never—
I'd never use this at all!
What should I even use this on?!
That means it's useless to her.
What IS it?
Wait. How do I use...
*BZZZ*
AH!
I SWITCHED IT ON BY ACCIDENT!
*BZZZ*
Huh?
So, like...
*BZZZ*
That's a sound that brings a lot to the imagination.
Wait, hold up.
So she doesn't know how to use it.
How did I do that just now?
Is it a lewd device?
Yeah, it could be. Good thing we can't see it.
A lewd device?
IT'S NOT A LEWD DEVICE AT ALL!
Wait, what?
It goes "Brrr" and "Vrrrr"
but I've definitely never used this before!
That's true.
What kind of person would use it?
What kind?
This is something an old man would use...
Ah...
I got it!
I know what it is!
It's an electric shaver.
Oh!
Is that the correct answer?
Or could it be
that it's not...
an electric shaver at all?
It is!
Yeah!
Heck yeah!
It's an electric shaver!
You're right!
Fubuki-san, if you flip that switch up top...
Oh!
Is this the part that moves?
Hold on.
It's cute that she doesn't know how it works.
She's confused as to how it works.
OH, GOT IT!
IT'S WORKING!
You did it!
IT'S BUZZING!
But the sound it makes is lewd!
Whoa!
That's lewd!
Time for the results!
The first queen
of the black box challenge is...
🥁🥁🥁
Fubuki-san!
Congratulations!
Black Box Queen
Shirakami Fubuki
Yaaay!
BRR
Using it for sound effects is...
BRBRBRBRBRBRBRBRBR!
She's going wild from the excitement.
As I thought, you were able to guess quickly
and you were also able to convey
what your item was accurately!
I've learned that all the men in the world
use this to shave their beards in the morning.
You've learned how it feels like for them, haven't you?
I sure did!
With that said, it seems like
you have an announcement for us, Fubuki-san?
This video's... ah.
This'll go live on October 4th, right?
Yes, this'll go live on October 4th!
Which means... tomorrow, October 5th,
is, uh... actually...
What?
the date of my birthday concert!
Shirakami Fubuki's
Birthday Concert!
Oh!
Congratulations!
Yaaay!
And these two stooges over here
#TheStooges
will also be joining my concert as guests!
Say whaaat?
HEY! YOU TWO!
IT'S TOMORROW!
It's gonna be sorta like,
"Finally the Three Stooges are performing together!"
Shirakami Fubuki's Birthday Concert
Live on October 5th (Tuesday)!!
Wait, what?
Yup!
Yeah. We're finally going to perform as a group!
I'll be counting on these two!
To all the viewers who enjoyed the video,
please like & subscribe to
the official hololive channel!
And please subscribe to
our guests' channels as well!
Please do!
And to our first-ever Black Box Queen, Fubuki-san!
Can we have one last word from you before we finish?
BRRRRR
You really like that, don't you?
BRR
BRBRBRBRBRR
BZZZZ
It's fun.
It's a lot of fun.
BRRR
BRRRR
BZZZZ
BZZ
BZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZZ