Nene-chan, you're trash!
Aqua-senpai, you're a big dumb dummy!
What?!
Battleground of Words!
Debate Battle!
Yaaay!
A debate is a formal discussion
on a particular topic in which
opposing arguments are put forward.
It requires logical thinking and
influential conversational skills,
which means this is a legit program
in which you can hone your skills as a streamer.
'Sup! I'm hololive 2nd Gen's Oozora Subaru!
Debates are nothing to me.
They say my IQ's 500 million, after all,
so this'll be a cinch.
Can you tell us who "they" are?
Me.
A-quality day to one and all!
I'm Minato Aqua!
A debate is that thing where you talk, right?
I've heard of it before. I'll do my best.
Yaaay! 'Sup groupies!
I'm hololive 4th Gen's Tokoyami Towa-sama!
Let's party!
"Let's party."
I'll use my lingual finesse to
blow your minds today! Yaaay!
You sound really dumb! Yaaay!
I'm hololive 5th Gen's
Orange Ranger, Momosuzu Nene!
Yay! Yay! Bounce! Bounce! BRRRRRR!
There's an extrovert in the mix.
We'll be having team matches
with the Subaru and Aqua team
versus the Towa and Nene team
in the debates today!
Seriously?!
I came here today to let Subaru carry me.
I'm counting on you.
What the hell are you here for then?!
Don't say that!
We might be the ultimate team.
In your dreams! Come back to reality!
Give it to 'em, Nene!
Swoosh! Whoosh! Schwing! Shiiing!
We're taking this W, you good-for-nothings!
They're so scary...
Is it just me or does it
smell like teen spirit in here?
Without further ado, let's start the debate!
I, Friend A, will be judging the battles.
This is the first topic:
Which is stronger? The elbow or the knee?
Ooh!
Oh, I see.
Elbow vs. knee: Which one is stronger?
Team Aqua-san and Subaru-san
will argue for the elbow.
And Team Towa-san and Nene-san
will argue for the knee.
I can see victory ahead.
Really?
Aqu-tan, do you see something?
I see.
Yeah, I do. Yep.
You're not really convincing me here!
I'm a little bit interested in what she sees.
Now, let's start the debate battle! Go!
The debate is on!
I think that the elbow is stronger.
There are more ways to attack
using the elbow than with using the knee.
With the elbow, you can just jam it
directly into the stomach,
and of course, it's also powerful
when applied directly to the face.
We've jumped into
the deep end right off the bat.
Whereas with the knee, it's a lot
of trouble to reach someone's face.
Nice!
Nene! Tell 'em why the knee is strong!
Umm...
You're directing Nene like a Pokémon...?
Uh...
You see, the knee...
It's strong cuz it's got a cap on it!
You're trying to explain that
it's physically strong, right?
Also, we're able to move around
because of our knees!
They're why we can walk!
They're how we're able to move forward!
Towa-chan, you said we couldn't stand
without elbows and stuff.
Rebuttal!
Towa-chan, you said we couldn't stand
without e̶l̶b̶o̶w̶s̶ and stuff.
knees
But if we lived in a world where
doing the army crawl was standard,
we'd need elbows more than knees!
Rebuttal!
There's something that everyone has to do
before they walk on two legs, right?
Crawling on all fours!
And you can't do that without using your knees!
Rebuttal!
But before you crawl on all fours,
you crawl with just your elbows!
This debate is supposed to be about which
is stronger, not which is more necessary.
Then how do we measure strength in this case?
I say we should use these two points:
Number of techniques and physical strength!
Oh, also that thing where you say "need" ten times
and then ask them to spell knee...
Aqu-tan, just be quiet for now, would you!
I guess it's time to bring out
the ace up my sleeve.
What?
Knee and elbow.
Please look at their hiragana lettering.
Ace?
For knee, the "za" in "hiza" is
the first character in the "sa"-column.
Oh, here she goes!
And for elbow, the "ji" in "hiji" is in second place!
That means the knee is stronger!
HiZA! The "za" part is stronger!
The "ji" in HiJI is strong, too!
How does that tell strength?!
Ji!
Jii!
Ji jii!
Za!
Okay, well, that was certainly heated, I guess?
I'd like to give both teams the chance
to make a closing statement.
Each team, please choose a representative
to give your final remarks.
Okay, Team Elbow's representative, go ahead.
On the merits of flexibility, strength,
and variety of techniques,
the elbow stands alone at the top
as the strongest!
Interesting. Thank you!
I rest my case.
Brilliant!
Yay, Aqu-tan!
And now, Team Knee.
Let's hear your final remarks.
Nene! Go! Nene!
Senpai, go! Senpai!
Nene, go!
Nobody's gonna say anything?
The knee, well...
it's physically larger than the elbow.
And it's got the first character
in the "sa"-column of hiragana!
Knee \ˈnē \ (n.)
The joint which connects the upper leg to the lower leg.
It is listed before elbow in the Japanese dictionary.
So if you look them up in a Japanese dictionary,
the knee is listed first!
It's strong!
The debate is over!
I, Friend A, will now decide
which argument was more compelling
and announce the winning team!
Okay!
The winning team is...
Team Subaru-san and Aqua-san!
Congratulations!
Elbow wins!
Elbow for the win!
Why did we win?
When Subaru-san said you have to crawl
on your elbows before crawling on all fours,
I thought, "She's right!"
Debate Battle
Round Two
And now on to the next topic.
All right!
Okay!
Aliens vs. ghosts!
If they fought, who would win?
Aliens vs. ghosts: if they fought, who would win?
Team Aqua-san and Subaru-san
will argue for aliens.
Aliens!
Oh, geez.
And Team Towa-san and Nene-san
will argue for ghosts.
Let's start the debate battle! Go!
The debate is on!
I mean, ghosts were originally just humans.
True.
In other words,
if an alien fights a former human,
then I think the alien is
going to come out on top.
I see.
That's true.
Towa-senpai, let me handle this one.
Sure! Go for it!
Ghosts are well-known
for being transparent, right?
If an alien tries to jab 'em with a left,
their fist would just pass right through
and do no damage.
So the ghost can win just by standing there.
Just like Nenene says,
if you try to fight a ghost
that's transparent and has no body...
Isn't that pretty much a nonstarter?
Okay, but!
Just a moment.
I just uncovered the truth.
What is it?
Ghosts can be exorcised.
That's right! You're totally right!
They can't even win against humans!
Preach!
Tee hee hee hee!
What have you guys been doing
in horror games all this time?
Tee hee hee hee!
If I may for a second.
You know,
I'm originally from another planet
called Planet Taotao.
Which means I'm an alien!
Now that you mention it!
So from an alien's point of view,
all of you people are aliens to me!
And do you all like ghosts?
What are you talking about?
If you're going to label us as aliens,
we know how to fight back against ghosts,
so that makes the alien the winner, doesn't it?
Wait...
So we win, right?
what?
Huh?
Well, if the fight was in a place with
no oxygen, the ghost would win!
Aliens come from a place
without oxygen already.
Ah!
Uh-oh!
Ahh!
Shut your trap already!
Okay! Time's up!
And we'll have our closing statements now.
A word from
the Team Alien representative, please.
Say something!
Who, me?!
Tee
hee
hee!
It's been me this whole time!
You say something, Aqu-tan!
Umm...
Just try!
Nene-chan, you're trash!
What the heck!
We were about to win!
Are you trying to throw this?!
Team Ghost, what's your response?
Don't let her get away with
calling you trash! Fight back!
What?!
Aqua-senpai, you're a big dumb dummy!
The debate is over!
I, Friend A, will now decide
which argument was more compelling
and announce the winning team!
The winning team is...
It's a draw!
What?!
Neither team wins!
But the alien side did better!
I was going to call it for the aliens at the end,
but then Aqua-san opened her mouth!
You can't do that!
Aqu-tan!
I thought that was it,
but then Nene-san and Towa-san fired back!
What were you thinking! You can't do that!
Well...
Towa-senpai told me to fight back,
so I think this is her fault...
That's some top-class scapegoating!
It sure is.
I was backing you up
this whole damn time!
Make sure you all play nicely together!
Please subscribe to the hololive production channel
and today's participants' channels below!