I've had it, Ruud Gullit!
Let me out! Let me outta here!
All I did was go after a genmate a little...
Need to find a way out.
Don't even bother.
Who are you?!
I'm the Pro of Prison Breaks.
Th-The pro of prison breaks?!
Likes Red
Omaru Polka
Look.
There's a ferocious Cerberus
keeping watch over the inmates 'ere.
You're done for if it gets to ya.
Don't get any funny ideas.
Just serve yer sentence.
Wait, if you're such a pro,
why are you still here?
...
The guard's too cute.
You like it?!
Food! That's right!
We can distract the guard with food and run away!
That's not gonna work, sister.
Why? It's our best shot!
The server's too cute.
I bwought your food.
Some pro you are!
What's with the alarm?!
Someone must've tried to escape.
Probably failed, though.
Grawr! Let me out!
What's gonna happen to her?
Torture by Cerberus awaits.
Torture...
Gonna have to listen to her chat all night.
Wow.
Now's our chance! Run for it, pro!
Roger!
And so we ran,
seeking the light of freedom!
That's when we finished this song.
Please enjoy.
This will be on the exam.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!