Let's play catch, Matsuri-chan.
Huh? Catch-as-catch-can Figure Plus Leg Lock?!
Did you even try to catch what I said?
Look what I found in the storage.
Oh, you wanna play catch?
Be clear, Hoshimachi.
Huh? Why am I being criticized here?
Here's your glove.
Got it.
And the ball?
Here.
That's a boulder, Hoshimachi.
How can you pick that up?
Hello.
What's with the gloves?
Figured we could play catch.
Oh? And the ball?
*point*
Okay, and the ball?!
Up we go.
Catch!
Eep!
Calm down, Hoshimachi!
Let's play something fun!
I've got cards!
But Old Maid blew up the office recently.
This game of catch is just as risky!
Hell, it ain't even catch!
You know what the two most important things in life are?
Consistent hard work.
Trustworthy friends.
And the risk of losing it all.
Damn, Sui-chan, who hurt you?
Hello, everyone!
Uh, what's going on?
Rushia! Come play cards with us!
Please!
That's some peer pressure.
Okay, be right... flair!
Rushia!
Owwie... I can't move!
We're all tangled up.
…
Catch-as-catch-can Figure Plus Leg Lock!
Excellent job!
How did she even bring that boulder in?
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!