Towa is not your puppet!
What is that?
Drawing...
Huh?
Wait a―!
W-W-W-W-Wai―Hold up!
Moving on to the next segment!
Here it is!
The Slick Comeback Championship!
This segment is brought to you
by yours truly, Yukihana Lamy.
Rules
In this segment, you're given
a mundane-yet-unexpected situation,
Ex.: I broke a plate...!
and you have to guess how I,
Yukihana Lamy, would make a comeback!
Q: How would I make a comeback?
A: I'd go on a date to buy new plates!
Sure.
And Towa-senpai, Flare-senpai,
Guess How Lamy Would Make a Comeback!
"Let's go buy new plates together!"
"Looks like we have an excuse
to go on a date tomorrow!"
and the viewers will guess the correct answer.
Correct!
Got it!
The next situation is as follows.
You're about to pay at the cashier
but you realize you don't have enough cash!
Oh, I got this!
This happened to me once!
I've done this before, for real!
What'd you do then?
I left.
Why did you―
I said I don't have the money and left.
Hmm, okay.
Can...
Can an answer be too normal?
That depends on whether or not
I give a normal answer.
That's fair.
So, am I supposed to guess, like,
what you would do if you saw me, for example,
without enough cash to check out?
Is that right?
Yes!
Yeah, that's it.
That's exactly it.
You know, this feels like
The Improvised Comeback Championship
one of those improv segments.
Yes, it is.
If I wrote something normal,
people would go, "well, duh."
Give the people what they want.
Well, you know what?
I ain't gonna play along!
Towa is not your puppet!
I'm good!
Has everyone finished?
In this answer, I have become you.
Oh?
Here are their answers!
Oohh!
Hm, hm...
Let's look at each one.
"Lend them money!"
"Quickly tap your card to pay."
Ah―
Tap in quickly to pay...?
Like you whoosh it on the card reader?
"Ah! Please wait a moment!"
"I might have some money," then you let it go beep.
That's what I think you'd do.
Oh!
Ohh!
I get it now!
Beep, beep!
Without saying a word!
Yep.
Like a smooth wingman, huh?
Yes.
That's our mama!
Umm.
We'd be like, "Thank you, mama!"
Mm, okay...
Ma―
Mama doesn't seem very convinced...
And you, Towa-senpai?
I would simply just lend them money.
Oh, so you'd lend them money,
not give it to them.
That's―
You're being responsible, huh.
No giving!
I'm too poor for that!
Uhm, well, let's look at my answer, then.
Here is my answer!
"Hey, you dropped this."
Look at this stud!
But it's only 100 yen!
That's just an example!
Paying for them might make them feel bad,
so I'd go up to them and be like,
"Flare-senpai, you dropped this."
Ooohh!
But wait,
isn't that a pretty cool move?
It is!
Is it a slick comeback?
Is it?
I guess...
What's with that reaction?!
Towa-chan's answer is probably
the least cool one of them all.
This isn't a "Cool Moves" Championship!
Ahahaha!
"Slick Comeback" Championship, okay?!
In terms of accuracy,
I think Flare-senpai's answer comes the closest.
Yeah.
I guess elves are just
naturally considerate.
Ahh...
I see.
Wait, what?
What did you say?
Sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
I just ran my mouth.
Sowwie.
I'm sowie!
Okay.
It's Towa-senpai's
See Through Her Devilish Deeds!
Oooh!
Please introduce the segment, Towa-senpai!
Aye! In this segment,
given an everyday situation
where a prank can be played,
Rules
Ex.: Giving a present to a friend.
you can try to guess
what kind of devilish deed
A: Gift them with a jack-in-the-box!
I would do!
Gift them with
a jack-in-the-box!
Lamy-chan, Flare-senpai,
Correct!
and of course, the viewers
will guess the answer!
Next situation.
A friend walking in front of you
has their backpack open!
Huh?
What kind of pwank would I do?
Do?
Would I?
I got it!
Huh?
How open is it?
Like, really wide?
Yep.
Really wide open.
This is super devilish.
I'm also devilish.
Or rather, I'm...
a devil.
I'm a devil.
(laughs)
Wh―
Why are you trying to convince yourself?
I'm a devil!
Both of you are total softies,
so I don't think I would learn much
from your answers.
I'd like to see some thought put into this.
Ahhh!
I'm actually feeling pretty devilish here.
Really?
I'm ready!
Okay!
Let's start from Lamy-chan.
Uhm―Sure, okay.
Lamy-chan, if you will.
Very well...
What is that?
Well,
a backpack is open right in front of you.
Yeah?
Are they sticking their head in?
So you'll charge in from―
Sure that's not a 100 yen coin?
It isn't!
That's definitely a 100―
Or is it a bottle cap?
No, no.
You stuff your head inside,
That's huge.
and go, "RATATATATATA"
inside it.
Huh?
Mmm, 'kay.
Towa-sama's Devilish Deed
Ignore her junior.
Let's look at Flare-senpai's answer.
So, uhh,
I'll give the backpack cords
a good pull back!
Give it a tight closing, before saying,
"Your bag's open!"
in their face.
Oh, I see it now!
You grab the cord and give it a heavy tug!
Ahh!
Devilish, isn't it?
It really is!
That's really good!
I like how you think!
Really?
Yeah, I love it!
Wait, how...
How's mine, Towa-sama?
That's a bottle cap, right?
It's a bottle cap with a cord for some reason?
That's...
The one they dropped?
This bag closes with a zipper.
Is that the zipper tab?
No, that's actually
the backpack's lid dangling down.
The lid...
is a bit small.
Come on! That's nitpicking!
Agh...
Don't sweat the details!
We care about the small details!
What's Towa-senpai's answer?
This is my answer!
Ta-da.
Sneak a clown doll in before telling them,
"Your bag is open."
That's creepy!
That's cute!
Isn't it scary?
It's creepy!
They'll go, "Oh, it is?"
That's way too creepy!
Then they look in the bag and
find the clown doll in there.
That's
sca―
cre―
creepy.
It works, right?!
Fear me!
Why are you walking around
with a clown doll, anyway?
Umm, that's, I'm not actually...
Well, uhh,
I buy it.
You buy it.
Although, the way Towa-chan puts it―
Yeah?
You'll just be met with,
"You prankster!"
"Come here, you!"
That's cute!
It's adorable!
Oh, geez!
Today's not my day, huh?!
These two are a pain!
Save me!
Now, here is our next segment!
Sketches Speak as Loud as Words?!
This segment is brought to us by Flare-senpai!
Flare-senpai, please introduce it!
Sure!
Okay!
In this segment,
Rules
you'll be given a situation
Secret Situation
Please draw
"Shiranui Flare singing"!
that I need to figure out as you draw it!
The faster I get it right, the better!
Okay!
Towa-chan, Lamy-chan, and of course,
Thinking...
all the viewers can participate!
Me singing!
Got it!
Now then, since I'll be
doing the guessing, I'll have you two
check on what the answer is.
The audience and I will guess the correct answer!
Let's go!
I've looked at the answer!
Okay.
I don't know what that answer is.
Good luck to us!
Drawing...
I wonder what it is...
It's definitely me.
It's me!
Wait, it's not me.
Kintsuba!
This is Kintsuba. Definitely Kintsuba.
Hehehehehe...
Hmm...
Sticky, sticky...
Kintsuba with a small mustache.
Ah.
It might be Noel.
An extra-large beef bowl being eaten
by Noel.
Huh?
Wait a―!
W-W-W-W-Wai―Hold up!
They cleared before the sketches
could even begin to speak.
What?
Hold on!
Wait! Wait a sec!
Huh?
Man...
Who thought...
This is, uh...
Really?
Ahahahaha!
That was a super play.
Commander Noel eating a beef bowl
I should have expected this...
Is this real?
Seriously?
NoeFla, Destroyer of Games
I guess I get one point this round.
There's text written on yours!
I thought it was fine.
But it wasn't!
Aha.
Writing "glob glob" does get it across.
This is a bit...
This is expected.
She's my wife, after all.
So of course I would get it.
Smooth!
I didn't even need to see―
No, really! I didn't cheat!
The one on my end...
You cheated!
...was just―
My panel just had
question marks on it.
You saw it, didn't you?!
I'm serious!
Haha!
We were shown the strength of your bonds.
Goes to show just how much
Noel keeps talking about beef bowls.
Amazing!
That was absolutely incredible!
BONUS
To...
Towa...!
Towa-chama... I...!
I will protect you...!
Gross.
W-W-Wait―
Say this.
You'll love me even more.
Now, whisper it!
Disgusting.
Seriously.
I broke into a cold sweat.
I heard about it.
You like cool voices, Towa-chan?
I do.
Did you always see me that way?
You okay today?
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub channel on NicoNico for the full stream archives!
Y-You guys...
Who are you?!
Bring out your wallets and show me the money!
You―
You sound really old.