Moonlight Merry-Go-Round
Candy-Go-Round
Ready-Go-“Live”
Let's take you there
yume no youna
at the speed
supiido de
of dreams
esukooto
hololive IDOL PROJECT - Candy-Go-Round
Lyrics: Aiko Takase
Composition: Devin Kinoshita
Arrangement: Taishi Kawai (Arte Refact)
Vocals: Minato Aqua, Shiranui Flare,
Aki Rosenthal, Yozora Mel, Roboco-san
Time always flows so slowly
toki no nagare wa itsu demo yukkuri
Yet the heart moves at its own warp speed
dakedo haato no ugoku supiido kimagure waapu
Make it loud and clear, let your sound reach us here
kikasete yo kono basho e chanto todoku youni
Let's hear your clap-clap-clap
kimi no Clap-Clap-Clap
(Everybody Clap Hands Up)
and drive to fantasy★
kuusou e doraibu★
Moonlight Merry-Go-Round Candy-Go-Round
Ready-Go-“Live”! Let's take flight at the speed of dreams
Ready-Go-“Live” yume no youna supiido de tobitatou
We'll march there to the beat of our song
uta ni norikomeba ikeru n da
There's no stopping this timeslip now
taimu surippu mou tomerarenai
Starlight Merry-Go-Round Candy-Go-Round
In a parallel world, when the night bell rings
to signal a new beginning,
Parallel-World hajimari no beru ga narihibiku yoru ni
we'll come pick you up
mukae ni iku kara
We'll vibe to the same beat, hum the same melody,
onaji biito de hitotsu no nanbaa
and come together in song
kanadeyou