Roboco-senpai learns so fast.
She's seriously impressive.
That strong, sturdy body.
Now that's what I call a pirate!
Marine, aren't you going to root for me?!
Roboco-senpai!
Lose already!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Damn, we're not getting any customers!
We sure aren't...
There's nothing to do...
This is so boring...
Since there's nothing to do, want to play Charades?
Yeah!
Are you sure we should be doing this?!
No one's coming anyways!
Stuff summer reminds you of!
Charades
Topic: Things that are summer-y!
I'll start!
Okay.
Charades
Topic: Things
that are summer-y
What?
Boss is too small for me to figure out what she's doing...
Boss moves so little!
What?
Suck, suck, suck...
Ah, I got it!
Huh?
What was it?
Okay, Captain Marine!
Yeah!
Mosquito!
Correct!
All right!
I don't see it!
Correct answer:
Mosquito
No summer goes by without 'em!
The bonds of the Boss Captain duo!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Ah! Someone's here!
We finally have a customer!
Welcome!
Welcome! Welcome!
Can we get your name?
Sure!
Hello-robo! It's your high-spec virtual robot
from hololive Gen 0, Roboco!
Yaaay!
The airhead!
Today's guest:
Roboco San
Airhead?!
I'm not an airhead!
I pissed her off.
Don't suddenly insult her.
You'll see soon enough how clumsy she is.
Hey!
I actually have a finishing move.
What did you say?!
My greeting is actually "Hello-robo,"
but if I say the "bo" part strongly, it becomes...
*inhale*
Hello-
BOOO!
Thoughts?
Wait, what's with this mood?
I don't understand you anymore!
Roboco-senpai...
Retorting
Frozen
Disappointed
You weren't like this three years ago, Roboco-senpai!
Today's guest is someone I know well, Roboco-san.
Roboco San
Favorite game genre: FPS/TPS
Most attractive features:
Efficiently free-spirited (and sometimes airheaded)
MENT
LUCK
Well, she probably isn't worried about much...
...is what I thought, but she apparently has one?
I want to know.
Why is your luck only 1 star?
Right.
It is!
Even in games,
when it comes down to chance, I...
crash and burn...
Like in those games
Been getting min-pulls lately...
that you have to pull in.
But your MENT's 3 stars, so you're hanging in there.
Perfectly balanced, as all things should be.
She's holding in there.
Your DEX and SPD are pretty good, though.
Confident in her dexterity and speed!
Yeah!
Nice.
They're really good!
So, what brought you here today?
Remember how Marine
called me an airhead earlier?
Hmm? Did I really say that?
She did! She was insulting you. What a meanie!
So, like...
I want to fix that part of me.
I want to do something about it.
So you do think you're a little dumb.
Leave it to us!
And there we have our request!
We've got just the thing!
Roboco-san's problem is, in short:
"I want to become a more high-spec robot!"
I do!
We have the perfect game for you, Roboco-san!
Really?
Yeah!
Ratchet & Clank: Rift Apart!
The latest entry in a widely popular action game series,
Ratchet & Clank: Rift Apart.
The grand adventure through the galaxy of Ratchet & Clank
has come back with even more enjoyment on the PS5.
Hey, it's okay, see...?
Just me.
We promise nothing nefarious will befall you.
We promise.
Dr. Nefarious...
this is the part...
where you lose.
Ratchet, the Dimensionator!
The two familiar protagonists
use their teamwork and flashy weapons
to stop the evil robot emperor
from destroying all life in the galaxy.
Without the Dimensionator...
...I think we have to build a new one.
The boundaries between the universes are coming undone...
Avast, ahoy, yo-ho yo-ho!
Our time has finally come!
It's me! It worked!
Whoa, another Lombax...
Wait, I have to find my friend!
Where are you, Clank?
You okay, bolts?
You came after me.
From charming new characters
to weapons that are more exhilarating and powerful than ever.
Moreover, smooth gameplay and beautiful, immersive graphics
made possible by the processing power of the PS5.
Both never-before-seen planets and an alternate
universe version of the familiar planet await.
It's the most chaotic the Ratchet & Clank series has ever been!
On to a grand adventure
across the galaxy and through another world,
set sail!
YOU!
Oh, I have sprained my ankle!
I'd like for us to suggest ways
for Roboco-san to become high-spec
from all the high-spec robots appearing in this game!
Let's go wild today!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Have you played a Ratchet & Clank game before?
I haven't! This is my first!
Then, Subaru, I'm counting on you.
Okay!
This is actually my first time playing this entry,
so let's learn together!
Sounds good!
Let's input the basic controls
into your body by playing chapter 1,
then aim to become a high-spec robot!
Seems robotic.
Let's start!
And we're off! Whoa, the graphics!
It's beautiful, right?
They have aircrafts!
It's set in the near future, but it feels a little familiar.
Yeah, that's the thing!
There are so many aliens here!
Oh!
You know, Ratchet...
He's saved the world a number of times,
but he's bad at making speeches, so he's nervous.
I see!
So he has to give a speech now.
Yeah!
Roboco-senpai, you can start controlling him!
Whoa!
Oh, you have an objective.
It said to obtain the OmniWrench.
It did.
Let's clear the objectives for now!
The graphics are insane!
So much confetti.
Can you get on that platform?
Okay!
What you have in your hands now is the OmniWrench.
Omurice?
OmniWrench.
Omurice?!
Is she hungry?
This wall is blocking the way...
so let's break it with the OmniWrench.
So you can break—
Nice!
Please proceed.
It's like an event at an amusement park.
You're really good!
It got stronger or something.
Sounds good.
Use R2 to shoot the Blarg ships.
Okay!
Nice.
It's like a festival.
Who are these guys?!
They look strong!
Goon-4-Less?!
He's getting messed with.
They're such stereotypical bad guys.
Yeah!
Beat them up!
It's the Goon-4-Less!
Get 'em!
Nice, nice! It's hitting!
Her aim is so good.
She's pretty good.
The reticle's not—Is it like this?
Doing good.
Nice, nice!
Thanks for the special effects.
You're really good!
Really? Yay!
You were dodging really well.
Go straight and stand on that.
Aren't you quite high-spec?
I think I've proven myself.
Roboco-senpai usually plays PC games,
and is—
AAAH!
Oh?
Is that a sign?
Is it because they called her high-spec?
And now!
Ah, she's on it!
Looks fun!
What is this?
Press X here!
Ah, she can jump over them!
Nice!
Can she get the timing down?
Doing good.
It's so tanky!
Ah, your weapon leveled up!
Whoa!
So you can level those up, too.
Burst!
Roboco-senpai is so good...
She's really making use of the pillar.
Cover's important, after all.
That's an FPS player for you.
She plays them quite a bit.
R-Roboco-senpai.
She's so good, I had to laugh.
She's so good!
What's this advanced movement?
Let's get up front now!
That hurts!
Let's proceed!
You have a new objective to destroy the battleship.
It's that!
You're getting damage in!
18 percent left!
A little left!
9 percent left!
Die faster!
Nice!
That's the winning run!
Wonderful.
There!
I have repaired the Dimensionator.
So you can travel through dimensions
and find your family.
To find his family...
He can travel between dimensions with this...
Or was going to.
Oh, pal, I...
They're stealing it!
Dr. Nefarious?!
This is the boss!
Dr. Nefarious arrives!
That bastard!
I didn't expect to see you here—
Dr. Nefarious
So he's why we got attacked!
considering my GOONS were meant
to ANNIHILATE you eight MINUTES ago!
He'll pay for that!
And now,
we have to deal with this sudden development!
Whoa, this is cool!
Let's catch Nefarius!
Go straight ahead!
You can?
Won't I fall?
You can get on that.
Seriously?!
That's amazing.
Style points 100!
What did you do?!
wHaT DiD yOu Do?
So he's kind of dumb.
He's a bit of a birdbrain.
He dun goofed!
Oh shoot, things are leaking through.
This is getting out of hand!
What just happened?
Try pointing at one of them.
Oh?
Okay.
Let's try it.
Warp?
By pointing at a rift, you can do a Rift Tether
and instantly warp across.
So you can warp!
What, you can warp?!
You can go wherever you want.
Yeah.
Ah, you can get across.
Stop it!
There!
That's so mysterious!
Right? It feels like you're pulling the space to yourself.
It looks impressive.
She's so fast!
There he is!
She beats them up before she even knows they're an enemy.
Now then, Roboco-senpai!
Are you ready to save the world?
I'll save the world!
L and X.
I see!
Nice, nice!
Nice dodge!
A little more!
Ah, the beam's coming!
Ah, it leveled up!
Nooo!
Nice, nice.
Nice dodge.
Great job dodging that!
You got this!
Here it comes.
Ba-ba-ba-ba-bam!
Okay!
18 percent left!
16! 15!
3 percent left!
I'm so glad I beat it!
You did it!
I got nervous just watching!
It was as tense as a movie.
Dr. Nefarious defeated!
We're going to a dimension where I always win,
so YOU can finally know how it feels!
Nicely done!
There's a dimension like that?!
What did he say?
He can go to any dimension he wants, after all.
That's not fair!
Yeah!
Roboco-san safely cleared the prologue.
There's more of the fun Ratchet & Clank world in store,
so stay tuned!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Now then,
the adventure starts from here!
Are you excited, Roboco-senpai?
I am!
I'm super hyped right now.
That was cool!
I'm curious where the story goes from here,
but we're trying to make Roboco-senpai
a high-spec robot today,
so we here at Maruyama
will be drawing up a proposal to make you high-spec!
From here, the three employees at Maruyama
will be showing their proposals
for Roboco-san's high-specification.
The first person to present will be...
Towa!
Okay.
My proposition for making Roboco-senpai high-spec
is this!
Bam!
Super
gigentic
Roboco
San
Ban!
What the heck is this!
Wait!
You lookin' down on us?
No I—
This is
a gigantic Roboco-san!
What's that on her boobs?
It adds a nice touch, doesn't it?
My idea of a high-spec robot is, of course,
gigantic.
Though I messed up the spelling there a little.
You're right!
That's an e, not an a.
gig(e)ntic
Well, uh...
Once you look at this robot from Ratchet & Clank,
even you guys, who are constantly complaining,
will completely change your minds.
Now then, let's play!
Yay!
I wonder what kind of boss it is.
Ah!
Now then!
Ooh! It's the new character.
From here,
you'll be controlling Rivet-chan.
Cuuute!
The new character, Rivet,
is a Lombax like Ratchet.
She'll be fighting back against
the robot army's assault with us!
Let's see...
Let's see... What's that?
That's adorable!
The way she grabbed him.
By the head.
Yeah.
She was grabbing him by the head.
She might rip it off...
As for why Clank is with Rivet,
enjoy the story for yourself to find out!
Right.
To find out what happened.
Cute.
Whoa.
Oh...
Play for yourself to find that out too.
So there's a reason...
The animation is so grand.
They broke the wall!
He looks like bad news!
The gigantic robot makes its appearance!
Oh no!
Nooo!
This looks bad!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Oh no, they're getting sucked in!
That's some crazy suction power.
Ah! They're taking him!
This looks bad!
You know, we should
break its legs, one by one.
Hey, that's disturbing.
Why are you...
She unexpectedly likes torture.
suddenly saying some psychopathic stuff?
What's that?
It's a bug robot.
So you ride it.
I can ride it!
What the—It's so fast!
What is this thing?
You wouldn't think he could sprint
so fast at first glance.
Yeah. So now you fight this giant monster, Seekerpede
It's interesting how there's
so many different ways to move around.
It says to hold R1 while jumping from the slope.
You got this!
Let's get on top of it!
There's apparently a slope somewhere.
Where?
Ah! It's that! On the right!
Oh! It's this!
Hold down R1!
Whoa! They're flying!
Nice!
Whoa!
Go!
This is so thrilling.
Amazing.
This is insane.
It's so fun!
Ah! She fell! Ow, ow.
Whoa!
It's time for the boss battle!
Roboco-senpai, watch out!
Now then,
Roboco-san will experience the pros
of a giant robot firsthand in battle!
You'll see the upsides of having a giant body!
Remember your earlier fights!
I have to recall my training.
With X, jump—
Ah, here it comes!
Nicely dodged!
Amazing!
Nice dodge!
A big body has the advantage of having an immense presence.
She's really good at dodging.
Yeah.
Roboco-senpai learns so fast.
Yeah, she just absorbs it all.
That was close! I hate that beam!
You're doing fine!
Also, since they have a huge body,
they have a lot of power.
Go!
The one from before!
Get on!
They're calling you raw garbage
Can this bastard shut up?
"Bastard"?!
Okay!
One more time!
Another one!
And she's off!
Roboco-senpai's so good.
You're doing good!
She won this for sure.
You can do it!
How mean!
You got this!
You can do it...
She got shaken off.
It dug—Urgh.
It's time for the 2nd round!
Here we go.
Like a 2nd phase?
Yeah. This is the 2nd phase.
She's already gotten it down 50 percent.
Go!
What is that move?!
That was insane!
What was that?
The enemy has so much destructive power.
It's pretty strong.
He's too big!
Changing weapons
Negatron...
What does this do?
Wanna try shooting it?
What was that?
Whoa!
She making clones of herself!
3 percent left!
2!
1!
Go! Go!
I'm powering through!
Roboco-san defeats it!
I'm sure you all saw the appeal of having a huge body
from the fight with the Seekerpede.
Please consider my suggestion.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Next up is, Marine! The floor is yours.
Okay! My proposition to Roboco-senpai
to make her high-spec is...
This!
Ba-bam!
Cuuute!
Pirate
Roboco
San
The drawing's so good!
This here is...
Pirate Roboco-san!
It's cute.
Isn't this just a Marinification?
If you want to become high-spec,
you just need to become a pirate!
But you'll rust if you go out to sea.
Will I be fine? Salt's kinda...
You'll be fine! I'll just pour some oil on you.
Really? I might be fine, then.
All right. Moving on.
Let's see if this will make you the ultimate, high-spec robot!
Without further ado, let's get started!
What kind of enemy will it be?
Are you ready?
Look at them!
This here
is the Pirate "Crusher" Francois battle!
Captain's proposal!
How good is the pirate robot?
It's the crusher!
It's a pirate, you know!
There's so much fire!
Ahoy!
Its weapons are so strong!
So he's Captain's underling...
You want to get close.
This is what becoming a pirate means!
Lots of power!
That's what a high-spec robot is all about!
I see!
I see...
Y-Yeah...
Ah...
Roboco-senpai doesn't even seem to be paying attention.
She's completely getting toyed with!
What do you think?
It's shooting a whole bunch of rockets at you.
Pirates never lose!
There's the shockwave!
The shockwave is a bit annoying.
You're doing good!
Just have to keep your distance.
There're so many adds!
That strong, sturdy body.
Now that's what I call a pirate!
I see.
She's only talking about pirates.
Take that! Ahoy! Ahoy!
Stop it!
Go! Go! Get her!
Hey!
Marine, aren't you going to root for me?!
Roboco-senpai!
Lose already!
Why?!
Pirates are the ultimate lifeform!
I don't want to lose!
10 percent left!
I want to dodge...
Roboco-senpai's in a pinch!
Francois, you did it!
It's too strong!
Overwhelming power!
How was that?!
She's so passionate!
It was amazing.
Not just what was on the screen.
I could feel a threatening aura from here, too.
Her aura was going through me to you.
From here
Yeah. I could feel her passion.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
The last proposal
is from me, Subaru!
What is it?
This!
Bam!
Extreme
ly fast
Ro
boco
S
an
Ta-dah.
That pose is so cool.
What's with this... "art"?
What's it supposed to be?
"Extremely Fast Roboco San"!
You're in no position to complain about my art!
Shut it!
Urgh!
True.
My idea of a high-spec robot
is fast, first and foremost.
I see.
I propose "Extremely Fast Roboco San"!
Does that mean the next boss is insanely fast?
Could you not read into it that much?
Please stop that.
Let's go see the next enemy
in order to become "Extremely Fast Roboco San"!
Ah!
Is it over? Ah!
Wait! Is this...
A-Are they going to finally meet?
Cute.
It is.
Ah!
Is that "Nice to meet you"?
Is it?
Cuuute!
Ooh!
And the enemy is...?
It's that guy.
Does this dimension love me or what?
Darn it!
My problems deliver themselves RIGHT to me.
True.
How many times you beat this guy?
Clearly not enough.
...Can I try?
Be my guest.
How nice.
Sounds good! Teamwork!
Take him with you!
She's so cool.
And now,
it's a rematch against the evolved Dr. Nefarious!
He's fast!
He's fast.
That's right.
Roboco-san!
It's a rematch against Dr. Nefarius
in his new, extremely fast form.
Whoa! He's shooting so much.
It's like fireworks.
So fast.
Well, when they're fast...
How pretty.
So strong.
Yeah, it's so hard to hit them.
Yeah, speed is pretty OP.
Ah, it's this world again.
This is pretty fun.
It is, isn't it?
Nyoom!
I see.
All sorts of things are going on.
Is it fine to fall here?
Save me!
Thank you for launching us back.
Thanksies.
He's way too strong!
Isn't he?!
He's too fast!
He's the strongest, isn't he?
He's too strong!
Don't you want to
It's okay! He's only at 80 percent health!
become fast like Nefarius now?
This is just plain unfair! I can't even see him!
Let's try out the other weapons too!
Okay.
Ahhh, he got mad.
You got him down to half!
It's a dinosaur!
Why?
It's a different enemy.
What time period is this?
This is cheating!
Oh, shoot.
Oh no!
I'll just force the last bit!
Force the last bit!
I will!
And now it's a battle against Nefarious again.
50 percent left!
That's half!
It's another warp.
He won't go down just yet!
We're back here!
Where did he go?
We're back on this field.
Where is he?!
There he is.
He's fast.
You can't follow him with your eyes.
Yeah. Where even is he?
There he is.
I want a weapon with lock-on!
A lock-on...
I don't have any bullets!
Out of bullets, seriously?
However, Towa-san notices something...
I'm running out of bullets one by one.
The lightning on the bottom left is full, isn't it?
Now that you mention it.
You're right.
Wait, isn't this lock-on?
That's so good!
It's lock-on!
That's a great weapon!
Nice, nice!
You're doing good!
This is a really good weapon!
Hmm? Maybe lock-on is better than being fast.
7! 7!
6! 6!
Stop it, Roboco-senpai!
You did it!
Roboco-senpai!
Lock-on is the best!
Oi, stop!
What did you think of extreme speed?
At first, I thought it was really strong
since I couldn't hit anything,
but...
Right?!
But?
Don't say it!
It can't win against lock-on, so...
Lock-on is...
You can't do anything against that!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
How was Ratchet & Clank: Rift Apart?
The graphics were beautiful,
and the visuals were really immersive.
It was amazing, right?
Moreover, Roboco-san was really good.
True.
She was!
I'm surprised she beat those bosses.
That concludes the presentations!
Which one will Roboco-san choose...?
This has to be...
Marine.
It was Marine!
Whaaat?
Approved
Proposal to make Roboco-senpai high-spec:
Roboco San Piratification
Of course! The Houshou Pirates are unparalleled!
Now that I think about it, she's not part of us.
She's in a different crew.
Yeah, she's from a different crew.
She's a rival.
Ah, right...
The appearance of the
Roboco Pirates?!
She might defeat me❤
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Please tell us the member who shined
the most, the Twin-crew for today!
This is hard...
Will it be me?
Who taught you a lesson today?
Oh? Oh?
Who taught you a lesson?
The Twin-crew for today!
Is Marine!
Roboco-senpai, welcome to the world of piracy!
It's her first star!
Welcome!
Nnng...
Roboco-san!
Ah...
She sounds like she hates it!
Roboco-senpai, you can still change your answer.
Can I really?
Shut it!
What was your reason for picking her?
The reason is because I lost to her.
She's the only person I lost to here,
so I chose her.
Yaaay.
Continue doing your best to become the boss!
Yeah!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Challenge From the Boss: the Maruyama Championship!
Yay!
At this point, we'll have our customers
try their hand at a minigame.
Yeah!
The one who finishes the season on top
will receive a Special Maruyama Trophy!
Yay!
So, how confident are you?
Well, I'm so old.
I'm so sold.
On the trophy?
So sold!
You had me a sec. That "I'm so old!"
Old Age
Sold? Yeah, surprise.
What? "Old"?
Yeah, I heard "old" too.
Have you played Puyo Puyo before?
I've played a little,
but I'm more of a Tetris player.
Oh, I see.
Not much.
Then let's get right to the game.
If you would.
Don't mind if I do.
You can do it!
Go!
The game has begun!
Oh! Looking good so far.
Wait a sec! How do I...
Oh, I see!
Right, rotate it.
I comprehend. I comprehend.
She comprehends!
What a relief.
I'm not doing good.
But you're looking good.
But you're looking good!
She's stacking them well.
She's stacking them very nicely.
I don't want them to chain!
She doesn't want a chain? I see.
Oh, whatever.
2-chain!
Nice, nice! 2-chain! Nice!
She's already passed the Subaru Line.
Wait, the Subaru Line's that low?
Hey, come on!
Subaru tried her best, you know!
She's well past the Subaru Line.
Crap, crap, crap, crap.
That was a bad distraction.
What now?
I see. So this is how you do it.
Focus, now.
Just over 20 seconds left.
What? It's timed? I need to hurry.
You're in trouble, Roboco-senpai!
You can do it!
Oh, I see.
You've got 10 seconds left!
You're in trouble!
Gotta clear, gotta clear!
Ah, crap.
I need to clear all of it?
It's the end! Clear 'em quick!
5 seconds! 5!
5 seconds left!
Hurry! Drop 'em quick!
4!
OMG! OMG! OMG!
3!
2!
OMG! OMG! OMG!
1!
Oh, just one more!
And so your final score is
8,649 points!
You're in 8th place!
Yay!
Marine, you've got mad skills!
I'm totally awesome, right?
Wow, so modest.
I know, right?!
Will a monster appear and beat that score?
Tune in next time and see!
Look forward to it!
Roboco san
Thank you for your patronage!
Yay!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
After Closing
How did you enjoy this episode of
Game Shop Maruyama?
I've asked Subaru-san to stay back this time.
Yeah! Let's do this thing!
Yes, let's do it.
Now, let's give our viewers some advice with their worries!
Yeah!
From@cY88LxrwP8DZJS5 on Twitter!
They have a pirate flag followed by "stan."
They're one of Marine's followers!
I've been making my own lunch for four years now...
They make them themselves. How diligent.
Respectable!
...but after thinking about the cost and effort,
my recipe selection shrank,
and now all my dishes are basically the same thing.
Are there any good, low-effort dishes
that I can eat all the time
or useful seasonings that can add
some variation to my cooking?
Oh, I get it!
I have a good idea!
Oh?! Give it to us!
You ready?
Fried butter!
This actually exists.
Fried butter?!
It takes pretty much no work,
Chef Subaru's recommendation: Fried Butter
and you can pump it out quick,
and it's chock full of calories!
Plus it's good!
Really?! I can down a whole stick myself.
It's probably a lot of calories.
You're crazy!
Put the butter in the shape of your lunch box.
Fill it with fried butter.
And now, we're accepting requests for advice from you.
If your request gets featured, you get this!
Oh?
A completely unique, personally signed request fulfilled sticker!
Yay!
So please send in your submissions!
Send them in!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Yay!
Woohoo!