We did spend the company's fortune
on this (holo World Record) series.
Don't waste the company's fortune on this!
The sleepy meek sheep sheepishly sweeps
her sleek hand through her horns.
!%!@%@%$#%!#%!%#%%!@#
!@%!$^&%^(*—
Well...
See you again in four years!
hololive's
Most Heated Battle
Starts Now!
Challenge everything! holo World Records!
Knock knock goes the fox, everyone!
hololive's self-proclaimed speedrun demon,
Shirakami Fubuki here!
Happy to be here!
Noon-nui! hololive 3rd Gen's Shiranui Flare here!
Hoof hoof helloof!
hololive 4th Gen's Tsunomaki Watame here!
Today's the start of a brand new series!
[holo World Records]
A show to decide hololive's No.1
in various given fields. In this episode,
we'll be taking on three different challenges!
What exactly are you gonna make us do here...?
Are you that worried?
Oof...
Phew...
Are you gonna drop out?
That's a problem.
I'm sure you girls have set some record
at least once in your life.
I do a lot of speedruns,
although none of them are world records.
Oh, yeah! You do!
That's true.
She does, yeah.
If we're talking about records,
I've got those speedruns.
I've been targeted by people before!
You DO look like you're likely
to be devoured, Watame-san.
Oh, that's true!
Indeed.
Members who manage to set a world record
will be granted a title full of renown:
The hololive World Record Queen!
Yes, that sort of queen!
Ooh?
You can get rice, a shoulder massage coupon,
and even an electric pressure cooker!
I'd like an electronic massager.
Really?
That would be nice indeed.
Yeah,
I'd like one too.
Don't you just want one?
I'll take that, thank you very much.
No, you won't!
Oh heck no you won't!
Let's grab all the prizes and bail!
The first challenge you girls will be taking on is this!
High-speed Blinking World Record!
High-speed Blinking World Record?!
Don't you girls know about it?
No, I don't.
I've never heard of it.
Rumors have it that they'll
add this to the next Olympics!
(It's a lie)
Really?
For real?
Yeah!
Let's aim to set the record, then.
It's pretty popular in France right now.
(To Be Confirmed.)
REALLY?!
This is a very simple challenge where you're tested
on how many blinks can you do in just 15 seconds.
I'll be the one in charge of counting the blinks.
Blinks...
Wow.
Well, my eyes are completely dry
so I'm confident I can do well.
Eyeballs dry as the Sahara!
Shiranui Flare sets forth!
Well then, let's begin!
Ready, Flare-san?
Begin!
She has 15 seconds to—
Good luck!
Looking good! I'm keeping count too.
Can you actually
count them, though?
Five seconds left on the clock!
My eyes are drying up even more instead!
Do your best!
Time's up!
How'd I do?
Your result, Flare-san, is...
41 blinks!
Ooh!
Whoa!
That's pretty good, right?
It is amazing!
That's pretty amazing, right?
She's currently in 1st place.
I have no idea
how this works!
Currently 1st place!
Obviously!
Forty-Score and Still Counting!
Shirakami Fubuki descends upon the stage!
Going over 40? That's pretty easy, ain't it?
Oh? Easy?
Uh-huh...
I like the sound of that.
Ready?
Begin!
15 seconds on the clock!
Looking good! She's pretty quick!
She's FAST!
FREAKING FAST!
I'm keeping count as well. She's focused.
Amazing.
That's really fast, isn't it?
Five seconds left!
Is she bugged out?!
Four!
Right?
Three!
Two!
One!
Time's up!
Wow!
Are you secretly a pro at this?
Have you done this before?
She's already...
Not at all!
This is all just talent!
Did you practice?
It's talent indeed!
Fubuki-san, your result is...
68 blinks!
Congratulations!
HOLY—
WHOA!
REALLY?!
HECK YEAH!
Seriously?! That's SCARY!
That's amazing!
All right, you're the last one up, Watame-san!
This is some INSANE pressure!
Flare-san blinked 41 times
and Fubuki-san 68 times,
so if you get about 20 more than Fubuki-san
we'll have a pretty clean gap in the score.
Okay, I see!
Yup!
Maybe I can get 100!
Oh, aiming for 100 I see!
Forty-Score and More to Spare!
Tsunomaki Watame enters the field!
Ready?
Begin!
Oh! Looking good!
Bit of a late start but you're doing well!
That's some adorable blinking.
How cute.
She's breathing fast.
Five!
Four!
Her breathing's faster.
Three!
Indeed. Two!
One!
Time's up!
Time is up!
Phew...
That was...
Never mind your blinking,
your breathing was faster.
My start was bad...
Watame-san's result is...
Did I make it?
I wonder...
61 blinks!
Congratulations!
Darn it!
Hold up!
Wait a minute!
That's a sizeable gap from your goal.
That's just plain frustrating.
Um... uh... can I try one more time?
Sure, let's do it!
I wanna get at least 10 more blinks in.
Back for Revenge!
Shiranui Flare won't let up!
Time for Flare-san's second attempt!
Ready?
Begin!
Huh? What?!
Ah! Oh, you're doing fine!
H-Hold on. This might be a fail.
Hmm? Huh?
Hm???
Her eyes are...
Is she...
Huh? What's...?
Four!
Is she blinking too fast for us to see?!
Huh? Flare-san?!
She's so fast I can't keep count! Two!
One!
She's too fast!
Time's up!
She's way too fast!
This might be a worse result than earlier...
I'm truly sorry,
but I can't count if you don't blink
at a speed for human eyes to catch...
CAN IT!
Flare-san's new result is... wow!
It's the lowest! 15 blinks!
Congratulations!
WAIT, THAT LOW?!
That was definitely bugged.
The High-speed Blinking World Record Queen is...
Shirakami Fubuki with 68 blinks!
Congratulations!
Yaaay!
Congrats!
Woohoo!
Well...
See you again in four years!
Inspiring words! Congratulations once again!
And the next challenge is...
The Tongue Twister World Record!
Ooh!
Oh...
Wow!
Tongue twisters!
Each member gets their own custom tongue twister
and pass if they say it three times without stumbling!
This should be right up your alleys!
I get the feeling I'm gonna stumble...
Oh? Really?
Huh?
Suddenly you're deflating?
Right?
I believe in you, Fubuki-san!
I've heard from your manager already about how
you pulled an all-nighter reading the script
Waddya mean "All-nighter?!"
You're taking it
pretty seriously!
and practicing hard for this.
You're scored based on whether or not you stumble
with 10 points being the maximum score,
so it all comes down to whether
you can read it smoothly.
It's the same system as how they score figure skaters,
so, uh, try to keep the audience in mind.
She may lack confidence,
but Shirakami Fubuki steps on stage!
All right, then! Here's your
Tongue Twister Challenge, Fubuki-san!
Shirakami shipped sheep curry to a canary in her quarry.
That looks HARD!
That's a long one!
At the stripped quarry, a strict Shirakami
proposed a perusal of laparoscopy.
What the heck is "laparoscopy"?
The second half is where the points are at.
Got it!
All right! Are you ready?
Let's begin!
The Tongue Twister World Record Challenge
starts... now!
Shirakami shipped sheep curry to a canary
in her quarry. At the stripped quarry a strict
Shirakami proposed a perfusion of laparoscopy.
Shirakami shipped sheep curry to a canary
in her quarry. At the stripped carry a strict
Shirakami proposed a perusal of laparoscopy.
Shirakami shipped sheep curry to a canary
in her quarry. At the skipped quarry a strict
Shirakami proposed a perusal of laparo—
Snoopy
Wow!
That was pretty smooth.
You did get stuck at the end there
but you managed to finish it off.
That's freaking TOUGH!
It is!
Here are the results of the examination by
an impartial board of international deliberators!
You got 7.5 points!
Congratulations!
All right!
Thank you!
You were adorable so they gave you
an extra 0.5 points.
Phew, thank goodness!
So that's also a thing!
Yeah, it's a bonus system!
I see.
Got it.
That's some good info.
Yup!
Maybe she's a master at it?
Shiranui Flare flexes her skills!
Here's your Tongue Twister!
Shiranui, she not knowing, set her hair aflame with flair.
Apparel paired with parental care
she bared as the price for winter's fare.
Say what?
Wait, what?
That's SCARY!
That's a little unsettling.
Flare's Tongue Twister World Record Challenge
starts... now!
Shiranui, she not knowing, set her hair aflame
with flair. Apparel paired with parental care
she bared as the price for winter's fare.
Shiranui, she not knowing, set her hair aflame
with flair. Apparel paired with parental care
she bared as the price for winter's fare.
Shiranui, she not knowing, set her hair aflame
with flair. Apparel paired with parental care
she bared as the price for winter's fare.
Wow! That was great!
How did I do?
That was very smooth!
What?
Flare-san's score is...
9 points!
Congratulations!
The initial one was a tiny bit off,
Yeah, I... um... uh, yeah...
but you picked up the speed, so it went pretty well!
Seriously?!
All you need is drive!
Tsunomaki Watame readies her drills!
By the way, Watame-san,
are you good with tongue twisters?
I'm bad with them.
Oh, really?
I stumble a lot.
If you think of it as you
being turned into food if you fail,
the pressure might be able to propel you through.
Fubuki-san's also here too!
That's some EXTREME pressure!
True, I'm here.
My life's on the line here?
Yes, your life's on the line.
That's pretty extreme.
Suddenly the heat's on!
Here's your tongue twister, Watame-san.
The sleepy meek sheep
sheepishly sweeps
her sleek hand through her horns.
Please read this perfectly
as if you're reading your last rites.
That's so complicated!
Do your best!
The Tongue Twister World Record Challenge
starts... now!
The sleepy meek sheep sheepishly %@#
her sleek hand through her horns.
The sleepy meek sheep sheepishly sweeps
!%#%@^@#^!$!%#%!@#
She's trembling.
!%!@%@%$#%!#%!%#%%!@#
!@%!$^&%^(*&!@%%!#%#^!^#!@!
She threw in a special act at the end!
That's cheating!
She definitely aimed for that!
You were definitely
going for that!
Well then...
Watame-san, your score is...
8.7 points! Congratulations!
WHAAAT?!
Your cute movements and
that final wink alone were worth 5 points.
That's a LOT!
Without those, you're at 3.7 points.
5 points!
That's pretty funny.
Now for the results!
Here are your scores!
Fubuki-san with 7.5 points,
Flare-san with 9, and Watame-san with 8.7!
Flare-san takes home the record!
Congratulations!
Yaaay!
Congrats!
It was an obvious result.
Oh? Strong words coming from someone
who only managed 15 blinks earlier.
I said, can it!
And the next challenge is...
The Long Tone World Record!
Yay!
Long tone...
Hurray!
Looks like you girls are hyped up!
In this challenge, you girls will be competing
to see who can hold their voice the longest.
It's a record that challenges your lung capacity.
Both Flare-san and Watame-san seem like
you can sing quite well,
so I assume that the both of you
can hold your tones, am I right?
Not really.
Nope, I sneak in some breaths of air.
Oh, you do that?
You're one of those types, huh?
It seems like you can use any word
you like for this challenge,
so words like "Whaaat,"
"Pad Kra Pao,"
and even "Pad Thai" count.
You can use anything.
"Whaaat?"
What will she yell?
Shirakami Fubuki, ready to yip!
All right, the Long Tone World Record Challenge
begins... now!
It's salmoooooooooooon!
Ooh, that's pretty long!
Looking good! She's holding it well!
Amazing.
How long
can she hold it?
She's pretty stable too.
She's even doing a cute appeal as well.
She can keep going!
That's so long!
It's REALLY long!
Whoa.
Is this...
Her cowlick's rocking around too.
That's it!
Isn't that freaking long?
She's landed!
Are you okay, Fubuki-san?
I'm okay!
You look spent!
You lasted a total of...
22 seconds!
Ooh! 22 seconds!
Ooh.
22 seconds, yeah!
That's pretty good.
Here's your salmon baseline!
Indeed.
Can you two do better?
I see.
Aiming to do better!
Shiranui Flare takes center mic!
Flare's Long Tone World Record Challenge
begins... now!
Saaaaaaa
"Sa—?"
"Sa" what?
She's pushing the record.
A beautiful and stable voice.
It surely makes you want to listen to it live.
Amazing!
She's lasting pretty long!
Saaaaaaans!
Oh?!
[Sans]
Shiranui Flare's beloved character
from the game Undertale.
It was Sans!
Here are the results of Flare-san's love towards Sans!
23 seconds! You beat out Fubuki-san by 1 second!
OH!
OOH!
Just a bit over!
Will she show everyone something good?
Tsunomaki Watame rolls initiative!
Well then, Watame-san's
Long Tone World Record Challenge begins... now!
Hambuuuuuur
Is she thinking of the time
she got prepped for cooking?
Is she a master at it?
Choosing to be a burger of her own volition.
Looking good. She's stretching it out.
Just a bit more!
Just a little bit more!
Her voice is fading.
Do your best!
Keep on stretching it!
Hambuuuuuurger!
OH! There it is.
Was the "Hamburger" just now you wanting to
become one or you not wanting to become one?
I wanted to eat one!
Oh, you wanted to eat one!
Watame-san lasted...
25 seconds!
Congratulations!
Whoa!
Everyone did great!
Amazing!
I noticed you lowered your voice midway.
Yeah, I did!
Oh, so it WAS intentional!
We noticed.
As expected of you.
You all noticed?
Now for the results!
Fubuki-san lasted 22 seconds!
Flare-san lasted 23 seconds!
And Watame-san lasted 25 seconds!
Look at this gradual increase.
The Long Tone World Record goes to...
Watame-san! Congratulations!
Yaaay! Thank you!
Congrats!
Nothing beats a good old hamburger!
Nothing beats a good old hamburger indeed!
How was it, everyone?
It was a lot of fun!
Completely coincidental,
but each of us set a World Record.
Oh, yeah!
That's true!
Thanks to that we've learned that the Three Stooges
are perfectly balanced as all things should be!
Indeed!
What do I get for my record?
Yeah! What do you get for
the Long Tone World Record?
Oh! What DO you get for it indeed?
Ah! You get a supply of crabs!
You get a supply of crabs.
CRABS?!
Whoa.
That's the best reward!
Crabs sure are delicious!
We did spend the company's fortune
on this series so please share some with us.
Don't waste the company's fortune on this!
We'll be doing this more in the future as well!
Do keep on improving your skills and become pros, girls!
And to the viewers, please like & subscribe
if you enjoyed this video!
Please also subscribe to our guests' channels as well!
See you all again!
Thanks for watching!
Bye-bye!