*flomp*
Lamy found a diary on the street!
Nene's Diary
Goodness me, my dear.
You can't go losing these things,
or your privacy won't be so private anymore!
Whoever could this belong to?
Okayu-senpai said she loves me today!
Okayu-senpai and I held hands today!
Okayu-senpai and I kissed today!
Nene's Diary
prrrrrrr
Hello? Is this the Oozora Police?
'Sup! This is the Oozora PD.
We protect hololive's peace
by catching criminal scum
and throwing them behind bars.
prrrrrrr
Let's gooo!
You've reached the Oozora PD!
My partner's cheating on me!
She said she loved me,
but now she's telling someone else
the same thing!
What do you think? So unfair, right?!
She didn't even lay a finger on me!
slam
Don't get involved in people's love lives.
That's the advice Mio-sha gave me.
Baawl!
What's up?
I don't know what to play
in tomorrow's Tsunomaki RPS!
That's your issue?
What if they complain
I only play rock, paper, or scissors?!
That's it! That's the whole game!
Time to come up with a new hand.
Sweet idea!
How about something like this?
I don't know... I like this one better.
I'm surrounded by carnivores!
This is Officer Oozora!
And Constable Nene!
Something smells fishy in here.
Interrogation time!
Those horns look awfully sharp to me, miss.
Pretty sure it goes past legal limits.
Tell us all about it down at the precinct.
Hell no!
Nene's Diary
I'm not saying goodbye
to my freedom yet!
No! My diary!
That was a diary?!
Bye-bye.
*flomp*
And that's the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!