In store today in Game Shop Maruyama:
Winning Post 9 2021!
Will they train the ultimate horse together?!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
That pizza was so good.
It was!
It was delicious.
The teriyaki chicken was quite yummy, too.
Heeey!
It was all right.
The bulgogi was good too.
Heeey!
Qua—?
You're all so full of energy today.
The staff are in high spirits again
Hello, Boss!
Hey there.
Hello.
Work hard today!
Okay!
Nya-hello!
Who will be today's guest?
Welcome!
That's quite the welcome! What is this place?
Today's Guest: Sakura Miko
D'you like it?
Welcome!
It's Miko-senpai!
There we have it!
Today's guest is Sakura Miko-san!
Sakura Miko
About Her: An elite shrine maiden, so pretty elite
Wishlist: Trash can
Finishing Move: Elite Destroyer
MENT
LUCK
A self-proclaimed... elite? miko idol.
The truth to her claims will be revealed...
"About Her: An elite shrine maiden,
so pretty elite"?
Yeah! That's right.
About Her: An elite shrine maiden, so pretty elite
Exactly what it says.
Your vocabulary seems kinda limited.
I want to put my eliteness out there as my selling point.
And do you know what "elite" means?
Elite means... I'm really...
really amazing.
Uh oh...
Stop bullying her!
Stop bullying her, Boss!
Yeah!
I see.
So you're a self-proclaimed elite?
I have people that can vouch for me!
Right, guys? Tell her!
Are there?
That's debatable.
Highly debatable
That's weird.
She also has a finishing move.
A finishing move?!
Finishing Move: Elite Destroyer
She apparently has one.
I've never shown you guys this.
She definitely just made one up.
I guess I can show you guys.
Hnnn...
Elite Destroyer!
Pew, pew, pew!
Mood Destroyer 💀
Huh?
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Let's see what she wants to fix.
I wanna know!
Even the elite have worries
You know,
I look like this,
so people always treat me like a kid.
She's starting to resemble Captain a bit.
The most unexpected suspicion
Don't lump me in with her.
Not at all.
Flat-Out Denial
You made her mad.
I wanted to gain some mature tastes.
So I wanna learn a mature,
adult-like hobby
Adult-like?!
going forward.
Huh... she is starting to resemble the Captain...
An adult-like hobby, huh...
My, how lewd.
And there we have our request!
We've got just the thing!
So,
since you want a mature and adult-like hobby,
Another victim of the Captain's poison?
Maruyama's game recommendation is...
Subaru uses Elite Guard
Adult ain't her thing
Oh?
Winning Post 9 2021!
Yay!
This game, uh...
What's wrong, Mikochi?
Hmm?
Never mind. Please continue!
To tell you the truth,
Miko-senpai played this game on her streams...
I screwed up...
Wh-Wh-What did you say?!
Already played it?!
Boss becoming a horned demoness is bad news, Miko-chi!
Really?!
Are you saying it's all my fault?
Get on your knees!
Apologize!
Is she gonna kneel for me?
Hey, why are you getting so haughty?
The elite likes seeing people kneel
Kneel for the elite.
What's with you?
Sorry.
You get on your knees too!
I'm sorry!
I guess you came to showcase
the game to the others, then?
Yeah! I wanna play with all of you too!
We might learn a thing or two
about showing a game off from her.
Yeah.
Right.
The game they'll be playing today is this:
Go beyond the ages and stand at the top of the world.
Winning Post 9 2021.
Rivalries finally extend worldwide.
America,
France,
England,
Australia, and others.
The best horses from around the world
gather in one place.
Challenge your rivals to the battle of a century.
Upon becoming the world champion,
you can gain higher-rated horses upon breeding.
For the first time, you can choose which year to start.
The 1980s.
The 1990s.
And the 2000s.
Rivalries and famous jockeys
exclusive to the decade.
The accomplishments of the star horses of that generation
make a brilliant comeback.
Moreover,
you can take ownership of famous horses
and experience "what if" scenarios.
Write your own story into the brilliant history
each generation has to offer.
The bonds with your family and with
your horse are even further evolved.
From your descendents' overseas debuts
to new overseas marriage partners.
You can unlock special abilities
by riding on the same horse.
The features from past releases
have been powered up.
Compatible with the newest horse racing data.
From the Tokyo Sports Hai Nisai Stakes,
being promoted to G2,
to all the prominent regional races.
The overwhelming volume of overseas races.
And new entries including the Saudi Cup,
held in King Abdulaziz Racetrack,
Europe's Stayers' Million,
and the Hong Kong Triple Crown.
Star horses from recent years
to historical horses from the 1980s
all gather in one place.
On top of that,
there's the new secretary, Rindou Shiori,
sibling horses in-breeding,
as well as new traits for racehorses.
It's loaded with new features
that make the game even more fun,
as well as quality of life features
that our long-time fans are familiar with.
A dramatic horseriding competition
on the world stage for all horse racing fans.
Without further ado, let's have them play Winning Post 9!
We're limited on time,
so I'd like for us to choose
a racehorse and play until our first race
this time around.
Wanna win, if possible
Sounds good!
Let's earn a fortune and buy all of Japan's ranches up!
It's not that kind of game.
This isn't that type of game.
Ah, sorry.
Without further ado! New game, start!
Start!
Today!
Yes?
We'll play 1991 Oguri Cap!
Choose your starting year
Four prominent eras of horse-racing history
+ one AU scenario for five in total!
That's Miko-senpai for you!
You know what's up!
Let's name the horse's owner.
What would be good?
Register the horse owner
Decide on name, gender, and age
and build your very own profile
Definitely "Miko-senpai."
"Sakura" would be good.
Can I really?
Yup.
You're fine with me being the owner?
Of course.
Wouldn't the name of this...
Maruyama?
Wanna go with "Maruyama," then?
Sounds good!
"Maruyama," please.
Maruyama, it is!
Let's go with "Maruyama"!
Yeah!
You can choose their gender as well.
If you choose "male,"
you can marry the women,
That's a feature?!
and if you choose "female," you can marry the men.
It has a marriage feature.
Gender will be male!
You can choose their outfits!
White is so cool!
You can design your jockey's outfit
You can choose the pattern too. What would be good?
Let's make it the hololive triangle!
Oh yeah, a triangle.
Will they have it?
So many options.
Will they?
You see them wearing these often.
Yeah.
You can choose the pattern.
Choose one for us!
There's no triangle though...
Ah, pink is so cute! How fashionable.
Stylish.
The horse's mask is also pink! They're matching!
You're right!
They're matching!
Wanna go with blue?
That's fresh.
It's hololive-colored.
Yeah.
Let's go with this.
Let's go with this, then!
Yeah!
Let's open up...
Mhmm.
...a ranch.
Ooh! Finally!
You can choose your ranch's name and foreman
Let's go!
What should we name it?
Ranch name...
Do we just...
Probably "Maruyama"?
Yeah.
How about "Maruyamalive"?
With the "live" from "hololive."
"Maruyamalive" sounds good!
Sounds good to me!
"Maruyamalive Ranch."
Let's do that!
Not enough letters!
There's not enough letters. It got cut off.
It became "Maruyamali."
How about "Marulive"?
"Marulive."
Ah!
"Marulive"?
Sounds good.
Okay!
Perfect!
Nice.
Marulive...
Farm?
Farm! Farm!
I like "Farm"!
Who likes "Farm"?
Meee!
"Farm" it is!
Next up is this!
You can choose the foreman of the ranch.
You can choose one, and they all have their own stats,
but I want you guys to choose who you like.
There are 6 foremen to choose from
They each have their own stats and specialties,
and may affect your racehorse's stats too
The cutest girl, of course.
There's one that stands out to me!
Bansaku-san!
He's passionate for sure.
Prioritizing Passion
His stats are insane!
Let's choose this guy, then.
Yay.
"My name is Seibu Banshaku, nice to meet you!
Acting Mode: On
Huzzah!"
Huzzah!
I used to ride in the past,
but now I dream of living my life surrounded
by nature and horses. You feel me?
He's so healthy!
Now we can choose
a secretary for the horse owner.
You can choose from all these cute girls.
Three secretaries to choose from
They each have their own story scenes,
and if you progress through them, you may get to marriage?!
Really?!
There was a girl with a ponytail, right?
Are you interested?!
She's so cute! Shiori-chan!
Shiori-chan!
She's a new secretary that got added in 9.
The fave favorite!
I think you could change their outfits too...
Cuuute!
It's cute, isn't it?
It's so cute!
It's Christmas!
She's quickly becoming my fave.
Let's go with her.
Fave is the new character, Shiori-chan <3
Shiori-chan it is!
Yeah!
Shiori!
Now that we chose our secretary,
finally!
We can choose the horse that will shoulder
all of our hopes and dreams.
Thank you in advance.
Finally!
What kind of horse will it be?
Purchase a horse
There are recommendations, so if you're lost, just go with them!
There're a few we can choose from.
Ah, a few recommendations, huh?
Yeah.
Probably.
"Leo Durban."
Mikochi the Free Spirit
Miko-chi...
Do you have to get that close?
Let's go with Nice Nature.
A recommendation!
I've heard of that name!
Yeah.
So, we'll be entrusting Nice Nature
Yeah!
with our hopes and dreams this time around!
We're counting on you!
Training Nice Nature This Time
Let's do it!
We can choose the name!
Yeah!
They let us change the horse's name.
Since we're playing together today, I want to
add a Maruyama element to the name.
You can change the horse's name to your liking!
The stats will remain the same.
Like, "Super Maruyama" or "Supermaru"?
"Super Maruyama Elite"?
The Add Everything Kind
Just mixing it all together.
So long.
How about, "Super Maruyama"?
"Super Maruyama" is good.
Then, let's go with "Super Maruyama"!
Yeah!
It's a great name!
Train to be the best in horse racing!
They're training the horse with guidance
from the experienced Miko-senpai.
Is it almost time for the race?
It's time... for the first race!
It's time for their first race!
Now then,
we have races starting next week!
Finally!
I wanna win.
Of course!
We wanna win!
Let's start!
For this race, we'll have
Shirai-san be our jockey!
We're counting on you!
It's all you, Shirai!
Yeah!
Go get 'em!
Although his condition is a triangle...
Why the heck?!
Let's have him do his best out there!
Tokai Teio is the favorite.
A legend appears!
Yeah! Tokai Teio's in this game!
They also have a newspaper.
Check out your rivals' condition
in the newspaper!
Let's check that out too.
Look at this Teio! Their stats are insane!
She only has double circles.
How about Super Maruyama?
We don't even have triangles...
We have nothing...
On top of that...
At least give us something.
doesn't it say "Out of its league"?
Huh?!
Out of its league
Don't sum it up like that!
Let's show them!
We gotta win this!
You can choose the strategy as well,
A mid-pack closer
gets to the front near the end of the race.
They close the distance.
That style's really cool!
It's the badass one!
Yeah.
Our strategy for this race...
Ah, our aptitude has a smiley face.
Right.
I guess mid-pack closer, then?
Let's close in on them all!
I wanna see it in action!
It'll be dramatic.
Understood!
With that settled,
let's go straight to the race!
Let's!
Let's win!
Okay!
This is nerve-racking!
You can do it! You can do it!
Whoa! There's commentary!
With commentary!
The commentary's so...
Here they go!
You can do it!
It's perfectly fine to be in the back at the start.
Perfectly fine.
He's a closer, after all.
How does this commentary work?!
It's amazing!
It's incredible, isn't it?
It's so easy to tell where everyone is.
Will he read our name too?
That'd be cool.
Tokai Teio, yeah!
Whoa! Super Maruyama!
It wasn't Su➚per➘ Maruyama.
He said the thing!
The pronunciation was different.
You can choose the pitch accent you like best.
It's after this corner!
Will he start closing in from here?
Here we go!
Can he win against Teio?
You can do it!
Go! Go! Go!
That's a good position!
Maruyama!
Show our horse! Show him!
You can do it, Maruyama!
Go! Go! Go!
You can do it!
Close in! Close in!
Sheesh! He's so fast!
Damn, he's fast.
Tokai Teio's a beast...
So fast...
Teio's awesome!
Tokai Teio stronk.
I'm not really satisfied yet.
I wanna place a little higher than that.
He would've placed higher with a little more effort, too.
We have a ton of room for improvement.
Yeah.
Some battles you just can't afford to lose
They can't lose this, no matter what!
Let's cheer on Super Maruyama's efforts!
Go get 'em, Maruyama!
I wanna see him win!
Su➚per➘ Maruyama's...
Su➘per➚ Maruyama's?
Yeah, Su➘per➚ Maruyama.
Ultra Cheap! Supermarket Maruyama
Gonna shop? lol
Hmm... wonder where
the spring onion is.
Yeah, that's how the commentator said it.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Continue!
Let's move on!
I'd like to use this "Ultimate Finishing Touches..."
New Bond Command introduced in this entry
Sounds amazing.
Whoa!
...in preparation for this race.
This will spend four weeks
to make the horse stronger.
Ooh!
That seems effective.
Let's do it!
It's using a whole 4 weeks.
Yeah.
That's right.
That's a good amount of time.
Use all the time they need.
We didn't use a command before,
so I'm a little excited about how much it'll do.
I'm excited.
Let's see...
Yay!
And so,
Super Maruyama is in good condition after 4 weeks!
Sorry for the wait!
Looking good!
Thanks!
He didn't build much fatigue either.
Yeah.
It's still a circle.
I was a bit worried about that.
He's perfectly fine.
You're right!
Don't we have a pretty good chance?
They've commissioned a legend,
Okabe-san, to be the jockey.
Will he accept?
The request goes through with no problems!
Will Super Maruyama make a comeback?
Let's get on to the race!
Yay!
Wait, we're the favorite!
Super Maruyama!
Somehow the favorite!
He's #1!
Our Maruyama?!
Our Maruyama is the bookies' favorite!
Our little Maruyama?!
This is pretty amazing.
Let's see how the newspaper looks.
Whoa!
Double circles!
He's that high up!
He has a ton of double circles!
I've never seen anything like it!
You're really giving us all these?
That's so nice.
It says "Contender"!
Wow, that's amazing!
Whoa! "Contender"!
Contender
We did it!
We can get first, can't we?
Yeah.
But seriously.
We have a real chance.
For real.
Let's start the race!
With our dreams in tow!
Maruyama, please!
You can do it!
You have a winning chance today!
Bansaku, you can do it!
Now, now. It's starting!
You can do it!
Kyoto Shimbun Cup Turf 2200m.
It's the main race!
Here we go!
Let's go!
He has the inner track!
You can do it!
Do your best!
Maruyama!
Go get 'em, Maruyama!
Maruyama's getting surrounded!
It's not a problem yet.
It's still the start.
Yeah, it just started.
Anything can happen still.
It's not as bad here.
Conserve his strength here.
Yeah.
Maruyama's all about the late-game!
Hang in there!
Our Maruyama is a mid-pack closer,
so he'll close the distance fast!
They're so packed.
This race is longer than the last one, after all.
It's a little worrying.
Yeah, it's on the longer side.
The horses that started off too hot might be in trouble.
Yeah. They might be wheezing by the end.
They'll get tired, won't they?
Super Maruyama!
Is Maruyama doing okay?
He's quite far back. Is he okay?
Won't this be hard to close in?
Well...
Let's believe in him!
He's the favorite!
That's right! Believe in him!
Yeah!
You can do it!
Tokai Teio was like that too!
Tokai Teio's here too?!
No Tokai Teio
Tokai Teio, huh...
Will they last if they run that fast?
That's right! You guys are going too fast!
Hang in there!
They said it's not time yet.
Since we're mid-pack closers.
Yeah. Our time's just coming up!
Okabe-san will make the call!
It's just starting.
Okabe!
He'll close up on you!
He will.
Close in! Close in soon!
You can do it, Maruyama!
Maruyama!
We believe in you!
Close in! Close in!
Maruyama, please!
He's making his move!
He's going! He's going!
He can do it!
He's so fast!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Wait, this is so hype!
Maruyama! Maruyama!
HE DID IT! HE WON!
Super Maruyama with an undisputed victory!
That was an exhilarating race!
Super Maruyama!
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
Dance of Joy!
I'm actually overjoyed!
I'm so glad! Yay!
Give me a high five too!
Yaaay!
Everyone's so excited.
An undisputed first place!
We won!
He's really showing us his cool side.
Right?
After all,
he was so far back at the start
that I was starting to lose hope.
He passed them all from the back, like, nyoom.
He was so cool!
He was way too cool.
Right?
That was so fun, right?
I can't stop because of moments like these!
There it is!
Miko-chi, that's not good!
Calm down!
Gambler Miko makes an appearance.
She lives for these moments, huh...
Elite Gambler Miko
A bit too adult... *murmuring*
I can't stop because of moments like these!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Sakura Miko-san, you wanted to find a mature hobby.
Did we manage to fulfill your request?
How satisfied are you?
The usual?
Tell us how you're feeling, on the weather scale!
The floor is yours!
Stormy
Rain
Cloudy
Clear
Rising Sun!
Rising... Sun!
Sun!
Well. There you have it.
Uh...
Okay. Let's bounce.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
That was new.
If everyone stinks it up, nobody stinks it up
Thank you very much.
She wanted to try it.
We wanted to do something about this mood.
We wanted to help.
Why are you all talking like I stank the place up?!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Challenge From the Boss:
the Maruyama Championship!
This season's minigame is...
Puyo Puyo Tetris 2's Endless Fever mode!
That's the one!
At the moment, Marine is in the lead with 57,726 points.
That's way too high!
That's the current high score.
What do you think, Miko-senpai?
Miko-chan, how confident are you feeling?
Well, I am elite.
Challenger: Sakura Miko
She's gonna fail hard.
You say that for everything.
"Elite" on fire sale!
Oh, shut up!
Okay, then! Let the game begin!
You can do it!
Okay!
This is an easy stack.
Here's red-green. And here's green.
Horizontal stacking?!
And I'll put a red here.
I think she knows what she's doing!
I do this like this.
I got it. I got it.
I got it. Got it now. Got it.
Oh, hey!
Got it! Got it! Got it!
All clear!
All clear.
You could have made that a 2-chain.
Marine analyzes the situation
Oh, that could be a 2-chain?
You need to build chains,
or your score doesn't go up much.
Right now, your max chain is 1.
You could've done a 2-chain.
What a waste.
Well, you know.
Except you knew that.
Yeah, I knew that.
Miko-senpai knows that.
What happened to being elite?
Maybe we shouldn't talk so much?
Hold on, hold on...
Actual advice
You shouldn't talk?
The point of the show is for you to talk.
I know, but...
10 seconds left! 10!
You can do it! You can do it!
10 seconds!
Crap!
But she crossed the Subaru Line!
Don't call it the Subaru Line!
Subaru Line: 2516 points
Yes! I crossed the Subaru Line?!
Zero!
Not bad! Not bad!
And just like that, 60 seconds are up!
Let's see what your final score is!
Get counting!
She crossed the Subaru Line!
Don't call it the Subaru Line!
What does "elite" mean again?
Hold on just one second!
Subaru, did she beat your score?
She did by a hair, but she didn't beat me in spirit.
Boss, is this an elite score?
This score...
...is not elite!
There! You heard the Boss!
Didn't get an elite score
What the heck?!
I wish we could see an elite one!
I wanted to see an elite score!
Anyway, thanks, everyone!
Thanks!
See you!
Elite coming through.
Elite coming through!
Bye-bye!
What'd she say?
Elite passing through here!
"Elite passing through"?
That sounds...
Elite passed through.
...pretty low IQ.
Very low.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
How did you enjoy this episode of
Game Shop Maruyama?
We helped our customer with her worries.
She must be very pleased.
I've asked Towa-san to stay back this time.
Yes...
We'd love to give our viewers advice
regarding their worries,
but due to reasons, again,
we haven't received any submissions yet.
So, Towa-san, is there anything bothering you?
You know how my voice is
a little deeper than most people's?
So since my voice is so deep,
when new viewers hear it for the first time,
it seems that they find it kinda scary.
Oh, I see.
I mean, it's not like I'm half ready
to explode or anything,
but what can I do so first-time viewers
don't get scared away?
Current worry: How to not scare people when you meet them
I have a good one for this!
Huh?
So, after you finish a sentence,
you say, "Man, that was good."
No matter what you say, at the end,
you whisper, "Man, that was good."
Oh, I see!
Boss's Answer: Say "Man, that was good"
after every sentence
So, like, when you mention
what you did today, like...
"Hey, I ate XYZ today," you stick it on the end.
Try it out.
I did my best today!
Man, that was good.
Hey, isn't that kinda weird?
You okay? Boss?
Huh? That's funny...
Hold on, it sounds like it was supposed to be a joke.
Man, that was good.
Maybe you need to breathe?
Like, while sucking in your drool-
Saliva? You mean suck in my saliva?
I-Is the drool part important?
Sucking your drool.
Man, that was good.
Hey, isn't that kinda weird?
Oh, and this!
"Heee!" Try laughing like that.
Here's another racehorse.
Hey, you've never laughed like that before, Boss!
Make them think, "They're really laughing hard."
Like, "They really think that was funny."
Heaaa!
Can I get a cut?! Cut!
I really don't like this!
"Man, that was good. Heee!" Like that.
Heeaaa!
How do you do that, Boss?
Yeah, this won't work.
Dum-dum, that was fun!
Hey, that last one was good.
I like it.
Let's stick with that!
Okay!
Say, "I'm going to take a bath and go to bed."
Dum-dum, that was fun!
That's good. Really good.
This is pretty cute.
Nice. I like that.
This is cute, so I guess it won't scare them?
Yeah, I like it.
That was fun!
Pose also included.
Heee!
Hey, can you stop doing that?
With that done...
We're accepting requests for advice from you.
Yeah!
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique,
personally-signed request fulfilled sticker.
So please send in your submissions!
Send them in!
Bye-bye!
*pose*