"Once you've decided something,
you go through with it no matter what.
However, once you're hooked, that's all you do."
Darn... they're right on the money.
"You have a devastatingly low
possibility of dating."
Whaaa—
So it's saying I should make my job my life?!
This show is brought to you by Ookami Mio, and...
...Nekomata Okayu, and...
...Robocosan!
Good morning, everyone!
Good morning...
Where's the energy, everyone?
Before we get into this exciting project,
let's have our fabulous members introduce themselves.
Were you always like this?
Is something wrong?
She's more...
You're not drunk, are you?
No, no, no.
Hellobo!
I'm hololive Gen 0's virtual robot, Roboco.
What's this about?
I'm Nekomata Okayu from hololive Gamers.
I'm Ookami Mio from hololive Gamers.
I'd like to fire you guys up before we start,
Is she okay?
I wonder.
but first, I have some bad news for you all.
Steel yourselves.
Wait, with no windup?
Is this that kind of show?
What kind of news?
Today might decide your fate.
Mhmm.
My fate?
Who has the best fortune in the second half of 2021?
Holo
Fortune Ranking!
What?!
What?
We had the young,
mysterious fortune teller, Anan-san,
who predicted the future success of many celebrities,
tell the fortunes of the four of us.
We got someone with real celebrity clout.
One way or another,
we were able to have them tell our fortunes!
Yay!
That's so cool!
It sure is.
You're all interested in fortunes, right?
I am! I am! I am! I am!
Enough to have Mio-chan tell my fortune before.
Mio-chan's told your fortunes before,
Ookami Mio is good at tarot reading and often
tells the fortunes of the other hololive members
and now, she'll be having her own fortune told.
We'll be revealing your fortunes
one by one by their ranking.
Prior to this, do you remember a person
on the management team
asking for a picture of your palm?
Yeah, I do!
There was.
Oh, yeah.
I thought they just wanted to see my hand.
That's scary.
I'd like to start from 3rd place of
the latter half of 2021's fortune rankings.
What?!
It's already ranked?
It is!
Already?!
And in 3rd place is...
Anything but 4th.
Nekomata Okayu-san!
First one out.
True.
Apparently, they can tell what
your personality is from reading your palm.
"You're a quiet person
who excels at supporting others.
You're highly intuitive, and acting on instinct alone
goes well for you, so others end up envying you.
On the other hand, thinking doesn't do you any good,
so when you're worried about something,
stop thinking and take action!"
I totally understand.
Do you?
So you're the intuitive type.
I rely on my intuition a lot! After all...
I moved to Tokyo on a whim.
On a whim?!
Oh, you came here on a whim?
Let's move on to your work fortune!
"Your work fortune in the latter half of 2021 is...
Good!"
Ooh!
So even 3rd place can get "Good"s.
That's great!
"Even if you work true to yourself,
others will still find that interesting,
and your popularity will continue
to rise next year onward."
Ooh.
Ooh!
"When you don't know what to do,
believe in your intuition!"
Going with your gut seems crucial.
How much is using my brain backfiring for me?
Let's move on to your romance fortune.
Oh?
Romance, huh...
"Your romance fortune for the latter half of 2021 is...
I'm excited.
Ominous!"
Too bad.
Wait, ominous?!
"You struggle to control your emotions,
leading to your partners burning out.
However, you've just entered the period of
your life where you'll run into your fated partner.
But if you miss this opportunity,
you'll struggle with romance for the next 15 years,
so don't procrastinate!"
So specific!
15?!
I'm speedrunning to a single life.
I'm in a pinch.
I gotta find a partner from one of the Onigiris.
Eenie-meenie-miney-moe...
She's choosing her dinner!
The results for 3rd place didn't seem that bad.
It wasn't bad at all!
Pretty good.
Now then, 2nd place is...
Ookami Mio!
What, me?!
Nooo! No more!
It's just the two of you left.
One of them will be last place
Oh no...
"You're an honest but realistic person
who chases after their ideals and dreams.
You aim high, but you also form
a realistic plan of action to achieve your goals.
While you're full of love to give,
you end up holding everything in
and consequently snap at your partner with
phrases like 'Why can't you understand me?!'"
She's got social anxiety.
I feel like the "honest but realistic person who chases
after their ideals and dreams" description fits her.
Right?
Yeah.
Oh, really?
She's well put together, but she's also clumsy.
Yeah, she is.
She shows that side of her at times, so it fits.
"Your work fortune for the latter half of 2021 is...
Great!"
Whoa, really?
"Your work will become a centerpiece of your life,
and you won't run out of job offers any time soon."
Is this about this current job?
That's amazing!
That's amazing.
Let's move on to her romance fortune
for the latter half of 2021.
It's...
"Disastrous."
Hold on, her love life's gonna be that bad?!
Is this why I'm 2nd?
Yes.
"You have a devastatingly low
possibility of dating."
Whaaa—
"You don't have a desire to start a relationship,
but before that, you don't have sex appeal."
That's so mean!
That's not true!
I'll have you know, Mio-chan's as sexy as can be!
She's sexy!
Step outside!
"However, that is not to say that
you won't be able to marry in the future.
You may be compatible with eccentric people,
foreigners, people 20 years apart,
or people considered strange
by those around them."
Huh...
So it's saying I should make my job my life?!
That does seem to be the case.
Now it's just 1st and 4th left.
Can I just leave?
Who knows, you might be 1st, Roboco-san!
That's right!
You guys have a point...
Who'll be last?
Please not 4th.
I don't want to be last either.
Last place is...
Please don't be me...
Please...
"Friend A," me!
My heart stopped for a bit!
"You're a person with insane mental fortitude
who is never perturbed by the opinions of others.
You're a free spirit to the core." Am I really?
That fits my image of her.
Wait, really?! I didn't think you saw me like that.
"Moreover, you get more and more energetic
the older you get, so your health is no issue."
I'm so jealous!
"You sometimes act quite recklessly,
so don't forget to double think your actions."
Like that thing at the start.
Ah, right.
That, huh?
Good morning, everyone!
Good morning...
Things like this.
Let's move on to my work fortune.
My work fortune for the latter half of 2021 is...
"Terrible."
Whaaat?!
Why?
"You work diligently,
but you tend to be pessimistic,
and because of that,
your coworkers often worry about you.
You should watch out for
work-related accidents for the next 3 years.
Watch out for
money-related scandals in particular."
Don't do it, A-chan!
Lending or borrowing money is a no-go!
That's scary biz.
"The money you lend won't ever come back."
Eeek!
That's certainly terrible.
It sure is.
Next up is my romance fortune.
This one is...
"Disastrous."
They're all pretty bad.
You're 4th place, after all.
Really?!
"You're nice to people,
but they may see you as meddlesome."
Wha... It's going nowhere.
"However, you don't seem to have a desire
to marry, so does this one even matter?"
Hey!
So that means...
That means!
My mood is lifted!
Oh?
Without further ado, our most fortunate member
for the latter half of 2021 is Robocosan!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
On to her personality.
"You don't usually assert yourself,
so you're seen as the quiet type.
However, you have a strong rebellious spirit.
Once you've decided something,
you go through with it no matter what.
However, once you're hooked, that's all you do."
Darn... they're right on the money.
"You perform better under pressure,
but you also can't find the motivation
until you have your back against the wall."
Manager-san, please back her into a corner.
It sounds kind of like her.
That's so me.
"Your work fortune for the latter half of 2021 is...
Gr—"
No, "Excellent!"
Wow!
"Robocosan is a renaissance woman.
She'll earn a large sum from starting a side job."
A side job?!
I guess I'll start something.
Apart from hololive?
I'll start something.
Disclaimer: Results of palm reading
may not reflect actual plans
Maybe like a YouTube channel showing off your cat?
Disclaimer: Results of palm reading
may not reflect actual plans
Nice idea!
I'll be on as a guest, too.
All right!
Disclaimer: Results of palm reading
may not reflect actual plans
"Your romance fortune is...
Excellent!"
This one is also really good.
Isn't my luck a little OP?
Whoa!
"You're extremely popular.
Your sex appeal and pheromones are overflowing,
so people may approach you randomly.
What?!
"However, you have so many choices
that you might lose out on all of it.
You also have a higher chance of being
approached by good-for-nothings, so be aware."
That's no good.
You'll need to have a discerning eye.
Next up is your lucky item.
"A black hair tie.
It will reduce the chance of
good-for-nothings approaching you."
Say no more.
How many do I need to wear?
That's all for the fortunes
That was fun!
They were pretty accurate, too.
Leave for me, the fortunes were on the lucky side.
Yeah, A-chan's were a bit shaky.
Right.
They were.
Just try not to be pessimistic about work.
That's right. Call me if you ever need me.
Thank you, everyone. You're all very kind.
I'll live on with the vitality of a cockroach.
If you enjoyed this video,
please smash that like button and
subscribe to the hololive Official Channel!
With that, we'll see you next time!
Thank you for watching!
Bye-bye!
This show has been brought
to you by Ookami Mio, and...
Nekomata Okayu, and...
Robocosan!