Throw it out!
Throw what out?
The very fact that I'm an idol right now is all thanks
to my fave being such a fantastic―
Good evening, everyone!
Welcome to the show!
This is holo's Bonjour,
a variety and talk show
where one of the guests
changes every month!
Yay!
Yaaay!
Yaaaaay!
*giggles*
Ya-yay!
Now then, let's introduce our cast for today!
Let's start off with me, the genius vampire!
Sweet bites!
It's your friendly vampire
from the Underworld, Yozora Mel!
Let's have some fun today!
Yaaaaaay!
Yay!
Our second guest is...
It's your shooting star, your diamond in the rough!
Idol VTuber, Hoshimachi Suisei is here!
A wink here!
You're cute today too!
And our third guest is...
Hello there!
I'm hololive 5th Gen's roaring lion, Shishiro Botan!
Thanks for having me!
The lion goes roar!
Thanks for coming!
Rooooar!
Yeeeaaah!
That's all of us!
The three of us will be doing today's show.
With all that said,
Yeah.
let's start with our first segment!
Alright.
Sure.
Random Rapid-Fire Interrogation!
Yaaaaaaaay!
The echo's quite a nice touch, isn't it?
You added in the echo, huh?
We're supposed to add in an echo?
I'll keep that in mind.
The echo lets it fill the entire space we have here.
Okay, got it.
So for this segment,
Botan-chan will be pelted
with a stream of questions from both me and Sui-chan.
Yep.
This would be your first time. Are you ready?
You ready?
I'm actually nervous!
What kind of questions, I wonder?
Hehehehe.
Let's start with my questions to Botan-chan, then.
Okay.
Starting!
Twenty questions. One after the other.
Start!
Q1: An artist you look up to?
An artist, huh?
Any artist is fine?
Yep! Any artist is fine!
Hmm, if that's the case...
One I look up to, or rather, one of my faves
has to be Björk.
Björk?
Björk is an Icelandic singer-songwriter.
Björk is an artist
Whoooa!
from overseas.
She's one of my inspirations.
What genre does she do?
Oh right, no deep dives yet.
Let's ask about it after...
Alright!
Q2: Where would you take me on a date?
That one, huh!
Erm... That question, huh...
I think I'd take you to
a haunted house.
I see.
And why is that?!
Let's leave the explaining for the end.
Q6: Anything new you want to try out?
I think one thing I've yet to do is
have an offline collab.
Q8: A dish you'd recommend?
Stir-fried shrimp and asparagus.
That's delish.
Q9: Do a cute confession!
A cute confession? Let's see...
I like you...!
There's even an echo...
Q10: A message to yourself two years from now?
I'll go with...
"Watch what you say."
That's pretty legit, actually.
Okay, that's it!
🔔🔔🔔🔔🔔
Good work!
Rapid fire?
That's all of my questions!
That was rapid fire?
I wonder if that qualifies?
It wasn't that rapid, but I'm actually
pretty curious about the artist
she mentioned in Question 1.
Could you recommend to us a song from her?
Let's see here.
People who watch movies would probably know
this song despite not knowing its name.
She did a song for the movie
called Dancer in the Dark. Ring any bells?
It's a duet song.
I see.
I'll take note of it.
Is it a rock song?
It's closer to alternative rock if you ask me.
It's a pretty emotional song.
Emotional?
That sounds good.
Thanks for sharing!
So you said you'd take me out to a haunted house.
Why did you pick that as a date spot?
I honestly just want to see
how Mel-senpai would react in such a place.
Are you good with haunted houses?
Bad with them?
I'm not good with them!
Oh really?
But yeah, I want to see your reactions.
Hence, haunted house.
I want to see your reactions too, so I guess it's good.
It could work. Let's go to one someday.
Yeah, let's do it.
An offline collab in one would be great.
I like that idea!
If you insist...
Let's have Sui-chan ask questions now!
Okay!
Sui-chan, if you please.
We're going full auto!
High speed!
Rapid fire!
Let's GO!
Q11: Favorite color?
Black!
Q12: (D*sney) Land or (D*sney) Sea?
Land!
Q14: Recent obsessions?
Hmm...
Crap. Looking at cat comics!
Q15: Favorite food?
Shrimp!
Oho.
Q19: You free after?
For a bit, maybe.
Q20: What's your LINE ID?
I have one but
I only use it for coupons and stuff.
🔔🔔🔔🔔🔔🔔🔔🔔🔔
You said here that your favorite food is shrimp
and you recommended stir-fried shrimp and asparagus...
There's asparagus there too.
I really love shrimp.
Oooh!
Yeah. Whenever a place
sells shrimp dishes, I'd often order those.
What kind of shrimp dishes?
Breaded shrimp?
Any kind, as long as it's shrimp!
I once went to a place famous for crab fried rice
and ate their shrimp rice.
Ahh!
Yeah, I can totally relate!
Ordering something other than the special.
I've totally done that before.
Between Land and Sea, you picked Land...
Going to Sea is fun too,
especially since 5th Gen went there once.
Oh, really?!
Yeah, we all went to Sea once.
We had a lot of fun there,
but I do think that
Sea is better suited for the drinkers.
Oh, I see.
I don't really drink,
so I'm probably better off in Land.
So you're saying Lamy-chan would be at home in Sea.
Definitely!
She does, huh?
Since we're still asking questions,
we should check if the viewers
have questions of their own.
Oh!
Do you guys have questions for Botan-chan?
Anyone?
Let's see...
Q: What flavor of ramen do you like?
Oh? That's a good question!
My favorite ramen flavor...?
Hmmmm.
I'm okay with anything,
but I usually eat iekei ramen.
Really? Same here!
[Iekei ramen]
A ramen bowl with tonkotsu-shouyu broth and thick, straight noodles
topped with nori, chashu, spinach, and sliced onions.
Whoa!
You too?
Yeah! I love iekei ramen!
Iekei! Iekei!
It's really delicious!
You really love it, huh?
I really much do!
Just leave out the spinach.
What, why?!
Just throwing away the spinach...
Star of the bowl: spinach.
Let's move on to our next segment.
Here it is!
Genius Vampire Test!
Woo!
Woo! Hoo!
🦉🦉🦉🦉
It's that time again.
It's time for this
demonic game again.
First time, Botan-chan?
Yeah, it is!
I don't quite know the rules yet...
Alright, let me explain then.
In this segment,
Rules
you just have to fill out a middle-school level quiz
A middle school-level quiz
and see how much you can score!
How much can you score?
But as you all know, I'm a genius vampire from the Underworld,
Definition: An awesome person.
Kind of a big deal.
so there's no way I can be wrong!
Can never be wrong!
Yep.
That means,
all my responses become the right answer!
Every other answer is wrong!
Whaaat?!
This'll be tough...
It's really strict.
You have to think like an Underworlder.
You guys will do fine.
Yeah.
Alright.
So I'd have to give an answer,
or rather, the common answer,
and then check if it is the correct answer...?
Yes, exactly.
Well, I guess.
Underworld logic, after all.
But if that's the case, then―
I might phrase this weirdly,
but, uh,
say I bluff out a wrong answer
while claiming that you would
actually answer like this.
It would be really awkward if you call it correct, right?
That would be super awkward!
That's one way
to look at it, yes.
"So you had that impression of me, huh..."
Yeah, like that.
Let's start off the first quiz then.
A'ight.
Here is the first quiz!
Ta-da!
Ta-da.
Give the S's of cooking!
Pretty much the basics.
It seems like
today's quizzes are all about the home.
That's right.
The moment I heard the theme,
I went, "Home... Chores...?"
Yeah.
To be honest, I think this is
pretty important for us,
being women and all.
Right.
I guess?
As knowledge.
Even as idols!
Right!
As idols, we need to
make sure that
we know these things.
I'm sure you all have an idea now.
Let's start with Sui-chan's answer!
I'm sure I got everything right.
Absolutely perfect.
Take a good look.
So confident.
Of course.
Okay.
Her answer!
Ta-da!
Satou (sugar), shio (salt), su (vinegar),
serori (celery), miso.
That's a vegetable, right?
It's essential
in the S's of cooking.
Oh, hmm.
She has a point.
You can't just be eating all meat.
Yes, exactly.
Celery is necessary.
Yeah.
Like as a palette cleanser.
Yeah, that's it.
I hate celery though.
I don't like it too.
Not too fond of it either.
Aaagh!
Well then...
This might actually be...
This is incorrect!
Next up, let's look at Botan-chan's answer!
Sure.
Slide please!
Satou (sugar), shio (salt), su (vinegar),
shouyu (soy sauce), miso.
Miso!
Actually,
I was thinking what
Mel-senpai would write here for se.
What were you thinking of?
I had a moment where I thought you would
write something like seabura (back fat).
I wouldn't write that there!
Geez, Botan-chan.
Hold on...
Shouyu does fit in se!
Oh, it's correct.
In human terms.
Correct in human terms, at least.
Oh, okay.
Shouyu would probably be in shi for Underworlders.
That's...
Oh! I think there's an old reading to it!
Yeah, that!
se = soy sauce (seuyu)
They wrote it as seuyu.
Just like with butterfleoge (butterfly)?
Yes, it's seuyu.
Hold up. That's so smart.
Seriously.
Botan-chan's really showing off her smarts here.
It's so big-brained.
The praise is unwarranted,
please stop.
The bar―
Please don't make it harder.
Want to raise the bar?
I see.
So this is the human answer.
Yeah, this is how humans would answer it.
In that case,
let me show you how a genius Underworld vampire
gives her answer!
Here it is.
The correct answer!
Let's see.
Satou (sugar), shio (salt), su (vinegar),
seiso ni (clean and), soboku ni (simple).
Yes.
Soboro?
Yeah, I also thought
she meant soboro.
Soboro― Soboro―
I'm getting hungry right now!
What you're saying is
you should keep cooking clean and simple.
Exactly. You shouldn't be too messy,
or like,
cooking isn't about how it looks anyway.
Plain and simple is good as long as there's love.
Ahh...
Is it like,
"It's not the seasoning that matters,
but the feelings that went into it."
Yes, that sort of idea!
Thou must reconsider thy feelings!
The ways of the Underworld are deep!
See, this is the reason why
you shouldn't be bound by common sense.
The Underworld makes a great point here.
Yeah.
We're beat.
Blown out.
That's Mel-senpai for you.
Yeah.
Keep this in mind, everyone.
We got three points each here, right?
Three points.
It's three poi―
Same score, huh!
Yep, same score.
I'm not gonna lose, Shishiro!
Won't lose!
Who's gonna win?
It seems like sugar, salt, and vinegar are
also Underworld staples.
You're right.
That's true.
Seems to be orthodo―
Wait a minute―
They're exactly the same!
Basically, yeah.
There might not be much difference in taste
between the human world and the Underworld
when it comes to food.
Not much, yeah.
That's good.
The difference isn't much.
True.
Okay, let's move on!
Here is our second quiz problem!
Give the name of the veggie slicing
technique used in the picture.
I think we can handle this.
I think we can, but...
Probably.
It's just that...
This, uh...
Does this foodstuff even exist in the Underworld?
Ah, I see what you mean.
Of course it does. That's a carrot.
*coughs*
Huh?
Oh.
So that's settled?
Sure looks like it!
Yeah, sure.
That makes sense.
Okay then, hold on.
Here's my answer.
Let's start.
Go on, Sui-chan.
Alright.
Quarter slice.
I don't think I'm wrong.
How romantic!
Romantic?
Romantic...?
Oh, you mean like a paysanne cut?
Oh, yeah right!
It does look like a fancy
and French way of slicing.
It took me a while to notice.
Yeah.
Do Underworlders do this too?
We prefer the brunoise cut.
Oh, brunoise!
Oh, wow!
That's pretty interesting.
We have a lot more down there.
Next up, Botan-chan!
I also answered quarter slice.
Paysanne!
Yeah.
Botan-chan also gave a romantic answer.
She sure did.
Just what's going on down there...
Don't question it.
In the Underworld,
we call it like this!
Something like reverse cut?
Solace Slash!
Oh, I see now!
Behold.
Solace Slash.
Oh okay. I see.
I'm not too fond of this cut.
It works for most dishes though, right?
True.
I guess it works.
And if you notice,
Everyone uses it.
it's "slash," not "cut" or "slice."
Oh, you're right!
It's a bit more advanced from just cutting.
Oh yeah, you got it wrong.
Sui-chan got it wrong.
Does everyone
in the Underworld use a katana to cut stuff?
Yep.
Society down there gets pretty rough, after all.
Makes sense.
I had a feeling that would be the case.
Is it some sort of basic Underworld technique?
It sounds like it.
Going like, "Solace Slash!"
It's cool, right?
Yeah, I guess it is.
Let's move on to the next segment!
Title card, please!
Wish Away Your Worries Upon a Shooting Star!
Yaaaay!
Yaaaaaaaaay!
For this segment,
our viewers have sent in some minor problems
Rules
Every single thing my beloved shooting star does
is so precious, I'm starting to get addicted to her!
What do I need to do to actually develop an addiction?
they have in their daily lives.
Suisei's answer
Don't get addicted.
Befitting of a shooting star, I've come up with
quick and haphazard solutions to those problems,
Suisei's answer
???
and you'll try to predict what they are!
Guess Suisei's answer!
Is that clear?
Bam.
"What makes Suisei Train move?!"
"Thinking about it keeps me up all day!"
Yeah.
What makes it move...
Both of you know what Suisei Train is, yeah?
I do.
Suisei Train goes choo, choo...
You wanna get on, don'tchu, choo!
That's how it goes.
If I remember correctly, Suisei Train can
do three revolutions around the Earth in a second.
What.
Makes you wonder how
Suisei Train is actually powered.
This isn't really a personal problem though.
It's more of a question, yeah.
Let's give an answer.
It's a question!
Thinking time starts now!
Wait, what did you say?
Three times around the Earth?
I'm done writing.
Maybe it's this...?
Has to be this.
Can't be anything else.
Mel-chan's still deep in thought.
Okay.
I'm done.
Alright, let's start by
looking at Mel-chan's answer.
Sure.
Mel-chan.
"Everyone's support...!
... is what you thought I'd say, huh?"
That's so Sui-chan!
I got it?
Like looking at a mirror.
I'd definitely say that.
It's on-brand.
This train isn't gonna play nice.
You're all getting a rough ride!
No mercy for everyone!
Okay, next is Shishiro Botan.
Here you go.
"Nuclear power."
Not wrong, per se!
I mean,
It makes sense!
if you can go around the Earth thrice,
then you have to be nuclear.
So I'm thinking Suisei-senpai might have a reactor in her.
I see.
I won't deny that this might be the answer.
Having said all of that,
what is the correct answer?
Let's find out. Here's my answer to this!
It's powered by my fave!
Your fave?
Think about it for a sec.
That makes a lot of sense!
I wouldn't even budge if not for my fave.
The very fact that I'm an idol right now is all thanks
to my fave being such a fantastic idol themselves.
Just seeing them makes me want to be like them
and stand in the same way as an idol.
That's why I―
Understand?
Understood.
Got it?
That's my life.
Your fave, huh.
Yes, it's my fave.
Their name is Nmwrwrbr.
Sui-chan's Fave
Nmwrwrbr Rbwebrwrwr-san (temporary name)
Their full name is Nmwrwrbr Rbwrbrwrwr-san.
Please understand.
I can't say it in full here.
Okay.
Alright then, let's move on to the next question―
Scratch that. Problem, not question.
"Every morning, I'm glued to both my bed and phone.
"Do you have any tips on how I can get out of bed
"so I can get to work and studying as early as possible?"
Let's get to
resolving their problem.
Done.
We're all done?
Yep!
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's start off with Botan-chan this time.
Sure.
Ms. Shishiro.
Here.
"Throw it out."
Throw what out?
Everything!
Take your work and study
and throw it all out!
I like how you think!
Now, how about you, Mel-chan?
Okay!
Ta-da!
"Take off that bed!"
That makes sense.
It's not wrong!
Yeah.
You shouldn't be sleeping on the bed anyway.
Yeah, exactly!
Don't sleep on it!
If you don't sleep on a bed,
then you won't need to get out of bed.
True, true.
Sleep on the chair if you have to.
Sleep on the chair!
I'll be revealing my answer now.
With this, I'm very sure
I've solved everyone's problems.
Behold!
"Just get up."
Get up already.
They're, uh,
they're asking how to get out of bed though...
Is this a cliffhanger?!
Like making them watch the next part in a separate video.
Well, if you just want them to get up,
then I guess they would do it
since you said they should.
Ah!
Could happen.
By the way,
I'm not the type to get out of bed early either.
I'd spend my mornings
lying on the bed
while fiddling with my phone,
thinking about how I don't wanna get up.
But it seems that if you get past that urge
and get out of bed
as soon as you wake up from sleep,
it could, uh,
lead to better waking mornings,
or at least that's what science says.
Ooh.
Yeah, that's why―
Yes!
Like, serious advice here is
Willpower!
if you really wanna get up and do stuff,
then you should get out of bed
as soon as your alarm starts ringing.
That sounds right.
This seems to be the best way.
You'll feel more motivated too.
Let's all get out of bed.
It's willpower.
Just do it!
I know you can!
Alright!
Next, we have
a brand new segment!
The title is
Okay, Shishiron! Search and Lock On!
Yaaaaay!
Botan-chan will handle this segment!
Please explain the rules.
Okay! So for this segment,
Rules
you all know how whenever you look up
stuff you don't know
Shishiro Botan
in a search engine,
you would see the number of hits, right?
Like it says, "About *** results"
Around 3,310,000 results
after you press Enter.
Yeah.
You can use the AND function of the search engine
Goal: Reduce to around 1,200,000 results
to further restrict the search space.
Shishiro Botan cute
Add search terms
The goal here is to get as close
Who would be closest to the goal?
as possible to the target number of results.
That's how it goes.
I see!
However, you will receive a penalty
Shishiro Botan shiitake
if you go below the target number!
Going too low nets you a penalty!
WHAAAAAT?!
Whoa!
Please keep that in mind.
We can't narrow it down too much then!
I don't like this!
Narrowing it down too much is also bad, yes.
I want to stay visible!
I don't wanna disappear from Bonjour!
You might fade away.
I might slowly fade away.
Our first search term is...
"summer vacation"
If you input "summer vacation" in the search engine,
you'll get a lot of hits.
The number's at around 110 million results.
That's a big number.
As expected of summer vacation.
What we'll do now is narrow down the number of results.
Our first target would be...
Let's go for 10 million hits.
10 million!
10 million, huh.
Taking out the 100 million!
Add a search term so that it goes down
from 110 million results to just 10 million.
We have to shave off 100 million from this, you know?!
Alright! Thinking time starts now!
Ehh?!
🔔🔔🔔🔔
I'm also participating in this,
Oh, you are?
so it's possible for me to be hit by the penalty as well.
Ahaha! Is that so?
Shishiro Botan.
Yeah. Anyway, "summer vacation," huh...
I think this is a good one.
Ah!
I'll go with this.
This is hard.
Makes you think.
I'm struggling here.
Does everyone have an answer?
I'm done!
Same!
Okay then!
Thinking time, stop!
🔔🔔🔔🔔🔔
These were the words
that we used to narrow the search!
Ta-da!
Are they up?
Ooh.
Hmm, okay.
Let's hear from Suisei-senpai first.
August 32nd is
such a power move.
I'll explain later.
Okay. Um, so,
Steam is a PC game store platform.
I was thinking
that "games" would be a good search term.
My first thought for "summer" was "video games."
Mmhm.
There are a lot of summer-themed games too.
Plus―
A lot of stuff is on sale.
Yeah, that!
The Steam Summer Sale
had already ended as of late July 2021.
That's why I thought adding in "Steam" would at least
narrow down the search results quite well.
I can see that.
You might just get close to 10 million.
She might.
Feeling good.
Next, Mel-senpai.
My answer is pretty similar to Botan-chan's.
They are, yeah.
Yep.
"forever"
Mm, yeah.
Might be a good move.
Indeed.
Mel-senpai and I basically had the same idea.
I wrote "August 32nd."
"Don't let it end,"
Yeah, I get that.
It's such a good idea.
is what I was going for.
There are a lot of stories
and urban legends around August 32nd.
I've heard of those.
Right, it also comes up sometimes in the related searches.
Okay, could staff please
check the number of results
for Mel-san's "summer vacation forever"?
Thank you.
*klangklangklangklang*
🥁🥁🥁🥁🥁🥁🥁
Whoa!
Oh?
7,810,000 hits!
So close!
It's a bit below 10 million!
It's lower.
Damn close!
Crap, I might be too low!
Almost...
It's close!
It's pretty close.
It's a bit lower
than 10 million though.
Okay, next.
Please check the numbers for
Suisei-senpai's "summer vacation Steam."
Ah, crap.
🥁🥁🥁🥁🥁🥁🥁
I should have just written "game"!
🥁
:SuiScream:
1,200,000 hits!
That's so low!
:SuiShriek:
I blew off too much...
It's the summer sale! Buy games!
Steam Summer Sale is over
She's right! You guys should be buying games now!
Okay, now for the last one.
Please check the numbers for
my search term, "summer vacation August 32nd"!
I should be close to Mel-senpai.
What will pop up...
Good question!
*klangklangklang*
:SuiShrill:
Wait.
It's the most―
That's a lot!
78 million!
Seriously?!
Why is it that much?!
I didn't expect this.
It's more than we expected,
Oh?
but it's far off the mark.
Way off.
If we're looking for the closest answer,
then it's Mel-senpai.
Yeah.
That's true.
Would that make me second place?
Yeah.
I would be, right?
The number I got
was way too big.
Seems like everyone was
combining them as search terms.
Looks like it.
We're getting the penalty, aren't we?
How will this go?
What's gonna happen?
Are we really gonna get it?
You're joking.
They just flashed "Wanna fade?" at us!
Yeah, let's do it.
Just a bit then, sure.
Yeah, just a bit.
AAAAAA!
Aaaaa!
I can see the window!
The window!
Aaaaaaah! I'm fading away!
Give me back my existence!
Extras
How would you do a chunk cut?
Chop like mad, I guess.
RAGE
Cut with all your rage.
Please search "ghost" with "Minagawa Junji."
No honorifics, sorry.
Sorry for the rudeness.
Sorry for that, Junji.
We are very sorry.
Sorry for not adding "-san."
Sui-chan...?
:SuiShock:
Where are you...?
I'm. Right. Here!
We can't see you!
RIGHT. HERE.
If you're out there,
I'M RIGHT HERE GUYS.
give us a sign!
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub channel
on NicoNico for the full stream archives!
Look for the aura of my soul!