This is a disaster.
Aren't you gonna ask what happened?
Wh-What happened?
Just this morning, I've tripped on the sidewalk,
gotten chased by a dog,
slipped on a banana peel,
and landed in a barrel.
Today's been a total disaster.
Seriously?
Now I'm stuck and can't get out.
Fine, I'll help ya out.
Can you, though?
Ever heard of "beggars can't be choosers"?
Okay, here I go.
Wait, you're bruteforcing this?
One, two...
Owwie!
Not happening!
Stop! Stop!
Shuba!
Yikes.
Ooomaru-maru-maru Pol-Polka!
Eek! A murder!
Huh?
No murders allowed in my classy daily life!
Adios!
What is wrong with that sham fox?
Miko!
And Nene!
Well, they won't be useful.
What're you doing in a barrel, Towa-sama?
I wanna play with the barrel too!
Does it look like I'm having fun here?
I got stuck in here due to a banana peel.
Wow, you're ditzier than I thought.
Don't wanna hear it from the Priestess of Klutz.
Who're you calling a klutz?!
Anyway, let's get Towa-senpai outta there.
I'll show you what elite experience can do!
Actually, no thanks, I'll pass!
Three-Minute Cooking
Add in lots of stuff!
Stir well!
And voilà? Voilà!
Looks kinda like a popular toy.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!