'Tis I!
Freeing us from the freeze,
spring is in full bloom!
Salmon!
But 'tis also the season
when people tend to slack.
Bear!
I'm going to find those slackers
and whip them into shape.
I'll have them screaming "onigosh!"
Sally I forth!
Man, I just cannot be bothered!
Leading off, oni in the house!
Going, going, gone!
You! Stop slacking off!
What's this now?!
I have come to cure your May Blues.
Get your mojo back!
This is sensory overload!
Eat this!
Eek! Don't bean me!
Run away!
Yeesh, what was that all about?
Did you like it?
Zip it!
What now?!
I expected this might happen
and made Roboco-san overheat beforehand!
Just what were you expecting?!
Indoor temperature rising! Indoor temperature rising!
My body's burning up.
Is this... love?
No, it's all her!
Hot! Too hot!
This is not good!
Hah! Gotcha!
Can't laze around in this heat, can you?
Hot... too hot...
What a moroni.
Live by the sword,
die by the sword.
This heat's gonna get us both!
Tell a bad pun. It'll go away.
Bad puns are how eye roll!
She's actually laughing?!
C-Cool story...
A-Anyway, we stopped it somehow.
Did you like it?
Come here for a sec.
What's up?
Strike three, oni out!
Show May who's boss!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!