Did she run out of battery?
Oww...
O-Oh, hello there!
That's an RIP.
Huh?
Oh.
Nooo!
See? RIP.
Repairing
Phew. By the way...
What are you doing?
Aqua-chan stopped movin', you see.
Huh? Isn't she just asleep?
Didn't budge even when
you came crashing down.
Oh, true.
Any idea what could've caused this?
Hmm...
Nope.
Yeah, right!
You totally know!
Why'd you do it?!
Because the pendulum's there.
Mallory Korone?!
What're we gonna do to fix this?
It's all your fault!
Ah...
Phwoop.
I smell sushi over there!
Gotta bring it back!
Gotcha!
Oh no, my excessive strength!
Got it!
*huff puff* Nice job!
Wait, that's your own damn tail!
Get back here!
Bow, wow!
My pigtails!
Hold up!
Whoa!
My hat!
Give it back!
Huh?
Huh...?
Huh? What was I...?
We're truly sorry!
Huh?
She'll be hologra's mascot.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!