The office feels spacious!
Who goes there?!
We got rid of all the boxes lying around!
hololive's Three Super Musketeers?!
It's only two of 'em.
Witness
Friend A
Friend A had this to say on the matter:
Oh, man, they were a huge help!
I hope you got paid for it.
Oh, for sure.
Wait, did these guys get a big stack?!
We got a whole bunch of
"You helped!" stamps.
What're you, eight?!
You're being exploited!
Isn't that illegal?
Suspect
Friend A
What? A crime?
Hold up, don't handcuff me.
So much space!
But it feels a li'l empty.
Want to decorate?
Oh, let's go buy some stuff
to leave around the place!
Sounds good.
Full speed ahead!
So huge!
What is this place?
JUSCO's got it all.
Well, yeah...
Korone, stop running around!
Wait, that's just a dog!
Hmm? This delectable aroma...
They have taiyaki!
Mikochi?!
Gotta stay calm and keep in touch.
"Where are you guys?"
"Here."
Where even?!
Oh, I'm glad you're back, Mikoch...
Do you mind filling me in?!
What do you live for?
Why do you get baked every day?
Do you get "You helped!" stamps?
*snap*
You fool! Apologize to it right this instant!
And so we had a good time at JUSCO.
Guess who's back!
Back again!
We didn't shop together at all.
What'd you two get?
Let's show and tell!
I don't mind, but you didn't buy
any messed up stuff, did you?
Remember, this is an idol agency.
Oh, please. Have some faith in us.
Yeah. We're all in this together, right?
You guys... Yeah, you're right.
That's totally messed up!
Look, I could feel it calling out to me, okay?!
Oh, yeah?
Well, I'm calling you out now!
I didn't fool around.
I got something useful.
Wait... have they infested this office?
Hey, look at this!
What now?!
Palmtop moai!
Go return it!
What are you all up to?
Sora-chan?!
Y-Yikes.
What's so yikes? Come on, tell me.
Eek!
Just kidding. You've been trying to
improve this office, right?
You can have these.
What's this stuff?
"You helped!" stamps!
Only the goodest girls get them, okay?
Y'know, these stamps...
...are pretty neat.
Currently farming "You helped!" stamps!
If you enjoyed this, smash that like button!