Nicely done!
Nice!
Aww...
It ended before I could get back again!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Game Shop Maruyama
Get to work, girls.
Okay, I can't tell if you're cleaning
or causing a mess.
We're cleaning!
Look at us clean!
Cleaning the Store
Cleaning!
Uh, get the... the...
We're cleaning!
Huff... puff...
Get the chair.
Your sleeves aren't sweeping the floor, right?
Feeling itchy, Boss?
Let's make this spotless.
Leave it over there.
Towa-chan, the right side of my face.
The right side?
Yeah.
A little more...
There, there!
Right there!
Hey, Boss!
Don't go feelin' good over there!
What are you doing?!
Maruyama Theater: (The Real) Episode One
The First Customer
Nice and clean!
Perfectly done.
Perfect!
But wait, look!
We have a customer!
Welcome!
Thanks for having me!
Today's Guest:
Yukihana Lamy
Welcome!
Lamy-chan!
Narrator:
Friend A
(A-chan)
There we have it!
Our guest this time is Yukihana Lamy-san!
MENT
LUCK
Yukihana Lamy
About Her: Loves her fans to death
Hobbies: Streaming, drinking
Finishing Move: Smile of the Lamy
(Puts a smile on everyone's face)
The heart-shaped cowlick is very cute!
But... those are some interesting answers.
You love your booze?
I love my booze with all my heart.
Biggest Appeal:
Drinking Streams
She drinks, uh, a lot.
What do you usually drink?
Uh...
What's your style?
Mainly sake.
But I'll drink anything with alcohol.
Anything.
Anything?!
Anything goes?
Dayum.
Really?
Do you all get together for drinks?
I have drunk with her before.
What's she like drunk?
She, uh, didn't go crazy.
She stayed sane?
Well, Marine-senpai gets wasted really quickly.
That's right.
Lamy can hold it.
But she gets really cute when drunk.
Oh.
I've seen how she gets on her drinking streams.
She gets drunk and becomes super clingy.
Yeah, she looks the needy type.
What's that supposed to mean?
But yeah, that's it.
Moving on...
Whoa, 5* for luck?
You gave yourself that,
so you think you're lucky?
Well, you know...
Just getting to join hololive
was the biggest stroke of good luck possible.
Ah, how sweet.
I'd say that was more skill than luck.
Yeah, yeah!
They do say luck is a skill itself.
Q to Lamy: What do you make of the three?
A question to Lamy-san:
What does she make of the three poster girls?
For Subaru, "She's like the sun.
She brightens up everyone around her."
That's some praise.
I see her as bright and energetic.
Right on! Thanks!
How about Marine?
She has a way with words.
The gift of gab!
True that.
Though she does come on a bit too strong a lot...
Well, that's an issue.
That aside,
She's really, really nice.
She's always there for anyone who needs help.
A keen eye.
How about Towa?
As for Towa-senpai...
She makes me rethink my definition of devil.
Everything she says or does is angelic.
Everything She Does Is Angelic
Hey, you're ruining my gimmick!
TMT!
Stop that!
You know...
The Mighty angelic Towa-sama, and all that.
She was an angel in devil's clothing?
No more!
No more devil?
Not what I meant!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
I heard you guys would resolve my issues for me.
That's right.
Indeed we will.
We do sell games,
but we're no ordinary game shop!
We recommend video games
to customers who are facing issues
Game Shop Maruyama: A place that recommends
video games to customers and
has them game their worries away!
and have them game their worries away!
Game over!
I see.
Well, can I get some help with my current problem?
Go for it!
Of course you can!
When I do collabs and stuff,
I usually let the people
who invite me on plan everything.
All the time.
For once, I'd like to take charge
and ask the other members to join me and stuff.
How can I do that?
And there we have our request!
In short, our guest's request is this:
She wants the leadership skills
to take charge and guide her colleagues.
Can we let her do this?
She's popping off.
What's your problem?
Marine Theater!
It's Marine's stage now!
That came out of nowhere.
She took over so suddenly.
You came to the right people!
We have the perfect game for you!
What is it?
Her moves...
...are so lame!
Maruyama's game recommendation is...
Monster Hunter Rise!
You can try it out here,
so would you like to?
Yes, I would love to!
That's the spirit!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Have you ever played the MonHun series, Lamy-san?
I have. I play it on stream a lot, too.
She's kind of an expert.
And it seems she played the previous entries, too.
She's the most experienced hunter of us all.
That's convincing, coming from Marine-chan,
who's better than the rest of us.
So, like, my Hunter Rank is 5.
And Yukihana Lamy's is...
Uh, 7, but you're really putting me on a pedestal.
Our Leader!
Master!
Master.
Captain!
General!
This is a lot of pressure.
Let's have her take charge.
Let's move on, shall we?
Take it away, Subaru-san.
Okay, Leader,
which hunter are we—
Wait, wrong word.
Not Hunter.
Okay, take two.
Which monster are we taking on first?
Okay, so the quest we'll be attempting
is 2* urgent hub quest, "Hellfire."
Our target is Magnamalo.
That's our monster.
Target: Magnamalo
Okay!
Gather up in the hub!
Assemble!
Good luck.
By the way, what'll your gear be?
I play Great Sword.
Oh, how cool.
That's a really awesome weapon.
Super cool.
While we're at it, let me see
the others' gear too. You first, Marine-chan.
Sure.
Take a look.
This is mine.
I have Horn Maestro,
and I clearly look like someone
about to play the horn.
True!
The horn does seem obvious, yes.
And, well, this horn on my back...
It's the exact same one Towa-sama has.
Oh, you two match.
But it's really good. It comes with continuous healing.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a very useful weapon.
How reassuring. Thanks for the concise explanation.
Okay, I'm done.
Next, Subaru.
Sure!
I brought the strongest-looking thing in the box.
Makes sense.
You only started playing recently.
Moving on, Towa.
My weapon's the same as the Captain's,
but my armor's the Bnahabra Set,
which looks over all else.
It's super cute.
How fashionable.
So, in order to provide more support for you all,
I have this Wide-Range armor,
which will heal you when I take potions.
Key to Victory: Wide-Range Skill
Allows items to also affect nearby allies.
Its effect and range go up by level.
That's nice to have.
That's our 7.
It'll help!
Okay!
Let's go!
Yep!
Set sail!
Okay, here we are.
So, this Magnamalo...
Yeah?
Its attacks are... really powerful.
Each hit could prove fatal.
Oh, boy.
So it'd be a good idea to buff yourself
with Spiribirds before you go.
That's right.
I'm getting worried about Subageezer.
If you see one, take it.
You should take Deodorant.
Deodorant?
Which is...?
It's in the box.
Deodorant: An item that cures Stench, hellfireblight, and blastblight when thrown down.
The smokey thing?
Deodorant...
You got it, Subageezer?
Subageezer got it.
Great!
Ready to go?
Let's go.
Let's follow our Master here.
Leader!
We gotta follow Leader Lamy!
Go, Leader!
I'm not good with pressure, you know...
Master! What's this big thing?
Which?
It's gone now.
You okay?
How free-spirited.
Okay, she got the Spiribirds.
Her defense has gone up.
Yeah, Subaru got it!
Nobody needs it, though.
You're setting death flags here.
I think we'll see it soon.
There it is!
Subageezer!
Go, Subageezer.
Go land the first blow.
Wait, gotta mine first.
Go for it!
Make it good.
Here goes Subageezer!
Always with the first blow.
And he's walking a bunch again...
Here goes Subageezer!
Ride your dog!
There's the first hit!
Guys!
Hang in there, Subageezer.
Good luck, Subageezer!
Shine!
Be careful, Subageezer.
I think I'll buff you all.
Bring it on!
Thank you!
I'll do it too.
Watch out for the hellfire.
Subageezer in trouble!
Subageezer!
He's on his last legs!
Head, tail, arms, and back.
You can break those parts.
Oh, okay, got it.
Quit moving!
Looking good.
Way to go.
Face is bad news!
We did break some parts.
Nice job!
What? Really?!
It freaked out and ran away.
Okay, pick up all this stuff now.
Yeah.
Oops, I messed up.
Booty, booty!
That was really smooth.
Yeah.
Master's amazing.
Have a Master really helps.
Okay, this is starting to feel good.
Whoa there.
You feel good?
All this praise feels nice.
My buddy's lost... Oh, there.
Are they being nice?
They really are!
But Lamy only talks in praise, so...
Don't make it sound like a bad thing!
What's wrong with that?
She'll praise you even if she has to lie.
Is that true, Lamy-chan?
I'm just praising you because you deserve it!
Is she doing it now?
Smooth.
Hey! Lamy!
It's not like that.
Oh, there it is.
I don't see Subageezer.
He's on a stroll right now.
Again, Subageezer?!
It's a regular feature with him.
Hang on. He needs his walks.
This hurts.
Well, he is an old man, after all.
Wait, is our target tired?
A little, yeah.
Maybe.
You can see it.
There goes the tail!
Nice break.
Impressive.
Hunt...
Whoa!
Be careful, Subageeer!
It evolved or something.
The color changed.
This...
This reddish-pink means it's raging.
It's mad.
Oh damn, is it reee-ing?
Subageezer!
I'm worried about his HP!
I need heals!
Wait!
Thank you! Thank you, guys!
Thank you all!
Wait, Subageezer's getting all dramatic.
Oh, wow.
It ran away.
Did its tail drop?
Its tail, yeah.
You can have it.
Remember to collect mats from the tail
Here it is.
Nice break.
Awesome!
Nice, we got the tail.
Tail!
Its rolls are bad news.
Yeah, need to dodge them.
This is crazy!
It's glowing more than Subageezer's face.
It's got you beat.
Subageezer, with the ultimate Harajuku Flash.
He wanted to be king of Takeshita Fashion Street!
Ow!
This sucks.
We're at Fashion Street right now?
This is a kind of fashion battle.
His facepaint's a bit fancy, you see.
Oh!
Very fancy.
No! Subageezer!
Press F for Subageezer
Subageezer!
RIP.
He'll run now.
Look, this is a badge of honor.
Okay, Subageezer, come back to us.
Don't worry. We'll wait.
Thanks!
This thing won't go down anytime soon.
It'll take time, so don't worry.
But it is tired.
Check the top-right.
It has the tired icon.
Tired icon!
Where you at, Subageezer?
Hurry up, Captain!
Wanna try and kill it before Subageezer gets here?
Don't!
I wanna see it go down!
Hang in there, Subageezer.
I will.
He's on a different show right now.
"I'm gonna make it back to Budokan!"
Hang in there.
I wanna get the items too, though.
Fight.
Huh?
Where am I?
We wanted to avoid this!
This outcome!
We'll need an alternate route now.
Absolutely.
I sent you a "Good!"
Another Story.
Nicely done!
Nice!
Nicely done.
We could only do it
thanks to Subageezer's attacks.
Y'know, I'm standing in front of a rock.
Subageezer Stands Still by Rock
That was a good hunt.
It really was.
Nicely done.
Nice and quick.
Now, Marine-senpai will...
Yeah.
...trade places with the Boss.
Thank you.
Wow, Boss Captain moves out?
Boss Captain!
Our bounds... strong...
More Hunting Coming Up!
Thanks, thanks.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Next up, it'll be Boss, Towa-senpai,
Subaru-senpai, and me
taking on a large monster.
Kick its ass!
Uh, Marine-senpai... What are you doing?
Uh, well...
I have nothing to do,
so I'll be the moderator.
Stop it! Nobody's cheating!
Stop it!
You doin' it right?
The quest we'll be attempting
is 3* hub quest, "A Friend In Need."
Our target is Tigrex.
Shall we go hunt the Tigrex?
Yeah!
Why so hype?
It's really, really fast.
It's fast?
Very, very fast.
Has your gear changed? I'd like to see.
Let's check.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's start from the left, with Lamy.
Sure. Earlier,
I was using Wide-Range to act as support.
It was a big help.
But I'm going for this time.
For some gacha feel.
How's it work?
Well, you see,
this has Divine Blessing.
It has a predetermined chance
of reducing the damage you take.
I see!
Sounds good.
You, Subaru-senpai?
This strong-looking thing.
Subageezer: Hammer
Look at him glow.
Look at all those buddies!
They're sniffing you!
Stop it!
That's a good visual.
I got fascinated by Subageezer's brilliant fall from grace...
and...
That's the wrong thing to be fascinated by!
I really liked how dramatic he got.
Stop it!
So I copied all his gear.
I copied it,
and even grabbed Insect Glaive,
after I'd given up on it before.
How's it looking for you, Towa-sama.
Well, uh, I haven't changed anything.
Same gear?!
How lame!
What's the problem?!
Still going for cute, huh?
Why'd you guys change, anyway?
Tell me first!
Lamy-san.
Let's go.
Pump up the party before you go.
Fine...
Let's get hunting!
Yeah!
How come you get to face the camera, Captain?!
Lucky.
Lucky!
Lucky you.
Yay!
It begins.
Let's go!
Whoo!
I'm going with Lamy.
You're safe with her.
C'mon!
Follow me!
Let's go with her!
Yes, let's.
Lead the way, Master!
Whoa.
Got a Spiribird already.
Whoa?
Spiribird.
What's this chonker?
Yeah!
Get them buffs.
Got it!
Do you lose your inventory if you touch this lava?
No, no.
Doesn't happen?
It's okay.
It's just hot.
This way, this way.
So, like...
Hold up!
Gotta mine!
Oh, come on.
Master, this party has zero teamwork.
Get it together!
Crap!
I can't believe Marine was actually the glue.
I was.
Lamy!
Uh, Lamy's riding this thing!
I'll catch up after some mining.
Forget that!
Look, it's important.
Oh, wait!
Let's go!
Let's do this!
Okay, where is it?
Is it happening?
Ow!
Oh, shit!
Wait, gotta mine.
Never mind. It was a dud.
Rex is here.
So this thing's Tigrex, huh?
Huh? Why are there two monsters?
Yeah, right?
Something joined the fight.
Wyvern Riding time!
Yeah, it's a good chance.
Bind and get on that thing.
Huh? What's going on?
Which one's...
Whoa!
Hot!
Boss fell off!
That's not good!
Now...
No, not that one!
Not this, right?
This ain't Tigrex!
It's not.
Huh?
Guys, that's not Tigrex.
Let's pursue, everyone!
Press that...
Isn't this Tigrex?
It's not Tigrex!
It's not!
It's not?!
Party In Disorder
Wrong monster.
Tigrex!
Hey!
Wrong monster!
Where is it?
Which one's Tigrex, then?
This way.
Why's Subageezer the sensible one?!
Yikes!
Amidst the confusion, the Boss falls
I died!
Forget her. Let's go.
No!
All she did was fall off a cliff, and mine.
Don't rub salt on my wounds!
Master! Help Subageezer!
Towa Arrives Fashionably Late
Welcome her.
I'm on my way, guys!
Just wait.
We're waiting!
We're waiting.
Oh, snap, gotta mine.
Forget that already!
Press F for Subageezer again
Subageezer!
We're gonna lose our rewards!
This is bad. We're done for.
Nah, you can still cart one more time.
Yikes!
Just focus on dodging.
This the target?
Yeah. Heal up now.
Heal up.
Don't get hit.
Look out, Boss!
Yikes!
Hang in there!
Run away!
Hide and heal!
This is no time to be laughing!
What's up, Boss?
Boss!
Watch out, Boss!
You can't get hit!
Down goes the Boss
Boss!
It ended before I could get back again!
It's all over.
This is just like real life.
Seriously, Boss?
Not the time to be defiant, Boss.
Sorry, Master.
My bad.
D-Don't worry.
I only trained Towa-senpai.
A new bond forms.
Woohoo, trainee!
Towa-sama did her best.
I figured we'd fail when Subageezer died.
You're the last person I wanna hear that from!
You died twice, Boss.
Not you!
Now it's time for the latest information
on Monster Hunter Rise!
In the free title update released 27 May, Version 3.0,
Crimson Glow Valstrax appears!
In addition, there's Apex Zinogre...
new quests, new weapons, armor, and items!
Also...
Monster Hunter Rise Title Update: Version 3.0!
Currently available!
Your hunter life won't end anytime soon!
Have fun!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
So, Lamy-san, you said you wanted leadership skills.
Did we manage to fulfill your request?
Tell us how you're feeling, on a weather scale!
Stormy
Rain
Cloudy
Clear
Rising Sun!
The stage is yours!
Sure!
Rising... Sun!
Oh...
What the heck?
The air in here sure is chilly, though.
Cut it out!
Challenge From the Boss:
the Maruyama Championship!
Something's going down!
Uh...
At this point, we'll have our guests
try their hand at a minigame.
Their results will be ranked,
and the one who finishes the season on top
will receive a Special Maruyama Trophy!
You can put it up on your streams.
Yeah, on our streams!
This season's minigame is...
Puyo Puyo Tetris 2's Endless Fever mode!
Have any of you tried it before?
Puyo Puyo?
I'm sure everyone's played it, right?
Nope.
Nah.
Never.
Gah!
That was one hell of a noise.
It's just you, Marine.
Just so you know, back home,
I was the strongest player in grade school.
They called me Puyo Puyo Marine-chan.
That should be fun.
Give it a shot, then.
By the way, my puppets...
The show staff's highest score was
Puppets?
Puppets?!
21,716 points!
You'll know what that number means when you play.
The Puyo Puyo beginners get the first go.
But they didn't do great,
so just highlights.
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Over!
I think you gotta chain 'em together.
There are your total scores.
2516 points!
It's like one-tenth!
Let's go, Lamy-chan!
What's with the hype?
She's never played it, right?
Just watch me.
Just you watch.
Quick deci...
Slow decision-making?!
Too slow!
There, there.
She's trying to chain!
Makes sense.
She's not clearing them ASAP.
She's building up a chain!
Exactly!
She learned from watching!
She's building it up.
I'm just getting started!
Just watch!
Plenty more to come.
You okay?
Yeesh.
Uh oh.
It looked good, but I don't know.
She's building up the right side.
Ten more seconds!
And done!
What's the total score?
Surely 80000 plus...
Yeah, no.
8727 points!
Well, I scored more than Subaru-senpai.
Is it fun to pick on the weak?!
Behold Marine-chan's #1 Puyo Puyo from grade school.
I'll show you what I can do.
Go for it.
Check out my speed!
Fast!
Quick!
I'm overwhelmingly fast!
Snap decisions.
I do this...
Whoa, whoa.
and this...
...and this...
I see! That's how you do it!
and this...
You split it up evenly!
Perfectly balanced!
...and this...
The screen looks pretty!
Hang on... uh...
Hold up.
What's this even going to do?
Go!
This is awesome!
It keeps going!
The longest chain was 5!
The points keep piling up!
I don't know how high it'll go.
She laughs like Doraemon!
Ten seconds left!
Just ten?
Ten seconds left.
Five! Four! Three!
Two!
One!
Hurry!
All right!
This is what Puyo Puyo Marine-chan can do!
Puyo Puyo...
Marine-chan!
Calculating the final score, and... whoa!
57726 points!
Well, I wasn't the best in my school for nothing.
She's way ahead in the lead!
Call me Puyo Puyo Marine-chan from now.
That was incredible.
It pisses me off, but she earned that.
True that.
We'll be using that as the baseline from the next episode.
The minigame will change each season,
so look forward to it!
Yeah!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Make good use of the leadership skills
you developed today.
I will.
Thanks for coming!
Thanks.
Thank you for your purchase!
We look forward to your next visit!
Bye-bye!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
How did you enjoy this episode of Game Shop Maruyama?
Marine-san's stayed back for us right now.
To give our viewers advice
regarding their worries... or so we'd hoped,
but we haven't received any submissions yet, for reasons.
So, Marine-san,
is there anything bothering you?
Well...
Yes?
I only say this because we're alone.
Oh, what is it?
I can't say it out loud.
Really?
I went for a checkup, and they said my body was like...
Yeah?
a 45-year-old's body!
Huh?
Exercise?
That's not an acceptable answer!
"Exercise" is not a valid answer, huh?
I will not exercise!
Any other advice, please?
How resolute.
Yes.
Forty-five?
Huh?
You drink, don't you?
Lifestyle Questionnaire
Sometimes, only sometimes.
Huh?
How about the other thing?
You know...
I don't. Never.
You should start a job.
Work for Uber Eats.
Huh? Not here?
Boss's Solution: Exercise with Work!
Why Uber Eats?!
Uber Eats.
But I work here already!
With that done...
Yes?
We're accepting requests for advice from you.
Tweet out your worries
using the hashtag #まるヤマ駅前お悩み相談
Yeah.
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique, personally signed
request fulfilled sticker.
Whoa, that's awesome!
So please send in your submissions!
We're waiting!