What would you eat on Doomsday?
Final question.
Anything goes, as long as I'm with you all!
Cool flex, Goody Two Shoes.
Shaddup!
How many hours before are we talking?
Because that could change my answer.
How pragmatic.
I wanna eat candy!
I don't wadda say goodbye!
Double cheeseburger.
C'mon, pick something nice.
It's nice as hell!
Watame Roast
I vote for a Watame Roast.
Fubu-chan?!
No need to count calories if it's the last one.
Beef bowl it is, then!
Shirogane
Just another day for you, huh?
Some "test" that was.
Right?
Another year gone, huh?
Time flies.
Here's your last supper!
Let's eat!
One of you has swapped out
my broth for barley tea.
Huh?
For real?
No way...
Who would do that?
Whaddaya think?
Dunno.
It wasn't me!
Or me!
Trust me...
Psst, go ask who did it.
Why me?
...Uh oh.
Behind you! Look behind you!
Here's to another year together!