You actually like this development, don't you?
No no no!
I can see that.
I like Fall (aki).
I made Ollie.
Huh?
Here we are
with a new episode of holo's Bonjour.
This is hololive's official talk show, where we swap in a new member every month.
Now, let's get started by introducing
the talents on the show today.
I, Shishiro Botan of hololive 5th Gen,
will be your host today.
Glad to have you today.
Now, our next talent!
Yes! I'm hololive 1st Gen's half-elf,
AkiRose a.k.a. Aki Rosenthal!
Glad to have you today!
*clap clap clap*
And our final talent today is...
Nice to meet you.
I'm hololive 3rd Gen's Uruha Rushia.
This is my first time on the show.
Good evening.
Good evening!
The three of us will be presenting today's show.
Actually, I think this is probably the first time
that the three of us have been grouped together.
Yeah.
I'm actually a little bit nervous about today.
Are things going to be alright?
I hope we find some synergy here.
Yeah!
I hope we do!
So, like...
But, wait...
We all have our hair in pigtails!
That's true!
You're right!
"Pigtails"
Should we call ourselves the "Pigtails"?
Ah...
Sh-Sh...
Should we?
Let's not then.
Let's not.
How about the "Twintails" instead?
Have you got any ideas?
"Twintails"?
Yeah, maybe the "Twintails"?
There are lots of people with twintails though...
That's true.
There's too many twintails. That won't work.
Are there any good names we could use?
Anyway, that's how we fit together,
so let's get a move on to the first section.
Okay!
Okay, let's get started.
So, the first section is...
Random Rapid-Fire Interrogation!
"Rapid-Fire Interrogation"?
So Rushia-senpai,
in this section, the two of us
who have been on the show before
will be asking you lots of questions really quickly.
Was it 20 questions altogether?
Yeah, 20 questions.
That's heaps!
Yeah, it is!
Yeah!
It really is an interrogation!
Just like the name!
Yeah, it literally is "random rapid-fire interrogation."
Okay, let's start.
Okay.
Alright, let's go.
Twenty-question interrogation, let's start!
I'm kind of nervous.
Q1: Do you prefer dogs or cats?
Huh?
Huh?!
Huuuhh?!
Aghhhh... errr...
Are you ready...?
Dogs!
OK.
Q3: Do you like horror?
I love it!!
Q5: What's your favorite season?
Fall (aki).
Huh?!
Q6: What's your favorite thing in your room?
Errrrr...
Rushia!
Q12: What's your favorite food?
Curry!
Q15: What's your favorite thing to do?
Stare up at the ceiling.
That's kind of scary.
Q20: If you were to go on a date with me,
where would you take me?
Let's go for a drive together...
at night!
The end!
That was a lot!
Rushia-senpai, I was kind of surprised
when I asked if you like horror
and you were like "I love it!",
so you do actually like horror?
I absolutely love it!
Don't the two of you like horror?
I do! I quite like it!
You're fine with horror?
Yeah, I'm fine with it!
What about you, Aki-senpai?
Umm... I'm a little... you know?
No?
I can't sleep...
That reaction...!
No way!
You get scared?
I can't shower...
or go to the toilet...
and I can't sleep...
I end up not being able to sleep.
Is it that bad?
I get so scared...
I think about it when I'm in the bath...
Shampooing my hair is too much...
It's like they're after me... I get so scared.
Yeah, there might be a hand...
When you're washing your hair...
There might suddenly be another hand...
I get too scared to look in the mirror too...
Yeah, there might be someone watching you.
Why?!
Why are you trying to scare her?
Rushia-senpai, were you just trying to scare her?
One other thing I noticed...
Did you say your favorite season...
is fall (aki)?
Yeah, I love fall (aki).
Huh?
Just hang on a sec.
Did that get your heart racing?
Aki-senpai?
C-Can you say that again for me?
I love Aki!
Note: they're talking about the season
Aki-chan's done for.
I can go home now.
I personally like fall and winter too, though.
I prefer the cold weather.
She's suddenly super popular?!
I feel like I've suddenly become really popular...?
Our next section will be...
Okay, Shishiron! Search and Lock On!
This section is actually my section.
So, when you search for something on a search engine
it shows how many results there are.
Yeah.
So in this section, the three of us
each do a second AND search
to narrow down the number of results, and see who can
get the closest to the target number of hits.
That sounds interesting!
For example, when you search for "Shishiro Botan,"
Rules
you get about 2.8 million results.
Wow!
2.8 million results
Yeah.
Then when you look up "Shishiro Botan" AND "cute"
Example: Narrowed down to 600,000 results
Aim: To have only 600,000 results
You narrow it down to about 600,000 results
So we do AND searches to narrow down the results,
and the person who gets
the closest number of hits to the target wins.
Who can get the closest number of results?
But, if you get fewer results
than the target you automatically lose,
then you start to become see-through.
You lose if you go under the target!!
This again!
Are we going to disappear like Sui-chan did?
Suisei-senpai became completely transparent last time.
Our next topic is...
"Zombies"
"Zombies"?!
"Zombies"...
"Zombies"?
So, if you search for just "zombies",
you get about 32.5 million results.
Our goal is to do an AND search with another
phrase to try and get 2.8 million results.
2.8 million...
Yep.
Except, we're going from 32.5 million to 2.8 million...
It's a pretty big difference.
Anyway, let's start thinking.
So Rushia-senpai, you're a necromancer...
Are zombies your friends?
Yeah, they are.
They're my boyfriends.
Your boyfriends?
They're your boyfriends...
Actually, we might already be married.
Already married
Boyfriends & Waifus
I guess there are girl zombies too, right?
Yeah, there are!
Ollie-chan is a zombie too, after all.
Yeah, she is!
So she's actually a Fandead?
Yeah.
I made Ollie.
* Please don't make things up
That's the first I've heard!
Ah, I actually just randomly made that up...
You know what?
I'm going to pick "kelp"
because it's my favorite type of rice ball.
Yeah?
Oh, like "zombies + kelp"?
I'm going to make the zombies eat kelp!
Alright, I'm ready. This is it!
Okay.
Alright, Rushia-senpai, are you ready?
Okay!
Alright.
I've decided.
Thinking time is over!
Alright, let's reveal our answers
at the same time, okay?
Okay.
Alright, let's reveal them all together now.
Here we are!
Rushia-senpai's is "zombies + kelp."
I really put "kelp"!
Aki-senpai's is "zombies + hololive member's reaction"
Yes!
and I chose "zombies + chainsaws"
That seems like you'd get lots of hits,
Oh, that's a good one.
with "chainsaws."
Yeah!
Aki-senpai, can I ask why you chose that?
As your answer?
Well, you answered with "xxx's reaction"
before, and I thought
that seemed like it would
give some interesting results...
I see.
Yeah.
Yeah, so I thought that "holo member's reactions"
might bring up quite a few hits too?
That's true.
I thought it might give
a pretty decent number of results.
That seems possible.
And Rushia-senpai,
why did you pick "zombies + kelp"?
I guess... I really do just want them
to try one of my favorite foods.
I see.
Yeah...
Oh, you like kelp?
Yeah, I do.
But, Rushia-senpai,
if you like rice balls with kelp in them,
wouldn't it have been better to
just give them the whole rice ball instead?
Ah...
Whatever!
I'll eat the leftover rice for them!
You'll give them just the kelp?
Yeah, that's right!
Just the kelp!
I'll be like, "This stuff is yum!"
"You guys can have the good part."
So you'll give them the good parts?
Makes sense.
"I'll eat the rice for you!"
And I picked "zombies + chainsaws."
Chainsaws are pretty much a staple
in zombie movies and games.
You can't really have zombies without chainsaws,
which is why I chose "chainsaws."
Alright, we've got all our answers now,
so let's check the search results.
Okay!
First up...
Umm...
is my answer...
"Zombies + chainsaws"!
The number of results is!
1.25 million!
I went too low!
The goal was 2.8 million.
Isn't that pretty close though?
I went too low...
Now, let's look at Rushia-senpai's.
"Zombies + kelp."
The number of results is!
Hey, you should all look up
"Zombies + dried kelp" more!
There should be more than that!
472,000 results!
So low!
So like, kelp came up before
when we were searching for Minecraft stuff
so I thought this would work,
but there's hardly any results!
What is this?!
It makes you wish people
would give kelp more love.
Yeah, please give kelp more love.
It tastes so good...
And, lastly...let's look at Aki-senpai's.
"Zombies + holo member's reactions."
Huh?!
104,000 hits.
So low!
Where are all our subscribers?!
Yeah, true!
You're right!
That's way too low!
Come on, watch us more!
After seeing the other two, I thought
"Yeah, mine'll probably be about right"...
You were completely off the mark.
Even lower than kelp.
Lower than kelp!
By the way, the answer
that gives 2.8 million results?
"How to survive"
gives 2.8 million results apparently.
So is everyone expecting...
there to be a zombie apocalypse?
They are, aren't they?
Like, if you survive...
Like, how to stay alive?
Yeah, they might be.
So, Botan-chan, this means you won, right?
Yeah, I did, but everyone...
We all become see-through.
We became see-through!
Ah, we did...
Aki-senpai's results were the lowest,
so her opacity is probably the lowest too.
That's true!
Our next section is...
Alcoholic's
Concentration Game!
This is Aki-senpai's section,
so please do the honors, Aki-senpai!
Okay!
In this section,
we basically play a game
of concentration that's themed
around one of AkiRose's favorite things,
alcohol and snacks.
Let's take a look at how it works.
So here, we have cards for drinks and snacks,
arranged randomly like this.
You'll pick one drink card and one snack card
by picking their numbers.
Then, I'll judge whether I think that combination
goes well together or not.
It's all about whether I like it or not.
The game will end after three rounds,
and whoever ends up with
the most cards at the end wins.
Okay.
Alright, let's give it a go.
Okay!
Alright, let's start!
We'll start with Rushia,
so please pick an alcohol card and a snack card.
Okay!
Umm, let's see...
I'll take alcohol eight...
No... alcohol four,
and snack eight.
Snack eight...
Order up for alcohol four
and snack eight, please!
Beer!
Beer and...?
Wheat juice!
And the snack is...?
Salt?!
Hey!
Why is that in there?!
Salt isn't a snack!
This is quite a difficult decision...
That's a seasoning!
It's the taste of summer!
Getting your salt on,
and washing it down with beer!
"Getting your salt on"?!
Won't you get dehydrated though?
You replenish your sodium with the salt...
And replenishing your fluids with the beer...
So, I just had a sample to try...
Yeah?
For me... This combination...
is...
good!
It's good?!
Really?!
Wow!
I think it's actually pretty common
when you go out for drinks,
I'm curious!
but in the end, you're fine with
any shop where you can drink.
No matter where you go,
you always seem to end up with
some salt or soy sauce left over
after you're done eating...
So you're saying it's like having a beer
while dipping your chopsticks
in your soy sauce and licking them...?
That's not...!
Botan picks a pretty normal combination
Smoked eggs!
This should be a pretty good combination, right?
I mean, if you can do beer and salt, you should
be fine with lemon sour and smoked eggs too!
For me, this combination...
is...
good!
Yaaay!
She passes this round and we move onto the 2nd round!
I'd have rioted if you said no!
This is turning out to be a pretty heated match.
Yeah.
Let's start the second round then.
Let's go with an alcohol card first.
OK!
For liquor, I'm gonna pick...
Alcohol eight―!
Actually, no. Alcohol three!
Change?
Yep. Change to alcohol three.
Change to three.
Order up for alcohol three!
Wine!
Wine, huh...
Yeah, it's wine.
What pairs well with wine?
Cheese, right?
You wouldn't be wrong in thinking that.
Hold on. I think I got it.
It's coming to me.
I can see it! I'll go with my clairvoyance.
Number three.
Three?
I'll go with that.
Going by your rules, huh?
Order up for snack three!
This is...!
Raw fish!
I think... this works.
Hmmmm.
The bar is...
I shouldn't have lowered the bar
with the salt pairing a while ago.
3) Wine + 3) Raw fish
We're not sure if it's red or white wine.
Oh, right.
The drawing shows it as red wine, but...
If we assume this is red wine,
then it might be a good pairing with raw fish.
Blergh!
This combination is...
bad!
Aaaaaah!
Why?!
You see,
if this were white wine and raw fish,
then it would've been a perfect match.
Red wine, however, pairs better
with things like red meat.
Oh, I see!
So that's what goes with it!
Most white wines tend to have a
fruity and light quality to them.
That explains it.
And?
That's why it goes well with raw fish.
On the other hand, red wine has a lot of body.
Sometimes it also has tart or bitter qualities to it.
That's why something as flavorful as red meat
would stand up to the wine.
That's cool!
TIL.
It sounds so high-class though.
My eyes have opened up
to a whole other world.
Oh my!
Would you like Big Sister
to teach you the ways?
Really? You would?
Alright! Your turn, Shishiron!
Let's go for alcohol one!
Order up for alcohol one!
Japanese liquor!
Japanese liquor...
this should pair well with raw fish...
is what I would've said, but...
Why are you hesitating?
Should I pick something else, maybe?
Some of these other snacks
might work just as well.
It'd be boring for this stream
if I went the safe route.
She's feeling lucky.
I pick snack five!
Order up for snack five!
Mixed nuts.
Isn't this a good pair?
Aki-senpai has the final say, though!
She decides if it's good or bad.
Can't be bound by common opinion here.
1) Japanese liquor + 5) Mixed nuts
I'm ready to suck up to Aki-senpai for this.
Just in case.
You're learning well!
This isn't bad,
but if you ask me, this combination is...
bad!
It's bad?!
It doesn't work, huh...
It's not entirely a bad pairing.
But if mixed nuts were
among the things I could choose,
it wouldn't be my pick.
A good pairing for mixed nuts
would be red wine, actually.
Ah, I see.
Hm?
No good, huh...
Oh, I gave out a hint.
You gave out a hint,
but you already showed raw fish, so...
Oh well. We'll be moving on
to the third round now,
so I'll leave you guys to choose
whether to keep your pride as streamers
or to go for the easy answers.
Now at round three!
Take your pick, Rushia-chan.
As everyone knows,
I'm a streamer myself,
Hmm?
so I choose alcohol three and snack five!
3) Wine + 5) Mixed nuts
Huh?
Yes! Alcohol three: wine!
And snack five: nuts!
Umm, Rushia-chan...?
Are you sure?
My decision is...
Th-This combination...
is...
good...
YEAH!
This was gonna happen.
I got it!
I spilled it earlier, after all.
HEY!
Since you started it,
I'm gonna pick alcohol one next round!
Wow, so aggressive.
You sure about doing that?
So, Shishiron, what sort of move
are you going to show us?
I may be a streamer,
but I'm more curious
about all these varieties of alcohol,
so... hmm, okay!
Number eight.
Order up for alcohol eight!
Awamori?
Awamori!
I see...
Awamori, huh...
What sort of alcohol is it?
Awamori is a liquor made in Okinawa.
Its alcohol percentage is really high,
and is known for packing quite a punch.
For something as strong as this,
you might want to eat something along with it.
Which would it be?
I see, I see.
Raw fish might be good,
but I want to be a bit adventurous.
So instead... I'll choose snack two!
Order up for snack two!
What is it...?
Bitter gourd!
That can work, right?
Isn't this an Okinawa-Okinawa pairing?!
They go together!
Definitely!
You really got lucky here!
8) Awamori + 2) Bitter gourd stir-fry
What do you think, Aki-senpai?
It's an amazing match.
I think the person who made these cards
never expected someone
to actually hit this pairing.
Oh, really?
Give a bonus, then!
A shared locale bonus...
I have decided!
This combination is...
good!
Hooray!
If you ask me if these two
are a perfect match―
While the flavors would need
some getting used to,
I can't just ignore that
Okinawa locale bonus after all.
Special consideration for locale bonus
Full stream has Round 4
It passed!
Yay!
Isn't this a bit too good?
Here is our next segment!
What do you think of me?
Poll Up My Image
This segment is hosted by Rushia-senpai
so I'll leave it to you to explain the rules.
Alright!
So for this segment,
the viewers will be polled on a particular theme.
Rules
The viewers
Is Uruha Rushia wholesome?
Yes
No
Once we see the results, we'll start chatting
about a topic related to the poll theme.
35% Wholesome
HUH?
Topic
Recent obsessions
I've been making flower crowns!
After we finish the talk segment,
Yes
No
The same poll will be run
the same poll will be run again.
100% Wholesome!
* Wrong answers not allowed.
The results of the second run will tell us
what the audience took away from our talk.
Okay.
If you're not satisfied with the first polling,
you can try to influence the second one
through the talk segment.
So that's how it works.
You'll have to do well in the talk.
On the other hand, if you're okay
with the first poll's results,
then you should watch your words
during the talk segment.
Mmhmm.
Since this is a brand new segment,
we'll start with me as the theme.
Okay.
The theme of the poll is:
Is Uruha Rushia an idol or a comedian?
The latter.
Comedian, definitely.
The answer is idol!
To be honest, I am curious
about how people see me.
What do you see yourself as, Rushia-senpai?
An idol, of course!
'Kay.
Hmm.
Well,
as for everyone else...
It depends on the audience, yeah!
Well, yeah, that's true.
You all get me, right?
Anyway, let's uhh―
Staff, please put up the poll!
I think I felt some coercion
happening just now...
Not at all!
I won't do anything like that to the viewers!
Everyone has their own impressions.
Hmm, this is a pretty tough choice.
I'm in the camp of "doing everything" though.
Like, I'd want to do both
idol stuff and entertainer stuff.
So you'd want to be a comedian as well?
I'd want to do all that I can.
I can relate, actually.
I want to have the qualities of an idol,
along with the artistic flair of an entertainer,
so doing comedy isn't so far off for me.
Wow, you guys want to be comedians.
I don't want to be one, though.
I see!
Seems like the poll's over.
Let's have a look.
Please show us the results!
Bam!
WHAT?!
Where's the results?
"Rushia is an idol" is at...
Forty-four...
Forty-four!
"Comedian" is at 56%!
I expected it to be more skewed.
It's pretty close.
Indeed.
So now we'll start the talk segment,
and since Rushia-senpai
wants to be seen as an idol,
you'll use this time to convince the viewers, yes?
That's right.
This was the result,
and I personally don't like it,
so I'll be using this time
to show off my idol qualities to everyone.
Let's proceed then.
I'll use the following topic
to prove that I'm a real idol.
The topic is "recent stream activities."
Aki-senpai, Botan-chan, and I will talk
about our recent streams
to convince everyone that we're idols...
Kelp?
That's a comedy routine!
Nope! No! Not having it!
Anyway, any recent stream activities
you two want to share?
Well, this one happened yesterday.
It's been a while, so I thought of
doing a karaoke stream.
That sounds splendid.
Ah, yes. It was a good idea.
Her tone changed.
A truly jolly time!
Gonna be hard to keep up.
Ms. AkiRose finds it difficult to bother
Pray tell, what is the matter, Aki-senpai?
Anyway.
I wanted to get my throat back into shape
so I did a karaoke stream.
It's been such a long time
since my last one though.
So what happened was
one of the songs I picked
turned out to be a song I didn't know
and I ended up not singing it.
That is quite the endearing story.
I really messed up that one.
It really was embarrassing.
I found myself charmed hearing it.
Do you have a story, Rushia-san...
I wanna hear it.
From one of my recent streams, yes?
Let's see...
(elegance)
What have I done as of late...?
Ah, I held an ASMR stream the other day.
ASMR, huh...?
Y'all are suddenly so cold. Hello?
What's with those side glances?
We're, uhh...
We think it's cute.
Oh, really? You mean it? You do, right?
Geez!
Botan-chan's not taking me seriously!
I did an ASMR stream yesterday, okay!
So in that stream,
I was doing the ASMR
but I started getting sleepy.
Ohh.
Cute.
Agreed.
So cute.
Her voice is soothing, after all.
Wait, hold on.
I'm getting embarrassed!
Out of her element
Hold on! Let's slow down for a bit!
If you're getting embarrassed by this,
then it's clear:
you're a comedian.
Accept it.
Yeah.
Come to this side.
I don't wanna!
Anywaymovingon.
I did that stream the day after.
Talking about horror game streams
Ah, a horror game stream, yeah?
I played it on stream but I cried
from the scares.
How did you cry?
Like,
NGUWAAAA!
Comedian, right here!
That story just now...
Isn't that the more embarrassing one?
That exaggerated cry
is definitely that of a comedian.
It came out wrong!
It sounded more like "Eeeehh!"
Are you sure?
That's not what I heard.
It was more of a "BWAAAA!"
Am I wrong?
The volume was so high, we couldn't hear it.
I'm pretty sure it was―
REPLAY
You probably had noise cancellers on.
Do you have any other
"Other"?
stories you'd like to share?
More stories?
There was one time I played Smash.
I cried after getting beaten up.
...How did you cry?
GRAAAH― I mean, "Kyaaa!"
Can we stop it with the gags?
The polls got it right, I think.
We'll see about that! Put them up!
I think it's pretty much decided now.
Do me good!
I think I already know the result.
'Kay!
Pretty sure it's that.
I'm sure I'm an idol!
Staff, if you please!
After all that,
everyone's gonna call me an idol...
They'll all call me cute...
How cute.
Oh, screw off!
Why is the right one bigger now?!
My own vote is
in the 24% side over here!
You put in your own vote,
but everyone already sees you
as a comedian.
Yeeeep. Definitely a comedian.
Heck no! That's not true, Botan!
It went up by 20%, right?
Yeah! It went up by 20%!
It went up, okay!
Let's be honest, Rushia-chan.
You actually like this development, don't you?
No no no!
I can see that.
It's hard to rebut that, but...
Why'd you have to ask that anyway?!
Caught red-handed
In the end, though,
I firmly believe that I'm an idol.
That attitude of hers
gives it a stronger punchline.
It does.
Extra
Botan goes way off mark
Does this mean I'm gonna disappear?
Please don't forget me...
Botan-chan! Aaaagh!
Don't... forget me...
I can hear something!
A lion's soul
It's a supernatural phenomenon!
So, like, I'm moody, yeah?
So you admit it.
Yeah, I'm really moody.
Are you sure you agree with that?
If someone asks you that
and you just say yes to it―
Yeah! I'm totally fine with it.
If you straight up call out
Legit Mood-swinger
a legit mood-swinger to be moody then...
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub channel
on Niconico for the full stream archives!
Yeah, that's what I think too.