Y'know, Aq-tan, are you really a maid?
Wh-What's this, out of the aqua?
Could've just said "blue."
I'm just wondering 'cause I've never
seen you do anything like a normal maid.
Aw, I know I'm a super idolish gamer maid,
but you're making me blush!
That's... not what I meant.
If you call yourself a maid,
shouldn't you be doing housework?
Shaddup!
Whoa, why'd you start yelling?
Don't paint all maids with the same brush!
Uh, I guess that struck a nerve.
Hmph! I'm gonna go work!
Huff, puff!
Yikes, I made her mad.
The Next Day
Maybe you were right.
Maybe I do need to do things
more like a normal maid.
It's really bothering her!
W-Well...
It doesn't have to be housework.
Just having a special skill
of some sort would be nice.
A special skill?
Like walking globe?
W-Walking globe?
Look, Captain!
Guess what I'm doing!
It's the walking globe!
Doesn't that sound good?
That doesn't sound good.
Keep it simple!
I think you should stick to the basics,
like cooking or cleaning.
Don't wanna! That's such a drag!
I just wanna help with games!
Wha...
W-Well, nothing wrong with a maid
who helps with gaming around the house.
Exactly!
Maids aren't duty-bound to do housework!
We come in all shapes and forms!
So I'm fine just the way I am!
You sure snapped out of
that existential crisis quick.
But a special skill would be good to have.
A shtick to call my very own.
O... kay?
So, without further ado,
I'm gonna give the walking globe a shot!
Hold on! Timeout!
That's not safe!
Pick something else! You're an idol...
Quit forcing your idol views on me!
God! She's such a pain!
Behold!
Feast your eyes on
Minato Aqua's walking globe!
H-How do I look, Captain?
Like a small animal.
Oh meow god!
Show me how it's done, then!
You got it! Not that I've ever done this before...
But I can tell that
balance is key...
Gah!
Crash and burn! You aren't cut out for this.
What's wrong, Captain?
I think I heard a crack.
What.
What?!
YMMV: Your Maid May Vary!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!