The excitement we've longed for draws ever closer
sukoshi zutsu chikazuiteiru yo yume ni mita tokimeki
As it spreads like wildfire across the world
hirogatteku sekaijuu ni
We'll shine a light that puts smiles on faces
minna o egao ni saseru kirameki o
Because we're not alone, because we have rivals
hitori janai kara raibaru ga iru kara
Even the fiercest competition
kisoiau koto sura
Becomes part of the fun
tanoshiku nacchau n da yo
Dear My Friends
When we sprint toward our goal, it'll be fantastic
mirai e hashiridashitara Fantastic
hololive IDOL PROJECT - Dreaming Days
Lyrics: Yuuki Honda (Arte Refact)
We'll make our hopes bloom into our future
yume o sakasete Our Future
Take it one step at a time and aim for the top
ippo ippo o fumidashite toppu o mezasou
Composition, Arrangement:
Yuuki Honda (Arte Refact), Takuya Sakai (Arte Refact)
ippo ippo o fumidashite toppu o mezasou
Vocals: Shirakami Fubuki, Natsuiro Matsuri, Murasaki Shion,
Believing in ourselves will bring our hearts happiness
shinjiru chikara ga kokoro no Happiness
Vocals: Nakiri Ayame, Yuzuki Choco, Oozora Subaru,
Vocals: Usada Pekora, Houshou Marine, Amane Kanata
Let's relish this with all we've got
zenryoku de tanoshimou
Because it will, one day for sure,
sore wa itsuka kitto
Make our wildest fantasies come true
ookina yume kanaeru kara
Dreaming Days