I've been a good clock!
But your tick... your tock...
is making a lot of noise.
That proves you're lying!
Say no to violence!
We know you ate our snacks!
Time to bail.
Get back here!
Fools! Catch me if you can!
Don't get full of yourself!
I'm gonna shut you up for good!
Me too? Why?!
Wonderland
Welcome.
Ah'm de Jejhiye Gad.
Huh? What?
Bud gully...
Come again?
Id zo zimble!
Make it clear!
The Tooth Fairy took away
all her teeth.
I can't speak too well.
Speech isn't the be all and end all.
What matters is sinking
your teeth into life.
My back feels so itchy!
Wanna scratch!
Is this it?
Wrong place!
Here?
Close!
Hmm...
Talk about fighting tooth and nail, huh?
Shine me up nice and good!
Vroomio!
Nothing beats a tea party
on a car roof.
We are  going after the clock, right?
Come on, don't be westless.
You will arrive at
your destination in ten meters.
Hope you had a good time.
Is this it? Is this what you wanted?
You shameless cat!
Gimme more, i.e. gimmo!
Woof!
Vroomio!
Wait, there's the clock!
Yikes! I've been spotted!
Hey, taxi!
It'll cost ya a purrty penny!
A... tea-purrty penny?
Oh dear! The Miorati's honking with rage!
Go away!
Can't this thing go any faster?
Well, it can push harder...
On the double!
Vroomio!
What are you pushing out?!
Vroomio.
Now you're pulling things out?!
Blarrr!
aAaAaaA!
Yikes!
Watch out. That's the gang
lurking these woods...
Gang?!
Bow down to our mobile zoo!
Or else...
Booze drunk out of Houshou's skull
is sure to be tubular.
The zoo director desires a chalice!
Get your PolPols in, okay?
I know my way around hell, thank you!
Owie!
Alarm Clock! No!
I'll miss you.
Hmm?
At that moment, the clock's raging spirit took over.
Rise and shine, kids! Wakey-wakey!
Goonigh!
I, Marine-tan, have returned
from dreamland,
and feel positively splendid
after a pleasant nap.
You went and ate it, huh, Captain?
Uh, well...
Huh?
Something smells nice.
Do we got sweets?
Wait, you ate all that?
What a gwutton.
Wow, keen eye, y'all!
Cute, smart, and great dancers!
So much talent in one place!
Oh man, why can't I hold
all this respect I have for you girls?
I have such wonderful mates,
my heart's about to explode into a million pieces!
Don't forget me!
You left me hanging!
Teeth Care
After getting shot down and hit
with two Bionic Elbows,
Marine-chan suffered a compound fracture
to her nose and lived stuffily ever after.
And... that's all, Paul.
How'd you like this book, Luna-tan?
Gimme that.
Hmm?
I found the perfect use for it.
Gaa!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!