Achoo!
Momosuchoo Nene!
Bratty-Brained
Momosuzu Nene
Sneezing is infectious, huh?
That was a sneeze?
Did you know that spring's kicked off
by the vernal equinox?
Huh...
...
An actual ox?
Equinox! Look it up!
I know a lot about spring, okay?
Lots and lots!
Do you know the part
in Humpty Dumpty's Recitation?
"In spring, when woods are getting green,
I'll try and tell you what I mean."
In spring... when w00t!
Humphrey'll tell you what I mean.
Who the heck is Humphrey?
You don't know a thing about spring, huh?
I do! I saw it with my own eyes!
I swear it!
Nenechi?!
She ran off somewhere!
Huh? What was I doing?
Nene? Nene!
Hup.
This is the springworld,
and I am the goddess of spring.
Oh, hey, Miko-senpai.
Hey! No breaking that wall!
To ye, who believes in spring,
I bestow these spring powers.
Spring powers?!
Show them who's boss.
I'll try, Miko-senpai!
I told you, I'm the goddess of spring!
Oh, she's back.
Behold Super Nene,
now with new spring powers!
My headache's gone!
Huh?
*hack*
The first spring breeze!
Thanks, Nene-chan.
You're a lifesaver.
A goddess! The goddess of spring!
Goddess! Goddess!
Kneel down and worship me! Hah!
Zzz... In spring, w00t...
Goddess
It's a sleepy time of year.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!