Rolls BAR
I'll have the usual.
Sure thing.
Did you change the rice?
Nope. Same as always.
Is that so?
So, you said you wanted to talk?
Huh? I did?!
Oh, uh... I can't stand bell pepper.
If you gaze long into a pepper,
the pepper also gazes into you.
You wha...?
Are you open?
Been expecting you.
Here, take a seat.
Huh?
I know what's bothering you, Lamy.
Bothering me?
Booze, right?
Uh, not particularly?
Here's my pearl of wisdom for you.
Consume alcohol.
Dani...
Cap't...
Genius...
It's "Don't let it consume you"!
Om, nom, Okayu!
I know exactly what you two wanna hear.
"Pond of eons past
Splash of a frog jumping in
A moth to the flame"
- Suisei.
Let's gooo!
Taking all manner of concerns
into my own hands,
I smash them into a ball
and consume them whole!
Marching to my own beat,
talk to this brick wall!
I am the Counsel Chief,
and that's the way I roll!
Counsel Chief
You aren't the only chief in town.
Y-You are...!
Musclebrain Monarch
PPTyrant
Y-You are...!
Guwu
Fubuking
Looks like everyone's here.
I hereby declare the
hololive Queen Tournament officially begun!
Declaration Despot
Y-You are...!
Rolls BAR seems like a fun place.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!