Fine, I'll do it.
I'm gonna do it!
Tremble in fear!
Isn't she, like,
totally nude here?
HA
That's too risque!
Make it sensual,
Flare-senpai.
Max sensual.
And now, for the next segment!
It's Towa-sama's...
See Through Her Devilish Deeds!
Yay!
Yeah!
In this segment,
given an everyday situation
where a prank can be played,
Rules
Ex.: Giving a present to a friend.
you can try to guess what kind of
devilish deed I would do!
A: Gift them a jack-in-the-box!
See if you can ace this quiz!
OK.
Gift them a jack-in-the-box!
Flare-senpai, Nenene,
and of course, the viewers
Correct!
will guess the answer!
Aye!
I see, I see.
You were asked to bring a gift
for a gift-exchange event!
Ah...
So I'm going to turn this
into a devilish deed?
Hmm...
Fine, I'll do it.
I'm gonna do it!
Tremble in fear!
Huh?
What was that?
"You were asked to...
bring a gift for a gift-exchange event," huh?
The others are probably
bringing some really nice stuff.
Yeah, yeah.
The budget must've been set
beforehand, though, right?
Like, "5,000 yen max, okay?"
Oh yeah. That makes sense.
Okay, I'm done.
Y'know, I'm... I'm going to
go for the Towa-chan play here.
Something she's likely to do.
So you're gunning for the right answer, huh?
Huh... Let's start with Nenene's answer, then.
You ready, Nenene?
Yep! All set!
Go for it.
Buy something new, use it once,
put it back in the box, and gift that.
Yikes!
That's a good one.
lololol
Man, that's a great idea.
That's nasty!
Absolutely nasty.
And, like, it's pretty doable, too.
Totally doable.
Nenechi's going to win this one for sure.
And now, let's check out
Flare-senpai's answer too.
Oh?
Go homemade and save money.
Hahaha!
Hah-hah-hah!
You get told to buy something nice for,
like, 3,000 yen,
but you just make something
that'd be worth around that much
and spend that money you save on yourself.
I figured this would be
the right kind of devilish for Towa-chan.
That's so sad!
Well, let's take a look at my answer.
Dun!
Oh? Did we get it right?
The gift is just... money.
Haha!
Cold, hard cash?
The laziest option.
In a way, this might actually be nice.
Yeah, it might make the recipient happy.
No way!
But it's so sad!
So cold!
Isn't it?
I mean...
But, if the alternative is something
that was used exactly once,
cash might actually be the better option.
That's... a good point.
Okay, yeah, I can't argue against that.
It makes sense. You get to buy
whatever you want for yourself.
Okay, so, the winner...
It's gotta be this.
The second-hand gift is, like,
the nastiest idea.
Never give me used stuff.
If it were socks, for example,
I'd wear them once
and give them to you.
Yikes.
Do Not Want!
Don't wear them!
Used clothing?!
Even from a good friend,
that'd be kinda gross.
I was thinking,
if I were to buy a gift for you two...
Yeah?
I imagined I'd get a hat or something
and put it on real tight before giving it.
Well, I wouldn't mind that with a hat.
Yeah, a hat's okay.
It's, like, whatever.
I figured you wouldn't want to
scalp kiss with me.
Scalp kiss?!
lololol
So, like, an indirect kiss
with our scalps?
Yeah.
I think any gift from you
would make me happy, Nenechi.
Huh? (blush)
What? So you'd be okay wearing her panties?
What?!
You can have them!
Uh, sorry, I think I'll pass on that.
I'll get two used pairs of panties for you.
Super Do Not Want.
I don't want your used panties.
Okay, moving on to the next segment.
Sketches Speak as Loud as Words?!
This segment is brought to us by Flare-senpai,
so let's have her introduce it.
Sure!
In this segment,
Rules
Secret Situation
Please draw
"Shiranui Flare cooking"!
you'll be given a situation that
I need to figure out as you draw it!
The faster I get it right, the better!
Got it.
Whoa.
Towa-chan, Nene-chan,
Thinking...
and of course, all the viewers can participate!
Me cooking!
Got it.
Okay.
Okay, so I'd like to start with the next topic.
I'll close my eyes, so bring on the situation!
Draw
Answer
Okay.
What will it be?
Shirogane Noel Working Out
Ah, I see, I see.
I see.
Okay.
You can open your eyes now, Flare-senpai.
Okay!
Let's begin!
Get drawing, you two!
Let's do this!
Okay.
I know what I want here...
I've gotten the right answer
while waiting before,
so I'll just keep quiet.
True, true.
You've got the super instinct.
Wonder what it's gonna be!
Well...
Uh...
Wonder what you'll draw.
I can't wait to see.
By the way...
What are you drawing on, Nenene?
A graphic tablet?
Oh, me? I'm on iPad.
Grr.
Ah...
Meanwhile, I'm using a mouse.
What the heck?
The heck?
So what?
Towa-chan first.
Let's see it.
Dun dun! Feast your eyes!
Holding dumbbells...
Noel working out?
Oh?!
Whoa!
Huh?
Yay!
Bingo!
Hahaha!
No way!
Awesome!
Hahaha!
That drawing was really easy to understand.
For real?!
Yay!
I thought it'd be "working out" and not
"holding dumbbells," and I was right!
Hell yeah!
Awesome.
You drew it too, right, Nenene?
Yeah, I did.
I'd like to see yours too.
Ah...
Okay, that's hard to figure out.
No!
Why?!
I mean,
she's working out...
holding a beef bowl? Why?
Isn't she, like,
totally nude here?
HA
That's a bit too risque!
That's too risque!
This is hard!
Okay, next up, Nene's segment.
Okay.
Love Letters From Nene!
Yay!
Please introduce the segment for us.
Sure thing.
In this segment,
Rules
I've sent love letters to hololive members
I've fallen in love, love, love with in advance.
Okay.
And the letter I got in response
will form the basis of a quiz.
This letter will form the quiz!
Flare-senpai, Towa-senpai, and the viewers
Fill in the blanks!
will try to guess the content of the responses
I got from the hololive members.
The last person I sent a love letter to
was Marine-senpai!
Oh!
Captain!
Indeed.
To Captain Marine,
I sent a love letter that went like this.
"Dear Captain,
Before I joined hololive,
I used to watch your drawing streams
to get my creative juices flowing
or as background noise while I worked.
You were my role model.
True story.
So when you invited me to
do a drawing collab with you,
I was so happy, my heart nearly exploded."
Now, let's take a look at the letter
the captain sent me in response.
Okay.
Whoa, that's some...
thick blanks!
Those blanks are thicc!
It's almost scary.
Reading Out the Questions
"You (1) ??????
I'm also (1) ??????
Normally, one would give up,
thinking (2) ??????
This is hard!
But, you know,
why don't we (3) ?????? together?
Let's (4) ??????
Let's xx the yy and
attack each other with words, too.
Of course, you sent this letter
prepared to take the next step, right?
Let's do this!
Y'know, I don't even want to think about this.
This is kinda scary!
Why don't we just...
reveal the answers and move on?
Think in the exact opposite direction
as Sora-senpai's letter.
Well, duh.
I know that.
Oh, don't look at the chat.
They got the right answer.
Okay.
They got it right, huh?
I see.
Wow, people really understand
the captain, huh?
Yeah, there are people who really know her well.
By the way, you two have to read this out.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Excuse me...?
Oh boy...
Make it sensual,
Flare-senpai.
Max sensual.
I want you to surpass Marine-senpai, personally.
Urk...
What are you trying to make her do?!
Apologize to her!
lolol
Okay, first, let's take a look at the answers.
Words first, voices later.
This is going to be so hard to read.
Towa-senpai's on the right,
and there's Flare-senpai's on the left now.
Please go first, Towa-senpai.
Mine's, uh, well...
Uh...
Hang on a sec.
Put your heart into it, okay?
You wha?
Towa Reading Her Answers
You (1) are a pervert through and through.
I'm also (2) a pervert through and through.
Normally, one would give up,
thinking (2) you never want
to be that kind of person.
Ahahahaha!
Hahahahaha!
But, you know,
Ahahahaha!
Hahahahaha!
why don't we (3) aim for a new world together?
Let's (4) break down that door.
That (2) answer was too funny.
Hilarious.
I want to hear Flare-senpai's now.
Yeah, me too.
It's so different from the Marine I know,
I don't even know anymore.
Flare Reading Her Answers
You (1) probably think you're a masochist.
I'm also (2) a masochist, you see.
Ah...
Normally, one would give up,
thinking (2) it wouldn't work
because we're both masochists.
Oh, I get it now!
But, you know,
why don't we
(3) hit up S&M clubs together?
Bwahahaha!
Gahahahaha!
Let's (4) take our masochism to the extreme.
HAHAHAHA!
Oh man!
Flare-senpai,
you're amazing!
I could give you an 80 out of 100.
Huh?
Srs?
What?!
That much?!
It's that close.
I don't know how to feel about that.
I didn't want to be right!
Let's take a look at the actual letter, then.
Here we go.
Reading Out the Actual Letter
You (1) are a masochist, I hear.
I'm also (1) a masochist.
Normally, one would give up,
thinking (2) two masochists can't
satisfy each other sexually.
But, you know,
why don't we (3) bully each other together?
Let's (4) seek out the ultimate pleasures.
Damn, I was close!
And that...
was the response I got from her.
You hit the jackpot with the masochist angle.
Yeah, amazing!
"Why don't we...
hit up S&M clubs together?"
Oh man!
Please, no!
Don't make it sound like I was part of this mess.
Seriously...
Too good!
It's nightmare fuel!
BONUS
Try seducing me in a sexy voice.
Q10: Try seducing in a sexy voice
Love ya, babeh.
pfft
But it's okay, because Towa-chan's an angel.
Huh?
Damn, this Flare-senpai person is annoying.
hahaha
Let's make takoyaki for real!
I love you all time.
Mwah <3
Man, this is one cringe letter.
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub channel
on NicoNico for the full stream archives!
Why are you looking at me like that?!