Good ol' Haachama's gonna make
all the couples of this world happy!
Can't see any stars, huh?
Right?
Haachama Beam!
Wow, Korosan! So many stars!
Yay!
I hear you and Lamy-chan are
getting on like a house on fire...
It's not like that!
Well, it kinda is, but...
Any elf will do for you?!
No! Wait, Flare!
Haachama Beam!
Haachama-chama!
Eek!
I'll protect you, Flare.
Noe-chan!
Whew, a good job well done.
Mass Outbreak of Blondes in Uniforms
Breaking news!
There's been a mass outbreak of blonde girls
in uniforms in the city.
Reports say they've been suspiciously
lingering around couples out in town
and having the cops called on them.
Here's what experts have to say...
Blonde?!
Girls?!
In uniform?!
Hell...
...o?
I've caught you now, blonde girl in uniform!
Huh?
Take her away, Haachamas.
Haachama-chama!
I'm innocent!
Phew. Now all the couples are safe.
Their lives will now be Haachama-colored!
And so the world was overrun by Haachama!
Here's to another year together!