Gah! A dog bit me!
My horns came off!
Coffee?
Yep. It's good.
Whoa, so grown-up.
How are coffee and mud any different?
In every single way.
Would you like to try?
Yes, thank you!
*pant pant*
It's good!
I see...
Coffee comes in many varieties.
Oh?
American,
Kilimanjaro,
Blue Mountain...
DeLorean,
crickets on toast,
boomerang?
You got them all wrong!
Well, coffee has a mature taste
that you two might not appreciate yet.
Gnh...
I will become a sheep who can drink coffee!
Apologize to me first.
My, my. Can you really, Watame-sama?
I can! I know it!
Then you'd do well to start by
grasping the situation you're in.
I tap! I tap!
Time to step out for a strategy meeting!
Let's go, Subaru-senpai!
Eh, I don't wanna... go?!
We've been out here an hour...
And yep, still creepy.
All right! I understand it perfectly now!
You sure?
Choco-sensei!
A cup of coffee, please!
Give it up, Boston Sheep.
I just wanna learn more about coffee!
👓Fret not, young lass.
Classical gentleman!
👓May I have a cup, m'lady?
S-Sure.
👓This is an American blend, is it not?
Correct.
Heck yeah!
Hip, hip, hooray!
It's actually a café au lait, though.
Strawberry Milk #1!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!