Will you really start dating me?
Aki-chan, I love you.
Ah!
Okayun was a masochist?
Yes.
Wait, really?!
It's started!
holo's Bonjour,
a variety and talk show where
one of the guests changes every month!
Let's introduce our cast for today!
First off is me, Aki Rosenthal,
a.k.a. AkiRose! Thanks for having me.
Our next guest is...
Bonjour, ladies and gents.
My name is Uruha Rushia.
Thank you for having me.
Bonjour, everyone. How do you do?
What a beautiful day.
Are you going with your graceful side today?
Huh?
Ah, uh... Nothing.
Oh, just, I couldn't hear you well.
And last but not least...
Om, nom... Bonjour, everyone.
Oh my.
My name is Nekomata Okayu.
My, oh my.
That om, nom sounded so elegant.
Right? It sounded somewhat like she was full.
I thought we agreed to keep us
eating together just before this a secret!
I couldn't help it! You were just too cute.
Yeah.
Have the three of us done
something like this together before?
I don't think we have.
I don't believe we have.
"I don't believe we have"?
How long are you keeping that up?
I wanted to keep it going from start to finish.
Let's just stop that here.
The three of us are part
of the comfy gang, aren't we?
That's true...
I believe so.
That sort of aura radiates from us.
It sure does!
Yeah.
So is this going to be a meditation
and healing stream from us, the comfy trio?
Now that we have a feel for each other,
let's proceed to our first segment!
Random Rapid-Fire Interrogation!
Ooh!
Wah!
Our first segment is
Random Rapid-Fire Interrogation!
For this segment, Okayun will be pelted
with questions from me and Rushia.
I'm excited! I love being pelted with questions.
What?! Really?
Is she an M?!
Okayun, you were an M?
Yes.
Wait, really?!
This is hard to retort to.
Rushia-chan's at a loss.
Do I really have to call her out here?
Let's go ahead!
Okay!
The 20 question barrage will now...
Start!
Do you prefer rice, bread, or noodles?
Hmm... I think noodles.
Anything you're hooked on recently?
Chiikawa!
What kind of person do you like?
A sadist.
Who would you date from hololive?
That's hard!
You, Rushia-chan.
*Rushia.exe has stopped working*
O-Okayu-chan?!
And that's all!
Okay!
That was intense.
The viewers were curious
about one of the questions.
Mm-hmm.
They want to question the fact
that you answered "noodles."
Your fans, the Onigiris, are commenting,
"But we're made of rice..."
Can you comment on that a bit?
But like... I like noodles.
Noodles are tasty, I know.
What kind of noodles are you craving?
I want some ramen right now.
Ramen's so good...
The Onigiris seem a little dejected.
But lately, I've been telling them stuff like,
"You're all made of rice, but I prefer noodles" to...
well, not necessarily "train" them,
but we've been keeping that relationship up,
so I think they'll be fine!
Wait, Okayu-senpai, you said you were
an M earlier, but you're a bona fide S!
But, like, I don't really get
that way towards the Onigiris
Ah, I see...
Ah, so like...
you prefer to corner them as an S?
Say, for Rushia-chan, I want to be an M.
What are you saying Okayu—
I can't take you away from them!
Darn...
Can I ask her about an answer
I was curious about, too?
Sure, go ahead.
Which question?
Okayu-senpai, will you really start dating me?
Of course!
Really?
And you don't say this to everyone?
Only if—That's only if you'll treat me badly.
That's one peculiar condition...
That's a high hurdle!
Oh yeah, it seems Aki-chan
is secretly an Onigiri.
Yeah! I'm trying really hard to keep
my creepy otaku side from leaking out.
Aki-senpai, I watch her as much as you.
Wait, what's going on?
I watch her singing streams a lot.
So you're my rival?
I tune in to her streams whenever I'm tired.
I've even got two onigiris in my hair right now.
So those tasty-looking mont blancs
on your head were onigiris.
That's right.
So they were onigiris...
I'll have you know I have
two triangular onigiris too.
Oh my, you're right.
Yeah...
We're really at odds today, huh?
You sure are.
Our next segment is... mine!
Alcoholic's
Concentration Game!
Ooh!
It's here!
In this section,
we'll play a game of Concentration
themed around
my favorite things,
alcohol and drinking snacks!
Ooh!
Please take a look at this!
We have alcohol and drinking snacks
on each side ordered randomly,
and you flip a number on
each side to choose your pair.
I'll be judging your combination based on
whether I think they go well together or don't.
However, even if they clearly don't go together,
if you're able to lift my mood...
Y'know?
I might consider otherwise.
It'll all depend on my judgment.
I see, I see.
Yeah. If I judge the combination as good,
you get the points for those!
This sounds pretty difficult, Okayu-senpai.
Right?
This will be hard.
We have to deal with her mood swings as well.
Mood swings?!
Seriously? Then, I'll take this chance to...
Aki-chan, I love you.
Ah!
I love you too...
Please stop flirting with me in-between!
You should take countermeasures too
while you have time, Rushia-chan!
Aki-senpai, since we both like Okayu-senpai,
why don't we get along?
That's kind of impossible.
Heeey!
I won't allow you
to support Okayu with me.
There she goes,
taking her all for herself!
Now then, let's start the game!
Okayun, please choose one drink!
Hmm... number eight!
Number eight!
Coming right up!
Oh?
It's a lemon sour!
Lemon sour!
For a snack... Some tendies would be nice, so...
Number three!
Number three, coming right up!
Oh?
That looks like it works.
Sashimi!
I see.
I'd like to decide on whether
it's a perfect combination or not,
rather than on whether they go together or not.
I see.
(8) Lemon Sour + (3) Fish Sashimi
They do work together,
but on whether they're perfect together or not...
This is looking bad.
Since it's for you, Aki-chan,
I'll put in extra sourness in your lemon sour.
I'm bad with fizzy drinks.
Wait, what?
(8) Lemon Sour + (3) Fish Sashimi
This combination...
is...
bad!
It's bad?!
No way, really?
Whyyy?
They're all right together,
but I want to pair lemon sour
with something more oily.
Yeah, it seems like
it'd go perfectly with oily foods.
That pair was around 75 points.
75?
I see.
That's pretty high.
This is my last appearance here,
so I want to make it a bit more challenging.
So that's what it was.
Rushia-chan, please select your alcohol!
I'm a bit scared now.
Then...
Drink number... six!
Oh?
Since I have my pride as a streamer and all,
I'll pick one that hasn't been picked before.
Snack number one!
Ah!
That's perfect!
(6) Beer + (1) Chicken Tendies
No questions asked, it's perfect!
Ahh!
Oh!
Oh I'm― I'm starting to
use my clairvoyance again.
This combination is something no one can deny.
I feel like I was overpowered.
Did it feel like I completely overwhelmed you?
Yeah! Yeah! I felt really good
when you flipped the card over.
Did you like it?
Similar to right now.
So we'll be like tendies together?
Y-Yeah.
I see, I see.
This combination is seriously the best.
It is, isn't it?
I want to have them right now even.
Dried fruits! (with shochu)
Okayu tries to get a point in the 2nd round...
I see.
I feel like this combination's pretty good.
How about it, Aki-chan?
This combination is...
bad!
A crushing losing streak
Whyyy?!
Whaaat?!
Oh? That looks good together!
Rushia, looking to continue her winning streak...
Tempura... (with white wine)
How is it?
This combination is...
good!
Huh? It's good!
She gets a point with a surprising pair!
Ooh! It's good together, huh?
Seriously?
I think we have time for another turn.
There are some that we haven't seen,
so I'd love for you two to flip some more over.
Okayun, go ahead!
Then... number eight!
It's lemon sour again!
Mm.
And a snack that would go well with it?
I want to pull something fried this time for sure...
Then... number eight for the snack as well!
Number eight, coming right up!
Oh?
Don't these go well with it? Salami!
They're really good!
(8) Lemon Sour + (8) Salami
This combination is...
good!
Yay!
Of course.
They go pretty well together.
You can buy these two easily
at a convenience store.
How convenient.
Convenient convenience store
She threw in a dad joke so nonchalantly.
I love her.
But I love Okayu, dad jokes and all.
Yeah... I love puns so I love her so much.
I looove puns.
Rushia-chan, please flip a card over!
Then, for me... number two!
Alcohol.
Number two.
Japanese liquor?
It says it's sparkling, too.
Whaaat? What is that?
Sparkling Japanese alcohol.
The staff added something extra.
Mm-hmm.
As for the snack...
Number two!
Number two, coming right up!
Ooh! That's looks good!
I wonder...
You've got an affinity for oily foods!
Rushia-san got oily foods 3 times in a row.
You're covered in oil!
I'm oily today!
How do I judge this one...
(2) Japanese liquor (sparkling) + (2) French fries
I feel like carbonation and oil
are pretty standard together.
Yeah, the carbonation is a big factor.
What flavor are the French fries?
I was wondering about that!
If it's only lightly seasoned with salt,
it might not go well together.
What flavor?
What would you like on
your fries for this, Rushia-chan?
For this... consommé.
Thoughts?
Is that good?
Consommé?
Is consommé your final answer?
Can I cheat?
Cheat?
The comments are saying cheese goes well.
Cheese.
Is cheese your final answer?
Is salt and ketchup not good enough?
You're cheating so much!
How about roe?
Okayu-senpai makes onigiri out of them too, so.
Ah, that's true. I like roe.
I'll stick with roe!
I'm not quite sure what French fries
with roe would taste like.
This combination with cod roe mayo is...
good!
Oh!
Oh, it works!
Yay!
I'd have given you a no if it was consommé.
That was close!
Way too close!
However, the salty spiciness of cod roe mayo
goes well with Japanese liquor.
Oh, so that's how it is.
I see.
By the way, why was consommé no good?
Consommé is because...
Javanese, I mean, Japanese liquor!
Oh, really?
Are you okay, Aki-senpai?
You're not drunk, are you?
Is she already drunk?
You're still sober, right?
I haven't drunk anything yet.
You were slurring quite a bit there.
Javanese...
Cute.
I was talking like I was at an izakaya.
And the next segment is...
What do you think of me?
Poll Up My Image
This is Rushia-chan's segment,
so I'll leave the explaining to you!
Okay!
For this segment, the viewers
will be polled on a particular theme.
Rules
The viewers
Is Uruha Rushia wholesome?
Once we see the results, we'll start chattingabout a topic related to the poll theme.
35% Wholesome
HUH?
Topic
Recent obsessions
After we finish the talk segment,
the same poll will be run again.
The same poll will be run
The results of the second run will tell us
what the audience took away from our talk.
100% Wholesome!
* Wrong answers not allowed.
I see!
I see.
So next we're gauging our viewers' feelings?
I see you've noticed something important.
If we spell it out, yes.
We have to stay on the viewers' good side.
I see.
This is the first theme!
These three go off to defeat the demon lord!
Who's the hero?
I see. Seeing who'll be the hero
if we form a party, huh?
I see?
So now we'll be polling this?
Yeah.
Please vote for one of us!
But out of the three of us...
Yeah?
the hero would have to be me.
I can already see her charging at the enemies,
screaming, "Arrrrgh!" at the top of her lungs.
Yeah.
Stop commenting that I'm the demon lord!
They keep calling me the demon lord!
But yeah. If I had to say,
you'd be in the demon lord's army.
Really?
Yeah... Okayu-senpai seems
like the hero type too...
And Aki-senpai seems like a female hero.
Like an Amazoness.
She seems capable.
Yeah, that!
The comments are saying Okayun
seems like she'd betray us.
I'd probably be a close aide to Rushia-chan
and betray her before she suspects me.
Nooo!
I want to read that manga.
Nooo.
I'd definitely join the dark side after that.
You'd turn evil and become the new demon lord.
I'm no longer the hero, then!
I became the demon lord...
Oh? There's the bell!
It seems the poll has finished.
Here are the results of the poll!
Ta-dah!
Blue: Hero
Red: Demon lord
Hey, are you guys trolling me?
Rushia-chan and I are
more villains than heroes.
Villains, huh...
Yeah.
It's great.
So now we have to convince them to switch us
from the demon lord's army to the hero's party.
Right.
This is where the true battle starts.
Yeah, that's true.
The chatting topic will be about
what I snapped earlier,
about a recent irritating event.
But first, I'd like to ask you two
about your experiences first.
An irritating event, huh...
Yeah, do you have any?
I wonder if I do... An irritating event, huh?
Yeah.
Ah! But that time might...
I thought I started the washing machine, but I didn't.
Happens all the time!
So I started throwing a tantrum in front of it.
It happens so often.
It does! It does!
Like, "Why?!"
It happens so often.
Is that it?
That's all that comes to mind.
You're so mild-mannered.
Am I really?
I don't have much that irritated me either.
You know how it's important
to just let some things slide?
Ah...
I don't know if I'm just overflowing
with justice like a hero or something,
but I try to be the bigger man.
I see... By the way,
are you two perhaps...
saying things that make you seem like a hero?
No, no, not at all.
Are you?
What about you, Rushia?
I have none.
I was surprised you guys had to think about it.
Like, "Wow, they have a lot
of things that pissed them off."
"I have nothing that comes to mind."
"I'm just looking up at the ceiling."
Are you fine even when a bug shows up
while you're looking at the ceiling?
A bug actually did appear.
Huh?!
There was a bug and
my cat started chasing after it.
Ugh!
I thought, "This is bad!" and tried hard
to let the bug escape, but it disappeared.
You didn't try to kill it?
No way!
I felt bad for it since the cat was about to kill it.
I see.
I tried to save it.
It would've been bad for the cat too.
I wonder where it went.
I'll go save it later.
Rushia-chan, did you... k*ll it?
N-No, I didn't.
Rushia-chan... you killed it, didn't you?
I... I didn't.
"It disappeared" is a bit cliché, isn't it?
I didn't.
This is bad...
This is looking bad for me...
I'm just making it worse.
I really did just ignore it.
I have something to say to you too, Aki-senpai.
What is it?
You said you wouldn't let me support Okayu.
You were irritated then, weren't you?
You couldn't let it slide then, could you?
That's why you said that, right?
It's not like that...
Hey!
Tell me the truth!
This segment is scary...
Trust me, Okayu-senpai! Trust me!
C'mon, trust me!
Our little chatting time is over, it seems.
The bell rang.
It rang, huh.
How will this turn out?
Let's have a re-poll!
I'm excited.
We showed how hero-like we can be, after all.
Yeah.
How will our efforts play out?
I wonder.
Let's take a peek at the results!
Results!
Let's reveal the results now!
The results of the poll is this!
Blue: Hero
Red: Demon lord
Bam!
Hey, what the heck is this?!
Mine hasn't even changed!
Aki-senpai's 56.1% hero now.
Okayu-senpai is 26.7%
I'm 1...
What's with this?!
It hasn't changed!
It's the same.
Is this bugged?
Hey!
The cue card's saying yours is .1% more heroic.
Rushia-san,
you're 0.1% more heroic!
Yay!
Like hell I'm happy about that!
Congratulations!
Yay!
I'm the hero!
And we're the villains, huh.
We are.
Well, that's fine.
If Okayu-senpai's a villain, I'll go bad anytime.
I'll be betraying you, but are you fine with that?
I'll... um... uh...
Yeah.
Then I'll become more and more evil.
I see.
So you'll get stronger and stronger, huh?
Yeah.
I see.
I'll get stronger and force
Okayu-senpai into submission.
Ah, that might be good too.
Please stop appealing to her fetish.
Let's move on to the next segment.
The next segment is this!
Can I Affirm That For Ya?
She's got my speech pattern down.
Om, nom, Okayu!
She sounds so like me!
This is my corner.
Please explain the rules, me.
Since I can affirm anything and everything,
in this segment,
The Fail
You went to change for PE but found out you
were wearing pajamas under your uniform!
Viewer
I'll read a viewer's fails and have
the other two guess how I'll affirm them!
I see...
Ooh!
Let's have a look at our first one!
Okay!
Our first failure is...
this!
"I was sitting in a chair
and thought it had a backrest,
so I leaned back only to
fall straight down and hit my head."
Let's have these two affirm this person's failure!
Let's try.
Let's see...
We're affirming this?
Yeah, let's affirm them!
Oh, I got a good one.
I got one too.
Aki-chan's looks really long!
I want to add one more thing...
Aki-chan...
Aki-chan, that's a script at this point.
I'm thinking about what I want you to say.
Not a scriptwriter
Okay! I'm ready!
Then, let's start from Aki-chan!
Roger!
There it is. Please start reading!
Nooo! I want you to read it!
Okay, ready?
"Wow, that was clean!
Well... I'll take you to the infirmary."
👏👏👏👏👏
Très bien.
What was that?
Is this "clean" about how they fell?
Yeah!
I see, like tens across the board.
She teases them a little bit,
but is still kind to them.
That's smooth.
I see.
I'm fulfilled.
This female Onigiri is completely satisfied.
You're satisfied?
I'm satisfied.
Well then, Rushia-chan, you're next.
Whenever you're ready!
Mine is this!
"That was so good!
That'd make the whole party laugh!"
Ah, that's good!
I see.
That was affirming, wasn't it?
It's got a little drawing, too. How cute.
There's a little cat.
So when you're sitting in a chair
and fall because there's no backrest,
you want me to be like,
"Ah, Rushia-chan, that one-shot joke is great!"?
I do! I want you to laugh at my mistake.
'Cuz I'm an M.
You are?!
I guess we just weren't meant to be...
What?! No way!
Well then, I'll reveal my answer!
I wonder what it is...
I would affirm them like this!
"Nice catch, floor!"
You're praising the floor?!
To the floor?!
Wait, so you're affirming the floor?
Yeah, she's talking to the floor.
Well, yeah. Don't you think the floor deserves
some credit for catching us so often?
That was such...
She's built different.
an unexpected answer.
I guess this won't be as easy as I thought.
It certainly won't.
The floor is amazing.
What?
Let's move on to the second failure!
This is difficult.
This is our next fail!
Ready!
"There was a person that looked like
my friend at the train station,
so I shouted hey-yo,
but they turned out to be a stranger."
Ah...
This is quite embarrassing.
When I saw your answers,
you two had answers
I wouldn't have been able to come up with,
so it was interesting.
Wait, really?!
So it was pretty far off?
Yeah. But it was interesting.
Aki-chan, what is that?
I was thinking about how you'd respond
so much that I'm confused now.
Rushia-chan's writing a fair bit!
I finished!
Rushia-chan's is kind of funny.
I feel like you'd say this.
Let's have a look at their answers!
Let's start with Rushia-chan's!
Okay!
Please show your answer!
It's this!
"What beautiful yodeling!"
I see, playing off of hey-yo huh?
Yeah!
But if you saw a person that looked like your friend,
Uh-huh.
and you called out to them,
only to realize that they're a stranger,
and then I slipped in and said,
"What beautiful yodeling!"
I'd be teasing you, right?
I'm taunting you so much.
That would be nice.
It would?!
I want you to say it.
I've been pretty unrestrained for a while.
Okayu-senpai's image of me
is becoming more and more...
She's finding out how I really am.
I do feel like you want to be
treated badly or talked to harshly.
She really is an M.
I see.
This is bad, this is bad.
"What beautiful yodeling,
but you know what else is beautiful?
You, Rushia-chan."
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
So that's what you want.
Really?
So that's it.
I see.
Crap... I can feel my consciousness leaving...
Don't faint on us!
Suck it back in!
Let's see Aki-chan's answer!
Okay!
"Hey-yo! Hey-yo!
Let's greet the world together! ♡"
Both of you thought of it as a yodel, huh?
Or rather, played it off by pretending it is.
I think repeating their shout
makes all the difference.
Like, "Hey! Hey-yo!"
I see!
That's why you said it twice.
Yeah!
I see... "Let's greet the world together!"
Does this heart also have some meaning to it?
The heart... is just my desires leaking out.
But really, I wanted to go
for one where she teases you
but still goes along with you in a kind way.
Yeah!
I see.
All right, let's compare answers!
I would affirm them like this!
"Just become friends with them from there."
Ah, I see.
Ah!
Since they waved at a stranger,
use that opportunity to become friends with them.
That's my answer.
"Ah, sorry. I got the wrong person."
"But, well, this must be fate.
Wanna become friends?"
Like that.
Ooh!
That's a clean way to cover it up.
Yeah. I feel like it'd work.
Yeah. It's natural and no one gets hurt.
But it's a completely different
direction from you two's.
I couldn't live up to your expectations.
I don't understand Okayu-senpai
at all the way I am now.
What do I do...
What should we do?
Extra
I found some cheese called "Chiikama"
It's called Chiikawa!
* It's "Chiikawa."
You know that cat character?
It's not Chiikama!
That's a drinking snack!
What fillings do the Onigiri-chans have?
They're empty.
Uh...
So they don't have any.
Yeah, they're empty to the core.
Do you drink alcohol
and eat drinking snacks, Okayun?
I don't drink alcohol much...
I get the Asian flush and drunk really fast,
so I'm not a strong drinker.
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub channel
on Niconico for the full stream archives!
Cute.