I mean, idols don't p*o, right?
It really grosses me out!
That's what makes you so cute...
Starring:
Ookami Mio
Nekomata Okayu
Robocosan
This show is brought to you by Ookami Mio...
...Nekomata Okayu...
...and Robocosan.
Random 5W1H
No.1 Chad Grand Prix!
So, do all of you know what 5W1H is?
Robocosan, please tell us one.
When!
And what's that in English?
Wh-
When!
Next, Okayu-san!
Who!
In English?
And now, Mio-san...
Wh-
Where?
And, in English?
What's?
Alright! So...!
That's not quite right, but...
For our No.1 Chad Grand Prix...
She got it wrong?
It was wrong?
What we're going to do is...
First up, please take a look at this.
Wh-
What's this?!
Can you see the panels for
When, Where, Who, and What?
You'll each select a square from each category,
Rules
Select a square from each category, then improvise
a Chadly line based on the scenario that's revealed.
then you'll deliver a Chadly line
based on the scenario that's revealed.
Robocosan, you have a kind of boyish voice,
and can be a bit of a Chad,
and you're good at doing scenarios, right?
Naaa.
That's a fresh response...
Huh?!
Did her brain just short circuit?
With that said, let's start off with Mio-san.
What kind of scenario will it be?!
Challenger: Ookami Mio
So, we'll have you choose
one square from each category.
Which number do you want for When?
I don't know!
Yeah!
The "M" in Mio looks like a 3 so...?
Umm, alright. I think I'll choose #3.
She's being herded.
I'll pick #3.
Alright, let's see When #3.
"On your birthday."
On my birthday!
This should be easy to follow through with.
Yeah.
What number will you pick for Where?
I pick #6!
"In the toilet"?!
I knew it'd be something like that.
What number will you go with for Who?
I'll go with #2.
"To your female childhood friend."
That's kind of sus.
What?!
That's a scary situation...
Yeah!
You wouldn't normally go to
the toilet together, right?!
I'll... go with #4.
Alright, let's see #4.
"Say farewell"!
Why?!
And on your own birthday, too!
Say farewell
To your female childhood friend
In the toilet
On your birthday
Please give us your Chadliest performance.
Seriously?!
That's a really, really, really tall order!
This is ridiculous!
Wow...
This should be fun!
Hey, you lot have to do this afterwards too!
So now, please give us your Chadliest lines.
3, 2, 1, go!
Thanks for celebrating
my birthday with me today.
It means a lot.
That's a nice voice.
We've been friends for so long...
There's the childhood friend trope.
But honestly... I'm sorry...
But I just can't deal with girls
who take ages in the toilet.
I mean, idols don't p*o, right?
That was such a frank farewell...
Fin
Should I have said "p**p" instead?
I don't think that's the problem here...
"P*o" might be a manlier thing to say, though.
You think "p*o" is manlier?
Yeah, I think "p*o" is manlier as well.
That's not a word that idols
should be saying over and over again!
And, here are the results from
the International Society of Chad Evaluation...
There's no way something like that exists!
From a perfect score of 10...
8.7!
That's pretty high!
Congratulations!
Wow!
And now, our next victim is Robocosan.
No way.
So I'm next?
Can she unleash her inner Chad?
Challenger: Robocosan
What number do you want for When?
I think... I'll go with #1.
"The day before your
high school graduation."
I see...
Which number for Where?
I'll take #5.
#5.
"In the park."
This might hit us in the feels.
Which number for Who?
I feel like #6 might be something weird,
but let's go with that.
#6.
"To your homeroom teacher"?!
What a match!
Right in the feels!
It really is!
If this keeps up...!
Yeah, it's turning into a nice scenario.
I've picked #6 and #5, so how about #3?
Let's see What #3.
"Scold."
Why did it turn out this way?!
What did you do, teach?!
What should I go with? This is hard.
Scold
Your homeroom teacher
In the park
The day before your high school graduation
So, how is she going to do this?
Please give us your Chadliest lines.
3, 2, 1, go!
Hey, teach...
Do you know why...
I called you out to the park today?
She called them out...?
You're always...
giving me that weird look...
You're always looking at me like that...
It really grosses me out!
Tomorrow... you'd better call me by my name...
Make sure you call me "Robocosan,"
'Kay?
Fin
No more!
Waaah...!
I wonder what triggered that...?
Aah...
Aaah...
Give me a break!
So cute...
And, Robocosan's Chadliness score is...
3.6!
That's so low!
She was just complaining!
The feedback was that it
was a little on the cute side.
A Little on the Cute Side
It was cute!
I see... The judges do love
their Chads, I guess.
There's a pretty big variance in scores.
Yeah, there is!
It's a pretty big gap.
Can she beat the current record?!
Challenger: Nekomata Okayu
What number do you want for When?
Hmm...
I'll take #5!
Oh! "Christmas"!
Nice.
What number do you want for Where?
Hmm...
#3!
"On the way home on your bicycle."
Hey, isn't this kind of nice?
It is!
Hey, how come everyone else
gets normal stuff?
Why was my one "in the toilet"?
Isn't that kind of weird?
What number do you want for Who?
Hmm... #1!
"A junior that you've liked for a long time."
That's a great scenario...
This hits you in the feels too!
What number do you want for What?
#6.
"Be kind after you get mad."
That's violence in the home...!
How horrible!
This is pretty bad.
Be kind after you get mad
To a junior that you've liked for a long time
On the way home on your bicycle
On Christmas day
You're a bad cat!
This is pretty bad...
I wonder how I should get mad...
That's kinda terrifying...
I'm scared...
Please give us your Chadliest lines.
3, 2, 1, go!
Jingle bells, jingle bells ♪
Ah... It's Christmas already...
She's even setting the mood...
When we're...
walking along like this, me pushing my bike,
it reminds me of the day we first met.
The vibe is pretty good so far...
When I remember that day...
I get so fr*cking mad.
She's mad now!
We were out with a bunch of friends,
but you wouldn't look my way at all!
I kept wondering when
you'd realize my feelings for you,
and now it's Christmas and
you still haven't realized at all...
Her love is becoming warped...
You're such a dimwit...
But...
That's what makes you so cute...
Fin
That was scary...
I got chills for a second there...
It wasn't scary!
It felt like you had some emotional baggage.
That's true!
So you wanted them to confess to you?
So, Mio-san is leading
with 8.7 points right now.
You have to beat that to win.
Yeah, beat my p**power.
The p**power...
So now, Okayu-san's Chadliness score is...
7.8!
That's pretty high!
It seems there was a bit of deliberation about
whether being clingy is actually manly.
Deliberation Over Whether or Not
Being Clingy Chadly
Ah, I see.
You acted pretty possessively...
So this time, Mio-san had the
highest score, with 8.7 points.
Chad Queen
Ookami Mio
If we do this again...
Congratulations!
Congrats!
Thanks!
If you enjoyed this video,
If you enjoyed this video, please subscribe to hololive's
official YouTube channel and smash that like button.
please subscribe to hololive's official YouTube
channel and smash that like button.
Now, let's end this on
a Chadly note as well.
Thank you for today!
Later!
Catch!
Thanks!
Laterz!