Wrap it by the Big 0!
That's in, like, one minute!
Give me a count.
Three cuts left!
That's some F-stop.
Hmm? Freeze it there.
I want a knife there instead.
What?!
Can you do that?
I-I can try!
That's my KanKans.
Avocado toast, on me.
Thanks... (Grr.)
So fix this cut too.
Huh?
Juxtapose the girls and then zoom!
G-Got it!
Smash cut to a block shot of 90210!
Uh...
Verite the mise-en-scene,
superimpose the cold open,
use the dynamic dolly shot here,
gobo the money shot,
overcrank the pillowbox,
wide-release the credits,
and tie it up with gesundheit...
Enough! I have no idea what you're saying!
And finally, RuRu here!
Bueno.
I'mma choke a bih!
Producer, we're running out of time!
What?!
Not on my watch!
Hup!
Master up by the Big 0!
I did nothing wrong... right?
You did everything wrong!
We're not done yet,
but it's time...
to hit up Tinseltown with the Tubers of Big Holo.
Huh?
I mean you, stars of the show.
Think that's what hololive producers are like?
Don't cast me in that role!
It's not like that, we swear!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!