If you
fail this quiz,
you'll get guillotined?!
What are their fates?!
Guillotine Quiz
It's a bit early,
but Happy Halloween!
Happy Halloween
Well then, girls. Take a look above you!
Above?
This ain't right.
Those look pretty dangerous.
Dangerous!
Absolutely Dangerous!
It's freaking scary!
Since it's Halloween this time around
and we're doing a horror-themed episode,
we prepared these custom-made guillotines!
Yaaay!
hololive's one scary company.
This is one messed-up company.
Let's start off by introducing yourselves, shall we?
Knock knock goes the fox, everyone!
I'm Shirakami Fubuki and I don't wanna be
plated up as a Halloween dinner.
Please spare me.
Happy Halloween!
That's some
juicy meat.
I'm Shirogane Noel from hololive's 3rd—
Juicy?
Hey! Eyes up here!
Looks delish.
They do look delish.
The juiciest of them all.
I'm in awe at the size.
Being humiliated like this in an official show
is a stain upon my pride as a knight!
End me!
End my suffering!
Right now!
Hey, you came, ta!
Uh...
I'm Amane Kanata and I'm probably gonna
go back to the Celestial Realm in a different sense.
Happy to be here!
I'm Yukihana Lamy from hololive 5th Gen!
I'm rocking the same hairstyle
as Kanata-senpai today!
Hey! We look just like sisters, don't we?
Victory's in the bag, now!
Anyways, thanks for having me!
So to give a breakdown on
what we're doing today,
I've got a letter from the mastermind
which I'll read out.
The four of you will have to take on a quiz,
and if you get five questions wrong,
a guillotine will drop and you'll go bye-bye!
This is basically a death game
that you need to escape from.
However, we've planted a traitor
among you posing as a participant.
That traitor is our demonic Joker card!
The Joker knows
the correct answers to every question.
Do your best to answer every question
and find the Joker
and survive this quiz!
HAH! HA! HAHAHA!
She's doing it again!
Oops! That's our signal to start the game!
Well then, let's start the Guillotine Quiz!
First Question
First up, a Halloween-related question!
What?
What's the representative fruit of Halloween?
Ah! I see!
Ah!
We're not kindergarteners, 'kay?
Suddenly she's smug.
This is way too easy.
Are you making fun of us?
All right, let's take a look at your answers.
All at once, if you will.
Here.
Yup!
Pumpkins all across the board!
The correct answer is...
...Pumpkin!
Yaaay!
Easy, isn't it?
Easy as pie~ ♪
Second Question
Halloween Day is on October 31st.
However, what day is the following day,
November 1st, in Japan?
W-W-Wai—
November 1st...
A. Sushi Day
B. Tempura Day
1st?
C. Ninja Day
Okay! Answers, please!
It's pretty easy, right?
Hold on a minute.
Wait.
Time out.
The difficulty level just spiked through the roof.
What happened?
What day is it?
What the heck IS this?
All right, let's take a look at your answers.
All at once, please!
A, C, B, and C...
That's quite a spread!
Wow!
We're split up!
This is the answer!
We're all over the place!
Okay...
Why'd you pick C,
Lamy-san?
I knew it. I'm definitely wrong
since you're asking me first, right?
No such thing!
That's not true at all!
I'm just starting from the right.
Stop scaring people!
I mean with ninjas, they do that pose
with their hands, don't they?
And the finger looks like a "1" so...
True.
But why'd you draw a caterpillar?
I just thought it'd be cute.
And now they're starting
to pick on each other.
Caterpillar...
As for me,
the reason I answered "Tempura Day"
was because I thought you could get 111
from lining up all the fried shrimp.
I think this was a pretty
Ah. I see.
smart answer, don't you?
And how about you, Fubuki-san?
I picked "Sushi Day"
but I actually had the same
thought process as Kanatan.
When you line up the tuna sushi,
you'd get a straight row that looks like 1.
Oh! I get you. That makes sense.
The correct answer is...?
...A. Sushi Day!
Ooh! All right!
Fubuki-san is the only one correct!
Sushi was the right answer!
Yaaay!
This reeks of a setup!
I smell some final boss shenanigans!
Isn't it weird that she got the answer for this?
Isn't that just sus?
It's not! There's nothing sus about it!
We're on your tail now~.
There's nothing sus going on at all!
We're closing in on her~!
Third Question
The next question's a drawing-based one.
What shape is the Japanese archipelago?
Drawing!
SPARE ME!
Please draw it out!
Ooh, I see!
Here it is!
I knew this would come!
I mean this is definitely drawable.
This is gonna be easy!
It's gonna be super easy!
All right, let's take a look at your answers.
Open them all up, please.
Here are your answers.
Uh-huh, I see.
That's REALLY detailed!
Hmm, okay...
We all did pretty well, didn't we?
They're pretty...
Don't you think the detailed ones are pretty sus?
'Cause the Joker can look at the answers, right?
You're right!
The correct answer is...?
Noel-san's!
Oh! Yay!
Wait, just her alone?
Her drawing was the most detailed,
so she's the only one correct.
Huh?
Because mine was the most detailed? (lol)
That's how it works?!
Quality plays a part?!
Only one may live, huh? (lol)
It looks like there are
reasons for the incorrect answers.
Isn't it all just guesswork?!
The scale of Kyushu
in Lamy-san's drawing is a little...
SCALE?!
It looks like a tail.
True. Kyushu's way bigger than that.
And apparently, it's also the same reason
why Kanata-san's answer failed.
What? Kyushu's right up there
in the top left, ain't it?
Ah! On the top left?
Yeah! Kyushu and Okinawa
are up there in the top left corner!
Isn't there a gap there?
Doesn't it look like they're
split down the middle?
I didn't have enough space
to draw it down there,
so I did it in the top left corner instead.
Ah.
If that's the case,
it doesn't count since that's Fictionalized Japan.
No way.
Why?! That makes no sense!
And for Fubuki-san's case...
You drew a face and arms, so that's right out.
THAT'S THE PROBLEM?!
THAT PART?!
REALLY? COME ON!
But this proves my theory.
Noerun probably looked
at the answers to draw the map!
That's gotta be it!
No way. You're imagining things!
Yeah, it's gotta be.
Fourth Question
When it comes to the sake, Daiginjo,
what's its rice polishing ratio?
D-D-D-D—
Daiginjo?!
A. 50% or lower.
Daiginjo, huh?
B. 60% or lower.
First I've heard of it.
C. 70% or lower.
Isn't this just biased
towards Lamy-chan?
You know the answer, right?
But this is common knowledge, y'know?
That's true.
Common knowledge?!
It's common knowledge?!
Looks like Fubuki-san
and Kanata-san are worried.
I have no idea!
I don't know the answer!
We'we babies!
We don't know anythwing
abouwt awcohow~!
That really makes me wanna
deck you just once.
All right, let's take a look at your answers.
All at once, now.
B, A, A, and A.
Well then, everyone other than
Fubuki-san picked A.
Oh!
Huh?
Ooh!
It's A?!
By the way, I'm assuming Noel-san and Lamy-san
already knew the answer was A, right?
Huh...?
Well, obviously!
It's common knowledge.
I see. As for Kanata-san...
Was it your gut feeling? (Doubt)
It was my gut feeling!
The correct answer is...?
...A. 50%!
Yay!
All right!
Yes!
Fubuki-san's the only one who loses a life!
Nooo! Not like this!
By the way, Lamy-san,
what goes well with Daiginjo?
Well...
Simmered fish.
Ah, how elegant.
Sounds good!
Fifth Question
Here's the question.
Autumn's a season where
chestnuts are delicious, isn't it?
Do you girls like
the chestnut-based dessert, Mont Blanc?
Well...
It is delicious.
I like it.
Now, then! Tell me which mountain
the name of the dessert originated from.
Which of the following is the answer?
A, B, or C?
How would I know?!
I have absolutely no idea.
It's the one in Europe, right?
Huh?!
You know of it?
The one in Europe?
I guess I'll have to go
with my gut feeling for this.
I think it's this one?
Let's take a look at those answers!
All at once!
C, C, A, A. That's a perfect split!
Hold on. Lamy-chan?
Wow! That's amazing!
Lamy-chan, that's po*p, isn't it?
MONT BLANCS ARE BROWN, OKAY?!
I drew the exact same thing
as Fubuki-senpai!
Fubuki-san's Mont Blanc is
an actual Mont Blanc, though.
It's definitely a Mont Blanc~!
The correct answer is...?
...C. The actual Mont Blanc!
All right!
Yay!
Still, that was pretty tough.
That was probably a tough question, wasn't it?
It was tough!
How do you even answer?!
Yikes. I only have 2 lives left.
How does it feel?
Lives Left : 2
That's 2 lives left, all right.
I just realized something
now that we're this far in.
Lamy-chan's probably not the Joker.
Wh-Wh-Why would you say that...?
You got way too many wrong answers
and you even drew po*p!
That's rich coming from you!
We're both 2 shots from death!!
By the way, Kanata-san,
who do you think is the most sus?
Well...
Noel, I guess?
She's got 4 lives left.
Hold on! Y'all—
No, no, no.
What I wanna ask is
how do you girls NOT know the answers?
Especially the question
about the map of Japan.
That level of guesswork is just weird.
Actually, I think it might be Fubuki-senpai.
Yeah, I think so too.
No way!
It could be that she's good at faking.
True, true.
She could be failing
the tough questions on purpose.
That's scary.
Sixth Question
How many milliliters
does a one shō bottle hold?
Actually, why are there
so many questions about alcohol?
What?!
It's Halloween, y'know?
Haha!
Isn't this just to make us
suspicious of Lamy-chan?
Wait, wait.
On the flip side, are...
are you gonna be okay?
We can just guess who the Joker is
from this question, can't we?
On the other hand,
I don't like the fact that you'd get sussed
just from answering correctly.
I hope I get this right.
It's all a matter of perspective indeed.
One... shō...
Show those answers all at once!
1500mL.
1800mL.
Ah...
1000mL.
1800mL.
Well then,
I'm 300mL short?
Huh?
The correct answer is...?
1800mL!
Yaaay!
Ugh...
I'm 300mL short.
Lamy-san and Noel-san are correct.
What?! It's 1800mL?
Yeah, it's 1800mL.
Exactly!
Lamy-san even wrote a thorough explanation.
The small bottles you
often see people drink from
or find in stores are 720mL bottles.
Oh-ho. I see.
I thought one shō was like... 1 liter.
Kanata-senpai, your bottle's crushed up, ain't it?
It's a defective one!
I don't know the shape of a one shō bottle,
Crushed up!
so I was just, uh...
imagining something made from La France!
My head's gonna roll at this rate.
Indeed.
Whaaat?
Looks like Kanata-san's on her last legs,
so I'm sure you'll want
to get the next one right, won't you?
Seventh Question
This one's a freebie.
Freebie?
No three positive integers (x, y, z)
can satisfy the equation
x^n +y^n = z^n
if the integer value of n is greater than 2.
Freebie?
What's the name
of this mathematical formula?
WHAT?
Please answer.
I guess I can go
with my guts on this one?
Ah, well...
You've got one life left, so...
I can go with my guts, right?
Ugh, this is just...
The only option is to return to monke. 🐒
Well then, it looks like
everyone's answered, so...
How would
we know this?!
Let's see those answers all at once!
The Law of Nature
(Natural Law)
Ah, it's space, I see.
Fermat's Theorem.
Facturization.
That's a good drawing.
I see we have a space cat among us.
Yeah, we do.
I don't know!
Lamy-san's answer is "Facturization..."
In the 210 years that I've lived,
this is the only thing I remember.
Even so, was it that hard to spell?
Yeah!
I only remembered the "zation."
Kanata-san. Your life is on the line
and you answered "Fermat's Theorem."
There's a song called "Turing Love"
and it's a song about math formulas
and there were words like
"Fermat" and "Euler"
and I've looked those up before!
That's what comes to mind for me
when talking about math.
And then Noel-san who
gave up trying to answer.
Yes. I just can't.
That so?
I have absolutely no idea.
The correct answer is...?
Fermat's Last Theorem!
WHAT?!
You were
so close!
My answer's
not good enough?
Why didn't
my answer count?
Apparently, there are
various "Fermat's Theorems."
Say what?
Huh?
There are a lot of theorems by Fermat, such as
Fermat's Little Theorem, or
Fermat's theorem on sums of two squares.
And the one in the question just now
was specifically Fermat's Final... uh...
Final Form!
Right. Not Final Form,
but the Final Theorem.
Therefore, while it's a shame, Kanata-san,
it's time to say goodbye!
But it's still Fermat's Theorem...
You've gotta be kidding me!
Do you have any last words, Kanata-san?
I TRUSTED YOU, FERMAT!
Time until the guillotine drops:
Three.
Two.
One.
Goodbye!
Yikes!
Whoa!
Kanata-senpai!
That was pretty smooth.
This is one
SCARY company.
I guess I won't be sleeping tonight.
We could be next.
Scary.
Among the three of you is
a Joker who knows all the correct answers.
Please discuss between yourselves and
name one person who you think is the Joker.
Who's the Joker?!
Whaaat?
Still, it's that dilemma thing, ain't it?
It's either Fubuki-senpai or Noel-senpai.
I see.
Exactly.
I think it's Fubuki-senpai.
I hear a voice from the depths of hell!
You can't say that on television!
Fubuki-senpai seems like
she can do anything,
so I think it's likely that—
Well, if I was the mastermind,
I'd give Fubuki-senpai all the answers.
I'd make her the Joker.
That's totally possible.
She's playing 4D chess.
She is.
Well... if that's the case,
I think it's Noerun!
Should we write the names on our boards
and reveal them all at once?
Ooh, shall we do that, then?
Let's do it!
That sounds great!
By the way,
how was the guillotine, Kanata-san?
Although asking that's a little...
That's one scary question.
It made one shocking sound.
Yeah, it did.
I won't be able to rest in peace for some time.
Oh, really?
The heck are you on about?
You're already resting in peace
for all eternity.
She's enjoying her time off.
True.
All right! Seems like everyone's done,
so let's look at your votes!
Show your Joker candidates!
Noel-san, Fubuki-san,
Fubuki-san, and Fubuki-san!
WHAAAT?!
Fubuki-san's making that
"I'm innocent!" expression.
It really isn't me!
It's DEFINITELY Noerun!
Well then,
if you're correct,
the Joker gets the guillotine.
If you're wrong,
the remaining two
will get guillotined instead.
I'm scared!
Phew...
Hurry on up here, girls!
No! I'm scared!
Time until the guillotine drops:
Three.
Two.
One.
GOODBYE!
I'M SCARED!
All right!
The last one standing is Noel-san!
Great job on playing the Joker!
All right!
I KNEW IT!
I survived!
SERIOUSLY?!
Congratulations!
Thanks!
Phew, I was worried at the start,
but it was easy!
SHE GOT US!
I trusted you!
I KNEW IT WAS YOU!
To the three of you
in the Celestial Realm,
now that you know she's the Joker,
do you feel like it adds up?
Now that you mention it,
I think she might've been
picking questions to answer correctly
while keeping an eye on her remaining lives.
You say that,
but you still went and died!
Dammit!
I knew it!
You were definitely looking
at the map while drawing it earlier!
It was way too good!
Yeah. Honestly, I looked at it while drawing.
It was pretty detailed, right?
Dammit!
Well then, to Noel-san who survived
and won in the end as the Joker!
Please close us out!
Please smash that like button and
subscribe to both the official
hololive YouTube channel as well as mine!
We're all super strong!
Please keep on supporting us!
All right! And let's finish it off with
a Happy Halloween to the viewers!
Ready?
Happy Halloween
Wait, we're not even on-screen!
Oh, yeah!