One, two, one, two!
What're you doing?
Training for the concert.
A star needs brawn...
...brain...
...and beauty!
But... it's tomorrow.
Oh my gawd!
I need to pack.
Got my malt, tendies, and triangle...
Do bananas count as snacks?
As appetizers, sure.
Quit freaking out!
Pause for a sec!
…
Don't actually freeze on me!
Listen, you gotta accept the fact
that the concert is tomorrow.
It's vital to go into it
calm and composed.
Hey! Let's make today's concert a good one!
Concert Today!
Oh lawd!
Gotta make that call... 1-800...
I'm a potato starch for you!
Ninja Arts: Bloodsucker!
Huh?!
Entering DEFCON 3!
Enemy at 2 o'clock!
They appear to be using
disruptive tactics!
Grab your spears!
Ya-ha!
Settled down some?
Yes, ma'am.
Can you really perform like this?
It's fine.
We've been at this for three years now.
Do you remember the choreography?
I'm quitting the idol biz.
Are you in crisis 24/7?
The rest of you remember, right?
Rotate the knee 90 degrees.
Netfl*x goes best with popcorn
and a large cola.
Excalibur's in B1 of the overlord's castle.
All of you forgot?!
What now?
We have less than three hours!
Isn't that obvious?
You have a plan?
A Haachama in need
is a Haachama indeed.
We cram like hell!
Aye!
No way.
The next two hours or so...
...we drilled the dance steps into our brains.
You might be wondering what's wrong with us...
...but this is hololive 1st Gen.
This is...
...who we are!
Are you all ready?
Up on cloud nine!
Here's the gorilla essence
I made in advance.
My favorite drink is carbonated judo!
আমার প্রিয় পানীয়টি কোমল জুডো
Oh, so I just have to snipe
the mayonnaise date.
Gum syrup for president!
Did we manage to memorize all the steps?
What's gonna happen to us?!
The concert's on May 28!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!