I feel the ripple of a fox, I do.
Hey, hey, hey!
Is this the hololive I've heard so much about?
The Most Flamboyant of Fennecs
Omaru Polka
Omaru Polka is here to take pole position!
Now take this!
Wh-What was that for, Senpai?
First impressions are key, you see.
What the... achoo!
Ah! Did you catch a chill
because she tried to act cool?
Gah! That joke landed as cold as the tundra!
You okay?
Lie down. We have a blanket.
Yahoo!
Fox Solidarity Springs Eternal...
What are you saying?
You're a cat, y'know?
A cat, y'know?
A cat.
You're a cat.
A cat, y'know?
Y'know?
P-Pol... a cat...
A cat.
Meow! ^-^
I'm a cat meow, then, forever! ^-^
Who's a good kitty?
Hey, hey, hey! This is the cat police!
A cat is among you, right?
We're taking her in.
Takin' in!
Eek!
A-A cat? A-Among us?
I-Impossible. No way.
Yeah, yeah, meoway!
Found her! Take her in!
Aye, aye, sir!
Fubuki-senpai!
No... She's innocent!
It's all my fault!
Polka...
Let's get her back.
We're taking Fubuki-chan back!
Yeah!
And so, after overcoming
many trials and tribulations,
we finally cornered the cat police!
If you can make it here...
...we'll give you Fubuki-senpai back.
Leave it to me! I've got this!
That's our circus girl!
Our ringmaster! Woo!
No, it's because...
I'm a cat!
I can handle these things easily!
Polka!
She made it!
Gah!
Let's head back, Fubuki-senpai.
Yeah!
Hurry up and get over here, you two!
Listen, Polka...
I need to apologize to you for lying.
You're not a cat. You're a fennec fox.
Huh?
Plus one to the hololive fox gang.
If you enjoyed this,
please subscribe for more!