Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
It's so cold!
Brrr...
So cold!
Since it's super cold today,
So cold...
Yeah?
let's play Oshikura Manju to cuddle up!
You okay there, Gran?
Good idea!
Who you calling Gran?!
I wanna play Oshikura Manju!
Me too!
Oshikura Manju!
Yeah!
Okay, let's do it!
Have at it!
We're doing it!
Oshikura Manju!
A push and a shove, hey, don't cry!
Gwaaargh!
Blargh!
Landslide victory, there.
Oshikura Manju Champion: Houshou Marine
Nice job, Marine-san!
Back to business
When it starts getting cold,
you start wanting warm things—
Yeah! And sometimes,
your appetite goes crazy.
Warm things, yep.
And you want to eat warm food!
That segue was so sloppy.
What was that, Towa-chan?
When it's cold—
Uh-huh.
When it's cold, my appetite goes crazy...
That's so true!
I know that feel!
What're you laughing for?
So true!
Hey!
Oh! Is there something
you want to eat, Subaru?
Mille-feuille hot pot!
Whoa!
That sounds pretty nice!
That's really fancy!
Mille-feuille hot pot is definitely tasty.
It's really yummy!
What about you, Cap'n?
Hm? What I would pick?
Hm, I wonder. Let me think...
Oh, but this might creep you out...
What the?!
It's okay! Just say it!
You sure?
Creep us out? What are you on about?
I'm your friend, I won't be creeped out!
You absolutely sure?
What is it?
I've got a bad feeling...
Really?
Porn mags and the like!
Oof...
Huh? What's wrong, you three?
Um, did she just say that?
Weren't we talking about stuff
we wanted to eat?
And thus, today, Marine died from hypothermia.
Towa-chan, can you give us
some ear bleach?
I'd love sukiyaki!
That's the best!
Sukiyaki's great!
Sukiyaki sounds good!
Sukiyaki!
♪ Su-ki-ya-ki! ♪ Su-ki-ya-ki! ♪
It's perfect when you have fresh meat! Also, eggs!
♪ Su-ki-ya-ki ♪ Su-ki-ya-ki ♪
Eggs!
Oh boy...
That sure is a nice choice.
Yum... I'm getting hungry now.
Now I'm craving it. Sorry, be right back,
gonna go get ingredients!
Oh!
Hey, wait!
So please excuse me.
Wait, what about us?
H-Hey!
Good job today.
What if—
Why are you trying to leave?
I'm very sorry.
Hold on! What if a customer comes in?
I'm just closing up shop.
Wait, is that—
Just close the shop up for a bit—
Huh? Wait, no—
Ah, it's a customer!
Oh!
Ah, a customer!
Here she is!
Huh? Oh!
It's a customer!
Whoa—
Cod milt!
What?
Excuse me?
Oh! She's bringing us back on topic!
Oh I see, that's her craving on cold days.
So that's what she wants to eat!
Oh, that's a dish you want to eat!
Wh-What?!
I was wondering what she was on about.
She must have been eavesdropping.
Cod milt!
Whoa!
That—
Oh, hello!
Today's Guest:
Hoshimachi Suisei
Hello!
Thanks for having me today!
That—
That was one sudden jump.
Wild.
MENT
LUCK: None
Hoshimachi Suisei
About Her: Cute
And so, our guest for today is
Hoshimachi Suisei!
She's accumulated so much gacha salt
that her luck stat is zero?
Hobbies: Otaku stuff!
Finishing Move: Suisei Train! Choo-choo-choo!
It appears she has a reason
for visiting the shop today!
Oh yeah!
Huh, what is it?
I just remembered, but didn't you tweet
that you wanted to play Endless Puyo with us?
Oh!
She totally tweeted that.
Oh yeah, I did!
@suisei_hosimati
Endless Puyo!??!?!?!
Hit me up!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
#GameShopMaruyama
Yeah! Like—
She even included the hashtag.
Marine was being all high and mighty,
Yeah, I guess I was.
Oh!
Marine was being all high and mighty,
even though everyone knows
I'm the queen of puzzle games!
Oh? No kidding?
Hold up!
Sui-chan! Even if you're good at Tetris,
Yeah, I'm not kidding!
it doesn't necessarily mean
you can play Puyo Puyo.
I can totally play Puyo Puyo!
Just the Stairs pattern, though!
What—
What's that?
Stacking colored Puyos like a staircase,
so that chains can be formed.
One of Marine's specialties.
"Stairs pattern"?! Did I hear right?!
Yes, the Stairs pattern!
That's the same one I use!
Right?
Okay, Sui-chan, can you build transitions?
Transitions...
Using patterns like Stairs,
a method of stacking vertically
allowing bigger chain formation.
might be hard for me with the time limit...
Oh, wow.
Uh-huh. Okay, then, in under a min—
They're already getting into advanced topics?
Yeah, I guess so.
If you're able to discuss all that,
do you want to give it a go, Sui-chan?
Yeah, I do!
Against Captain's reco—
Right! I thought my chance was gone
because the season already ended.
Nah, let's do it since you're here!
You'll let me?
We still have the game here. It's totally fine.
I'll do it!
Come at me, sis!
What was that?
It's just the pose that goes with that phrase.
And that brings us to...
A Last-Ditch Attempt!
Will She Surpass Marine's Record?
Hoshimachi Suisei Takes a Shot
at Puyo Puyo's Endless Fever!
Now to the point.
In Maruyama Championship Season 1,
Marine won the title in Endless Fever
with a record of 57726 points!
50k, huh.
We'll be having Sui-chan take a shot
at beating that record, today!
I'm gonna beat this lassie to a pulp!
Come at me, sis!
Hush!
Go, girl, go!
Get her!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Okay, Suisei-san, let's have a go!
I've got this!
Whee!
Good luck!
Let's go!
I'm so nervous!
Wait, is this game for real?
Captain was really rowdy after all.
It's starting!
We're starting off with this?
The game has begun!
Lo—Wait, already?
Whoa, she's quick!
This minute's gonna be over in a flash.
She's quick!
Oh, she's starting off with an All-clear.
And right off the bat from that—
Huh, what's that?
Mhm-hm, okay.
Her stacking is very steady.
She's stacking away.
Plop.
Captain! What pattern is this?
The Stairs pattern!
Thanks for the expert commentary!
I see.
Plop.
It's just like that.
It helps a lot.
Uh-huh.
I still have no idea what she's doing.
And a plop.
I see where this is going.
I don't get it.
Plop!
Wouldn't you need to clear them faster than this?
On one hand, sure,
Plop.
but at this point, she has a 5-chain ready.
Oh!
A 5-chain at the ready!
Oh! I think it might be a 6-chain now?
There!
You're kidding me.
Well? Will this actually get to six?
Wow!
It's getting to six... right? Yeah, it is!
Phew.
What! Amazing!
Great!
Damn! A 6-chain already!
A sudden 6-chain!
Wow!
Nice!
That was crazy!
A 6-chain is no joking matter.
You're kidding me!
That's incredible.
Seriously?
Plop.
I think she can get another one in.
She has 20 seconds!
She can do it again!
Doing a 2-chain here!
She can totally get another in.
12 more seconds!
You can do it, Sui-chan!
Wait up!
Wow.
The Captain's cheering all of a sudden now!
Hold on...
Hurry!
Eight more!
Wait for it...
Here we go!
Oh no, wait!
Oh no!
Wait up!
She's so good!
Five left!
Hurry, hurry!
Wait for me!
Four!
Wait!
Ahh!!
Three! Two!
You can still do it! Get going!
I can do it!
You can do it!
There, yes!!
Oh my gosh!
Whoa!!
Well now!
Yes!!
Oh!
Gwaaah!
Let's go!!
Wow!
That was crazy!
Just wow!
Say it ain't so!
You're seriously good!
Yes!!
And now!
And Suisei-san's score is...
Your pace was terrifying.
Still loading, oh!
Woo!
And the result is out!
Sui-chan's final score is 82717 points!
Yay!
Whoa, amazing!
Gwaaah!
Which means...
I can't believe it.
A new record!
Woo-hoo!
Hold your horses!
What's the matter?
Huh?
What?
I concede that she surpassed me,
What is it?
but Sui-chan, hey,
that season is already over, which means
Huh?
I have the right to another
attempt for this season!
Really now?!
Captain Marine calls for
a rematch to regain her throne!
Well, then...
Can I begin?
You lost!
Please do!
Here I go!
Start the game!
Break a leg!
Do your best!
Gotcha! I'll do my best and stack some transitions!
Go for it!
Will you be able to do that though?
But can you stack it well enough?
First, lay out the base for transitions...
Oops, she has a lot of blue Puyos!
Wait...
Uhh...
That might be a problem, huh?
Don't give up, Marine!
Towa, do you know what
she's gonna transition?
Not the slightest idea.
Will you tell us when you make one?
Sure.
Well, to put it shortly...
She already made the...
The transition...
You mean she already made one?
She... kinda did one, yeah.
What did she do?
And so, with her stair stacking,
the base for chaining is complete.
Now, to get more chains,
Marine-san is stacking more Puyos for transition.
25 seconds left...
Will you make it?
Uhh, hold on...
Try removing one chain.
Go away, go away!
Could it be that you...
You can probably remove all that
weird stuff with it— Ah!
Hm?
Wait, green, so much green...
She just keeps stacking them!
Marine, only 10 seconds left!
Just 10 seconds!
Huh? Marine-san, can you handle it?
You okay there?
Transition...? Where?
Will she finish this?!
Dammit!
I messed up!
That's it!
Oh no!
Hold on!
It's over!
Don't do it!
Oh no!
What just happened?
Ah!
Marine?
That was so close!
What happened?
I just...
Hmm?
I just messed up big time at the very end!
Well, then...
Here's your total score.
2319 points!
I got too greedy...
And that means... No new record!
No new record!
I lost to Sui-chan...
Eat that!
But you were really cool there, Marine!
Yeah, you were!
No idea what was going on, though.
Well, I'll be taking my leave, everyone.
Stop right there!
Hold up!
Sui-chan, wait, please!
Come back!
Good job, everyone.
Sui-chan, you can't! Come back!
Hold your horses.
Stop!
Why did you even come, then?
Huh?
Sit for a moment.
Please stay for a bit longer.
Why?
Sui-chan, you came because
you had some worries, right?
Not really. I just wanted to play Puyo Puyo.
Don't say that.
No, no, no.
Here at Maruyama, we solve
our guests' worries with games.
Exactly!
Wow, really?
Yes, really!
You can't just barge in carving for some milt,
play Puyo Puyo, and leave!
I can't?
Why did you come, then?
Yeah, why?
I'll go pick up our special, so sit still.
Hm? What is it?
Off she goes.
*rustle*
*rumble*
That sounds awful.
Yikes!
What do you not like about my rumbling?
What kind of looking is that?
Shut it! *rustle*
Found it!
This one! Boss, say the line!
That one, yes!
And there we have our request!
We have just the thing!
You stand up too!
"We have just the thing!"
Do you like the Kirby series, Sui-chan?
Ah! I played a bit of Kirby Air Ride.
Oh!
It was good! I liked it!
If you liked that one,
then we have just the thing for you!
Yay!
The game we recommend for today is...
Kirby Star Allies!
Yaaaay!
The first game in the Kirby
series for the Nintendo Switch:
Kirby Star Allies!
In this game, you, of course, can play solo,
or play together with three more players.
Team up with others and go on a fun ride!
Furthermore, Kirby can throw a Friend Heart
at enemies to befriend them.
The Friends system makes its appearance!
Limitless combinations unfold into
an infinite amount of possibilities!
Let's go on an adventure with Kirby!
As for what we're going to be playing today...
There you have it!
While the main story in
Kirby Star Allies is quite enjoyable,
today we're gonna focus on sub-games.
Sounds fun!
Yay! Sub-games!
The first sub-game we have is...
Chop Champs!
The one to chop the most amount of logs
while avoiding caterpillars and Gordos wins!
We're gonna have two rounds.
Starting with the middle difficulty: Chop Chief!
Prove your chops, everyone!
It'll start with one button press.
Get ready, girls.
Got it!
Ready!
It begins right away.
Well, then!
And... start!
Let's do it!
Swing with all your might!
Here it comes!
Here I go!
Here it is!
Wow, wow, that's fast!
Yikes!
Ah, a caterpillar!
Swing it, swing it...
There's more of them!
Swinging all day...
Uh oh...
Dodge the caterpillars by going left or right.
Got it! Ouch!
Oops...
Chop, chop, chop!
One, two, three!
Nice speed, keep it up.
Oops, bugs!
Ouch!
Ah! Why now?
Keep going—Ah!
Suisei-san is so fast!
She's super fast!
More chopping, more chopping!
She's a natural gamer!
Chop that one too!
Sui-chan is so fast.
Oh no!
Oh no, not now!
Ouch!
Heigh-ho, heigh-ho!
Dang it!
Come on, come on, come on!
Oh, come on!
Marine!
How are you all so fast?
Really now?
Huh? Did I just...?
That was a very close match!
Nose-to-nose!
Ahh, I kept messing up at the very end...
Why am I the only one without
the house?! There's only some base.
Just a pillar there.
Did you forget to build it?
Subaru's house is not good with rain.
Everyone's so fast...
Come on...
Let's bump the difficulty to the Chop Champion!
Got it! Well then, let's start!
Gotcha!
Start!
Let's see how you handle 3 axes difficulty.
It's started!
Here I go!
I'll be careful this time.
Look at them go!
Unlike last time.
Nice!
Towa-chan got much better, didn't she?
Cut this one...
Did I?
You definitely did!
Yikes!
Now here...
Nice pace.
Cut this one...
Careful, careful... This is the highest difficulty.
I'll become the champ!
Careful...
Ouch!
Looking good, girls!
Marine got some nice chops too.
Oh no!
Sui-chan is so fast!
Ah, I messed up!
Oops!
Ah, crap!
Oh no...
Yikes!
Ouch!
Subaru, try to avoid the caterpillars.
I'm trying!
Oh no, I messed up!
It hurts!
Finish!
Huh? This time...
Towa-chan is the winner with 6550 points!
Wow, really?
Wow!
Nice!
Sorry for being the champ!
There she goes.
Go be a lumberjack.
"I beg your pardon," and all that.
Annoying one, huh?
Next sub-game!
Star Slam Heroes!
Yay!
In Star Slam Heroes,
you charge up your power
to bat out an infalling meteor
at the correct timing!
For this round, they will be playing
at mid- and high-level difficulties.
Get ready, everyone!
Alright!
Okay!
Got it!
Let's go!
Start!
Go out there and save the country!
A'ight.
One-two... one-two...
Rrah!
One-two!
Keep that meter up.
Go!
AAAGH! I WAS OFF!
Let's go!
Whoa, this is...!
I flubbed that hard!
Huh?
I bugged out here.
Let's see who gets
the farthest in light years.
Hold up.
How is it?
Huh?
Wait, could we have done multiple presses?
Down to two...?
Don't tell me...
I think we could have!
What?
Wait, what? Huh?
Towa-chan...?
So that's what happened.
And Captain remaining...
That's how it works...
Aah, I was stopped!
Wooow!
Towa-sama's a natural!
Aaaagh...
Oh man.
No way!
Finish!
As for our results,
1st place goes to Towa-chan again!
Wheee!
GG.
She went 5575 light-years!
Piece of cake.
Darn...
Towa-sama's like one with her Kirby.
She is!
You're quite good.
Her compatibility's high.
Amazing play.
I am one with my Kirby, if you must know.
With Kirby?
I can see it.
Sui-chan here's a comet herself,
though! There's potential.
Exactly!
It's possible.
Watch out next match!
Next one!
Sure!
Okay! Next, let's go for
the highest difficulty: World Crisis!
World Crisis, got it.
Five charges, it says!
Oh yeah!
Build up five charges
and go for a home run.
Okay, okay.
You really gotta build up those charges!
Ready!
Start!
Okay!
Gotta charge up!
Time it well for five charges. Got it.
Build up five charges.
One! Two! One! Two!
You're doing good, Captain Marine!
Aah, so tense!
Damn, I don't get it!
How's this for charging?!
HIIIT!
Agh! I think I undershot that one!
Hmm? Did someone mess up their hit?
Made a mistake there.
This is getting crazy!
This might just go overboard!
Keep going!
Doing good?
Y'all doing great!
Get through with passion!
You're not dropping out like last time.
I'm gonna make it!
You can do it! Let's go! Let's go!
Doing great!
Go harder!
Come on!
Go on! Don't give up on me!
I'm gonna win!
Don't stop!
Don't give up!
Everyone's getting pretty far!
Impressive, Captain Marine.
Darn it!
Finish!
Now for our results.
1st place goes to
Captain Marine at 8014 light-years!
Ehehe! Yaaaaay!
Towa-chan was pretty close
at 2nd place, though!
Maaan.
She's really good!
Such a pro.
True!
I guess I'm just a natural at these games.
Your overall performance was great.
You still lost, though.
Cut the flexing!
Look at her talk.
Looks like Subaru-senpai's
doesn't just suck in Puyo Puyo and Tetris,
7800?
but in Kirby as well.
I got 7k.
Hey!
And Captain got...
Mmmm. Well, sure. There's that.
But it's fine as long as you have fun!
As long as you have fun.
I guess that's true.
Agreed!
Correct!
Winning is fun, though.
Does anyone even care about the scores?
True, True!
No one does, right?!
Hah?
No one cares!
It's more fun when you win!
Okay! Moving on,
our previous game was a 4-way match,
but our next one
is gonna be a 4-man coop game!
Let's all work together!
Let's go!
Okay!
The sub-game we'll be playing is
The Ultimate Choice!
Yay!
Yaaay!
This is a boss rush-type game
where we all work together to beat each boss!
There are difficulties in this game as well,
where higher difficulties mean more bosses
but fewer HP and recovery items!
It has that kind of difficulty scaling!
I see!
Okay! Hands out, everyone!
Okay!
Let's do this!
Yeah!
Sui-chan, you sounded off...
S-Sui-chan?
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Starting with character selection!
First off, pick your character!
Which should I pick?
Roger! Got it.
Which fits me best?
This wave one looks like it'd fit you.
The wave?
The wave one looks good!
Oh, this is Water!
It fits my theme! I'll take it!
Looks good!
I'll go with this yo-yo guy.
Wait, I haven't picked one yet.
Cute.
Let's go with this spidey boi! NESP!
A'ight!
'Kay!
Captain Marine chose Kirby with the Water ability!
Subaru-san went for the Yo-Yo user, Gim.
Sui-chan picked the sweeping Broom Hatter!
And Towa-sama had NESP,
the long-ranged psychic attacker, for her pick.
Their characters have been chosen!
Let's begin!
So in this stage area,
we can do some practice
to get a feel for the controls,
Mmhm.
like how you can release
your special by pressing B.
Then once we're done―
Oh right! There are energy drinks here!
Yes, there are!
Don't grab these just yet!
Understood!
Okay.
All right.
There's only a limited number of items,
so only use them if you need the healing!
I see!
Got it!
Okay, now that we've all gotten
used to the controls,
let's start for real!
Follow me, guys! This way!
Following!
Don't grab the items!
Got it.
One! Two! Follow the leader, guys!
Get in!
I'm getting tense.
Which bosses are we gonna face?
Oh, it's the tree!
We're already here.
This is Whispy Woods, right?
The heck is it doing?!
It's that iconic tree!
Yeah, it's that famous―
I'll shoot at it from a distance.
Apples are falling! Apples are falling!
Ouch!
The peaches are falling!
Oh, they're apples.
It's gonna air drop!
What's happening?!
What's it doing?!
Where did I go?
Please team...
Please attack as a team!
Did we do it?
Ah, good!
Gottem! Nice!
Crushed!
That was too easy.
Oh, that was quick.
It's getting smaller!
We done? We done?
It's crying.
We did it!
Nice one!
Too easy.
Now, let's move on to the next boss.
Our HP's still in the green.
'Kay.
Just some light scratches. We'll be fine.
Seems doable.
We can do this!
Let's keep going!
Ah, it's coming from the right.
It was smacking its butt!
Drink this!
Wait, wait, wait!
Whoa, wait!
Ow-ow-ow-ow!
A shower of Marine water!
Here's a shower!
Owwie!
A shower of Marine water!
Crushed!
It's a Marine water shower!
Drink this!
"A shower of Marine water!"
How are we still on the air?!
Let's keep this up!
No stopping now!
King Dedede, their sworn enemy, has appeared!
It's Dedede!
Will they be able to clear this stage?
How 'bout you drink a glass of Marine water?
Marine water!
Come on, take a sip!
Place here...
Thanks for the drink!
Drink your water!
Thank you very much!
That was close!
Please spray some more.
This guy's a hater―
THAT. HURT.
Got the beatdown!
That's what you get for calling him a hater.
He wasn't a hater.
Blast him away!
Not one of those guys.
What?
Oh, he's mad!
What's going on?
Now that's...
Now he's serious.
He suddenly got swole!
That's some serious muscle building!
Now that's macho!
Seriously?
Those arms are long!
Isn't this harder for us now?
Save me!
He's gonna get a spraying!
Marine water!
This is a bad spot.
We're in a pickle.
We went down!
The stage changed!
Stage change!
What happened?
That's cool.
Where are we?
Is this a― ow!
Close...
He's throwing stuff now!
That's cheating!
Y'all hang in there!
Wait! Wait!
Just a bit of HP to take out.
We're going down each floor!
We went down another floor!
His HP's getting pretty low.
That hurt!
What's this attack?!
Yeah...
Those with low HP should get to the back!
Run! Run! Run!
Just a bit more!
Go all in!
Last assault!
Just a few more attacks!
Splash him with water!
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no!
Just one― Okay!
I'm gonna die!
Good job!
Nice work!
Sui-chan was in a collision course
with King Dedede's aerial smash...
But at that moment,
Towa-san's attack connected!
It was a last-minute save!
Amazing teamwork!
We won?
Who's the blue one?
P-Player 3!
I was on the brink of death right there!
Sui-chan...
Did we win?
You better heal up, Sui-chan!
Let's use some heals!
Heal, please!
What do I get to heal?
Let's chug some energy drinks!
Drink the energy drink!
Here.
This one?
Go get it, Sui-chan.
I should be fine.
Ooooh! Okay, I got it.
A kiss?!
Did you just throw a kiss?
What're you doing?
Kiss?
When using recovery items,
you can feed your allies with
the item to restore their HP!
Items are limited in this mode,
so use them wisely!
You can feed others the items to heal them!
Cool!
That's a really nice mechanic!
That's nice.
Right?
Having mastered the controls,
Crap, it's biting me!
the four proceeded to take down
bosses like Bugzzy, Meta Knight,
and Pon & Con in quick succession!
They're down to just three bosses to beat!
The team synergy's getting better, guys!
A'ight.
This guy looks tough!
He looks strong!
I've seen this before!
We're gonna need to douse this
with Marine water, aren't we?
Marine water time? Got it!
This boss is pretty well-known, isn't it?
I can't get close.
No, no, no, no!
Hold on, lemme spray it upwards.
Owa-wa-wa-wah!
That hurts!
Oh crap! We're being trapped!
If we get hit, we're―
This is bad! We can't deal with it like this!
Funny how everyone went up to evade.
Nice attack from below!
Great!
Ah, thank goodness!
So fast!
Okay! Okay! Okay!
You guys defeated it quick!
We're good? We've done it?
I think we did it.
We've finished it, right?
We did it!
Oh! It split into two!
Wha?!
Hm? What?
What?
We haven't?!
We're not done.
They multiplied!
No darn way!
This ain't good.
We're not done!
Is this real?!
You're kidding me!
I'll die!
Attack! Attack!
I'm dying...
You can do it!
This rain is dangerous! Keep away!
Watch out for the rain!
Try not to get rained on.
My shower can't hit them!
That spot's dangerous!
The rain's gonna end us!
This is bad! Time out!
I'm sorry!
Towa!
Towa Down!
Someone save us!
YEOOOWCH!
I need help!
Anyone! Help!
Save your teammates! Hurry!
Y'all can do this!
Revive! Revive!
Time out...
Thank you!
Okay, okay! Thanks!
Nice work!
Keep laying on the damage!
Keep attacking! Keep attacking!
Whittle it down!
Crushed!
Wait, seriously?
We're not done?
Is there more?
You're kidding me.
Ahhh! Thank goodness we're done!
No more of this!
That was so much fun!
Only two more bosses left!
'Twas fun.
It's fun! It's fun!
Just two more.
We should heal up.
We almost got wiped!
If we hadn't worked together...
We definitely took a beating from that.
Let's grab a bite of this.
Let's eat.
Everyone line up! Mwah! Mwah! Mwah!
Mwah, mwah, mwah!
Gimme a smooch!
Thanks.
We're all at max HP!
Okay, okay, okay.
Two matches remaining!
Okay!
We almost failed the last one.
We almost got wiped.
Let's go!
It was a near wipe.
'Twas tough.
What's this girl's deal?
Isn't that a human?
Gotta dodge.
What the heck?
She's a fast one! Watch out!
Fast! She moves fast!
She's faster than anyone you've ever faced!
Almost at half! Almost at half HP!
Boss at half HP!
Marine water, go!
Ah, wait. Stop.
She attacks with lightning!
Something's coming.
Something's―
Towa's pretty good at dodging!
Yikes, that's close.
It hurts if you get hit!
Attack, attack! Just a bit more!
Shave off that HP!
A bit more!
Go, go!
Here's our chance!
NICE WORK!
Nice work!
Crushed!
Great job!
Got it!
Gottem!
The next one is the final battle!
We got it!
Let's all work as one...
...and win this!
Let's win this!
Let's win!
Yeah!
That was a bit forced.
Whoa, that's...
Hyness.
Hyness!
Looks strong.
Let's see... Marine water...
We're still unsure what gimmick this has.
Let's spray him from below.
Whoooa. He's moving.
The way he moves is quite smooth...
Watch out!
His attacks are also focused.
From below...
Not hitting...
I'm not hitting him!
He's dodging the Marine water!
Marine water ain't connecting!
This might screw us over!
The Yo-Yo's glowing.
Waaah, that hurt!
That's how it works, huh?
The floor looks dangerous.
Watch your feet, guys.
It does!
The floor's wet? It's wet?
It looks wet.
What's happening?
We've almost got it!
What?! Time out! Time out!
Ahh, flare-ups!
From the floor?!
Oh NOOOOO!
It's a flare attack!
We can still do it!
Get to center!
Shave off that HP!
Almost got it! We're close!
Get to center!
A few more hits!
Okay!
Huh?
Whaaat?!
Whoa! It's a second form!
Freaky!
Second form time?
He took off his hood.
That's freaky!
Scary! Gross!
His hood is off now!
He has one of those...
What's he doing?!
I've seen you before!
His minions are...
This won't be an easy win.
He's got fire, lightning, and water, all in one!
We won't be winning that easily.
I can't―
The real fight begins now!
Wait, but isn't this like...
The main body's the one in the middle.
This one?
Oh, that makes sense!
This might be it.
This is the only one taking damage.
Oh, Subaru took notice!
Come on, take the Marine water.
It's starting to spin! Hearts are flying!
What's he doing now?!
Nice!
What's it doing?!
I don't know!
Healing, maybe!
Healing?
Wait, no!
He's rolling towards us!
Waaah! I hate this!
He's rolling back!
Roll incoming!
This is crazy!
How long is it gonna spin like that?!
We're gonna get...
What's this, a roller coaster?!
We're gonna be squished!
Damn it, he's just shredding us!
It's rolling back!
I'm down!
Start healing! Start healing!
Suisei Down!
Sorry!
Healing! Healing!
Okay, okay! I'll heal!
We're in deep trouble.
Sorry! I'm down!
Towa Also Down!
Hold on, I'll heal you!
Healed!
Okay!
Excellent teamwork!
Come on...!
A bit more! Push harder!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Erode his HP, Marine water!
Just go down already!
Okay, okay!
We can do it!
Yesss!
Crushed!
That was way too close!
We actually did it!
Tight match...
Good coop play, team!
What a thrill.
That was tough!
After many battles,
we have won!
That moment you guys were all hit
by rain and lightning was peak comedy.
That was great.
Today's Highlight by Boss
That downpour just wouldn't stop.
It sucked!
That was rough.
That was so funny.
Now that we've all had our fun,
I would like to hear from you now.
Suisei-san!
Which of the three had the best performance?
Yes!
Please tell us your pick for Twin-Crew!
Sure!
Today's Twin-Crew is...
🥁🥁🥁
Marine Water!
Waaah! Sui-chan!
Congratulations!
We were amazing at Puyo Puyo, weren't we?
We did real good!
Congrats!
So it was all just Puyo Puyo in the end!
Yep!
Since Marine is today's Twin-Crew,
she will be awarded this star!
Hooray!
Ain't it extra special that you got it from
Hoshimachi Suisei while playing Star Allies Kirby?
You're the best!
Thank you, Sui-chan! I wub you!
Of course it is!
Mmmnn...!
Mwah! Mmm! Sui-chan...!
She's feeding her!
Do it like we did in-game!
I'm good...
Unwanted Feeding
Let me heal you, Sui-chan!
I'm full!
I'm already full!
My HP's already full!
Oh, really? Okay.
Yes, I'm good.
I'll leave it at that.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Challenge From the Boss:
the Maruyama Championship!
At this point, we'll have our customers
try their hand at a minigame.
The one who finishes the season
on top will receive a trophy!
Season 2's game is
SEGA AGES Sonic the Hedgehog.
Players will compete in
Green Hill Zone Act 1's time attack mode.
The clear time shown on the
results screen will be your record.
By the way, the one with
the best time currently...
is Marine, with 41.25 seconds.
Yeah.
So, Suisei-san, how confident are you?
Yes?
Oh, I'll beat that time.
Screw her!
I'll beat her time again!
Let's get right to it, then.
Aim for the top! Go for it!
3... 2... 1...
Now!
Start!
Go! Go!
You have to collect those coin-like thingies.
No wasted movements!
These things?
She's good!
She's really stable.
Hup.
Nice, nice.
Calm and composed...
Ow, ow, ow!
Or so I thought!
I gotta get those rings.
Wait, what's this?
You can go up.
Okay, so I go up...
Ah, right, up.
I go down...
Yeah, yeah.
Really smooth and precise.
Then I go here...
Here's the part everyone had trouble with.
Great time incoming?!
She's fast! So fast!
This is gonna be good.
We could be looking at...
She's super fast!
Suisei-san's time is 36.56 seconds!
We've got a new best time!
So, how do you feel, having tried it out?
That felt so good!
There it is.
There's the "felt so good."
I don't think we're going to hit
Towa-chan's 1:03 mark again.
Stop that!
Don't bring it up!
What do you make of her time?
1 minute, 3 seconds?
What were you even doing?
Yikes.
Be nicer about it!
Hoshimachi Suisei
Thank you for coming!
Come again, if you like.
Sure.
Thank you for your patronage!
Thanks for having me!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
After Closing
How did you enjoy this episode
of Game Shop Maruyama?
I've asked, uh, Subaru to stay back this time.
Yeah!
Let's do this.
Yes, let's.
Let's give our viewers
some advice with their worries!
Okay!
This one is from @Vanitytale.
"I've never been great at
putting faces and names together.
I've switched jobs lately,
and I'm worried I won't be able to
memorize my coworkers' names and faces.
Do you have any good ideas?"
And there you have it.
I see, I see.
I'll give you just...
the answer you need!
What's with that doorbell noise?
Here it comes!
Okay.
Just say it at the start!
"You know...
My memory is completely shot.
So I can't memorize your names!"
Just put it out there.
That's your shortcut to success.
Oh?
Makes sense.
So you're saying they should
be honest and own up to it.
Exactly. Don't try to be someone
you're not. You'll regret it.
That's right!
Yeah. I think that's solid advice.
Unlike Towa, I can actually provide solutions!
Remember that!
Hey!
What was that noise?
Did you hear that?
Must be some kind of animal out there.
What?
What was that?
Moving on, before it comes in here.
Yeah.
We're accepting requests
for advice from you.
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique,
personally-signed request fulfilled sticker!
For you!
So please send in your submissions!
Please do!
Can I stop now?