The Pekonsultation Center is open for business!
Got problems that need to go?
You've come to the right peko!
You! Speak!
Wanna be va va voom.
Way to kick things off on hard mode!
Try supplements?
Been there, done that.
Massages!
That too.
Uh, everybody has things they're born with.
Things that are for life.
What're you trying to say, huh?
Get over it, rabbit!
You said you'd make my problem go away! Liar!
It pekan't be helped, okay?!
Next.
I want to have a more devilish aura about me.
Of all the things to ask a rabbit...
Try getting someone with a prank-o.
It's the most basic devilish deed.
Yeah!
Take this toy hammer and give
the next person to walk in a good smack-o!
Yeah!
Now! Go!
-1 HP
Oh?
S-S-Sorry!
I was just trying to develop
a devilish aura!
Tell her, Pekora-chan!
What's with the rabbit hole?!
Why don't we have
a nice, long chat o'er 'ere?
Aieeee!
My bad, for real.
Next...
Brr!
Cold!
What the heck?
No better place to spend summer
than in the fridge!
You probably don't have
a worry in the world, do you?
Nope!
I'm here!
To lend you!
A helpful ear!
Who, me?
Before helping others,
shouldn't you fix
your own problems first?
Will you... Will you hear me out?
With delight!
De
Is it time I peko my last peko?
How long can I keep talking like this?
Uh, everybody has things they're born with.
Things that are for life.
Don't throw my own words pek at me!
No gain, only pain peko.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!