M... Miosha?!
I found her out in the cowwidor.
A ducc!
I ain't no duck!
Mad? She mad?
Make her angwy, and she'll eat you.
Afraid... very afraid...
Subarucha-senpai...
It's your damn fault!
Just kidding. Come on, it's okay.
Here, kiddy, kiddy.
No eat?
No eating.
Friend?
Oozora's a BFF for U.
Okay, Subau-oneecha!
Do the Momotawo!
Huh?
You gotta earn her twust.
I dunno if I can...
I'm the bad guy?
You'll be pewfect!
Fine! Method acting time!
Shuba
Shuba...
Prepare to meet your maker, Momotaro!
Oh...
Cute! So cute!
Whatever floats her boat, y'know?
Wait, you see...
Don't worry. We saw nothing.
Quit jumping to conclusions! You'll hurt people!
lul
You are the last person allowed to laugh here!
Let's just call it water under the bwidge.
Oh no! There she goes!
Miosha's being swept away!
Idol competition is at its peak.
I will keep up with the changing tides!
Ru, ru, ru your boat.
There is no boat! What are you saying?
I slide!
Whee! Whee!
Spwash Mountain!
Are you having fun, Miosha? Are you?!
Flow with some ramen!
Wrong type!
Instant toodles anyway!
Cwimbing this waterfall
requires immense core stwength!
Hup! Hup!
Urk.
Look! Luna's back gave out!
She's fin-ished!
A fishy!
Bwub, gwub...
Mind if I join in as a sea creature myself?
Attention, all passengers!
We're gonna hit the brakes hard!
Wait, don't do that!
Gwagh!
Ooh, looks like a feast washed up today.
A man-eating ogre... They weally exist...
Don't eat me! I don't taste too good!
You're just food for my beetles.
Don't they like sweet things? Does that mean...
Eyes in front, Miosha!
Hmm?
Be shellshocked by this spinning shell!
Upsy-daisy fun!
Hey! Stop!
Missy, ye ever heard of irresistible forces?
They're irresistible!
My bamboo home!
That shellfish really booked it.
What an impressive boom.
Sui-chan's boo-hoo was great, too!
How bamboozling, eh?
Booyah! How'd you like that?!
Huh?
Is she all sleepy now?
Not sleepy yet...
But... I'll...
Pass out?
...soon...
Gonna crash?
Crash...
...dig a hole and sleep.
Uh.
Whoa, she zoomed straight down!
Miosha!
Can you hear me, Brazil?
Sim.
Is Miosha okay?!
She's alive and punching.
I'm alive and punching.
We're coming to help!
Can't let her beat us to the punch!
You sure you're not punching above your weight?
We just gotta roll with the punches!
What's the punchwine?
You look well-salted now.
Hmm... Too salty.
A sweet fruit drink would pack quite the punch here.
Stoogeplex
Emergency
Fin
And that's all for Is This a Bad Joke?
Momotaro: Onigashima Strikes Back!
Thank you for watching.
Did you like it?
...u
Please use the exit to the right.
She's sleeping with her eyes open!
Movie
Is This a Bad Joke?
Momotaro: Onigashima Strikes Back!
Starring
Ookami Mio, Oozora Subaru, Shiranui Flare,
Himemori Luna, Uruha Rushia, Shirakami Fubuki,
Starring
Hoshimachi Suisei, A-chan