Ah, Saki-san.
Heya, transfer kid!
Have you seen the flower beds
in the courtyard?
Hello...
They were blooming most beautifully.
My name's Hanabi!
One of your new crewmates on your academic voyage.
I did!
They were resplendent.
I raised them with care
This here's Inari.
and watered them every day.
Welcome aboard!
U-Um... I-It's nice to meet you...!
It was so rewarding to see them bloom.
Oh, you were the one
caring for the flowers, Saki-san?
I-I just want to say,
if you ever need anything, please ask!
Why, yes.
I had assumed one of the
custodial staff was responsible for that.
Whoa, take it easy, Inari! You're startling them.
Not so.
I'm on the Groundskeeping Committee,
so I did it.
Oh, I'm so sorry...
Um, I'm the class representative, so, well...
Oh, you're on the
Groundskeeping Committee.
I apologize, I had no idea.
If you're ever unsure of anything... I mean...
Wait, weren't you present when we selected
Haha, isn't she adorable?
all the committee members, Touka-san?
Her heart's in the right place,
but she gets ahead of herself sometimes.
What's this?
Did you sleep through that class assembly?
C'mon, Inari. You've got this!
R-Right... Thank you...
Certainly not.
That was a while ago,
so I merely forgot.
Why don't you tell us about yourself?
What's your favorite food?
Besides, does anyone actually remember
Oh, and what sports do you like?
And also... your favorite video games?
all the committee assignments?
Do you, Saki-san?
And what you find attractive?
Hanabi-chan...
No, actually.
What? We should find out what we can, right?
You see?
It's not something one remembers.
For the welcoming party next weekend.
Well... I guess you're right.
Well, yeah, but...
Heh-heh.
Do we need to know what they find attractive for that?
Ah, yes. Say, Touka-san.
Would you help me prune the flower beds?
Darn, you got me.
Prune... them?
Hey, I couldn't help myself.
Yes.
We have to pluck a few of the flowers,
Don't tell me you're not curious, too?
W-Well, I-I don't...
to make sure the others
get enough nutrients.
For the record, I'm attracted to people
who are there for you when you need them.
Just take the shears and *snip*.
It seems a bit of a shame, really.
Come on, Hanabi-chan,
now's not the time for that.
I know.
That's why we put the cut flowers in vases
and place them in the classrooms.
Oh, Inari, you take everything too seriously.
I see, how nice.
Loosen up a bit! Relax!
Very well, I will help.
Ha-na-bi-chan...
Thank you!
Please make some time after school, then.
Whoops, sorry about that.
Certainly.
I'll be back for the answers to those questions,
so think on it!
U-Um, it's nice to have you at our school.
Please look forward to the welcoming party.