We've finally made it, Princess...
We only made it this far
thanks to you two!
We'll definitely defeat the Demon Lord!
Exactly!
If we work together, we'll be able
to beat the Demon Wowd Fubuking
in a Quiz Battwe!
My Candy Kingdom is being targeted by
the White Demon Lord, Fubuking.
To fight back against this threat,
the Magician, Aki Rosenthal,
Magician
Aki Rosenthal
the High-Spec Robot, Robocosan,
High-Spec Robot
Robocosan
and I, Luna, the Princess
and also the Hero,
Hero
Himemori Luna
set forth to defeat her!
Defeat the Demon Lord Fubuking!
Quiz Quest!
Okay, we're heading in, evewyone!
Knock knock goes the fooox!
Hahaha!
What brings you all the way here?
Princess Luna!
Demon Lord Fubuking!
I'm here to protect my kingdom
by defeating you in a quiz battle!
Hah! That sugary kingdom of yours
will be painted with jerky
by the time I'm done with you!
You pathetic little
Sil
Silly
Silly Sisters
are no match for me!
Ha!
Silly Sisters?!
Silly Sisters?
Ga!
Who's she talking about?
Ha!
I'll give you fools a quiz.
I only have 3 HP!
Oh, she only has 3 HP.
In other words, if you can get
three questions correct...
it'll be your victory!
However!
The questions in this quiz
are secrets that only I know!
You fools have no chance of
ever answering them!
Gahahahahaha!
What the heck's with this Demon Lord?!
She's actually explaining everything!
The day the Candy Kingdom turns into
the Jerky Kingdom draws ever closer!
Gahahahahaha!
Ugh!
We have to win!
Doesn't jerky go well with drinks?
Potions
Take this!
First Question!
What's a bad habit of mine that I often do?
A. Sniff other people's feet.
That's crazy!
B. Sniff my cats' feet.
Seriously?
C. Sniff my own feet.
Wow, you're sniffing everything!
D. Make my cats sniff my feet!
Aren't you embarrassed, revealing all this?
She's basically exposing her fetishes.
Are you okay?
What a sinful woman you are!
What do we do, everyone?
Uh...
Wait, she's a cat herself,
B and D might refer to
her sniffing her own...
Silence!
I am a Demon Lord Fox!
What are you derpheads trying to imply?!
Don't you think B's the likely answer here?
Isn't that too safe of an answer?
Well, B might be the
least embarrassing answer, but...
Don't we wanna inflict
massive damage on her?
I kinda wanna pick C or D, honestly.
True, I feel the same way.
We've decided!
The answer is...
C! You sniff your own feet!
The correct answer is...!
You're WRONG!
Hahahaha!
Whaaat?!
No way!
I'll never tell you the true answer!
It shall forever be buried in darkness!
So that means it's one of the other three.
It's definitely B.
She seems like the type to do that.
Whether I answer or not,
both options lead to hell!
(Demon Lord Fubuking
took mental damage.)
That's a lotta damage.
Eat this!
Second Question!
Which of the following was I, Demon Lord Fubuking,
really into when I was young?
A. Poking at rhinoceros beetle larvae.
That's plausible.
B. Licking rhinoceros beetle larvae.
THAT'S MESSED UP!
C. Eating rhinoceros beetle feed.
That's understandable.
D. Eating rhinoceros beetles.
Well then, which one is it?
Hang on.
These are all disgusting.
Any one of these may disgust you
but one of them is the truth.
You lick stuff a lot,
so you enjoying licking
rhinoceros beetle larvae...
isn't that unbelievable.
You're right.
That's true.
Do you really think that low of me?!
But this question is a pretty tough one...
Didn't we have a Limit Break
that can get us some hints?
Looks like it's time to
unveil our Limit Breaks!
Is it time for me to fire my
Derpo Cannon?
You're up!
Let her taste it!
Take this!
Derpo Cannon!
Gaaaaaah!
My brain is turning into muuush...
Obviously
I've definitely never put a
rhinoceros beetle into my mouth before...
You said held a rhinoceros beetle, right?
Huh?! What did you do to me?!
Looks like she's recovered!
I feel like I ran my mouth off...
So that means it's either A or C, right?
Yeah.
She said she never put
a rhinoceros beetle into her mouth before,
so maybe she's put in beetle feed before?
That could be it!
That's it!
We've decided!
The answer is...
C! Eating rhinoceros beetle feed!
The correct answer is...!
Incorrect!
What? No way.
Whaaat?
Say it ain't sooo!
As if I'd ever eat
rhinoceros beetle feed!
Wait, you don't eat it?
You don't?
You totally look like
you do...
I don't.
Don't say that!
The true answer is
forever buried in darkness!
You practically told us
the answer already.
The squishiness was super fun!
Even so, you're all weak!
Pathetically weak!
Even after using your skill,
you couldn't even land
a single blow on me!
Why...?
Here's the next question!
Take it!
Uh, which one of the following
is a childhood secret of mine?
A. Wetting myself when I was three.
Oh, I see.
My, oh my, oh my.
B. Wetting myself when I was four.
My, oh my...
C. Wetting myself when I was five.
It's all just
you wetting yourself.
D. Wetting myself in first grade.
This secret of mine can
never be revealed to the world!
For starters, we pretty much confirmed
that you wet yourself.
Even the Demon Lord was
cute at some point.
Cute moments indeed.
It all happened when I was a kid!
I've never wet myself once after
becoming the Demon Lord!
I really wanna know the truth here...
You do?!
Didn't we have something that
narrows our options down to two?
Looks like it's time for me
to use my magic!
Whaaat?!
Dance! Spirits of Booze!
Beer Splash!
Gaaah!
Ahahahaha...
It's working!
Wow! Amazing!
The number of answers
has shrunk down to two!
You know...
Even if we get this wrong...
We still know the true answer.
Stop it!
I said stop!
The cat's out
of the bag now!
Don't focus on that!
Don't turn high-spec just for that!
Very well, then.
We've decided!
The answer is...
D! You wet yourself in first grade!
The correct answer is...!
Hahaha! You're WRONG!
So that means...
Gahahahaha!
You wet yourself in your
last year of kindergarten.
S—
Stop digging that up!
When was the last time
YOU girls wet yourselves?
Answer me, AkiRose!
You've definitely wet yourself before!
I know you did!
Within the last year?
Wait, within the last year?!
Huh?!
W-Wait.
Within the last year?!
Within the last year?! Seriously?!
Sh-Should we switch places?
You wanna do it?
Stop right there, Demon Lord.
Gahaha!
AkiRose's joining the dark side!
Oh no!
All right, next question!
Take this!
Honestly, I didn't want to pull this out
if I could've avoided it.
Which one of these cringe things
did Demon Lord Fubuki do in the past?
A. Reading a hard book in the library
and acting as if she understood everything.
That's just painful.
B. Talking to her own
reflection for three hours.
Oof...
C. Purposely dropping her own original manga
in the classroom and getting bashed by others.
That's just sad...
D. Running off to school
with bread in her mouth every morning.
HECK NO!
Now...
That's too cringe!
ANSWER!
Don't call any of these cringe!
These actually happen for real!
It's my attack but
I'm taking damage from it!
By the way, have any of you
done any of the four options before?
It wasn't in the library
but I've read a hard book before
and acted as if
I understood.
SO YOU DO HAVE EXPERIENCE!
Uh-huh, I see!
I wanted to look smart.
If the Princess has done it before,
then there might be a lot of people
who've done the same thing.
But she's the Demon Lord,
so she might be one step ahead of us.
I feel like she's the type
to draw her own manga.
That's true.
That's possible.
She seems like
the type to draw.
Her getting bashed by others
is kinda pitiful, though.
Yeah, that's just sad.
Stop it!
I'm really curious in what she drew, though.
Well, then. We've decided!
The answer is...
C! Purposely dropping her own original manga
in the classroom and getting bashed by others.
The correct answer is...!
Hahaha! You're WRONG!
What?
Really?
That's the wrong answer?!
It's not C?
Whaaat?
I'd never risk such a mistake!
Because I'm the Demon Lord!
Whaaat?!
I wonder which one's the true answer?
You'll never know 'cause
it's forever buried in darkness!
Hahaha!
She's burying everything.
But now you know I definitely
did one of the other three answers!
Pain...
The next one's my final question!
Perhaps the three of you
still have a skill remaining
that can shave off
all my HP in one hit?
Here's your final question!
Take this!
Since we're this far in,
damn the consequences!
Demon Lord Fubuki's
past cringe actions: Part 2!
Whoooa!
A. Staring up at the sky in the middle of
the schoolyard during a rainy day.
She's in deep.
B. Clapping her hands together in prayer
by the window and photosynthesizing.
Ah... I definitely thought
it was something doable.
C. Practicing Summoning Magic in
the middle of the gymnasium after school.
Did you perhaps
draw something?
D. Pretend to shoot an arrow
at somebody she hates.
She's not even fazed at any of these!
Now, guess which one it is!
The Demon Lord's starting
to look cute to me.
She's pretty funny.
I definitely wanna try all of them.
I did want to try a few of these.
But speaking of stuff we wanna try,
summoning magic's gotta
be the answer, right?
I thought so, too.
Don't you wanna try it out?
Don't you wanna just hold a book on sorcery
and try summoning something?
Clapping your hands in prayer by the window
and photosynthesizing
kinda makes you feel
like you're gaining power.
I did that before myself, actually.
You did?!
Really?
Seriously?
You actually did B
without batting an eye!
Putting the rest aside,
what do you think about A?
She's in real deep.
She sure is.
It's plausible.
Even if you answer this question correctly,
I still have 3 HP.
You can't defeat me without a Limit Break!
I still have my Wimit Bweak!
What?!
This power will increase
my attack power through the roof.
It's the Wimit Bweak to end you in one hit!
That's just cheating!
Are you kidding me?!
Even so,
it doesn't matter if you can't land a hit!
Hahahaha!
I'll follow you unto the end, Princess.
Yeah.
I've picked my answer!
It's A! Staring up at the sky in the middle of
the schoolyard during a rainy day!
Here I come! One shot, one kill!
Pwincess...
Gaa!
Bwaaade!
The correct answer is...!
Ugh...
YOU'RE WRONG!
Hahahahaha!
Argh!
WHAT?!
Nooo!
It can't be!
With that, you weaklings
challenged my quiz
and got every question wrong!
Ugh... that can't... be...!
It can't be!
From now on, the Candy Kingdom
is the Jerky Kingdom!
Hahaha!
It's the end for all of you!
Become my underlings!
Delicious salty jerky...
Let's all eat some jerky then.
Let's!
Everyone could use some salt
every now and then, right?
Oh, my!
These came in
at just the right time!
Let's have a drink with
our jerky, shall we?
What are you
pulling out?!
And so, Princess Luna and her companions
as well as the Demon Lord
joined hands and learned to
understand one another
and lived happily ever after.
Please like this video
and subscribe to the official hololive channel
as well as our talents'!