Oh, hit them from behind!
Man, this is hard!
Can I go here too?
We moose-t beat this deer game!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Geez, it's so cold!
It is!
It sure is.
It's so cold.
Of course it's cold! It's snowing!
Oh, snow!
So it was snowing!
No wonder it's cold.
Does snow bring back any
fond memories for you all?
Memories of snow...
Snow...
I liked riding a sled downhill.
But y'know, snow makes you excited as a kid,
but once you become an adult, you're like...
"Snow, huh... The commute's gonna be rough."
That's depressing...
Seems it's bringing back bitter memories for her.
I see.
What about you, Subaru?
As for me...
I did snowball fights with my friends a lot,
and made snowmen.
I quite li—ow!
They're starting an...
Air snowball fight?
I... I've been bested by Towa's snowball...
Towa's snow...
Subaru-senpai, you're not actually hit.
But it hurts!
So, well, I was playing with
my friends like just now.
That had nothing to do with snow, though.
I suppose that happens sometimes.
Well, then.
Let's open up the store!
Open!
Looks like we have
our first customer already!
Haachamachama!
Welcome!
Yaaay!
Why's everyone's excitement through the roof?
We got caught up in it.
If you don't have this much energy
going into today, you'll die, Boss!
Oh, is that what's happening?
Yay! *kicks*
Chama!
She's a vibrant one, so.
So this one's vibrant.
She's the number one vibrantist.
So she's a vibrantist.
If you can't keep up with her...
Can you introduce yourself?
Sure!
Haachamachama!
This is your ultimate worldwide idol,
Akai Haato AKA Haachama!
Today's guest:
Akai Haato
Oh! So you're called Haachama.
This is your ultimate worldwide idol,
Akai Haato AKA Haachama!
Oh! So you're called Haachama.
* The stats are self-answered
MENT
LUCK
SPD
1 million
100 million
1 billion
Today's customer is Akai Haato!
Her stats are highlights all around!
It's too much for me!
Wow, your MENT is 5 stars on a 5-star scale?
Oh?
Wait, 1 million?!
I don't really know what I was doing here.
What?
Huh?
What's with this girl?
Chama?!
She's free-spirited.
She's quite unique.
Although, Boss, she's the
most senior one out of us.
Oh, really?
Is she in the 1st Gen?
I'm their senior!
Wow!
The 1st Gen are something else.
I'm already exhausted.
Right?
Our energetic members are already...
being overwhelmed by Haachama.
Don't get tired already!
You seem pretty carefree, but I'll ask anyways.
Do you have any worries?
I really don't,
but since you asked, I'm gonna answer.
Everyone's in Chama's world now
Responding even though you don't is admirable.
I'm sure you all think this at some point.
Uh-huh.
I have this desire to make a mess of things—
to put to ruin
anything and everything!
And it won't calm down!
It's leaking out!
Haachama... aren't you always like that?
But it still won't calm down!
So it won't!
Oh no, Subaru-senpai's joined the dark side!
This is getting fun, Haachama!
Please help me fulfill my desire!
A-All right. Well, then.
Leave it to us!
And there we have our request!
Yaaay!
Thank you!
Haachama's request is, in short,
to become a god of destruction!
Ooh!
What a leap in logic.
You're scaring me.
We have the perfect game for you!
Ooh!
The game we recommend for today is...
DEEEER Simulator: Your Average Everyday Deer Game!
Yaaay!
It's perfect for her!
A novel game featuring a deer as its protagonist!
It's a bird... It's a plane... It's a... "Deer"?
That is what DEEEER Simulator:
Your Average Everyday Deer Game is!
You've been reincarnated as a deer
after getting in a traffic accident.
To defeat the bosses that come your way,
lay waste to the city in order to
obtain powerful guns and explosives!
As you continue your destruction,
the quirky animal police will be deployed!
They'll try to stop your deer carnage,
so watch out for them!
You can freely run around the city with
the final goal of defeating all the bosses!
Who shall become the god of destruction this day?
Your Average Everyday Deer Game
To fulfill Haachama's request
to become the god of destruction,
Ready?
On three! One, two...
Deers for doe win!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Before we start playing
Your Average Everyday Deer Game,
I'll explain the plan for today.
The Maruyama—
Maruyama Queen of Destruction Race
No...
Deer-Deer Queen of Destruction Race!
Deer-Deer Queen of Destruction Race
Deer-Deer!
I shall now explain the rules!
You'll form teams of two, and whichever team
kills the Giant Koala in the city faster wins.
You can switch out with
your teammate when you die
or before that point if you want.
I'll leave it up to each team to decide.
Okay!
I'll be giving hints after you start,
so don't miss it!
Do your best.
We'll have our guest,
hololive 1st Gen's Haachama
Making the teams.
and 2nd Gen's Subaru as the senior pair!
hololive Senior Pair Team
Yaaay!
They'll be going against
3rd Gen's Marine and 4th Gen's Towa
as the junior pair!
hololive Junior Pair Team
Let's gooo!
Yaaay!
Let's get that dub!
Let's get it!
Whoo!
Yeah!
Ugh...
Our hype levels just don't compare...
Yeah...
Do your best with your pair.
But since they're tiring
themselves out now...
It's all part of the strat.
My Haachama here isn't so frail.
My HP is infinity.
Her HP is infinity?!
Freaky...
Isn't that right, Haachama?
Yeah!
Where's the energy, guys?
You both seem down.
We're not down, we're composed.
Chill for a bit.
LOL!
You're too loud.
Subaru & Haato
Towa & Marine
Now Haachama just has to win
in this Deer-Deer game!
Deer-Deer Queen of Destruction Race
Seniors vs Juniors Destruction Race starts now!
Chama, let's go!
Battle start!!
The battle has started, but what should we start with?
"L" is movement...
For starters...
Hmm? Which button is "L"?
just wreak some havoc.
Ah, this one, I see.
"L" is the left stick!
Wreak some havoc?
Got it.
Havoc, huh.
First of all — wreak some havoc.
If you make a mess in the city...
Yeah?
various things will happen.
Here I go!
She launched a car just like that!
Dang.
You can attack too!
That's what I call havoc.
Subaru—
Careful there!
You can ride cars, too!
You can ride cars?
Yeah, you can.
Ah, it says right there.
Let's go!
Oh, you can smash things.
Your antlers... Your face sticks out!
It says right there below, "X to ride."
Huh? Where—
You just destroyed it!
Yeah, you can ride cars in this game.
I wanted to ride it!
Chama, you...
Got myself a gun!
Looking good!
Nice.
Okay, okay!
I put it on!
Try talking to a person.
Get close to them first.
You can dance by talking to someone
Wait, you need to try stretching your neck first.
"Say Hi" "Deerify" "Dance"
Or so it says.
Now that you deerified
some of the humans, try dancing.
Dance?
Dancing? How— Ah, like that!
Look at me go!
What's with this dance? Makes no sense!
Make sure to deerify a lot of humans.
I'm done here. Peace.
That sure was quick.
You can stretch your neck it seems.
Stretching your neck makes you
into a Spider—Yeah, like that!
Way to go!
This seems familiar.
Ride and...
Hell yeah!
Destruction from the get-go
Let me out!
Let me out!!
Let me out from this sidewalk!
Hey! Hold your horses!
Do you see a letter in the top right?
Yup!
That's your Deersaster level.
I see.
The more you wreak havoc in the city, the more
your Deersaster level fills up and glows red.
I see, I see!
If you fill it up to the max, something will happen.
If you can handle that something,
you will get a weapon as reward.
Oof, right between the legs.
So we have to wreak havoc
and raise our Deersaster level?
So we should just make a mess?
Yeah.
Precisely. Please make an even bigger mess.
Ah, I get it now!
Please stop aiming for the crotch.
It breaks bit by bit—
Oh? Here it is!
There we go! The Junior team has
raised their Deersaster level,
and as a result,
the police enter the fray!
Watame?!
Man, it really is Watame.
Yup.
Sheep are here!
Beat 'em up!
Oh, there's a gun.
Oh, you're right.
You can equip it.
"Equip."
Look at it go.
So cool!
Very cool.
Do you really have to attach them there?
The antlers are no more.
We wear guns now.
Watch out! Here they come!
Here they come.
And now...
Oh!
Here comes the police! Here comes the police!
Nice!
The police are after us!
Come on!
It's your own Chama-police.
Bring it on!
It's a bunch of Watames!
Both teams are steadily raising
their Deersaster levels.
Keep on wreaking havoc and
getting even more powerful weapons!
The weapon from defeating
the B-level police helps a lot.
For real?
The weapon from defeating the B-level police is quite powerful.
We are only on D!
Really?
Good luck.
I really want it now.
I recommend going until B at least.
There's something shiny...
Hm? What is that?
This one!
There's a katana!
Whenever you think you can beat up
the koala on the building, go ahead and fight it.
You're right.
It says you can pick it up with the ZL button.
Whoever beats Giant Koala first wins, so be quick.
ZR?
No, ZL!
You need to smash some cars
to make the police come out.
I see.
And while the Senior team is casually bumping into
a wall with a single katana this late into the game...
Their opponents...!
Are you gonna challenge Giant Koala?
Are you going for it, Towa?
Is the Junior team gonna make the move?
Are you?
Junior team plunges into battle!
Go!
Oh no!
The heck is that?!
Eek!
It strikes back!
Towa-sama, that's bad!
Don't get hit by the beam.
Oh, nice!
You instantly die if you get hit by that beam.
It's too damn strong!
It's an OHK beam.
I'll pass the baton to Marine.
You got it.
Junior team
Towa→Marine
Player change!
Again, from the top. You will have to start over.
Barehanded style
We're at level C now!
Ah, I see!
...into Deersaster level up!
Nice!
That's what it is all about.
Looking good.
That's how you do it.
Junior team's gathering intel
They are on level C at the moment.
No good.
Senior team
Haato→Subaru
Player change!
Okay!
I'm taking over.
I'm leaving it to you!
Look, Chama, there's a koala!
There is?
Oh, new level.
Whoa, this one looks strong.
On man, it's Pekora!
This Pekora looks powerful!
Ear Walker!
The highest Deersaster level today: B!
Here comes Pekora.
It looks quite strong.
Let me take this one and...
And...? Oh, smash it!
Martial artist by nature
Let me smash it, and...
Ah, that's how you do it!
For that— Oh, here they come!
Oh no.
Get out!
That laser pointer looks dangerous.
Oh no, I'm gonna die.
No, don't! You can do it!
Ah, I see!
That might be too much.
Just run away.
I'm out!
Just retreat for now.
A getaway with a sheep in hand
Let's retreat for now.
Oh, wow!
There's a temple!
That laser is giving me chills.
There are so many after you.
Oh no!
Scary!
Oh man...
Oh, here are the rabbits!
Quick, do them in!
Right, I should take them out first.
Rabbits are no good.
Sharp-tongued idol
They are dangerous.
Right.
Man, that red laser is menacing.
I don't like it.
It's scary indeed.
Oh, hit them from behind!
Man, this is hard!
Go for it!
You really need to have weapons for this.
Oh, you didn't have any?
You had them, though.
I think I didn't have any on me.
I see.
I think we should hijack a car first,
run around with it, and make a mess.
Then, we get out, grab some weapons, and run
the police over with a car. How does this sound?
Sounds amazing!
Let's do it.
Okay, let's get it.
Can you destroy this?
You can.
Ah, I can!
Let's smash something big.
It feels nice, isn't it?
Ear Walker joins the fray!
I haven't seen it before!
Oh, it's a rabbit!
A rabbit?
Ain't it cute?
The weapon from this rabbit is quite powerful.
Pekora, is that you?
I'll beat it for sure.
You have to find it first.
Right. Let's find it.
Nice, nice, nice!
Got it from behind!
You did it?
Oh, nice!
Got it!
Powerful weapon acquired!!
Powerful weapon acquired!
Here we go!
Mow them down!
Let's go!
The Junior team got a crazy
strong weapon to themselves.
Well, then...
Can I give it a shot now?
Can I?
Are you sure?
Are you doing it?
Come at me!
You sure you want to go now?
That beam...
Wow!
A beam that mercilessly destroys all efforts.
How?!
I got so far...
But at least I've defeated the rabbit!
Wasn't that great?
That was quite good, yeah.
I tried so hard, and got so far...
Now that they're immersed
in the world of Deer Simulator...
Boss Hint Time!
Maruyama Confidential
Walkthrough Video
Provided by Affiliate Store's Deer Manager
Deer Manager from one of our affiliate stores
has provided us with
a Koala Battle walkthrough video!
However, it will only be shown to the team
that clears the Boss' challenge!
Clear the Boss' challenge to view the video!
Our challenge for today is...
Make the Boss laugh with deer puns!
make me laugh with deer puns!
Deer puns!
What?
It might be a bit difficult
to come up with good puns.
Piece of cake!
Deer...
Just raise your hand when
you come up with an answer.
Oh, but...
We have to come up with something like
"deer for doe win," right?
Mmm, yeah. Something like that.
I ain't laughing for that, though.
That didn't work.
Damn it!
Not laughing.
Keep them coming!
Have to think of a pun...
Just keep making them!
Captain...
Yes!
Go on, Marine-chan!
You want a scolding that deerly?
Elk-onsider it!
It's a fun pun!
But not funny enough!
Geez! Thought up of anything,
Towa-sama?
I can't think up of anything!
Anything goes!
Me!
Go ahead!
Can't be doen.
Gnu getting around it.
Huh?
Can't be doen.
Gnu getting around it...?
What did you just say?!
Has Subaru-senpai lost it?
Gotta keep trying!
It's one after the other now!
I got one!
The ideas just boil over!
Go ahead, Marine-chan!
Boss' chamois-ship for doe win!
That was good!
We have a winner!
You're the best, Boss!
Winner: Marine!
Our winner is Marine-chan!
Experience does come with age!
The First Maruyama Pun Queen
Do we even need a walkthrough?
As if! We don't need it!
Yeah!
THE LOSERS
We don't need a walkthrough!
You sure?
We'll figure it out ourselves!
You're not gonna enjoy the game if you use one!
This is gonna be tough without a walkthrough.
You fine with that?
A gift from Deer Manager!
Giant Koala Walkthrough Video!
We can't really discuss because they can hear.
Let's not give it away.
Yeah.
Right. They just go the standard route here.
Gotta know what to do and where.
Right.
I see, so they just beat up what's closest.
The start wasn't far off.
Our strat was right.
We were pretty close.
Gotta get that handgun first.
Right. Since the weapons dropped by the
animal police at Deersaster B are powerful.
Right.
Yup.
They're doing everything here.
You can get a lot here.
The other team can hear everything.
Oh, they already got it all?
Wow.
Really?
They can do it that fast?
What's happening?
I wish we won.
Tell us.
Here we go!
This part!
This part was scary.
Yeah.
Ah.
When they aim at you.
You guys still beat it, though.
Somehow, yeah.
You were good.
We dodged quite well.
That sniper is pretty strong.
They sure are.
But I could beat it earlier.
Right. You're good, so you can.
As long as I keep moving, it's probably fine.
Oh, nice.
And there it is!
Nice!
Once you have this, you have it in the bag.
Right.
Will they challenge the koala now?
It's right after this, right?
I wonder how they'll handle it.
And here we go!
Ah, already?
How will they fight it?
Here's the main problem!
Okay, do that, then...
It gets scary from here.
And then?
Huh? Isn't that too close?
Huh?
What will they do?
Something to...
Oh, uh-huh.
counter that.
Oh?
Wait, what?!
Huh?!
I'm so curious.
It's over?
What's happening over there.
No way.
I see.
We got this.
Well,
we have a plan of our own, so.
Yeah.
Really?
Wonder what it is.
Even without a hint, we made our own.
Now that we've seen this, we need to win.
Can the junior team finish this battle
with the walkthrough hint?
Deer-Deer Queen of Destruction Race
Let's begin the 2nd half!
Right.
2nd half start!
Chama, you'll die!
Run away!
Okay, that's one down.
Okay.
Ah, geez.
Close-combat as always
Chama!
Run!
Run away!
Go get 'em!
Chama!
Am I dead? I'm not! I'm still alive!
Get 'em, Chama!
Chamaaa!
Nooo!
Darn it...
Switch!
The junior team is progressing smoothly.
We do this...
Just like the video.
When shooting these, you aim for buildings too.
Right. At the same time.
Nice!
Okay, okay.
You got behind him!
Nice!
Do we keep going?
We beat these guys?
There aren't any red sight lines,
so I think you got all the bunnies.
We did!
Yeah.
Ah, nice!
Once you've beaten the police... Now, go!
We didn't get that thing, the grenades.
We don't have the grenades, but...
Yeah, we don't...
Well, we got this!
You're getting run over!
She got hit and now she's shooting randomly.
You could blow up some
parked cars and try to find it.
Let's do it.
The moving ones are hard to aim at,
so try your luck with the stopped cars.
Let's try our luck.
Like this...
Will it drop?
Ah, I think it dropped!
Really? Ah! We got it! Nice!
Let's go.
Let's get 'em!
I'll start, okay?
Do it!
Okay, okay.
Will Towa end the battle?
Do it!
Just like we saw.
They're fighting the koala.
Ahh!
You're kidding me!
Really?
They died! Let's go, Chama!
Instant Jeering
Hit by a car -> Flung into the air -> Hit by the laser
They were too focused on the koala
and got hit by a car!
Car
Gotta pay attention to your surroundeerings.
Pun intended.
You can't blame her. That one was unexpected.
Quick, start over!
Okay.
Nice.
Whoo!
Okay! We got it!
Nice!
It's this guy!
Beat 'em up!
I had a thought.
How about we get on a building
and shoot them from above?
You're a genius!
Like, get on that one.
Is it possible?
Oh no.
I can't!
They're currently fighting the rabbit.
Chama, let's get some distance first.
Run away!
Get away, then get in a car.
I think you're invincible in a car.
Find a car!
That one is...
That yellow one!
The red one's fine too.
Press X! Okay!
Press X!
Okay, nice!
Get 'em, Chama!
The other team is, unbelievably,
trying to run the police over!
What?
All part of the plan
They're trying to run them over.
Get 'em, Chama!
Wait, you're taking damage!
You're taking damage!
Nooo!
Cars were, in fact, not invincible...
So cars aren't invincible...
I don't get it...
They have their weapons, and now
they're challenging the koala again!
Checking her surroundings.
I guess I'll start from here.
Okay.
I'd like to start!
Go! Go!
Let's start! Giant Koala!
Oh no!
That's scary!
Wait, did I get him?! Did I?!
She got him!
Well, then.
The junior team has defeated the Giant Koala!
What?! Wow!
Junior team defeats the Giant Koala!
And so, the winner is the junior team!
Wow!
Yaaay!
Congratulations.
Mari Towa-nette.
We did it.
This game was really fun, right, Chama?
It was!
It was amazing.
Both teams were pretty into it.
It was fun!
It was interesting!
What're your thoughts, Haachama?
I had a blast! Thank you!
That sounded like an idol.
We're idols, you know.
Oh, you are.
Sorry, I forgot.
And that concludes the demo for today!
Did we manage to fulfill your request
with DEEEER Simulator?
You have!
But!
I'll continue my activities as
the Goddess of Destruction
But?
and destroy everything.
So this is where you start.
Declaration of Destruction
Yup!
I feel like we made a mistake.
Is this gonna be okay?
Oh no.
She's always been like this, so you're fine.
Are we?
I'll let you handle the aftermath, then.
I got it.
One last thing.
Please tell us the member who shined
the most, the Twin-crew for today!
Okay!
Today's Twin-crew is...
Captain!
Wait, me?
Congratulations!
Yay!
May I ask your reasoning?
Because her puns were legendary, of course!
That has nothing to do with the game!
You know, I cleared it!
It's because your puns were so legendary
that you were able to clear the game.
I thought that was wonderful.
Wonderful. Good for you!
Aren't you glad, Captain?
Well... I defeated that Giant Koala and all,
but all we've been talking about are my puns...
Even though you were trying hard for it.
They only remembered my puns...
It's too bad, but you did get a star.
Since Captain is the Twin-crew for today,
we'll give her a star!
Watching you guys play so energetically blew away my pent-up stress! Thank you!
Yaaay!
Yay!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Challenge From the Boss:
the Maruyama Championship Season 2!
Yaaay!
At this point, we'll have our customers
try their hand at a minigame.
The one who finishes the season
on top will receive a trophy!
Season 2's minigame is
SEGA AGES Sonic the Hedgehog.
Players will compete in
Green Hill Zone Act 1's time attack mode!
Yaaay!
The clear time shown on the
results screen will be your record.
By the way, the one with
the best time currently...
is Suisei-chan, with 36.56 seconds!
Ooh! Nice!
How confident are you?
I'll beat the thirty sig fif six seconds
five six to get twenty—
What?
What'd you say?
Thirty-what now?
Chama...
I'll get it down to the twenties
and get a world record!
Chama,
Chama, calm down.
Oh, wow!
Her confidence is amazing, at least.
Chama, sit straight.
Okay.
It's great that you have
a responsible person next to you.
Let's have her give it a go!
Wait, what are the controls?
Calm down, Chama.
Will she be all right?
Will I?
...2... 1...
Start!
Oh, so it's like this.
Yup!
She's starting to remember.
You're doing good, Chama!
Wait, why am I so slow?
Maybe you have to build up momentum?
Ah, I need more coins!
Let's go!
Oh nice.
Lookin' good.
Okay, Haachama. Only 2 seconds 'til 20! 1!
Okay, you hit 20.
She's ruthless.
Wait, you're so fast!
Ooh!
Fly!
Careful!
Oh, nice!
She's dodging them
Fly! Fly!
She's good.
Ah, this part gets everyone.
It's fine!
Okay, doing good!
The time!
Nice!
Nice approach.
Ahhhhhh!
Nice!
Using that momentum...
Doing great!
Not bad.
Yeah. She's doing great.
Nice!
And so, we have our time!
The time is 49.65 seconds!
Which means, she is...
Darn it...
4th!
Ooh!
So, how do you feel, having tried it out?
I feel like I could've done better!
But that was really fun!
I felt that using the jump
and dash correctly was crucial.
So you've noticed.
She's making sense.
She's suddenly making sense.
Will a monster appear
and beat the high score?
Tune in next time and see!
Thanks for coming, Haachama!
Akai Haato
Thank you for your patronage!
And look forward to it!
Thanks for having me!
Look forward to it!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
I've asked Towa to stay back this time.
After Closing
Let's give our viewers some advice
for their worries.
From @ZUNKO_holofan,
Le Zun.
"I enjoy reading manga,
and I generally pick them up in volumes.
The problem is since I have to
wait for the volume release, quite often,
I'll get spoiled by my friends
who are up to date with the series.
Do you have any advice on how
to avoid spoilers when I see them coming?"
What do you say?
Interesting...
Were I in your shoes,
I'd start by slapping le friends.
Back to this character, huh—
That's just the start?
Stop making me laugh!
Nice, go on.
Take le thoughtless lips and saw them.
Quite good, don't you think?
Take those thoughtless lips and SAW them?!
Yeah.
Hang on...
Not "sew,"
No, I— uh...
but "saw"?
Um...
Why not just "Shut up"?
Le shut up!
Okay,
There's your solution!
so...
the answer to your worry is
to basically just tell them to shut up.
That's right!
JUST SHUT IT!
Yes, you heard her, Towa...
Anyway...!
we're accepting requests for advice from you.
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique, personally-signed
request fulfilled sticker!
So please send in your submissions!
We look forward to them.
You better le keep 'em coming.
Please do.
Can't wait to read them.