Okay, then. Can you toss one
my way for starters?
Why are you excited?!
Is my head getting Haachamachama'd?
Yikes...
Ahahahahaha!
Hahaha!
Okay, welcome to the show!
This is holo's Bonjour,
a variety and talk show
where one of the guests
changes every month!
Now then, let's introduce
our guests for today!
Om, nom, Okayu!
I'm Nekomata Okayu
from hololive GAMERS!
This will be my last
appearance on this show!
Whoa!
That fanfare came in way too late!
Anyways, this will be my
last appearance on Bonjour!
Thanks for having me!
Yaaay!
It's great having you!
And our second guest is...
Om, nom, Okayu!
Huh?
Hm?
I'm Robomata Roboco from
hololive Gen 0 & GAMERS!
Thanks for having me today!
Robomata...
Okay, our second guest is Robocosan!
It's my second time on the show!
It's your second time here, yeah.
And our third guest is...
Yup!
Okay!
Chamachama? Chamachama!
This is your ultimate worldwide idol, uh...
Haachamamata Haachama!
Okay, that's pushing it.
That's just pushing it!
It's all just Haachama.
It's nothing but Haachama.
It really is.
It's just Haachama and Haachama.
You don't even need the "mata"!
The three of us will be presenting today's show.
I, Nekomata Okayu, will be your MC today!
Thanks for letting me!
It's reassuring with you around.
Thanks for being here!
Really?
I'm pretty nervous, actually.
I'll hurl abuse at you
when you're worried so chin up!
Wait, really?!
Okay, then. Can you toss one
my way for starters?
Why are you excited?!
What a masochist.
Let's start off with our
impressions of each other.
The three of us are a pretty
rare combination, aren't we?
Yeah!
We're a pretty rare combination, yeah.
Right?
Yup!
Have the three of us done
anything together before?
We haven't, right?
Nope!
Yeah.
The three of us never did
anything together before.
Uh-huh.
Nothing at all!
I've collabed with the
two of you separately,
but how about you two?
I've collabed with
the two of you separately as well,
but as a trio...
I don't remember ever doing so.
We might develop a new chemistry today!
I feel like it's been a while since
I last streamed with you, Haachama.
You're right!
The first—
Yeah!
The first person to ever go
"Haachama?!" was you, Okayun.
Oh, yeah!
She's right!
I think it was two years ago on New Year's?
Yeah, New Year's.
Just around this time, too.
Yup.
And by the time I realized it,
you'd embraced it.
Her name as well as her
personality just edged away.
Yeah!
Gradually...
And now I'm Haachama to a T!
You sure have changed!
Okay! Our first segment is...
Random Rapid-Fire Interrogation!
Yaaay!
Wooow!
Yay!
So, Haachama,
in this segment, the two of us
who have been on the show before
will be asking you
lots of questions really quickly.
Are you ready, Haachama?
C—
Comically!
What?
Nothing came to mind!
You okay?
I couldn't think of a word!
My Japanese wouldn't come out!
You need a break?
You can just say it in English.
Okay, let's go!
Go for it!
All right. Let's begin!
Twenty-question interrogation, start!
Q1: I want you to hurl abuse at me.
Dummy!
Gah!
Really?
That's kinda weak.
Q6: What's your childhood dream?
To become Haachama!
Ahahahaha!
Lies! Tell the truth!
Spill it!
Ahahahahaha!
Q8: What do you do
for a change of pace?
What did I do again?
Right! I make raps!
Q10: Please describe how
you currently feel via rap.
What the heck?!
♪ Okayun! ♪
♪ Wrapped up tight! ♪
♪ I'll give you a rap with my knuckles, a'ight?! ♪
What the heck is THAT?!
Q17: What's your specialty dish?
Haachamachama Cooking—
Tarantula Ramen.
Yikes...
Ahahahahaha!
Hahaha!
Uh...
Q18: What's your favorite food?
My favorite food is sushi!
Q20: Who are you right now?
Akai Haato or Haachama?
Both!
Akai Haato lives inside of Haachama!
Uh-huh.
I see.
Time's up!
Okay!
All right, that's all the questions.
That went by in a flash.
It did, yeah!
Yeah. Well, it IS rapid-fire.
Personally,
there are a few answers I'm curious about...
What, the abuse?
Wasn't that just sloppy?!
I mean...
You wanted something scathing
to satisfy yourself
so I gave you a gentle one.
Was that you being considerate?
Rather than being considerate...
It was me being sadistic!
I won't satisfy you THAT easily!
Ah!
Ah... okay.
I see now!
So you leave them hanging.
Don't think I'll give you
what you want THAT easily!
Whaaat?
She's blasting you hard!
What're you happy about?!
How do you feel, Okayu-san?
How do you feel?
This doesn't feel half bad. ♥
And as for Q10:
"Please describe how you currently feel via rap."
You were going all,
"Okayun, yun, yun, yun" and "Mon, mon, mon."
♪ Okayun! Wrapped up tight! ♪
But come on! It's absurd to ask me
to describe how I feel via rap on the spot!
So I put my frustration into the lyrics
but I flubbed it.
Really?
I guess it's hard to make
an improvised rap, huh?
How about stuff like your
Haachama Rap that you uploaded lately?
Yeah, that's true.
Do you actually take
a lot of time to make them?
Nope.
I make those in seconds!
That's an obvious lie!
How about your rap just now?
I made it in three seconds!
Three seconds.
So that whole rap about wrapping me
was done in three seconds?
She did rap you in the end.
All right! Let's move on
to our next segment, shall we?
Sure!
Okay!
Our next segment is...
Can I Affirm That For Ya?
Yaaay!
For Yaaa?
Okaaay!
This is my segment.
Nice.
Since I can affirm anything and everything,
in this segment,
The Fail
You went to change for PE but found out you
were wearing pajamas under your uniform!
Viewer
I'll read a viewer's fails and have
the other two guess how I'll affirm them!
I see...
We're guessing, huh.
You two will have to guess
how I'll affirm the viewer.
This one's a lot of fun.
It is, right?
Lots of fun!
How confident are you two?
This is gonna be easy!
Easy?
It's definitely easy!
As for Robocosan...
We're gonna have to
get inside Okayu's head.
You participated last time so
I think you already know how it works,
but this is Haachama's first time, so...
I get the gist of it.
Are you sure it's gonna be easy?
I more or less get how it works.
You sure?
There's a guaranteed method to win this game!
Really?
No, there isn't.
You serious?
We've already collected
some fails beforehand,
so let's get right to it!
Please do!
Our first failure is... this!
"I threw the egg into the bin
and the shells onto my frying pan
when I was making fried rice."
Try guessing how I'll affirm
this person's failure!
Without further ado,
thinking time starts... now!
We don't have to write
our answers down, right?
Or do we have to?
You have to.
Shoot, okay.
It's fine.
I don't know how to write my answer.
You just write your answer down.
The bottom left corner, Haachama.
Oh, okay!
Let's see...
Yeah, that one.
But wow, tossing the egg into the bin
and the shells onto the frying pan
while making fried rice has to suck!
It does. It's just plain sad.
It's one of those
"I screwed up!" moments.
But I do that often myself, though.
Actually, rather than do these things a lot,
it's more like, uh...
It's more like I make a lot of mistakes.
I've got my answer!
Your thoughts are
as clear as day to me, Okayun!
Really?
I want you to look deeper in.
No thanks!
You're passing, huh...
I suppose that's a shame, then...
Ugh...
She's egging me on!
It's impossible not to!
You're like...
You're like a grandchild!
I can't help but tease you!
Dammit!
She's treating me like a kid!
But you understand me,
right, Robocosan?
Haachama's like
a little pesky grandchild.
Understandable.
Why is that understandable?!
Are you both done?
Yup, I wrote my answer down!
Yeah.
Well then, thinking time's over!
All right, did you affirm them well, I wonder?
Let's take a look at your answers and find out!
Anyone here confident in their answers?
Me!
Still, this one's really—
Oh, go ahead.
Go ahead, Haachama.
Please go ahead, Haachama!
Reveal your answer!
Ta-dah!
"Let's OkaChama Cooking!"
What the heck is that?
Seriously, what the heck is that?
What sort of answer is this?!
What's that supposed to mean?
To explain it in detail,
you treat the bin as your plate
and cook the eggshells
on your frying pan and eat it.
It's still cooking!
Ah...
Okay...
It's not like cooking has to
involve edible food.
Mistakes happen.
So you're saying that "It's not a fail."
Yeah!
Exactly!
So this counts as cooking, huh.
Yeah, just eat it.
I see.
So you're saying,
"Just make the bin your plate!"?
Yeah!
Exactly!
That's scary.
That's messed up.
Okay! Please show us
your answer next, Robocosan!
Sure!
Here's my answer!
"It's your lucky day!
Maybe the next egg you crack
will have double yolks!"
I see!
So you might get double yolks
on your next egg
because of the first mistake.
Something bad happened,
so the next thing that'll happen
is bound to be lucky!
I see...
This answer's so good that
if I had a girlfriend
I'd want a girl like you.
Oh?
‘Cause I'd get down if
it was me who made the mistake.
I'd be like, "Crap, I screwed up!"
And then Robocosan would
come up behind me and go,
"It's your lucky day!
Maybe the next egg you crack
will have double yolks!"
You'd want such a girlfriend, right?!
What?!
Why?!
How about—
How about "Let's OkaChama Cooking!"?!
That's just scary.
Sorry, Haachama.
It's impossible for you.
I'll take Okayu, thanks.
What, you can't come out and go,
"Let's OkaChama Cooking!"?
Honestly, it'd be awkward
if you came out and went,
"Just make the bin your plate!"
Plus, your bin definitely has
something in it.
You're right!
Heck no!
All right, we saw both your answers,
so now it's time to show mine!
Here's how I'd affirm them!
"Isn't it like feeding Calcifer?"
You get what I mean?
Oh! Calcifer!
So it's like your frying pan is Calcifer!
Totally!
Who's Calcifer?
A fire demon from the movie
Howl's Moving Castle that eats eggshells.
Yeah!
Ah! That's a nice one!
It's like you're feeding your bin!
Don't feed it!
So, to the viewer who threw
eggshells onto their frying pan,
my answer to you is,
"Isn't it like feeding Calcifer?"
That's so like you, Okayu!
We weren't close.
It feels like you're just
messing around in your answer.
No, I'm not.
But even so...
Still... this is actually just
"Let's OkaChama Cooking," isn't it?
What?
What do you mean...?
YOU'RE RIGHT!
What are you saying?
You've got a point!
Like, the way you phrased it is different,
All right!
I got it right!
but they're still eating the eggshells.
Nope.
I'd like to firmly state that my answer
is NOT OkaChama Cooking.
(Firmly Rejected)
Hey!
Why not?!
It is NOT Haachama Cooking.
Here's our next segment!
Robocosan SOS
Wooow!
Save meee!
This is Robocosan's segment!
Please explain the rules!
Okay! For this segment...
I'm a high-spec robot,
but apparently, I don't have any luck,
almost catastrophically, right?
"Apparently"? Does that mean
you're not aware of it?
Well...
I really don't have any...
Okay.
So, in order to train my luck,
I'll have everyone play
a luck-based game with me!
Sure!
All right, everyone!
Please look at the screen.
Oh?
Wait, Roboco-senpai?
You're trapped!
As you can see, I've been captured.
So, everyone, please save me!
No thanks!
Oh my...
That's right, Haachama!
You don't have to save her if you don't wanna!
I'll pass!
If you—
If you don't save me,
you'll be cursed with bad luck.
But if you save me...
What happens if we save you?
If you save me without
getting me blown up,
that means your luck is top tier today!
So, what'll you do, Haachama?
I'll take the bad luck!
I'll live with the bad luck.
You sure about that?
Are you sure you want that?
Save me, dammit!
The method to save me is very simple!
All you have to do is push
each of these buttons one at a time.
However...
One of the buttons is connected to the bomb,
so if you end up pressing that one,
the bomb will explode!
And that'll result in failure.
If you manage to press all the buttons
that aren't connected to the bomb,
you'll be able to save me
and get your good luck,
so work together to save me, okay?
Let's get right into it, shall we?
Sure!
Okay!
For the first stage, one out of the eight
buttons is connected to the bomb!
Without further ado...
Robocosan SOS starts now!
Yaaay!
Okay, you first, Haachama.
I pick the "X"!
The red "X"!
I knew you'd go for that.
I'm red, after all.
Why do you want to press that one?
‘Cause it's red.
It's definitely because it's an "X," isn't it?
No! It's because it's red!
Really?
Like...
Are you telling the truth?
Your outfit's red too,
isn't it, Roboco-senpai?
True...
That's true.
All right... can you say the magic words, then?
Boop the Button ♪
Yikes, that was quick.
She needs to brace for it.
Yaaay!
Oooh!
Thank goodness!
It's a success!
Safe!
That scared me.
She just went straight for it.
That was nerve-racking.
It really was!
She instantly booped the button
without hesitating.
Yeah!
You go next, Okayu.
Got it.
I feel like I don't have
that much luck this year, so...
Say what?
I might boop the bomb switch.
Conversely, it'd be amazing if you did hit it.
Okay... I choose the bouncy ♪ button!
Bouncy bouncy!
Boop the Button!
Oooh!
Safe!
Now we're down to
a one in six chance, huh...
All right, Robocosan, press a button!
I've already picked one!
You did?
When you think of hololive,
you obviously think of a triangle, so...
There's no way they'd make
the triangle the detonate switch, right?
So it's not the blue button, huh.
The blue button...
Stop it.
I believe in the shape!
Roboco-san's being really cautious.
The shape, huh.
I trust my guts!
I'll push the triangle button!
All right, then...
Boop... that... Button!
It'll totally be fine!
All right!
Oooh!
Wait...
Can we actually save her?
That ain't good.
That ain't good for the show at all.
Wants to end with a bang.
You sure you want to end
with a bang and bad luck?
Who's pushing the button next?
Meee!
Go for it, Haachama!
Which button?
I pick...
The st—
Huh... hmm...
The star.
She's in a bind.
You were thinking real hard there.
Wait, no.
It's gotta be hololive's blue, right?
She went for it!
If this detonates the bomb...
Like, come on.
Strong-arming the Staff
Come on.
She's forcing your hand, staff members!
She's forcing the staff.
Like, what the heck.
Understandable.
Anyways...
Boop the Button ♪
The hololive choice is
definitely safe, right?
Yaaay!
Whoooa!
Have faith and
you shall be saved, indeed.
Saved by the blue.
The staff were also biting
their nails, weren't they?
They definitely were.
Wait... wow!
We're down to a one in four chance!
Oh, wow!
We can make it!
I kinda wanna save her
now that we made it this far.
You're next, Okayu!
Save me!
Don't save her!
Whaaat?
At this point, I feel that
I'd end up picking the button that detonates the bomb
if I think too hard about which one to press.
Yeah!
So I'm gonna just pick randomly!
Just pick one quickly!
Okay, then Boop that Circle Button!
Too quick!
Is the circle button safe?
It's kinda sketchy.
This ain't good.
It's definitely safe!
I'm done thinking.
I don't have a good feeling about this.
Oooh!
Whoa! Amazing!
Wow! Yes!
All right!
Last round.
Wait...
Shoot...
Just go with your gut, Roboco-san!
Guts?! Okay, it's gotta be
the double circle, right?
That's a little...
Boop the Button!
Is that really safe?
I'm gonna save myself!
Wow! Nice!
Yes!!!
Whoa!
We're doing it!
I'm next?
Oh, okay!
You wanna take the gamble?
Yup!
I pick... yellow!
Go ahead!
'Cause you're yellow too, right?
Yellow!
Let's all say it together!
One, two...
Boop the Button!
Save me!
Save meee! Please!
ARGH!
(Successfully Exploded)
Yes!
Nooo!
Dammit!
All right! Bingo!
I was so sure I could escape this time...
Still no dice, huh...
Dammit!
We were so close!
Plus, this is the first stage,
so it had the least amount of bombs, right?
Say what?
It's the one with the highest chance of success.
Seriously?
Even this one was a failure, huh...
That's amazing.
But we were close!
The dream was real!
The dream was real, indeed...
The dream was real, yeah.
It was fleeting and
died in the end, though.
All right! Here's our next segment!
Quiz Time! Haachama Rap!
Whoo!
Yaaay!
Yo yo yo yo yo!
Yo yo, yo yo yo!
This is Haachama's segment!
Please explain the rules!
Sure! This is my segment!
What're you laughing at?
In this segment,
you'll need to listen to
an original rap I came up with.
After that, you'll be quizzed on stuff
you can definitely answer if you listened to my rap!
This time around, I made a rap
themed around this show, holo's Bonjour!
Oooh!
Yay!
Okay, then!
Let's start off by listening
to the rap once, shall we?
I can't wait!
I'm excited!
You'll be quizzed on this later,
so make sure you listen!
All right!
Please listen to it!
Here it goes!
This is your ultimate worldwide ultimate idol!
Haachama-chama!
Ooh! Wow!
We're gonna shake up Bonjour tonight, y'all!
Bonjour to you, ladies and gents!
Remember the Slick Comeback Championship?!
A chance to stop dropping spaghetti?
Our apex champion was Towa-sama!
Watch the video where Lamy dropped the quote
[I'm the law in this world!]
Suisei Train?
Suisui Shoots!
Where does she get her fuel from, yo?
Supposedly, most of it's from her fave!
So speed it up and make her your fave!
Hey, Okayun!
You an M? For real?
I'll nibble those cat ears!
Om, nom, yummy!
Ding, ding, dong!
Today, I'm the one leading y'all on!
Y'all ready for me? (For me) (For me)
Okay!
With that out of the way...
That was amazing!
That was awesome!
You better memorize it!
How was it?
Really good!
Epic!
I was hooked!
All right, the questions in the quiz
are all taken from the rap,
so let's start, shall we?
Is that okay? Are you two ready?
Yup!
Let's go!
Here's the first question!
Hochimachi—
Wait, that's not it.
"Hoshimachi Suisei's
Suisei Train is powered by...?"
I remember this!
Oh!
I'm writing it down.
Wait.
Shoot.
I was wondering about this
while I was listening to your rap.
What is it?
You were aiming to lead us all on today, huh.
Yeah!
Exactly. And like...
My plan was to do that
straight from the get-go,
but I ended up
going with the flow at some point.
I see.
Yeah.
This is bad.
I'm doomed here.
Suisui. Suisuisui
Suisuisui.
I'm gonna try to lead you all astray and
make you forget the rap while we're talking.
Hey, hey, hey!
Please forget, 'kay?
Crap. She's got me curled around her finger.
Crap.
This ain't good.
Okay, I've written my answer!
You did?
Okay...
Who's showing their answers first?
Let's go with Okayun first!
Me.
Oh, I can go second.
Okayun first or Roboco-senpai first?
Either way, your answers are...
Wait, can't we just show both
at the same time?
Ready?
Reveal!
There it is!
What the heck
did you write there, Robocosan?
Suisuisui!
Did you lose all your vocabulary?
It's catchy.
Huh? Wasn't it in the rap?
Wasn't the answer,
"Most of it from her faves"?
Hang on!
I remember hearing,
"Supposedly, most of it's from her faves."
Oh yeah, that's what it was.
Hm?
Didn't you—
Didn't you go "Suisuisui" a few times?
Hm?
Is my head getting Haachama-chama'd?
Yeah, this is definitely a case
of getting Haachama-chama'd
Yeah, it is.
Okay, show the real answer.
Here it is!
Oooh!
All right!
Nooo!
I got it right!
Okayun got it right.
Why'd you write "Suisui"?
You definitely forgot while
we were talking, didn't you?
Yeah, I did.
You sure you're okay?
You're not gonna forget everything
when we talk more after this, are you?
Do we need to play the rap
one more time for you?
I'm in a rough spot here.
You okay?
I actually do wanna listen
to the rap one more time.
Should we listen to it again?
It's too good.
Listening to the rap one more time.
Here is the next question, the second one!
Ta-dah!
"What's the quote Yukihana Lamy dropped
in [The Slick Comeback Championship]?"
Oh!
Thinking time starts... now!
This one, huh.
I remember this one.
Same here.
Why do you remember it? Forget it!
There's no way you'd forget it
given how much of an impact the verse had.
I dunno about that!
For all you know, you might've
memorized the wrong thing!
The impact was too good.
True, true.
It was amazing, wasn't it?
It's just plain funny, isn't it?
Okay, this is my answer.
Okay! I'm done!
You both sure?
If so, let's take a look at your answers!
At the same time...
Sure.
Let's reveal them at the same time, then.
Let's! It's a lot faster that way.
Ready?
Reveal!
The law!
The law.
Are those your final answers?
Are they? Really?
They are!
Then let's look at the answer!
Answer: I'm the law in this world
Why?!
Hey! Why do you both have the same answers!
Yaaay!
Yay!
Was it too easy?
I remember—
I remembered that one.
I got every last word down exactly!
Well, I let you relisten to the rap earlier
but you won't get that crutch for the last question!
You better remember well!
That doesn't sound good.
It doesn't, yeah.
Your faces say otherwise, though?
Why do your faces say "Easy peasy"?
Watch the full stream for the final question!
Extra
Shoot, we have an extra four minutes.
Wait, really?
Buying Time
Haachamachama!
Q9: What do you always do
before you sleep?
I don't sleep.
Liar!
What?!
You definitely do!
I don't need sleep!
The archive for this stream will be up for
3 months—
Wait, no.
3 weeks!
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub
channel on NicoNico for the full stream archives!
That's really long!
Super long.
Too long!