Everyone, charge ahead!
But if I jump in, I'll get hit by friendly fire.
That's true.
Y'all go instead.
Stop yapping and go!
So how are you? Do you still drink?
Why, of course!
My liver's still up for it!
"ABOBO WILL NOT LET YOU PASS."
She's a hungover hag now...
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Okay then!
Let's open up for this week!
Got it, Boss!
So, unfortunately,
Yaaay...
Towa-chan won't be here today.
*Towa is on break for today.
I expect you two to do
her share of the work, got that?
We'll do our best!
Huh?
Let's... Let's do our best...
What's wrong, Marine?
Did anything happen?
We're not... We're not vibing!
You're throwing off my vibes!
Why'd you say that?!
What happened?
Let's try to get along!
We have a chemistry, ri―
Damn girl, you tiny.
Who're you calling tiny?!
Did you get smaller?
I'm not tiny!
That was cringe!
Maaan!
What now?
How are we gonna go from this?!
The mood is completely different
from the usual.
Did you two have a spat?
Well, Boss, to be honest...
The two of us are known in hololive
to have completely opposing personalities.
We've managed to cover that up thanks to
having Towa-sama around.
Seriously?!
We've kept it from coming to the forefront.
But now the buffer's gone,
is what you're saying?
Yes!
It's not like we don't
like each other or anything,
I know as much.
but we can't get a conversation going!
But that's not true, right?
You mean it?
Ouch.
That hurt.
Highly Incompatible
I felt our bones clash.
That hurt a lot.
Let's open up the store!
Please come here now!
We'll take anyone!
We need help!
Anyone! Please!
This suuucks!
We need a customer!
Please come in!
Yaaaay!
Hooray!
Finally!
Whoa!
Welcome to the shop!
Perfect! This is the perfect synergy!
Wha―
Did I interrupt something?
Perfect synergy!
Get in the middle!
Thanks for coming today, Lamy-chan!
You came at the perfect time!
Thank you, Lamy!
Welcome!
We've averted a crisis.
Stop it! Now I'm feeling awkward!
Our guest today is Yukihana Lamy-san!
MENT
LUCK
Charm Points
Drinking, handicrafts,
skin toners, accessories
Has she been drinking as hard
since her last appearance?
Welcome to the shop!
It's a returning guest!
So how are you? Do you still drink?
Charm Point: Drinking
Why, of course!
My liver's still up for it!
Your liver is...
Still chugging!
She said that with zero hesitation.
Her last problem:
She wants the leadership skills
to take charge and guide her colleagues.
Yeah!
I think we resolved that.
Did it help?
Just a bit, I think.
What a frank girl!
I did manage to go "Rising Sun!"
the last time, but...
Hm?
Huh?
Say that again?
What did you just say?
What was that again?
R-R-Rising? Rising?
Graaah!
Rising Sun...
Sorry, my ears are bad right now.
Can you say it louder?
RISING SUUUN!
Guys! Please stop!
That was really cringe...!
I'm sorry, Lamy. But I can't take this.
I'm so sorry!
This show is too much for me...
I exposed Lamy in such a sorry state.
I'm sorry...
This'll be another point of shame...
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
She's made the sun rise before us,
so in return, tell us your problem!
Okay!
I still feel like
my leadership skills are lacking,
so I would like to continue
training my qualities
as a proper leader!
Please teach me well, Maruyama staff!
You came to the right place!
We have a request!
Thank you for your patronage!
Lamy's last problem was
Her last problem:
She wants the leadership skills
to take charge and guide her colleagues.
Let us handle this one more time!
We have the perfect game for you!
Maruyama's game recommendation is...
Bam!
Kunio's Romance of the Three Kingdoms:
Everyone Assemble!
With the first game released back in 1986,
the still-beloved River City series
has released their latest game:
Kunio's Romance of the Three Kingdoms:
Everyone Assemble!
Characters in the series
are now feudal warriors
going wild across the entire Three Kingdoms!
The game retains the simple controls and
exhilarating action the series is known for.
Use the items available in the stage
to improve your playing experience!
Don't sweat the complicated stuff!
Defeat everyone standing before you!
Let's all enjoy playing
Three Kingdoms together!
If we follow in the footsteps of
those who shaped a whole country,
then leadership won't be the last thing
you'll learn about today!
Together now!
One Goal!
King of a Nation!
I'm fine with being
a normal leader, though...
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Our activity for today is...
Advance On, Lamy Troops!
Aim For All Stage Conquest!
Our goal is to clear
the four-player mode,
"Heroic Record of the Three Kingdoms".
We staff will be the troop members,
while Lamy-chan will be our troop leader.
Leader Lamy!
Leader!
Yes! More!
King of a Nation!
Say it more!
Go on!
I'm sure this will be
a fairly tough challenge.
There will be lifelines down the line,
so let's do our best!
We just gotta do it!
Yep!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Yay!
Well, Leader!
Any words of encouragement
before we start?
My people! I grant you
the right to protect me!
Onward!
She's going for that...
O... Oh...
Ooh...
Oh...
Let's start the first battle
with friendly fire set to ON.
Character Select
Let's choose our characters!
When friendly fire is set to ON,
your attacks affect both friend and foe.
Be careful of where you attack!
This kinda looks like me.
It does!
Yeah! It does!
Looks nice.
I'll go with this guy, then.
I heard Kunio-kun was easy to play.
Okay, I'll play as Kunio-kun.
Good choice!
Nice, nice.
I'll go with this guy
since we look kinda alike.
Like, by the outfit?
Because of the outfit?
Yep!
He does resemble Subaru-senpai!
You can see it, right?
I kinda feel like
playing as this guy.
A strong tiger!
That's a jacked-up cat.
I'm a cat after all. Is this fine?
Makes sense.
Yep. Easy indicator too.
Boss goes with the cat.
Just a jacked-up cat...
Think of it as an upgrade.
Upgraded cat.
'Kay.
All right.
Pick, done.
Let's get started!
Let's go.
Leader.
Read it out, Leader.
That's... a lot of big words.
Let's leave it at that.
Are we just skipping over it?!
Whoa, this is cool!
We can move!
The field is pretty wide!
That's cool!
A drop!
So from here, enemies will
start coming in, in waves.
We move on to the next stage
once they're all defeated.
We all have to work together to―
Teamwork, gotcha!
Teamwork!
Wait a sec!
Friendly fire is ON, right?
Yep!
She's right!
YEOWCH!
That hurt!
As you all can see,
setting friendly fire to ON
lets your attacks damage allies too,
so watch where you attack!
We're a team! Play as a team!
They're coming!
The ones with the blue bars!
Fight! Fight!
Hit those guys!
Roger!
Hit the blue bar guys.
Yep, them.
We're not gonna let them
into the screen!
If we see them, it's over!
Leader, orders, please!
What's the strategy, Leader?
Don't let the enemies into the screen!
I'd like to see what I'm hitting...
Finish them off-screen!
That's a strat, huh?
Oh, we can move on!
Subaru-senpai, you're hitting me.
It's not me!
I'm on the right!
Was that you, Leader?
No, no. Ain't me.
I tried to protect you.
You call that protection?!
This friendly fire is screwing us over!
We're doing pretty good, aren't we?
We're doing great!
Go! Go!
Me and Boss will just be
churning butter over here.
The heck?!
Get to work!
Y'all doing good!
The hell are ya foolin' around for?!
Time to do a skill.
Nice!
This guy looks evil!
Sawaguchi is his name.
That's the face of a villain.
Doesn't it look cool?
Zhang Bao, a.k.a. Sawaguchi.
He says he's booming
in popularity recently.
In what country?!
Crap, I was beaten up.
Let's stan him while he's popular.
While he's at his high.
Yeah.
Before he becomes old news.
No choice but to use a skill.
Is it time?
I wanna use my finisher!
It's time.
I wanna use mine too!
I can't pull it off.
Me too!
How do I do it again?
Left, up, SR.
Left, up...
Okay!
Hey, that hurt!
I got hit by that!
That was cool!
Who did that?!
Excuse me!
Pirate crossing!
How's this?!
Good job!
Piece of cake!
Flawless! Our teamwork's flawless!
Look at this booming Sawaguchi...
Sorry, not my fave anymore.
He picked the wrong opponent.
How did we do―?
Oh, there's a scoreboard!
Mine and the Boss' kill count is really high!
Leader beat down a lot of them for us!
Leave it to me!
She's reliable.
Indeed.
Oh, she's back.
She's cute!
However, all the big words mean...
...I can't read it.
Story mode...
Okay, they're here.
That's a lot of them.
Everyone, charge ahead!
But if I jump in,
I'll get hurt in the friendly fire.
That's true.
Y'all go instead.
Stop yapping and go!
Become...
Become my meat shields!
Aren't you gonna protect us?!
Some leader you are!
Okay, fine!
I'm on the left! Left!
I'm taking damage
from those kicks, Marine!
Sorry!
Cut it out!
Please let it slide!
Leader! She's bullying me!
Hey now!
I'm not bullying her!
Stop kicking all over the place!
Don't do those Evil Kicks!
Eat this and die, Marine!
Pay attention to where you're kicking!
Oh, I see how it is!
AAAAGH! NO! STOP!
Why did you kick me?!
That one was intentional!
That was Marine, wasn't it?
I saw her!
Leader, look!
These words are all easy!
You can read this!
Read it with feelings!
No problem!
"ABOBO WILL NOT LET YOU PASS."
She's a hungover hag now...
It's started!
Boss battle! Boss battle!
We're at the boss battle!
You guys handle the boss.
Ouch! Leader...!
What's wrong?
The Boss is going berserk!
She's attacking everyone!
She's a serial killer now!
All humans are food!
"I WILL NOT FORGIVE HUMAN."
She's a legit tiger now.
The Boss has returned
to her primal roots.
Abobo! Abobo!
I think I did an advanced skill!
And I got caught up in it.
Yay!
We won!
No need to pick up our weapons?
We probably should have!
Easy-peasy!
Read it!
Go.
"ABOBO LOST."
"YOU ARE STRONG."
This never gets old.
This is her hungover.
It's the alcohol voice.
Why am I doing this?
Nice work!
Wait.
Thirty kills?! Impressive!
That's a good record!
You've hurt us just as many times, though.
True, true.
That's true!
We paid the price for that 30 kill count!
Now at Stage 03!
Leader!
Any strategies you have in mind?
Good question!
We've been too uncoordinated!
That's right.
It's about time
we split into teams of two―
The enemies are here, Leader!
You're too slow!
Sorry! Sorry!
You were too slow!
What to do, Leader?
Your orders, please!
Let's go... TigerMarine!
Uhm... TigerMarine, flank right!
All the enemies are on the right!
SubaLamy, flank left!
Subaru & Lamy, flank left!
Yes, flank left!
Time to go wild!
Let's go! Let's go!
All the enemies are to the right!
I'm dying!
I'm gonna die!
Stop that!
Marine: Zero Lives Remaining
I'm dying over here!
This is the reality of friendly fire!
Never forget this!
I'm back...
Go! Go!
Let's go!
Oh, a recovery item!
Oh! It's the last boss!
She looks very...
Misuzu-san.
Very unique.
She's the character
Subaru was considering...
No, I wasn't!
Lamy recommended her to me!
What's this slander?
That ain't slander!
The beauty is here.
Battle start!
Damn, they look strong!
The boss is pretty big.
Her hitbox is huge.
Massive.
Massive and FAST!
What's that skill?!
This is bad!
She's strong.
She is a boss.
Not to mention, even the mobs are...
Strong as heck.
Lamy: Zero Lives Remaining
on the level of a mid-boss.
Right?!
I think we should all
unleash our finishers here.
We'd all be caught up in the friendly fire.
Yikes! I'm gonna die!
Stop it with the friendly fire!
Died to friendly fire.
Did we get her?
No, not yet!
The boss is down, though.
Yep, the boss is down! Good!
Are we done?
That was too close!
A close victory.
We were almost beat.
Her make-up's ruined.
Her face is melting off.
This series sure loves
showing its enemies beaten up.
Yeah, it's melting off.
True.
Advancing through the stages,
our party members are slowly losing their HP!
Hang in there, everyone!
The people with lives
should soak up the damage.
O-Okay!
Try doing it, Boss.
Alright!
Marine's dying! She's dying!
Oh no, Marine-san!
Huh? Hmm?
I've been revived?
Marine: Jiangshi Mode
I think I'm a jiangshi now!
She ran out of lives
and turned into a jiangshi!
You can't die as a jiangshi,
but you can't attack either...
Okay, I've gotten the hang of this!
He's a good-looking one.
Kamijou.
His other name reads "good-looking."
Good-looking...
That's what it means.
Good-Looking Kamijou.
Good-Looking Kamijou...
Oh no, I'm on fire!
I'm gonna die...
Farewell!
Lamy: Jiangshi Mode
We now have two jiangshi.
Jiangshi won't help―
Now I'm dying!
All a jiangshi can do
is stun the enemy.
Let's go!
It sorta does work, though.
I'm gonna get killed!
MariLamy stun the opponents,
you two attack them.
Roger that!
Now that's team play!
Here's the last of them.
Subaru: Jiangshi Mode
There's three of us now!
Only the Boss is left!
Boss!
Oh wait, did we revive?
Three of them have become jiangshi!
Their only attacker is the Boss!
This is gonna be tough!
Now they're gonna time out...!
Is this a time out?
Unleash your finisher!
Unleash it!
Use it, Boss!
Aaagh...
You look exhausted, Boss!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Since we were beaten up
quite badly on our first attempt,
why don't we try out
the lifeline mini-game mentioned earlier?
Let's do it!
We gotta do this
if we wanna clear the game.
Here it is!
Open the Lifelines!
Kunio-kun Series Quiz!
Wait a sec.
Making Kunio-kun beginners answer
a Kunio-kun quiz is quite a tall order.
It's not a short one, for sure.
As long as you guys
put your brains together...
Oh, okay.
Pool our knowledge!
I see!
Yep!
We're a team!
If you score well,
then we turn off friendly fire,
Yes, please! We need that!
This could give us a chance!
and add one more life to everyone!
The team gets to pick which one to unlock
each time you score a point.
That's the rules.
Got it!
Gotta delete the friendly fire, though.
Right?
I guess we're all on the same page here.
Let's begin!
The first Kunio-kun game,
Hot-Blooded Tough Guy Kunio,
was first released in 1986.
What also happened in that year?
1986?
A) TurboGrafx-16 was released.
B) Takenoko-zoku started trending.
Takenoko-zoku...?
I don't know!
C) Bikkuriman Chocolate boomed in popularity.
That came a bit after, didn't it?
I have no idea.
I wouldn't know.
D) OKAZU CLUB's YuiP was born.
Whoa! It's this one!
It's definitely that! Definitely that!
The answer is
definitely D!
YuiP was born, along with
the release of Kunio-kun.
You want us to score points, right?
I'm sure she's showing it off.
Without a doubt!
To be honest,
why else would they expose
her personal info like this?
Okay, then.
Our answer is
YuiP-san's birth year.
Yes.
Is that your answer?
Yes!
Final answer!
Final answer?
Correct!
The correct answer is
Reward
Friendly Fire is now OFF!
D) OKAZU CLUB's YuiP was born.
If the team gets one more correct answer,
I'll grant you all one additional life.
Ready?
We're ready!
Let's do it!
Did you have to ask?
Here is the next question!
Where did the main character's
name "Kunio" come from?
Good question.
A) Kenka de kuni wo osameru.
(Pacify the nation through battle)
Possible.
B) The name of Technos Japan's CEO at the time.
C) The name of a legendary ruffian
from the dev's hometown.
D) An anagram of "Oniku,"
a BBQ place the devs often went to.
This is pretty difficult.
They all sound plausible.
It does seem pretty hard.
Do you want to go 50/50?
Yes!
50/50, please!
It's come to this, huh.
To use the 50/50,
we need someone to do the Rising Sun.
We can do it like that, sure!
I can't shine with glory.
Let's all do it! Us three!
The Rising Sun?
Summon the Rising Sun!
The three of us should do it.
I can't shoot beams!
All three of you?
Do I...
Do I have to add more to my shame?!
I'm sure you'll emanate a kingly glow!
That's true.
Show it to us!
Ready!
RISING!
SUUUUUUN!
I knew this would happen!
The two of you could have
at least pretended to do it.
They had no intention
of doing it at all!
After the 50/50,
your only choices are...
B) The name of Technos Japan's CEO at the time.
and D) An anagram of "Oniku,"
a BBQ place the devs often went to.
My pick was blacked out.
Team B!
I'll go with their answer...
What happened to being a leader...
But well, if I had to choose between the two...
Here is the correct answer!
The answer is...
B) The name of Technos Japan's CEO at the time.
Let's go for the full clear!
Reward
One Additional Life!
Yeah!
Does that mean the Evil Kick
isn't banned anymore?
Go ahead!
Yay!
Let's do this.
Let's go!
Unleashing the kick already.
Awright.
Let's get 'em!
Come at me!
This is so much easier!
You're going at it so hard!
This is much easier.
Now that you've all aced the quiz
and turned the friendly fire off,
go all out attacking!
Yeah, it feels that way.
It feels so much easier to play.
It's like a whole 'nother game.
Yeah.
Splendid.
So much less stressful.
We got here fast!
Let's beat 'im up!
Let's get 'im!
Here I come.
Where's the boss?
Oh, a weapon.
Let's go!
Let's get some weapons!
It feels like the enemies are running from us.
Yeah.
Are they scared of us?
And when you, like,
throw these—
You're so fast at getting the coins!
They're fighting over money!
I'm a pirate, after all.
What a gal.
Let's not fight over money.
That gets messy quick.
Awright!
Piece of cake!
That was nice.
That went so fast.
That was perfect.
Right?
Oh?
Everyone beat up quite a lot.
We're all contributing well.
Stage six again, huh.
It's starting to get difficult.
They were able to reach stage 6
with their extra life,
but it seems to be getting difficult...
Focus, everyone!
I still haven't done anything.
But it's okay. We're a well-oiled unit.
Sheesh...
I'm switching to self-defence.
Self-defence...
Yeah.
Ah... I got hit.
Oh, no!
The cart-pulling guy!
Ah! I'm dead!
Nice!
She's a jiangshi!
Lamy...
What're your orders, Leader?
Protect Subaru-senpai's back!
AHHH!
I'm so dead!
Ahh...
Subaru-senpai, grab some heals!
I don't even have a sword...
Excuse me, Mr. Bush,
let me hide here for a bit.
That's good!
Keep hiding!
Good going.
Crap, he's coming for me!
Crap!
I need a bush to hide in...
O-Oooo...
Ooo...
OOO!
Subaru-senpai is making
high-pitched noises.
What kind of sound is that?
Give me a recovery item already...
There sure aren't any.
AHHH!
There aren't. Subaru-senpai—
Subaru-senpai, hide!
Subaru-senpai, this thing looks strong.
I can't use something
so close-ranged, idiot!
Oh, right.
It'd be good to use a recovery item.
I'm already down a life.
Ahhh! I died!
Now what?
You got this.
You can do it.
What's the plan?
Just try your best.
How are things recently?
Your liver, for one.
We have to grandmas over here.
The test results aren't looking bad.
The test...
Yeah, I've been setting records.
Wow, we cleared that?
I feel like you two can clear this.
They somehow cleared stage six,
but it might be getting tough for Marine-san.
Ahhh... I'm done for...
And so, Boss is the last one standing.
Boss, you doin' alright?
Once more.
Darn!
They have quite a lot of HP.
They're so strong!
The tiger only does like 10 damage.
Oh, so he doesn't hit hard.
Ah...
(Sigh) That was exhausting.
Thoughts on that last stand, Leader?
I thought the boss was amazing.
What a shallow assessment.
That was shallower than a puddle.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Now, then.
That's all we have for you today.
Okay!
What did you think of It's Kunio's Romance
of the Three Kingdoms: Everyone Assemble!?
It was fun!
That was a minigame?
There's so much content!
Right.
I wanted to try the campaign mode too.
Right? It makes you want to try it out.
One last thing.
Please tell us the member who shined
the most, the Twin-crew for today!
Leader.
Leader!
I think I'll have to see each of their Rising Sun's
and decide based on that.
Que?
M-Marine,
you can have this one.
What?!
You can have the star, Marine.
You don't need it?
Your raise is riding on those things.
Hmm, that's a tempting offer.
Can they pull it off?
Here I go!
Can they do it?
At the same time!
On three! One... Two...
One... Two...
Rising...
Sun!
Yup.
The winner is...
Marine-senpai.
Yay!
Why?!
Well,
you didn't say the Rising part.
That's right! What's with your "Sun!"?
Honestly,
I'll let you have this win, Marine.
Yay!
As long as you keep honing
your leadership qualities,
you might become the boss pretty soon!
Give it your all!
Okay!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Challenge From The Boss:
the Maruyama Championship Season 2!
At this point, we'll have our customers
try their hand at a minigame.
The one who finishes the season
on top will receive a trophy!
Season 2's minigame is
SEGA AGES Sonic the Hedgehog.
Players will compete in
Green Hill Zone Act 1's time attack mode!
The clear time shown on the
results screen will be your record.
By the way, the one with
the best time currently...
is Suisei-chan, with 36.56 seconds!
How confident are you, Lamy-chan?
Well... Never played before,
but I'll clear in 20 seconds.
Fightin' words!
Okay, let's get right to it!
Go for it.
Here I go!
It's starting.
How's it feel,
playing Sonic for the first time?
Huh?
Sonic?
Well...
I'll go barehanded.
Yeah, uh, that's Sonic.
Everyone does that.
This is good.
Four seconds until twenty.
Yeah, cautious and clean.
Just goes to show
how easy this is for me.
Oh, nice!
What even?
That's some weird noises...
coming from Lamy-chan.
Real weird.
Easy-peasy!
Let's go!
She's plenty fast.
That's a great time!
Okay, so...
Lamy-chan's time is...
43.48 seconds.
That puts her in fourth place!
That's great.
Well done.
Thanks.
What happened to 20, though?
Uh... it looks like 20 seconds to me, though?
Oh.
Get your eyes checked.
Maybe it is 20 seconds.
Did you enjoy that?
It was fun!
I think I'm going to grind until
I get my time under 20 seconds.
Seriously?
Will a monster appear
to beat the fastest time?
You'll just have to keep watching!
Lamy-chan, thanks for coming!
See you again soon!
Thanks for having me!
See you!
Bye!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
See you!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
After Closing
I've asked Marine
to stay back with me this time.
I'm here.
Let's give our viewers some advice
for their worries.
Let's do it.
This one's from @aw8w2BPJbkg3oLM.
Thank you!
"I have a pet cat who likes to sit on my lap.
I like petting her, and it's cute,
but my legs start to go numb.
But if I move the cat, she wakes up!
I feel bad, so now I wait
until she leaves on her own.
What am I supposed to do?"
There we have it.
I see...
Y'know what?
I'm allergic to cats, so I've never had one.
So, to see what'd happen,
I had the boss sit on my lap
to experience what it'd be like
to have a cat do it for a while.
Oh, so that's what I was asked to do this.
There, there.
Cute!
There, there!
That feels good!
So, thoughts?
Well?
That got old quick.
I'm bored.
Bored?
What's worse, wait...
My...
Whoa, those are some powerful sneezes.
My allergy!
Your allergy's acting up!
Gross!
Can I wipe my nose with you?
Don't!
Use your ear to wipe my nose.
What do you think about
the kitty sleeping on the lap?
Well, the thing is...
We're whimsical.
Yeah?
There are times when we want to sit,
and times when we don't.
Oh?
So if we're shooed away when we want to,
we get mad.
What a pain.
I'm light, right?
Light? Uh...
Right?
Not at all. I'm gonna die.
I weigh as much as three apples.
No, you weigh the same
as this one comedian...
Stop that!
So the solution this time
is to wait until she goes away.
Yeah.
By the way, Boss, are you gonna go away?
Nah. I think I'll stay here for a bit.
Oh, really? Even with the snot?
Do your best to hold it in.
Anyway, we're accepting requests
for advice from you.
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique, personally-signed
request fulfilled sticker!
So please send in your submissions!
Keep 'em coming!
We're doing this here?