Yooo, I so wanna eat sushi
using someone else's meagre savings.
But that'd be so mean.
It's tearing me apart...
Time to split into two, then!
Upsy-daisy.
Oh god, Polka split into good and evil!
You mustn't!
Put that away at once!
Gotta be ready to splurge
if you wanna order delivery!
Let's gooo!
How will you make rent next month?!
Life's gotta be lived in the present, the now!
We're doing this!
Why'd you use my account?!
Your order will be delivered in one hour.
Wha? I'm already losing my mind
being blue-balled here!
Just chop up them fishies!
I'm comin' to kick yer ass!
Language!
Miss, you mustn't come here!
My phone!
Hard to starboard!
Huh?!
I told you!
No sushi yet, even if you're eating in!
Wild Tentacle Sushi, go!
Uh, conveyor belt sushi?
Gah! Cooker, dude, I told you
to leave some rice for me!
-100 HP
You gave the rice
for my rice balls to her?
That's bollocks!
…
Keeping mum when
you're out of excuses again?
So unlike when the rice is done!
You don't shut up!
Just try and explain yourself!
Ow!
Hey, no need to get so heated!
Man, this place doesn't even serve tea?
Snide remarks are so crude.
Always stay classy.
aaaAAAaaa
Ha! Piece of cake!
"Bonjour! Got a stick up my ass!"
Are you mocking me?
Mediating Fox!
Kiss my ass! lol!
Well? Ready to kiss my ass?
This is a bit much.
Now I'm pissed. You wanna go?
Mediating Fox!
Be careful what you wish for!
Cause you just might get it!
Give back my phone!
Order received.
Yeah, no. The sushi's going wild.
Sounds like a you problem.
Huh?
You'll make it for us.
Uhh...
Right? You work at a sushi place.
Don't tell me you can't.
Them's fighting words.
Uh... well...
Will you?
Or won't you?
Make your choice!
You're on!
Hi-yah!
Yikes.
Don't stick food in your ear.
Hi-yah!
Wait, that didn't have fish on it.
So it's technically a rice ball!
Take some extra!
Ohoho! Hold up, missy!
Ear Canal
Roll, roll, roll the rice.
Tumblin' down!
Hmm?
Which was it that you lost?
This gold rice ball?
Or this silver rice ball?
Rice balls aren't medals!
Baller punch.
Nyuk-nyuk!
Rice ba—
Could this be...
A fusion factory?!
Ayup!
Ew! Gross!
So this is how sushi is made...
Mwahaha.
This tidal wave of sushi
was born from my bank account.
In the name of freedom, eat this!
Revenge Fox!
That was when I realized.
Rice and fish going wild in my mouth...
A miraculous harmony of land and sea
that was never meant to exist...
It only came to be out of
mutual respect and understanding!
You, too, are a part of me.
Hell, only together are we both...
are we all sushi!
How did we overlook
something so simple?
So, merge already.
Come back to me.
Heh. This is making me blush.
Polka...
Nu-Perezzorcjunmunospolkos...
Let us be one again.
Combine!
Polka Sushi, good to go!
Polka Sushi
Whoo! Hot rice!
Hold it! Get away from that, Okamew!
I see white...
Omnomnom.
Gaaaaargh!
Oww!
Awoo!
Oh, here we go.
Hmm?
Moo!
Holy cow!
They killed the cat and were left cattless!
That's bulls**t, but I believe it.
That's so amoosing.
Love that beefy unit.
Party time in the calfeteria!
That's moore than enough.
A spring in our step!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!