Ready?
It seems like it should
make a sound but it isn't.
*BRAAAP*
Whoa!
Lamy-san, we're recording here!
That's so cool!
I want one too!
It really is, isn't it?
Ready?
*THUMP*
Ouch!
That was exquisite.
Starring
Aki Rosenthal
Shishiro Botan
Sakura Miko
Yukihana Lamy
What's Inside the Black Box?
is brought to you by Aki Rosenthal...
...Shishiro Botan...
...Sakura Miko, and...
...Yukihana Lamy!
It's the second episode of
What's inside the
black boxes
they received?
Yaaay!
Did all of you receive
some shady-looking boxes?
Yuuup!
You did?
You'll be guessing what's in each others' boxes
by playing a word association game!
It's pretty simple.
The person who conveyed
what's in their box the best
will be crowned as our
second Black Box Queen!
Oooh!
The second, huh.
The Black Box Queen is
renowned worldwide
and your predecessor is Fubuki-san!
(Black Box Queen)
Shirakami Fubuki
Ah... I want this title.
Uh-huh. Okay.
You want it?
Anything goes as long as
we don't say what the item is?
Exactly!
Stuff like "It's hard." or
"You can use it for X."
are all in the green!
If that's the case,
I'd like to go first if you all don't mind.
Oh?
Really?
Please do!
What did she get?!
Aki Rosenthal's unboxing!
What's inside the black box?
Start!
Okay!
I'mma opuhn it!
Will we hear something good?
*RIIIP*
Oh! I hear ripping!
Huh? This is a little...
Huh?
What?
She's laughing?
Uh-huh, okay...
Okay...?
I don't own one of these at all.
It's your first time owning one.
She never had one before. Okay.
First time?
I think I've seen this somewhere before.
"Somewhere"?
I wonder what it is.
There's a part that looks like a grip
and a part that isn't the grip.
Uh-huh.
A part that isn't the grip?
The grip part's...
...about the length of three fists?
That long?!
That's pretty long.
Massive!
Is it long?
Isn't it that item?
Oh! Me! I got it!
Me!
You got it?
You first, Miko-san.
It's a beer mug!
I thought so too!
Is it a beer mug?
It'd be nice if it was!
Ah, looks like you're off!
But she'd like it if it was!
Wrong Answer!
How about its material?
Material, huh. It's probably...
...leather?
Leather?
It seems like leather.
And it's black.
It's black. Got it.
Black, huh.
When would you use it?
It's black?
Good question.
When would I use it?
That's a good question...
Can you use it right now, actually?
Try using it now? Hold on.
Are you asking me to use it on myself?
What?
Huh?! What do you mean?
Whaddya mean?
I have no clue what it is!
I'll need to stick my butt out for it to work.
Say what?!
Your butt?!
What do you mean?
Me!
Ah! Go ahead, Botan-san!
How far would you need
to stick your bum out?
Uh...
A whip?
No way!
Is it a whip...?
Correct.
She got it right!
Really?!
WHAT?!
Seriously?!
Aki's black box contained a whip!
It really was a whip?!
What kind of sound
does it make?
I wanna hear it.
Here I go!
Okay!
Ready?
*THUMP*
That kinda sounds like
something falling over.
That was exquisite.
Ouch!
Ouch?
This is the real deal!
It is?
I heard rattling.
How did you know, Botan-san?
Uh, she said it was leather-ish
and that you use it on someone else,
plus I thought the grip
might be a whip's.
And I've been watching
racehorses lately
so I thought that might be it.
I see! That was genius!
Oooh!
Uh-huh. Okay...
Let's go with Botan-san next!
Sure!
Can she convey it well?!
Shishiro Botan's unboxing!
Okay! What's inside the black box?
Start!
A'ight.
*RIP*
Oh, she's going in hard.
That's a nice sound.
It's really nice.
She's being pretty rough with it.
Ah, okay.
This thing's got propellers.
Propellers?
It's got four of them.
Sounds like it's some sort of machine.
The propeller—
I got it!
Go ahead.
It's a drone!
Correct!
She got it right!
That's so cool!
I want one too!
It really is, isn't it?
That's so cool!
Won't you
trade it with my whip?
Okay! Next up is Lamy-san!
Please go ahead!
Got it!
Explanations are her forte?!
Yukihana Lamy's unboxing!
Without further ado...
What's inside the black box?
Start!
Hmm...
It feels really light in the hand!
Oh, she already opened the box.
Ah, I see.
Light?
It's rattling a bit, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
Yeah.
I'm shaking the box right now.
Can you hear this?
Ah!
We're already getting some clues
before she opened the box.
I hear it.
I hear the rattling!
Ah!
"Ah?" Okay, what could it be?
What is it?
*Inhale*
Oh, I hear it!
Something you blow into.
She's blowing into it!
Yeah. Is she sucking it or blowing it?
Is she sucking it? Huh?
It seems like it should
make a sound but it isn't.
One, two...
*BRRRP*
Whoa!
Lamy-san, we're recording here!
Something that lets out air.
Stop right there!
Lamy-tan?!
That's some crazy sound!
Oh, me! I got it!
Botan-san, then?
Uh... a balloon?
Oh?
Boo!
No, it isn't.
Me!
Okay, Miko-san!
Whoopee cushion!
You're correct!
She's correct?
She is! The correct answer is
a whoopee cushion!
All right!
That surprised me.
So it IS a whoopee cushion.
By the way, Lamy-san,
have you ever used one before?
Not at all!
It's the first time
I've even touched one!
First time, huh?
And finally, Miko-san!
Please go ahead!
Okay!
Don't miss this elite breakdown!
Sakura Miko's unboxing!
What's inside the black box?
Start!
All right...
I'll open it now, okay?
Yes, please do.
I wonder what's inside?
It's kinda, uh...
Oh, it's rattly.
Oooh!
It's rattling, isn't it?
It's rattling.
Wooow!
Oh? She seems happy.
This is amazing!
I'm kinda happy I got this, actually.
Happy?
This thing packs a lot of girl power.
Packs a lot of girl power?
Something that packs girl power...
You've got one of
these too, Lamy-tan.
Everyone here probably
has one of these.
Everyone has one?
I... never bought
one of these before.
What is it?
When do you use it?
Uh... after a shower, I guess?
How about its shape?
Its shape?
Hmm...
It's slender and long.
Long?
It's long!
What do you get by, uh...
...using it?
Uh-huh.
Uh... I guess it makes you beautiful?
It makes you beautiful?
It makes you beautiful!
So that's what it does. I see.
Is it one of those beauty products?
I got it!
Oh, Lamy-san!
You use it after a shower,
Oh?
it raises your girl power,
Uh-huh.
and it makes you a charmer!
And it is...?
A face massager!
Correct!
The correct answer is face massager!
Do you have one of these, Lamy-san?
I've got like, three of them.
Three?!
But you're not Cerberus!
Wow.
Please exchange it with my whip!
I'm standing here with
a whoopee cushion, y'know?
They're still practical.
Oh, yeah, you got a whoopee cushion.
Time for the results!
Our Black Box Queen this time is...
Yukihana Lamy-san!
Congratulations!
Congrats!
Wh-Wh-Why me?
The fact that you conveyed what your item was
in one go by letting it rip clearly.
That was masterful use
of the whoopee cushion.
Understandable.
I see!
You blew into it very elegantly.
The gap between your elegant face
as you inhaled and blew into it
and the resulting rip
of the whoopee cushion
was what sealed the deal.
The sound's really dirty.
Okay.
As your shining Black Box Queen,
I'll continue to do my best here at hololive!
Please keep on supporting me!
If you enjoyed this video,
please like it and subscribe
to the official hololive YouTube channel
as well as to these girls' respective channels!
Who will get black boxes sent to them next
and what will be inside?!
Stay tuned to find out!
Stay tuned!
Starring
Aki Rosenthal
Shishiro Botan
Sakura Miko
Yukihana Lamy
What's Inside the Black Box?
was brought to you by Aki Rosenthal...
...Shishiro Botan...
...Sakura Miko, and...
...Yukihana Lamy!