I shall grant the wishes
of they who leave food here.
What's up with her?
She forgot to bring lunch.
Almost there!
Urgh...
I'll allow it.
Choosy, much?
And what is your wish, my girl?
I wanna do beetle battle!
Not exactly the season for it...
I'll allow it!
Weave me out!
And so the gang set out on a journey
to find the legendary winter king beetles.
So this is the WK Cathedral.
"WK"?
It stands for Winter King-Beetle!
I shall grant the wishes
of they who leave food here.
Hmm?
I wanna meet the winter beetles!
More bighearted than Fubuki-senpai!
What's with the wame dance?
...
It's the World Heritage dance.
It'll go on till this place is designated!
Join us!
Wait, I just want to see you guys fight.
Doesn't the thought bug you?!
<-
Bug
Wha...
Did you just...
Pfft.
A...
Attack!
Yikes!
So, are you happy now?
Please just never forget your lunch again.
The legendary winter beetle exists.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!