9:15 PM
Misora-san. A moment.
Y-Yes, what is it?
The transfer student and I
have plans to go to the cinema.
Would you like to join us?
Huh?
But Nanase-san,
I thought you said
you didn't have a ticket for me...
My, did I say that?
Well, if you do have an extra ticket,
I'd love to join.
Heh-heh.
We'll be having dinner afterward.
Care to join us for that as well?
A-Absolutely!
9:30 PM
Sheesh... What took you?
The custodian hasn't noticed a thing,
so get inside, quick!
Hey, school at night ain't so bad.
Shiina-san,
a lady shouldn't sit like that...
This test of courage is exciting,
isn't it, Shino-san?
Yeah... To be honest,
I'm pretty scared...
Pardon me, Misora-san.
Oh, I'm fine, but...
Nanase-san, you don't look well...
My head is killing me...
What's going on with me?
Nanase-san.
S-Sakura-san.
Do you remember
what I told you when we met
in the woods last year?
I told you to
stay out of those woods.
But...
I enjoy taking walks there.
...
You tell your father, too.
Don't cut down
any more trees from that forest.
A-Aogami owes its success
to the Furukawa family!
We're the driving force
behind this town's development.
Just stay away in the future.
Hurry up, you guys! Quit dawdling!
Art Prep Room
10:08 PM
Pfft,
Art Prep Room
10:08 PM
so much for those ghosts, huh?
Art Prep Room
10:08 PM
Right? Talk about an anticlimax.
Nanase-san,
is your headache better?
Don't talk to me!
Why won't you just disappear?!
You're such a nuisance!
Na-Nanase...san?
She's having another episode.
And it's worse than it usually is...
I sense something else
is about to happen...
Something very, very bad...
But why, Nanase-san?
You were so friendly to me earlier...
July 19XX,
approximately 10:10 PM.
A massive landslide devastated
the town of Aogami, causing terrible damage.
It was believed that the heavy rains a few days
earlier weakened the soil, causing the disaster.
However, some claimed it was
the work of vengeful spirits that haunt Aogami.