You shoot the girls on the screen, like this!
Whoa!
Wow!
It said, "twitch!"
I kind of feel guilty about this...
Don't hold back.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Do you all have any Maruyama
New Year's Resolutions for 2022?
Me! Me! Me!
Do you have one?
Oh? I like your enthusiasm.
Yes!
I want to renovate this bland brown place
into something more fashionable!
Let's make it shinier!
Let's make it sparkly!
That sounds good!
Let's install automatic doors too!
I want this store to... like...
I want Maruyama—
this world to continue.
Yeah.
Right.
That depends on you all.
Let's give it our all!
And we have a customer!
Welcome!
It's Okayu!
So you've come!
Hello!
Name yourself.
Okay!
I'm Nekomata Okayu of hololive Gamers!
Ooh! Her name sounds delicious.
Today's Guest:
Nekomata Okayu
Okayu's here!
Okayu-chan!
Today's guest is the cat with supercat mental fortitude
and excellent luck, Nekomata Okayu!
Nekomata Okayu
Skills: Basically, I'm a jack of all trades
MENT
LUCK
Nekomata Okayu
Finishing Move: Luck Eater
I frivolously suck other people's luck.
(Especially Subaru-chan's!)
What worries does she bring with her today?
I see you don't have much stamina.
It's only one star.
STAM: *
I'm a cat, so I don't have much stamina.
Because you're a cat...?
Aren't cats pretty energetic?
Boss is also a cat.
Bossman, you also
don't have stamina, right?
Frankly, no.
A strange theory is born.
See?
However, your MENT seems to be maxed out.
MENT: *****
I think I'm pretty mentally strong.
Your luck is also good, huh?
My luck is pretty good when Subaru-chan is with me.
LUCK: *****
(Especially when Subaru is there)
Huh?
Boss, listen to this!
How does that work?
Show us!
No! Stop!
Luck Eater!
ARRRGH!
She's draining her luck!
Boss, let's kick her out.
I drain Subaru-chan's luck...
Why only Subaru's?
I think it's because, deep inside,
she wants it drained.
I don't! I want my luck!
Marine, be my meat shield.
Ah, Okayu-senpai, drain me off ♡.
Ah, it doesn't seem to work on you.
Huh? Why?!
When I'm with Okayu, she does the impossible
and gets a comeback victory.
Ah, I see!
So when you're playing games
or doing stuff together,
Yeah!
your chances of victory get drained
and you end up losing.
Yeah.
And this supernatural Nekomata-san
has problems she'd like resolved.
Please tell us what they are!
Okay!
I'm happy I can live every day to the fullest,
Isn't that a good thing?
but since it's so peaceful,
I'd like some more stimulation.
Ah... I see.
I want to add some spice to my life!
Don't be greedy!
Leave it to us!
And there we have our request!
There we have our request!
Thank you!
Nekomata-san's request is, in short,
"I want more stimulation in my life! ♡"
That was not the nuance.
I do!
We have just the thing!
What's happening?
We have the perfect game for you!
Here it is!
The highest selling game in the series!
This popular game's definitive edition
is now on the Nintendo Switch!
There are more than 70 different girls!
Use the familiar Ecstasy Shot
to make the girls swoon!
I can't wait to play it
when it releases on March 17th!
As you just saw, this game,
Gal*Gun: Double Peace comes out
in March! Mark your calendars!
Ooh.
March?
What?
Huh? So this game comes out in March?
Yes, that's right.
Then how will we play it?
She has a point.
Wait, so we can't play?
We can't play it today?
Well, crap.
Shut yer traps!
Flappin' yer lips like sum fishes outta' water!
Wait fer me ta finish, will ya?
Since a new installment is on the way,
Scary...
we'll play Gal*Gun Returns today!
Oh! I see now.
You can try the game out here,
so would you like to play?
Yes! I would love to!
Yay!
We'll play Gal*Gun Returns and...
pierce your heart!
Wait, guys?
Guys?
Were we supposed to do it with you?
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Were we supposed to do it with you?
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
So, Nekomata-san. How confident are you
when it comes to seducing girls?
I don't have any confidence doing that.
Whaaat?
By the way, Boss,
all the hololive girls are
head over heels for Okayu-senpai.
Nekomata Okayu: Popular with the ladies!!
What? Really?
That's not true!
She slides into your girl's DMs.
We'll have the four of them compete
in the Score Attack Mode,
and the winner will get to play a special bonus stage as a reward,
so give it your best shot!
Yaaay!
Time to go all out!
Choose whichever stage you like!
Ooh!
There's a cafeteria—
Wait, there's an indoor pool stage!
Pool?!
I like the pool!
I want to see the pool stage!
In that case,
I'll play the indoor pool stage.
Yaaay!
And we're off!
There's a heart!
What is this?!
You shoot the girls on the screen, like this!
Whoa!
Wow!
It said, "twitch!"
What is this?
Where's your sweet spots?
There's no use hiding!
I'll pierce your heart!
Oh man, what is this?
Something's coming!
Ow! Ow!
The letters are attacks.
Oh, they're not cheering, they're attacking?
I see!
This is, uh...
The letters, huh.
They're love attacks.
If those hit you, you lose health.
I see, so you have to shoot the letters as well.
They're going for the kill!
Get those Ecstasy Shots.
You're really good at doing the Ecstasy Shot.
And there's also—
Ah, "Tell me a joke!"
"Tell me a joke."
We're not comedians.
Keep getting those Ecstasy Shots.
Wow, you're good.
Captain's so good.
Ah, she's saying something.
"I love you, okay?"
O... kay?
All these girls
love me.
Oh, it says Doki Doki Mode!
I can go into Doki Doki Mode.
They're attacking from so far away.
"Pet me!"
Too fast! Too fast!
This looks bad!
This is intense!
The attacks are intense.
Dive in already!
Maybe I should use the Doki Doki Mode.
That's dangerous! Don't run poolside!
I want to use the Doki Doki Mode,
Don't run!
but where to best use it...
I want to wait until there's more people to show off.
Captain's really good.
This is it!
What the heck!
I hit her on the butt.
That angle was risqué!
We're now in Doki Doki Mode!
What is this?
What is this?!
For this...
You get closer with ZR.
What do you think you're zooming in on?!
This is lewd!
How do you like it on your breasts?
You'll have to use
your imagination for this scene <3
This is quite something.
Where are your weak points?
Go for the ass!
The ass?
Let's go for the ass!
Go for the ass!
Thank you!
Where do you want it?
There's no point hiding it!
Please!
Show me her backside!
Thank you!
She's trying to cover it.
What the heck is this?
This is so lewd!
Is it bad if she covers it?
If she covers it,
I can't zoom in on it.
I see!
When she's not covering it,
Oh, so you can't zoom in then.
you get closer, and...
That one was really close-up.
Let's go for the ass.
Ass, please! Ass, please!
Ah, she covered it.
Thank you!
She covered it.
Boss sure loves ass.
She keeps covering it.
Captain's like a seedy cameraman right now.
Yeah.
A little on the head.
So it feels good on the head too.
"Feels good"? Phrasing!
Even closer?
She's getting quite a bit of extra time.
Yeesh!
How's that?
It's so long.
I'll go for your crotch!
This is amazing.
Ah, she's covering it.
Then I'll go for your boobs!
What modest breasts!
What a creep!
Marine's being so creepy, Boss!
The bar's quite filled up.
Captain...
Captain, do we need to edit that out?
We're almost—Huh?
You do realize we're still in the middle
of a hololive Summer ban, right?
Let's gooo!
Nice.
Captain's desires were clear for all to see.
All of you, fall in love now!
This girl will release an Ecstasy Aura
and make everyone fall for me.
This is amazing.
Oh, she's cute.
She's shouting something.
"Hey!"
Crap.
It was dodging quite a bit.
She ran away.
Are you moving the camera, Captain?
Ah, no, the game proceeds on its own.
Oh, so it does it all for you.
It's like one of those 4D shooters at theme parks.
"Let's study together!"
This is so fun!
She's really good.
She's getting pumped up.
It's so fun.
Everyone's so cute.
Oh, it might happen soon.
Those shouts...
The girls—
Ah! It's the teacher!
Teacher!
Oh! Who's that?
Get her! Get her! Get her!
She's not wearing swimwear!
So you can seduce the teachers too...
"Private lessons"!
Private lessons?!
If I get her weak points,
I can get some Ecstasy Shots...
"Private lessons."
Watch out!
That was close!
She's good.
You know...
This game and Marine go really well together.
There!
I didn't know she'd be such a good fit.
Yeah.
She's the perfect fit.
This teacher's pretty tough.
She sure is.
Too close.
Wow.
Did I get her?
I got her!
I seduced her.
Nice!
What is this device?
I wonder.
What is it?
I feel like someone will pop up from behind.
Ah! "We've arrived"!
Stage Clear!
Oh, so that's the goal.
This has to be a lot of points.
I wanted to use Doki Doki Mode one more time.
I wonder...
Yeah.
"Given Euphoria."
"Given Euphoria"?!
Marine's Score: 74,102
Oh my.
"Given Euphoria"?
So this is my score. Rank F. "Popular enough."
So that's what a popular guy's life is like.
I wanted to score higher, but this is it.
I see.
Wow.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
I got that it was quite the game while watching,
Mm-hmm.
but what exactly are we supposed to do?
Right.
I'm sure you saw all the girls appearing
one after the other, because I'm so popular.
I see.
I can't tell if that's the reason.
The girls will scream stuff like, "I love you!"
or try to give you their love letters.
Those are attacks.
Say what?
You can shoot all the letters to erase them,
or shoot just the red letter
to clear the whole thing.
Ah!
Oh!
So you don't have to shoot all of it.
When you aim at the girls,
a "Badump!" might appear on the screen.
Ah! I saw "Hnng!" too.
When that appears, shoot them
at that spot with the A button
to get an Ecstasy Shot.
Huh. An Ecstasy Shot!
An Ecstasy Shot, got it.
When you chain that on multiple girls,
you can form an Ecstasy Shot combo.
I see.
What even is an Ecstasy Shot?
So you give them euphoria with an Ecstasy Shot?
Exactamento!
I see...
I see!
As you give these girls euphoria,
it fills up the heart on the bottom right.
Oh! It did.
That lets you enter Doki Doki Mode.
If you use that, you move to
a place with just the two of you.
Is that what the place with
just the girl in the swimsuit was?
You'll have to use
your imagination for this scene <3
That's right.
So that's why you were taking shots of her ass.
Yes.
Who wants to go next?
I do!
Subaru!
Oh!
I want to go next!
Huh? But like...
can you even make girls feel good, Subaru?
That's right!
Is it even possible?
She seems self-centered.
That's not true!
What are we even talking about?
Is this about the game or me?
What situation, or rather, place
does Subaru want to play?
Hmm...
Maybe the school ground.
Ooh! That sounds good.
We may see some bloomers.
Nice.
Leave it to me.
Where will they come from?
We're starting from the parking lot?
Where—
Eek! That's scary!
They're in bloomers! So cute!
Aim carefully!
Nice job! Ecstasy Shot!
She's doing good!
Ah, crap!
Ooh!
She's getting those red letters!
Ah! She's twitching!
Ecstasy Shot x3!
This is scary!
Teacher!
Oh, geez.
I'm tellin' you, that's scary! Stop!
Doing great, getting the letters too.
They're so close.
She's cute!
So these aren't Ecstasy Shots.
They're so cute.
By the way, you can use
the Doki Doki Mode now,
Already?
so if you find someone you like,
or a good place to use it.
Oh! Here we go!
Here we go.
Ecstasy...
This is the Doki Doki Mode.
Ah! She's in the disciplinary committee!
She's cute.
She's got a headband.
You can get closer with ZR.
Ah!
So you get close and fire!
Whoa, is that fine? I'm getting worried.
Oh? Her heart's thumping.
Whoa!
You'll have to use
your imagination for this scene <3
Wow!
Subaru-chan, you perv!
It's her ass!
Ahhh!
This...
You can do precise camera controls too
with this one.
I kind of feel guilty about this...
Don't hold back.
Yeah...
You don't get many chances
to do these kinds of things.
That's right!
You've got time.
Ah, she covered it.
Eek!
Nice angle!
The meter on the bottom right is your time limit,
Subaru-chan!
so fill the gauge on the left up before it ends.
Wait, that's pretty hard!
You can do it!
Fill it up little by little.
She actually guards!
Aiming at her butt.
You're doing great!
Is she a class president or something?
Her armband says "disciplinary committee."
The head works too?
Yeah, you can.
Let's go for the viable places.
I'll go for anywhere I can.
Cute!
Her head is wide open!
I found a good spot!
It's not very...
The head doesn't raise the left bar that much—
You'll have to use
your imagination for this scene <3
Ah, I see.
So it's better to hit her weak spots.
Ah... I see.
How about her butt?
The butt raised it!
It raised it a ton.
There's no time!
Crap!
That's so difficult!
The places you focused on
weren't very good that time.
I see.
You have to hit where they like it.
It's the thing where everyone gets done in.
Unless you fill up the bar all the way,
it doesn't get everyone.
That girl's cute.
I see.
She's cute.
Ah, it's the teacher again!
It's the teacher!
Teach!
She's fast af.
Ah! She's scolding us.
She's reprimanding us.
She is. That hurt.
Now we gaze up at the sky.
What?
What was that shot?
Stage Clear!
Why were we gazing up at the sky?
So, Subaru's final score is this.
That was difficult!
There it is.
Subaru's Score: 53,048
It's pretty close to Captain's score.
It is. It's pretty high.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
It is. It's pretty high.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
I suppose it's time to switch!
Who wants to go next?
I do! I want to go next!
Go get 'em!
What stage would you like?
I like music, so I'll pick the music room!
Oh, sounds good!
I wonder who we'll see.
It's the music room!
This brings me back!
Come at me.
There they are!
An Ecstasy Shot, nice!
She's cute!
Nice Ecstasy Shot!
Ah! That's cute!
They're behind the drum!
There's twins!
Nice.
They're behind the drum.
Cute!
Cute.
Oh, wow.
They're playing whack-a-mole!
Whack-a-mole...
You can use Doki Doki Mode.
That's too fast!
Aim for the red letters!
This is hard!
You can use Doki Doki Mode
on someone with X.
Oh, who should I use it on...
"Over here!"
This girl...
Let's see...
You can get a bunch of points right now!
It's your chance to use it!
This is it!
Press X!
X!
X.
Oh! There we go!
Look for her weak points.
Pay attention to how much the left bar rises.
Cute.
Roger!
This girl's cute.
You can use ZR to get closer,
so once you get as close as you can, you fire.
You'll have to use
your imagination for this scene <3
Zoom in and pop.
I see!
Just like that.
Whoa!
The controller shakes!
Yeah.
Oh! Nice.
The butt is worth a lot.
That filled it up quite a bit.
This might be tough.
Oh! that's a lot of points!
Wow!
Pretty good.
When the "Badump!" is big,
it's usually a weak point.
I see.
You're right!
Oh! When it's like this!
I see!
Good advice.
Whoa, pan—
She said pan—
That part's not that big.
You're on a good pace!
I'm not sure if this part's good.
Look for somewhere with big letters!
Almost visible... Yes!
Ah!
What the heck is this game?
Like... this!
Oh! It's almost full!
Close! Almost full!
It's almost full!
We can see it!
Once it's filled up, you can press
X again to make everyone melt.
Nice!
I see!
That was good!
Okay, got it.
That was good.
I think you got everyone with that.
Whoa!
Whoa! Nice!
What the heck is this?
Perfectly in sync!
What was that synchronization?
That's the FPS Queen for you.
She's really good!
You're doing great, Towa-sama.
Am I doing good?
Really good!
That was really good!
She's so fast at getting those letters!
So fast! So good!
Towa-sama, your Doki Doki Mode
gauge is filled up already!
She improves so fast.
Come at me!
C'mon! I gotta use my Doki Doki Mode!
Someone! Anyone!
Come at me!
Is it over?
Come on!
It might be over! Oh no!
Someone come!
One more!
There's some more!
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Let's go!
Nice!
Nice.
It's the second one!
We've got our 2nd Doki Doki Mode!
I've mastered this.
Let's look for the big letters.
You'll have to use
your imagination for this scene <3
Right there!
Oh? It's pretty big.
Right here!
Oh, nice.
Is that her weak spot?
The letters there are huge!
Let's get the bottom!
When she starts covering parts,
go for somewhere else.
Okay.
I see.
Her butt doesn't seem worth much.
I've mastered this low angle.
Oh?
She's got the low angle down.
I've mastered it.
She's going for the low-angled butt shot!
Towa's changed.
Just a little more!
Towa's so good at this.
She is.
Ah! She covered it!
This b*tch! Covering it up!
You're scaring me, Towa...
How violent.
Stop covering it!
Show me your ass!
It's full!
Let's get it!
Towa's so good!
She's so good.
Towa's amazing!
She's got talent for this.
She's insanely perverted.
That doesn't sound like a compliment.
The girl next to her will get hit too.
This looks like a good run.
This looks good.
This will be quite high.
She's really good, no cap.
She's so good.
So many came out!
Her aim is on point.
Her aim's really good.
Is it?
Is it over?
Stage Clear!
This seems like a high score!
High expectations for this.
This has to be pretty high.
Huh?
Towa's Score: 43,419
What?!
Huh?
What?
This is... because her Ecstasy Shot
chaining was pretty bad.
Whaaat?!
I thought I got a lot of them.
I see...
I thought she was doing really good.
Does this mean she was being self-centered?
Right.
The girls weren't a big fan
of Towa's violent side.
Ah... I see...
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
With our runs as a reference...
Now the popular one's attempt.
Yeah.
Show us your full power.
What stage will you pick?
I like reserved girls, so I'll go with the library!
Oh?
Gotta be quiet there, yeah.
It started!
Where will they come from?
There's one!
There she is!
They're hiding!
This place has a lot of hiding spots.
Her shooting is so violent!
Okayu-senpai's shots are...
Her aiming is so lively.
It's so violent.
They're above too.
Wow.
Getting Ecstasy Shots is pretty hard.
Yeah.
Go for where the letters are coming from.
Nice!
She's so good!
That was good!
You have a six combo right now!
There's the seven combo!
Speed bonus!
I'll use the Doki Doki Mode when there's a lot.
That seems like a lot of points.
Nice.
Nice start.
Come at me!
Your Doki Doki Mode is
available now as well.
It'll be good to wait until
there's a lot of people around.
I want to use it when there's a lot of people.
Right. They're kind of...
They're just coming one by one.
Yeah.
It's a library, so...
You have two Doki Doki Modes saved up.
Oh, wow.
Ah! Now's the perfect time!
When they all show up.
Go, go!
Nice!
All right!
She's cute!
She is!
You're cute.
Zoooooom... Here!
You'll have to use
your imagination for this scene <3
That's good!
Nice. Ah, she's excited about this part too.
"She's excited about this part too."
She sounds like a perverted old man...
Old Lecher Nekomata...
She's hiding it!
She's peeking in the gaps.
I can't help wanting to see
what's hidden. It's a part of life.
Wut u talkin' bout.
It's filling up quite nicely.
Okayu's so lively.
Oh, nice!
Oh, what about here?
This part might be...
It's her panties!
So cute! She's got polka dots.
"She's got polka dots."
It's polka dots!
Old Lecher Nekomata...
Old Lecher Nekomata! That's not good!
Are you sure you want
to show me all this?
What about your nape?
Her nape!
How about your armpits?
Hey...
Do the armpits count too?
What about her breasts?
She's a bona fide pervert!
Her breasts don't give much.
I guess it's this place after all?
It's the crotch, huh?
Ah, it's this place after all, huh.
Ah! There we go!
Go!
Captain, "It's the crotch" is a bit too direct.
That should get all of them.
Let's get all of them!
There's no use hiding!
Take that!
It's pretty big that you got all of them.
Nice.
There's some rainbow, too.
You're right! We've got
some fever time going on.
It's fever time!
What is this?
Ah! It's the teacher!
The teacher's worth a lot!
Where do you like it, teacher?
Ah, here, huh?
I want to see the close up for the teacher.
Yeah. I want to go for that.
I'll try it after the gauge is full.
It's full!
Teacher, come at me!
Teach!
Will the teacher show up?
Teach, let's get cozy!
Will she come?
She's got glasses!
You're right!
Ah! It's a teacher!
It's the teacher!
Is she a teacher?
Isn't she the student rep?
Is she?
Isn't she a teacher?
She's cute though, so I don't really care.
She's a teacher!
You'll have to use
your imagination for this scene <3
Oh, she is!
She's really cute!
She's got tights on.
Find her weak points!
She's pretty tough!
Her gauge isn't filling that much.
So the teacher's difficult.
She's quite the opponent.
She hides a lot.
She does.
Her defense is impeccable!
She's still got her senses.
This is hard!
Teacher...
Ah... this is difficult.
This lesson is too difficult.
This is difficult.
This is my chance! Her ass is wide open!
Coming in through from the front.
Nice!
Even when you're already zooming,
if she covers it, it cancels.
Ah!
Is that how it works?
There's no time left!
You can do it!
Faster! Faster!
Okay, okay.
You can do it!
You got this!
She's defending!
She's protecting everything!
Why is she so hard to get?!
Ah! Teacher!
Teacher's defense is too high!
Too bad.
She's too strong!
"You can't!"
Her defense was too high.
The teacher's quite formidable.
Teacher's too strong.
Even though she knows she wants it.
What's with you?
Stage Clear!
Yaaay!
Perfect!
This might be pretty high.
This seems good.
Wow!
Whoa! Amazing!
Okayu's Score: 93,423
Amazing!
I got quite a lot!
That was the highest score.
Yaaay!
Living up to her reputation.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
First is Okayu-chan!
Yaaay!
Wow!
She was really good.
93,423 points! A nearly 20K gap!
Wow!
Yay!
She had the moves of a pro.
I'm a girl, so I know what makes girls tick.
She's saying some perverted stuff.
For our winner, Okayu-chan,
we'll have her try the Doki Doki Carnival
for some more stimulation.
What is that?!
What is that?
Doki Doki Carnival is something
of a bonus stage
where you give euphoria to
as many girls as possible.
Oh?
How do you feel going into this, Okayu-chan?
I'm very excited.
While Okayu-chan's playing, we'll have you three
make the same poses as the girls on the screen,
to double the excitement.
Oh no...
This is hell!
Yay! Yay!
Let's do it!
You'll see how it feels to be me.
Can I leave? I'm starting to get a headache.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
We're now ready to begin the Doki Doki Carnival.
Go ahead, Okayu-chan!
Okay!
Make sure to pose, girls. Okay?
I don't hear a response from the other two.
Being so laid back while we're about to suffer.
You do know who has power
over your body right now, right?
Dammit!
Let's get started!
There's only one person enjoying this.
Oh?
Now, everyone. Pose!
It started!
Look, her ass is in full view!
Come on, show your butts!
Your butts, come on!
Show your ass towards the camera!
And now her head.
Her head!
Okay!
Now the ass again.
The butt!
What is this?
Let's do here too.
C'mon!
New pose.
Marine-senpai's gung-ho about this.
How are you so into this?
She's posing too fast!
Ah♡
There, take this!
Is it here? Do you like it here?
Her panties are showing!
Eek, don't look!
What's wrong, Subaru? You don't seem into it.
Of course I'm not!
Zoom! Zoom!
You're cute!
I'm starting to feel hot!
Wh—
There.
Here, her panties are in full view!
Oh, no♡
The one in the middle is showing them off.
This angle is good!
Nice. And now...
I have to cover it!
Ecstasy!
I'm hearing some suspicious
moans from my side.
I don't like this.
This is torture!
She's getting all into it by herself.
How was it?
It was really fun!
Did you now?
Everyone was so cute.
And you, Subaru?
All I got was that this game is pretty beyond me.
You learned how vast the world is?
I feel like my horizons were broadened.
Yeah.
What did you think, Captain?
Please put me in this game!
Me too! Me too!
You two have fun by yourselves.
Towa and I are going home. Right, Towa?
Let's practice getting shot.
Ahn♡
How was it, Towa?
The Ecstasy scenes got me going.
Please tell us the member who
shined the most, the Twin-crew for today!
Okay!
The Twin-crew for today was...
Subaru-chan!
We don't get to see this side of Subaru often.
I love seeing Subaru-chan
uncomfortable the most!
Right, this b*tch's like this!
Damn it all!
C'mon, Subaru-senpai. She shot you down,
so you've got to do the motions!
I'll pierce your heart!
*Bang*
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Challenge From the Boss:
the Maruyama Championship Season 2!
Yaaay!
At this point, we'll have our customers
try their hand at a minigame.
The one who finishes the season
on top will receive a trophy!
Yaaay!
Season 2's minigame is the
Green Hill Zone Act 1's time attack mode!
Yaaay!
The clear time shown on the
results screen will be your record.
By the way, the one with
the best time currently...
is Suisei-chan, with 36.56 seconds!
So fast!
Okayu-chan, how confident are you?
I haven't played much Sonic,
but I'll give it my best shot!
You can do it!
Let's get right to it!
Okay!
Okayu-senpai's pretty good at anything.
Yeah.
Not at all!
Will she beat the time?
Go! Go!
Let's go!
Vroom!
Ah.
Huh?
Yaaay!
This is...
This is... a new record!
It's a new record!
I died!
It's the Okayu Line!
She's formed the Okayu Line!
Heck yeah!
Yay!
That was the funniest run so far.
No time.
Whaaa!
Will a monster appear and beat the high score?
Nekomata Okayu
Thank you for your patronage!
Tune in next time and see!
Okayu-chan, thanks for coming!
And look forward to it!
Thanks for having me!
See you next time!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
See you next time!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
After Closing
I've asked Marine to stay back this time.
Hello!
Let's give our viewers some
advice with their worries.
From @emusuken on Twitter!
"I pass quite a lot of doves on my commute,
and when I'm waiting for the light to turn green on
the crosswalk, they get on my shoulders and feet.
Huh?!
If I wave them away, they waddle
away slowly as if to say 'Darn it...'
I get embarrassed by the gazes it draws every time it
happens, so I'd love some pointers to make them stop."
Does this kind of thing actually happen?
Boss, is this really something
to feel embarrassed about?
Huh?
If I saw someone like that,
I'd think "Whoa, what a badass."
Right?
Ah, it's the doves again.
Fully embracing it like that, huh?
Like that.
Yeah.
Drawing doves to you is a cool thing,
so commit to acting like a dove whisperer
by carrying around a bird cage
A bird cage?
and always having bird feed on hand.
I don't know about that.
and walk around going like:
You're actively drawing them
to you at that point.
Anyway, we're accepting requests
for advice from you.
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique, personally signed
request fulfilled sticker!
So please send in your submissions!
Send 'em in!
Please send 'em in!
Coo! Coo!
Shoot, there's a dove in here.
Coo!
There's doves in here.