Up top now
te o agete
BLUE CLAPPER
Clap your hands
-PandaBoYremix-
BLUE CLAPPER
Music: PandaBoY
Clap your hands
Up top now
te o agete
Clap your hands,
and let the sound
Clap your hands
umi no mukou made
Clap your hands,
sail across the seas
Clap your hands
todokimasu youni
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
All together now
hora issho ni
Everybody
Clap your hands,
and let the sound
Clap your hands
sora no mukou made
Clap your hands,
echo across the skies
Clap your hands
hibikimasu youni
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
And light the way to our future
hikari sasu bokutachi no mirai
hololive 5th Stars
Let's begin, go diving
hajimeyou ka saa Diving
No point waiting, now's the timing
matte mo imi nai Timing
Make like that fish and
go swimming, swimming
ano sakana mitai ni
Swimming Swimming
Bring closer that lighting
hikiyoseru no Lighting
We still can't see it, maybe
mada mienai yo Maybe
What lies in our path ahead?
kono saki ni wa nani ga aru no?
It may be too soon to take it
mada hayai yo Take it
Till we catch up, we'll be shaking
oitsuku made Shaking
But it might be best to stop
and thinking, thinking
demo tama ni tomatte
Thinking Thinking
We'll make a
difference and change
kaetemiseru Change
Put our best foot forward,
stepping
fumidasu no sa Stepping
And seize my shining dream
tsukandemiseru yo
kirakira My Dream
Until that day comes,
I'll keep my story going
kanau hi made Story tsunagu kara
Because I want you to see it all
datte kimi ni zutto mite hoshii kara
Up top now
te o agete
Clap your hands,
and let the sound
Clap your hands
umi no mukou made
Clap your hands,
sail across the seas
Clap your hands
todokimasu youni
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
All together now
hora issho ni
Everybody
Clap your hands,
and let the sound
Clap your hands
sora no mukou made
Clap your hands,
echo across the skies
Clap your hands
hibikimasu youni
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
And light the way to our future
hikari sasu bokutachi no mirai
hololive 5th Stars
Today, there's no need for braking
kyou wa iranai bureeki
Kick reason to the curb,
to the point of breaking
risei kowase Breaking
24/7, every moment is
perfect timing
nanji demo ii desho?
shirokujichuu
What are you feeling?
kimi wa nani o Feeling?
Kick start it all, sparking
tokihanate Sparking
And unleash into the void
a laser beam
kurayami ni hanatsu reezaa biimu
Light it up and build a stage
hikarasete Stage tsukuru kara
Because I want you to
see it all the more
datte kimi ni
motto mite hoshii kara
Up top now
te o agete
Clap your hands,
and let the sound
Clap your hands
umi no mukou made
Clap your hands,
sail across the seas
Clap your hands
todokimasu youni
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
All together now
hora issho ni
Everybody
Clap your hands,
and let the sound
Clap your hands
sora no mukou made
Clap your hands,
echo across the skies
Clap your hands
hibikimasu youni
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
And start a wave to rock the world
kasanaru Wave sekai o yurase
1 2 3 4 5 6 Do it!
Oh, all good things come
to an end, I know
owari ga aru koto
kurai sudeni I know
But I'm not done
drinking it all in, no, no
demo madamada oyogi tarinai no
Boom!
(BOOM!!!!)
Give me the crazy
Give me crazy
Boom!
(BOOM!!!!)
Don't be lazy
marude lazy?
Boom!
(BOOM!!!!)
As your world and ours collide
jigen mazariau no
Everything will be
dyed a perfect blue
subete nurikaeru BLUE
Everything will be
dyed a perfect blue
subete nurikaeru BLUE
Everything will be
dyed a perfect blue
subete nurikaeru BLUE
Everything will be
dyed a perfect blue
subete nurikaeru BLUE
Everything will be
dyed a perfect blue
subete nurikaeru BLUE
Everything will be
dyed a perfect blue
subete nurikaeru BLUE
Everything will be
dyed a perfect blue
subete nurikaeru BLUE
Everything will be
dyed a perfect blue
subete nurikaeru BLUE
Everything will be
dyed a perfect blue
subete nurikaeru BLUE
Up top now
te o agete
Clap your hands,
and let the sound
Clap your hands
umi no mukou made
Clap your hands,
sail across the seas
Clap your hands
todokimasu youni
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
All together now
hora issho ni
Everybody
Clap your hands,
and let the sound
Clap your hands
sora no mukou made
Clap your hands,
echo across the skies
Clap your hands
hibikimasu youni
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
Clap your hands
te o tatakou
👏👏👏
And light the way to our future
hikari sasu bokutachi no mirai
hololive 5th Stars
Wow oh! Wow oh! oh!
Clap your hands
Oh... I messed up again
a~a mata yacchatta
Wow oh! Wow oh! oh!
It's not like I was hiding it though
kakushiteta wake janai no
Wow oh! Wow oh! oh!
I just didn't mention it
kitto tada ittenai dake
Wow oh! Wow oh! oh!
Because it's too embarrassing.
datte, hazukashii n da mon.
aimai chocolate
-PandaBoYremix-
Music: Junky
I get surprisingly lonely
igai to sabishinbo
I am surprisingly spoiled
igai to amaenbo
I act surprisingly in haste
igai to awatenbo
I am surprisingly a bit shy
igai to tereya
Like a round cloud trail
behind a plane
marui hikoukigumo
Or a cupcake with
its top overflowing
tobidashita kappukeeki
Like conditioning your hair
for the third time
sankaime kondishonaa
Or an extra puzzle piece
amaru pazuru
Floating lightly like a dream
fuwafuwa ukabu yumemigokochi
Counting till I fall asleep
hitotsu hitotsu kazoete
oyasuminasai
Counting till I fall asleep
hitotsu hitotsu kazoete
oyasuminasai
Counting till I fall asleep
hitotsu hitotsu kazoete
oyasuminasai
Counting till I fall asleep
hitotsu hitotsu kazoete
oyasuminasai
This secret feeling
grows inside of me
hisoka ni mebaeta kono kimochi
Don't stare at me like that
massugu mitsumenaide
"What was it again...?"
"nan dakke...///"
I'm sure it can't
be expressed in words
kotoba ni shichau to
kitto sou janai
I get shy and tend to joke around
terechau dake ocharakechau janai
I really don't want to
hide my true feelings
hontou no hontou wa
kakushitai n janai no
Sheesh, it's not like that at all.
mou, sou janai noni na.
I'm not being vague
aimai nan janai
This feeling can't be wrong
kono kimochi wa machigai janai
I promise
yubikiri genman
I'm a pretty clumsy girl
kanari dojikko de
And indecisive at times
yuujuufudan demo
But you'll still come and see me
zettai ni mainichi
Every day without fail, right?
ai ni kitekureru yo ne?
I am surprisingly a bit timid
honrai okubyou de
I am surprisingly a bit of a crybaby
angai nakimushi
But I have never stopped
zenzen kawarazu ni
Thinking all about you!
ganrai kimi bakka!
I fell for you like
it's the most natural thing
atarimae no youni
kyun tte shichau
Without you, I feel so empty
kimi ga inai to gakkari shichau
It really, really makes me so sad
hontou no hontou ni
shonbori shichau wa
I want to see you now...
aitaku nacchau na.
I always regret
koukai bakka shichau
But this time I want to be brave
kono kokoro mo yuuki dashichae
"Calm down, you got this"
kono yubi tomare
You see through
all my weaknesses
yowai tokoro kizukaretari
You see through
all my weaknesses
yowai tokoro kizukaretari
You see through
all my weaknesses
yowai tokoro kizukaretari
You see through
all my weaknesses
yowai tokoro kizukaretari
You see through
all my weaknesses
yowai tokoro kizukaretari
You see through
all my weaknesses
yowai tokoro kizukaretari
You see through
all my weaknesses
yowai tokoro kizukaretari
You see through
all my weaknesses
yowai tokoro kizukaretari
You hold me when I'm lonely
sabishisagoto tsutsumaretari
We always laugh together
itsu made mo warai attari
Despite sometimes
getting into fights
tama ni wa mutto kenka o shitari
But I want you by my side forever
zutto zutto soba ni ite hoshii
...Promise me.
...yakusoku da zo.
"Ahh, I said it..."
"icchatta///"
Maybe this is destined to happen
moshikashitara unmei kamo
Maybe this red thread
of fate connects us
akai ito ga miechau kamo
Maybe you've noticed
my true feelings
hontou no hontou wa
bareteru no kamo
Maybe I have to
avoid your eyes now
me awaserannai kamo
It's not unsure anymore
aimai nante nai
Hey, look at me!
takusan watashi o mitete!
It's a promise!
yubi, kitta!
Wow oh! Wow oh! oh!
yo yo yo yo
kon kon kon kon
Wow oh! Wow oh! oh!
mion mion mion mion
yo yo yo yo
Wow oh! Wow oh! oh!
kon kon kon kon
mion mion mion mion
Wow oh! Wow oh! oh!
yo yo yo yo
kon kon kon kon
Wow oh! Wow oh! oh!
mion mion mion mion
Oni, fox, and canine, in the shrine!
oni kitsune inu jinjaa!
Sing and cheer
utae sawage
The party goes on
utage wa tsuzuku
Break out the Oni'n'Furball Dance
mae onikemodansu
Oni'n'Furball Dance
onikemodansu
ONIKEMODANCE
yo yo yo yo
-PandaBoYremix-
kon kon kon kon
ONIKEMODANCE
-PandaBoYremix-
Music: PandaBoY
mion mion mion mion
Oni, fox, and canine, in the shrine!
oni kitsune inu jinjaa!
Take on a new avatar
on the count of three
hifumi de shichihenge
Gather on the internet
for another night
koyoi mo tsudoe intaanetto
With blessings for your fandom
oshigoto ni sachiare
This here is paradise
koko wa marude tougenkyou
One, two, and a hop, step, jump
isseeno de yoi yoi yoi
These horns light up
the shadows of the night
ukiyo ni kakure tsuno hikaru
Doesn't matter where it leads
docchi demo yoi yoi yoi
Walk your own path
waga michi o ike
Swaying, yearning
yura yurari koikogare
My passions flared up
in an instant
setsuna ni moyuru kono omoi wa
They are yet
a fragmented message
mada wakaranai kedo
May they mature one day
minorasete
And burst out in bloom
sakimidareyo
Humans and beasts,
right this way
ohito mo kemono mo tooryanse
Shrine dogs and foxes,
jump and fly away
komainu kitsune mo tobimaware
Life is so very short
inochi wa mijikashi
So leave a mark,
any way you can
gamushara ni kizame
A parade of good fortune,
backed up by an Oni
ichi fuji ni taka de hyaku wa oni
Hear ye, hear ye,
come one, come all
senkyakubanrai oidemase
It's a festival for the ages
appare omatsuri ja
Shoot for the stars
uchimakure
Sing and cheer
utae sawage
The party goes on
utage wa tsuzuku
Break out the Oni'n'Furball Dance
mae onikemodansu
ha!
yo yo yo yo
kon kon kon kon
mion mion mion mion
Come, come,
let me borrow you for a minute
saa saa ote o haishaku!
Will-o'-the-wisps as my pranks
onibi tobashite itazura shitai
I want to mess and play
with my dear humans
ningensama to dajare asobi
(Ready? Yo!)
(ara yo tto!)
Making a Too Sweet
sign with my hands
oya ni kusuri to nakayubi tsukete
What I wub most is inari sushi
sukoru wa gekikara inarizushi
(Kon!)
(kon!)
Nothing ventured,
nothing canine'd
inu mo arukeba uranai ataru
So I summon you, Hatotaurus!
ideyo shoukan Hatotaurusu
(Yikes, that made me jump!)
(uwaa! bikkuri shita!)
Enough Super Chats!
Stop, stop, stop!
suupaachatto mou yoi yoi
I feel the hopes
vested in those coins
koban o nagete atsu kakeru
So precious, those sweet fools
menkoi aho teetee na
Dreaming the most
innocent of dreams
amaki yumemishi
Drifting in the gentle breeze
fuwa fuwari yasashii kaze
Like the falling of petals
in the spring
karei ni hana ga chireru youni
As sad as it is
sukoshi setsunai kedo
Watch it unfold
mitodokete
And bloom in its place
sakihokoru wa
Specters, idols, or the gods divine
mononoke aidoru kamihotoke
Virtual or real, no borders within
baacharu riaru mo kakinenashi
Wagging our tails
shippo o furimawashi
Let's conquer it all
tenka tsukamou ze
Streaming the world I envision
shinshoufuukei namahousou
No borders, only broader horizons
saku wa naku tomo kisaku wa ari
Load your soul into the barrel
tamashii o komete
And fire away
uchimakure
Sing and cheer
utae sawage
The party goes on
utage wa tsuzuku
Break out the Oni'n'Furball Dance
mae onikemodansu
ha!
Hey, DJ!
I have something to say to you
iitai koto ga aru n da yo
Animal ears sure are the bomb, yo
yappari kemomimi kawaii yo
Wub, wub, wub, wub, big wub
suko suko dai suko yappa suko
Finally, I've found you, my princess
yatto mitsuketa ojousama
Linking the past to the future
kako to mirai o tsunaideku
Pursuing dreams to
the ends of the earth
yume o oikake doko made mo
I love you more
than anything in this world
sekai de ichiban, aishiteru
I love you so much!
a i shi te ru!!!
Jumping, from one
calling to another
shana shanari totsuideku
After the rain falls
in the fox's wedding
kitsunenoyomeiri no ato ni wa
A rainbow will form
niji ga deteiru kara
Bring it all together
tsumugasete
And shine forevermore
sakitsuzukemashou
Dance forevermore
odorimashou
Humans and beasts,
right this way
ohito mo kemono mo tooryanse
Shrine dogs and foxes,
jump and fly away
komainu kitsune mo tobimaware
Life is so very short
inochi wa mijikashi
So leave a mark,
any way you can
gamushara ni kizame
A parade of good fortune,
backed up by an Oni
ichi fuji ni taka de hyaku wa oni
Hear ye, hear ye,
come one, come all
senkyakubanrai oidemase
It's a festival for the ages
appare omatsuri ja
Shoot for the stars
uchimakure
Sing and cheer
utae sawage
The party goes on
utage wa tsuzuku
Break out the Oni'n'Furball Dance
mae onikemodansu
ha!
yo yo yo yo
kon kon kon kon
mion mion mion mion
Oni, fox, and canine, in the shrine!
oni kitsune inu jinjaa!
yo yo yo yo
kon kon kon kon
mion mion mion mion
yo yo yo yo
kon kon kon kon
mion mion mion mion
Oni, fox, and canine, in the shrine!
oni kitsune inu jinjaa!
ha!