It's two days after
Suzune-san hit the transfer student.
It seems she's come to apologize for that...
Heh... Hi...
...
So, like, how ya been? Haha...
S-Suzune-san?
You too, Touka-san.
What's the matter?
Suzune-san, it would be best
if you came right out with it.
I-I know...
Um... What's this about?
R... Remember when I smacked you
the other day?
Huh?
Oh! That was no big deal at all!
I-I'm sorry!
I got carried away and
hit you harder than I meant to!
It's fine, really!
I'd already forgotten about it!
If I may elaborate,
Suzune-san has always
rather lacked finesse...
She really meant no harm.
Honestly, I didn't mind at all!
I mean,
Suzune-san just meant it
as some friendly bonding, right?
E-Exactly!
In that case, will you...
forgive Suzune-san for what she did?
Will you... forgive me?
Of course!
Th-Thank goodness!
See? All you had to do
was explain yourself clearly.
But what Inari said got to me...
What she said?
You mean that rumor
about transfer students?
Y-Yes, that!
See, I'd never heard it before.
Don't you worry. I, for one,
knew about the rumor,
but I don't believe it one bit.
Huh...?
Hm? What's wrong?
Th-The classroom looked all weird...
And there was this girl...
Wh-What's happening?!
I-It's an earthquake!
Everyone take shelter under the desks!
I-Inari! It's okay, we'll be fine!
I-It's all because we mistreated
the transfer student!
Help, Hanabi-chan!
Just calm down! Please!
Ahh!
I-Inari!
I-Inari-san! Hanabi-san!
W-We'll get through this!
I-It's all my fault! All of it!
You two! Get under the desks!
I don't understand...
What is happening right now?
Everything's gone quiet.
All I hear are
ambulance sirens in the distance.
I'm still alive. But the others...
I-Isn't this...
one of the school's hallways?
But why is it intact?
I saw the ceiling collapse,
but there's not
a single piece of rubble...
What's going on?
And where is everyone?!
Th-That's the girl...
I saw in the classroom...
Hey! Who are you?
Did I survive?!
What happened to Aogami High School?
Where is everyone?!
Please... tell me!
So you... must be the transfer student.
Hee-hee.