I'm La+ Darknesss!
Nom nom nom nom.
Nooo!
Year 2222
Taking place in a futuristic virtual space...
It's hololive's Future Sports Test!
She's swaying really hard!
Hello, everybody!
It's me, Shirakami Fubuki!
(Class Rep, 1st Gen, & GAMERS)
Shirakami Fubuki
Are all my dear classmates present?
School sucks!
I'm sleeping here!
5 more minutes...
Y-You're—
You're sleeping?!
Let me reveal today's show!
(Gen 0)
Robocosan
(3rd Gen)
Shiranui Flare
(Secret Society holoX)
La+ Darknesss
Neo-Futuristic Fitness Test
Spring's Virtual Sports Test
The heck
is that?
Virtual?
Vi-Vir— What?
What?! You girls never heard of it?
How do you know of it?
Wh-What is it about?
Sorry, what is this test?
It's the year 2222!
This video is brought to you
from a Virtual Space in 2222.
We're in the future! The future!
Even without fitness gear,
A new era of fitness tests
done entirely in virtual space
we're now able to test your fitness
in this virtual space!
Fubu-chan, what the heck
are you going on about?
What am I going on about?!
I could ask you the same thing!
Here's the first test!
Reverse Gravity
Virtual
Side-to-side Jumps
H-Hang on.
That makes zero sense!
In this test, you'll be riding this machine
during your measurement!
Using this
reverse gravity machine.
This machine
generates reverse gravity in accordance
Futuristic machine that
propels itself forward
using sideways momentum
to you swaying left and right
to propel itself forward!
It's a super
technological machine!
That seems similar to pedaling
a bicycle to generate electricity.
Pretty analog if you ask me.
Nope! This is
super-duper uber tech!
We're in a neo-futuristic setting here.
The Class Rep
shows her mettle?!
Shirakami Fubuki
stirs up a storm!
Here I go!
Time limit: 10 seconds
Ready?
Start!
Whoa.
She doesn't disappoint.
She's going hard at it!
Wow.
Does having longer hair
give you an edge?
Honestly, she's doing amazing.
I'm making progress! I'm inching up!
That definitely doesn't bode well
for your blood pressure.
Whoa!
Shirakami Fubuki's
Record: 28 Times
10 seconds is pretty short.
That's an amazing result!
If you get 28 times or lower
it means you're beneath me.
That's not exactly
a bad thing.
That's not exactly a bad thing?!
Are you even trying?
La+ Darknesss
unleashes her power!
Ready?
Start!
She's swaying!
She's swaying a ton!
She's swaying
really hard!
Seriously, don't you think having
longer hair gives you an edge?
Isn't that cheating, then?
Time's up!
Did she
break the record?
Let's take a look.
I don't think I was the fastest.
Lap-chan's record is...
23 times!
Whyyy?!
Wow! That's great!
Huh?
Whyyy?!
The only thing I had going
for me was flashiness!
Roboco-senpai.
Roboco-senpai!
You're next.
Uh...
Sure...
Surpass the Class Rep!
Robocosan
goes full throttle!
Ready?
Start!
H-Huh?
Th-This ain't right. What the heck?
Is she still groggy?
You've gotta be kidding me!
What's going on here?
Roboco-senpai?
Are you vibing to
music or something?
This isn't a leisurely jog!
Roboco-senpai?
Time's up!
Roboco-senpai!
It's already over, Robocosan!
Roboco-senpai's record is...
14 times!
Robocosan?!
That's half of Fubu-chan's record!
What even is
high-spec now?
Will she set
a new record?!
Shiranui Flare
brings the heat!
What's your
target goal, Flare?
Hmm...
For starters...
10 times, I guess?
What a low bar.
Oh?
Okay, time for Flare's attempt!
Ready?
Start!
Huh?
Wh-Wha—?
Hold on. I'm lagging.
You doing okay?
You can do it!
You're a bit wobbly but you can do it!
She can definitely do it!
Your hair's swaying too!
She's trying her best.
Wait, my mic's
in the way.
Time's up!
She's encountering physical obstacles!
My mic's actually in the way.
Did you stumble onto
an obstacle course?
Flare's record is...
16 times!
Oh!
What?!
Hey, I went over 10!
(Shirakami Fubuki)
Record: 28 Times
(Robocosan)
Record: 14 Times
(Shiranui Flare)
Record: 16 Times
(La+ Darknesss)
Record: 23 Times
Lap-chan tried really hard
but what about the
two senpai over there?!
That's not true at all!
My mic was in the way!
That was a disappointing result
from you two.
Here's the next test!
Virtual
Tonal
Sit-ups
And just what is that?
That's some chaotic naming.
In this test, you'll need to
repeatedly shout your name
A cutting-edge virtual machine
that inflates you when you repeatedly
shout your name in different tones
at a cutting-edge voice sensor.
From your deepest register
How many tones can you create?
to your highest one,
this test measures how well
you can control your tone increments!
That's a tough one.
Aiming for that
second dub!
Shirakami Fubuki
fights to keep her crown!
Okay, time for my attempt!
Here I go!
Okay.
I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
Who the heck are you?!
H-Huh?
That sounds kinda off.
Are you okay?!
I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
Is that how this works?
That's quite the leap.
I've totally got this.
I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
It's getting shriller.
This is just plain amazing.
I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
She's really good!
Whoa!
I'm... Shirakami... Fubuki...
Fubu-chan's dying!
Okay, I see how this works.
Are 10 inflations
the best you can do,
Fubuki-san?
Grrr...
Oh? Lap's taking a flex!
Set that new record!
La+ Darknesss
coming out of the shadows!
Ready?
Start!
I'm La+ Darknesss!
That's one sleazy tone.
Oh, that her usual tone?
Now she's back to normal.
I'm La+ Darknesss!
She sounds cute now.
Wow, that's high.
Aww, she sounds
so adorable!
I'm La+ Darknesss!
That's so cute!
I wanna hug her!
I'm La+ Darknesss!
Now she kinda
ticks me off.
I'm La+ Darknesss!
Okay, now I wanna sock her.
She's going pretty high up.
I'm La+ Darknesss!
Wow, that's really high up there.
Whoa!
I'm La+ Darknesss!
Cough...
blagh...
That's just hell right there.
You okay?
Cough...
blagh...
Ding ding ding!
Cough...
blagh...
Lap-chan's record is...
12 tones!
What?!
Whoa!
Wow!
What an upset!
Dammit! I lost!
(Surpass the
Class Rep!)
She's got faith
in her voice!
Shiranui Flare
lights the fire in her heart!
Ready?
Start!
I'm Shiranui Flare.
Whoa.
That's amazing.
I'm Shiranui Flare.
Wow, that's good.
Ah, now
she sounds normal.
I'm Shiranui Flare.
She's sounding more like
she normally does.
I'm Shiranui Flare.
There we go,
she's back to normal.
I'm Shiranui Flare.
She's regressing
into an infant.
I'm Shiranui Flare.
Oh yes! She's a little girl!
How many points did she get?
What the heck was
that at the end?!
Phew...
This definitely left some scars.
It's pretty hard to top Fubu-chan.
(Surpass the
Class Rep!)
You feeling confident,
Roboco-senpai?
Honestly speaking?
I've got this in the bag!
No way.
Where'd that
confidence come from?!
Robocosan
readies her autotune!
Ready?
Start!
I'm Robocosan!
Ooh, that's a good one.
That pronunciation,
though.
I'm Robocosan!
Oh, she's back
to normal.
I'm Robocosan!
She's doing
pretty awesome.
I'm Robocosan!
That's cute.
That doesn't sound much different.
Agreed.
I'm Robocosan!
That last one's
pretty similar, no?
I'm Robocosan!
It sounds pretty
much the same.
I'm Robocosan!
I'm Robocosan!!!
17 tones!
What?!
Whoa!
I feel like there were
3 Robocosans there.
(Shirakami Fubuki)
Record: 10 Tones
(Robocosan)
Record: 17 Tones
(Shiranui Flare)
Record: 12 Tones
(La+ Darknesss)
The highest record belongs
to Robocosan with 17 tones!
Congratulations!
Yaaay!
Congrats!
Amazing.
Third Test
Virtual
Nomming
Marathon
Nom
Nomming
Marathon?
In this test,
The sensor will fly up
if it recognizes a "Nomming" sound.
you'll be using a cutting-edge
nomming sensor!
What's that?
The heck's that supposed to be?
This test records how long
can you keep nomming in one breath
Basically, you'll fly up high
as long as you keep
making nomming sounds.
Keep nomming away even
if just for a second longer!
Wait, we need to keep it up?
Okay, I see how it is.
By the way,
this test will
be done in pairs.
What?
Okay.
Team Shirakami Fubuki &
Robocosan's Attempt
Fubuki & Robocosan's
Nomming Marathon starts...
Now!
Om nom nom...
I'm not sure
how to feel about this.
Maybe we should give them
something to chew on.
They're so cute.
I wonder...
if we made them laugh...
Nooo!
...would that be unfair?
(Robocosan's Record)
21.9 seconds
Oh!
Fubuki's pretty good!
*Cough*
(Shirakami Fubuki's Record)
26.6 seconds
Fubu-chan's really good at this!
Yeah!
You wanna go next, Lap-chan?
This test was literally
made just for me!
Team Shiranui Flare &
La+ Darknesss' Attempt!
Ready?
Start!
Om nom nom...
I really wanna throw
food into their mouths.
They're getting higher and higher.
It feels good.
It's kinda pleasant to listen to.
Yeah, it feels good.
Wait, what sound
was it again?!
I think they should
be hitting their limits soon?
Huh? Wait, what? Flare?!
(Shiranui Flare's Record)
21.9 seconds
Oh? OH?!
I made so many
nomming sounds
You still in the air, Flare?
My brain couldn't even
process what to say anymore.
Your brain turned into mush, I see.
It was going,
"Papanpanpanamo"!
Lap-chan's still going!
Lap's still hanging on!
She's ascending higher!
It was going,
"Papanpanpanamo"!
Keep going!
Keep going higher!
How high can she go?
Agh!
(La+ Darknesss' Record)
43.6 seconds
43.6 seconds!
Agh!
An astrological record!
WHAT?! THAT'S INSANE!
Whoa! That's amazing!
Reverse Gravity
Side-to-side Jumps
Tonal Sit-ups
Nomming Marathon
Okay!
The member with the
highest physical ability is...
With an overwhelming world record set...
It's La+ Darknesss!
(Honors Student)
La+ Darknesss
Heck yeah!
That was amazing!
You were awesome!
A very great result indeed!
If you enjoyed this video,
please like it and subscribe to the
official hololive YouTube channel
as well as our respective channels!
Please subscribe!