I'm a Watame banner now.
Oh, yeah you are.
Yeah, just like that.
Aiya♪ Esnalabmi♪ Esnalabmi♪
Esnalabmi♪ Esnalabmi♪
Heya♪ Heya♪ Heya♪
It looks like everyone here today
has found themselves in The Upside Down!
What a predicament!
Something is up!
Oh no!
My head feels fuzzy...
I'm upside down!
Huh? Are you all right, Sui-chan?
The blood...
The blood's not reaching my head...
Huh.
Did you just wake up?
Nah, I'm like this
because we're upside down...
Oh, it's because you're
upside down. Gotcha.
*Hoshimachi Suisei just woke up.
Is your hoarse voice also because of this place?
Alas.
Yeah.
I see!
Yeah, it's because I'm upside down.
I guess I can't argue with that.
*Just woke up.
In order to escape from The Upside Down,
you'll need to figure out
the correct version
of the backwards terms
that you'll be given!
The more you get right,
the more you'll pivot
to your upright position!
That's how this works.
Pivot...
So this one requires brains, huh.
Lemme take notes.
Let us take notes!
Note-taking is cheating!
She's got a point.
Let's start with Fubuki-san!
Okay!
Good luck, Fubu-chan!
Puzzle #1!
Looks.
Loo?
What could it be?
Oh, school!
School! Yes!
School is correct.
Let's move on.
My angle!
She's coming back!
My angle's going!
Shid-ar dlekc-ip.
Shid-ar?
Shi-dar dlekc-ip.
Pickled radish!
Shid-ar dlekc—
That's correct!
Gotcha.
She's getting closer
to her normal angle!
Slowly but surely!
I'm steadily returning!
Eefwak.
Coffee!
Coffee is correct!
Woohoo!
I'm steadily becoming sideways!
You're almost on your side!
Keep at it, Fubu-chan!
Mh-ree-uts vh-ial.
Huh?
Hm?
What could it be?
What is it?!
Live stream!
Live stream is correct.
Oh! Gotcha gotcha.
You're just one step away
from being sideways now.
Whoa.
Mh-ree-uts vh-ial.
Ott-ahk-ats.
Ottahk Ats sounds like
it might be a place.
Ott-ahk-ats.
Three!
Two!
One!
Too bad!
Huh? Wait!
Ott-ahk-ats, sta...
It was staccato!
Oh! Staccato!
It was staccato.
Staccato, huh.
That's so hard!
It looks like you won't be able to
make it back upright anymore.
No way!
Oh no!
Gh-hab nihc-nup.
Huh?
Gh-hab, gh-hab gh-nihc-nup...
Punching bag! Punching bag!
Punching bag is correct!
Thank goodness!
Oh, I'm sideways!
Whoa!
Looks like you've made it
back on your side.
Sideways!
You look like a banner now.
Oh, I can see that.
She's right! I'm a banner now...
You two should join me!
Dh-yw dh-na raf.
Huh?
What could it be?
Far and wide, far and wide!
Far and wi-wide!
Far and wide is correct!
That one I know!
I've graduated from being a banner.
Laugniliab.
Laug...
Huh?
Laugniliab.
B...
Three!
Two!
Bi...
Bilingual?
Bilingual is correct!
Gotcha!
Bilingual!
Bilingual is correct!
Oh, wow!
Bilingual!
Lasreher touhtiw ghnitka.
Huh?
Actin...
Out with her, she said.
Try reading it backwards.
Acting without rehearsal!
That is correct!
She's coming back!
Whoa.
She's leaving us behind.
Time for the last puzzle.
Don't leave us!
Hknab lartnes.
Lard?
Five!
Huh?
Four!
Hold on.
Hknab lartnes?
Three!
Hknab lartnes...?
Two!
One!
What is it?
Huh?
Hold on!
Time's up!
Ult—
Hold on!
Fubu-chan!
Lard's all I could think of!
Central...
Oh, it was a soft C.
Central Bank?
Central Bank it was!
It was Central Bank, huh.
Who'd get that?
I wasn't expecting a soft C!
Hknab lartnes...
With eight puzzles solved correctly,
she's effectively back
in her normal world.
I look like the Leaning Tower of Pisa...
But you're still a little oblique.
She's a little crooked!
It looks like I'm about
to be stabbed into something.
Stabbed?!
Because of this slant.
Moving on, let's have
Sui-chan try to escape!
Okay.
I'll do my best.
Let's get started!
Lodia.
Lodia...
Idol!
Idol is correct!
I can't believe
Sui-chan's also slanted...
She's coming back!
Don't leave me behind!
See ya.
Nietorp.
Huh? N...
Protein.
Protein is correct.
Yes!
Ecnegludni.
Yes.
Ecnegludni?
Ecne...
Again, ecnegludni.
Huh?
Ecnegludni?
Indulgence.
Indulgence is correct!
Oh...
My brain cells are revving up!
They're revving up? Whoa.
Whoa!
Your voice sounds softer, too,
like it's gone up a notch.
Droker dlrow.
Hm? Droker dlrow?
Yes.
Droker dlrow...
World record.
World record is correct.
That was quick!
Good job.
Woohoo!
Tezolk.
What? Tezolk...
Tezolk...
Yep.
Closet.
Closet is correct!
Easy-peasy.
Whoa!
Nice.
You're sideways now!
Bring it.
She's gonna fall asleep—
Good night!
Sui-chan's fallen asleep!
Hey, don't fall asleep!
Goodnight!
Gab lbazuyer.
Reusable bag!
Reusable bag is correct!
That was really quick.
Easy!
The blood's flowing again!
So fast!
Flowing!
Nevee tegut.
What...?
Tegut?
Neve...
This sounds like
something you'd do.
To get...
Five!
Neve...
Four!
Three!
To get even.
To get even is correct!
Looks like Watame-san figured it out.
I've woken up now
and so my voice has gotten cuter.
That was sudden.
She's gotten cuter all of a sudden.
Is the effect really that great?
Emag laviavrus.
Viavrus...
It kind of sounds like a plant name.
Ema...
You said "ema," right?
Oh, I've got it.
Yeah, "ema".
Emag laviavrus.
I'm sure those who know, love it.
Yeah, I love these.
Laviav...
You love them, huh?
Survival game.
Survival game is correct.
Whew!
That was quick.
Two questions left to go!
Wowie!
I'm coming for you, my home world!
Repyep uhsit.
Huh, I don't get it at all.
Robitussin?
That's totally not it!
Repyep uhsit.
Uhsit...
What is it?
It has a soft letter, too.
The backwards version
sounds hard to say.
A few of them, actually.
Uhsit...
Repyep uhsit.
Oh, tissue paper?
Tissue paper is correct!
What? Whoa!
Excellent job!
Oh, wow.
That was so hard!
You're one question away from an A+!
Oh dear!
Sui-chan the Flawless?!
Secivres lakidem ysnegreme.
That's so lengthy!
Dem ysnegreme?
Yeah!
It's kinda weird.
Dem ysnegreme...
Is that a foreign word?
Lackdem... Laki...
Five!
Is that English?
Four!
Emergency...
What a funny word.
Three!
Em... Emergency...
Oh?
Two!
Emergency... Emergency...
One!
Too bad! I guess the last one
must've been too hard.
You solved 9 puzzles correctly!
By the way,
did you two figure it out?
Something about an emergency?
Oh?
Emergency?
Emergency medical services?
It was indeed
emergency medical services!
So that's what it was!
That's so hard!
So this means I didn't manage
to completely wake myself up, huh?
But you made it 90% of the way!
If Watame-san makes it to 100%,
you'll look kinda like falling dominoes.
Oh, I can see that.
I think I'll be the pillar
that stops these dominoes!
Stop them? Be my guest!
Puzzle #1.
Nomel.
Nomel?
Yes, nomel.
Lemon!
Lemon! Good going!
Woohoo!
Edyenomel.
Okay!
Huh?
Edyenomel?
Lemonade.
Lemonade is correct!
Nice.
Lssum.
Lssum?
Yes.
Muscle.
Muscle! Good job!
Muscle!
Muscle.
Lssum!
Muscle!
Gninrom doog.
Huh?
Gninrom...doog?
Gninrom...
The Eight Dogs.
Watame and the Eight Dogs.
That sounds cute.
The Eight Dogs!
An alternative pronunciation
could be "ninrom doog," too.
Oh.
Good mornin'?
Yes! Good morning it is.
I see!
Yep.
Good morning!
Noitcif tluda gnuoy.
This one's long!
Yoyung?
Scimoc tluda gnuoy.
Young...
Scimoc tluda?
Young scimoc tluda...?
Young adult comics!
Young adult comics is correct!
I made it!
I'm a Watame banner now.
Oh, yeah you are.
A Watame banner.
Nibj ebrag.
Nibj ebrag?
Nibj ebrag...
Huh?
Oh, Nibj ebrag, huh?
Yeah?
Garbag nobie?
Nibj ebrag.
Garbage bin!
Garbage bin is correct!
Nice.
Esnalabmi.
What is this?
Esna♪ Labmi♪ Ah♪
Esnalabmi.
What country is that?
Yeah, just like that.
Aiya♪ Esnalabmi♪ Esnalabmi♪
Esnalabmi♪ Esnalabmi♪
Heya♪ Heya♪ Heya♪
Haiya♪ Haiya♪ Haiya♪
She's getting distracted by the song...
Ahh, my thoughts!
Labmi?
Labmi.
Imbal?
Yes.
Imbal...ance...?
Imbalance!
What is this?
Imbalance.
Oh, right, imbalance!
Imbalance!
Imba♪ rance♪
Imba♪
That sounds like an actual chant.
Htgnerts lakiretsyh.
What? What even is that?
Oh, I figured it out.
Hysterical...
Five!
Hysterical strength?
Yes! That's correct!
Hysterical strength, in action!
She's almost there!
Almost!
Two more puzzles!
Looking good!
SPR ikamonust.
What?
Esper...Tsunomaki?
Oh?
Five!
Tsunomaki R...
Four!
Three!
Tsunomaki RPS!
Tsunomaki RPS is correct!
Oh, wow!
I'm getting there!
Let's move on to the last one.
Rviard iksat.
Irdixat?
Tax...
Huh?
Five!
Oh, I got it!
Taxi...
Four!
Taxi driver?
Three!
That is correct!
Watame aces the test!
Woohoo!
Ah, she stopped us!
Stellar answering there,
Watame-san.
As you are back
to your upright position,
you've successfully escaped
from The Upside Down!
Congratulations!
Yay!
I'm so glad!
She halted us, too.
I'll hold my ground
against the dominoes!
It stopped!
Your formation looks really uniform.
She stopped us!
Congratulations, again.
I stopped you all!
If you enjoyed this video,
please click the Like button
and follow the official hololive channel
as well as the channels of these girls!
Ay ees!
Starring
Hoshimachi Suisei
Shirakami Fubuki
Tsunomaki Watame
Escape from The Upside Down,
brought to you by Hoshimachi Suisei...
...Shirakami Fubuki, and...
...Tsunomaki Watame!