It's almost two!
Are you ready to alarm?!
Nice! That's the way!
That's the rhythm!
She's regained her spirit
as sports team manager!
Uh, but why's she talking to a clock?
Some days you just want to!
Isn't that alarm set rather late?
Nobody in hololive is a morning person.
Now!
Quiet! I'm trying to sweep!
What a horrible injury...
You won't recover in time for the summer tourney...
Then you enter in its pwace.
Birdman Rally
This is the tourney she was talking about?
Aight!
Those wings are cwearly souped up.
Is nobody going to stop her?
Go for it, Suba-chan!
I'm gonna win this thing.
Here I go!
That can't be right.
Entering the stratosphere!
Not yet! Almost there!
Oh, really?
Okay, okay.
Entering the stratosphere!
Not yet, but almost there!
Urk.
How about now?
Almost there!
I've been "almost there" for ages!
Now, now, now!
That's the stratosphere!
Huh?!
You can't just drop that on me...
Gaaah!
She's out of radio range...
Suba-chan became part
of the ozone layer.
Say, "So she's Oozona Subaru now?"
Huh? So she's Oozona Subaru now?
Nice.
What?
Got it.
You got DQ'd for cheating!
She went straight up and down,
so her glide distance wasn't great either.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!