You better remember this!
Bomber!
It felt good...
It felt good?! Really?
Explosion in T-minus 50 Kana!
Explosion in T-minus 50 Kana
Shiritori Bomber
Shiritori Bomber!
Yaaay!
Sorry to spoil
everyone's excitement here,
but please take a look behind you!
Huh?
What?
What the heck?!
So here is our
totally cliché bomb.
It's massive!
In order to dispose of this bomb,
Bomb disposal experts
I have called for what may be
our best bomb disposal squad.
As a researcher,
I am well-versed in
the handling of explosives!
I see!
That makes sense!
If you see a red and blue wire,
you always cut blue!
There is always only one truth!
I'm Hakui Koyori!
Secret Society holoX
Hakui Koyori
Did I Luive you all waiting?
From hololive 6th gen,
I'm holoX's XO,
Secret Society holoX
Takane Lui
Takane Lui!
The holoX base gets deliveries
for explosives all the time,
Really?! That's dangerous!
so leave this job to me!
The usual.
Is that alright...?
I'm hololive Gen 0's
virtual robot,
hololive Gen 0
Robocosan
Roboco!
I'd say I have...
...quite a history
with explosives...
Anyway, our amazing
bomb disposal team
has to dispose of this bomb
through a game of shiritori.
Sh... Shiritori?!
Yes.
Well, that's lame.
For this particular game,
the bomb will explode once
the chain reaches 50 characters.
Yep.
Wait, so once someone
reaches the 50-kana mark,
that person will have the bomb
blow up in their face.
Yes.
Is that right?
Exactly.
Huh?! Hold on!
No way!
No!
This'll be brute-force play!
No one-kana words allowed,
by the way.
Since they're, well, you know...
Two kana above are fine?
Yes!
Okay!
Let's disarm the first bomb!
First bomb?
First? Are there more?
There's more than one bomb?
Mmm, well.
The order will go as:
Robocosan → Lui-san → Koyori-san.
Okay!
Let's get started.
ba-ku-da-n-shi-yo-ri
Bomb disposal, good choice.
Whoa, that's clean.
It is.
Gotta start with this one.
A true starter choice.
ri-su
Squirrel!
A cute pick.
Cute.
su-shi
Sushi!
That's nice.
We got a normal game of shiritori going.
Hmm?
Are you guys sure you wanna
keep doing 2-kana words?
I've only been thinking
of stuff I want to eat.
So you're already hungry, I see.
If you're playing that game, then...
Robocosan is making her move?
shi...
shi-ma-ri-su
Chipmunk!
It wasn't that long!
Not that long!
Not too long of a word.
su-ru-me-i-ka
Oh! Flying squid!
ka-re-e-ra-i-su
(curry rice)
Going full-on on the su, I see.
Yes!
It's definitely the su strategy.
She's going in with that.
su-su-su...
su-zu-me
Sparrow!
me!
That's another cute animal.
Umm.
me-i-ji-o-bu-vu-a-i-o-re-t-to
(MAGE OF VIOLET)
Murasaki Shion's original song
This is Shion-senpai's...
Oh, the song!
Oh, okay!
...original song!
It's her original song!
We're throwing around songs now...
It makes sense.
It's so long!
Wow!
That's actually cool!
Real good angle of attack.
She suddenly got more aggressive...
This might be edging it close, but...
If there's one thing
that starts with to...
It's to-ki-no-so-ra!
Okay!
Tokino Sora!
R-R-R-Roboco-senpai?!
Umm...
What do I do?
How should I do it?
Fate Sealed
Well, I guess...
My answer is...
Wait.
Two kana...
ra-ra
ra-ji-o
Radio!
Ehhhh?!
Yep, she went for radio!
Hooray!
Any last words?
Senpai...
I apologize in advance
if I sound harsh but...
You better remember this!
Bomber!
You went a bit too hard
with MAGE OF VIOLET.
Any comment, Takane Lui-san?
It felt good...
It felt good?! Really?
That's crazy!
Really now?
So it felt good...
Was this bomb
laced with any weird stuff?
Are you fine?
Bomb Disposal
Round 2
Let's have the order be:
Koyori-san → Lui-san → Robocosan.
Sure thing!
Understood!
Shiritori Bomber, start!
Alright!
Let's start off with everyone's
yu-u-ji-n-e-i
(Friend A)
Thanks for the shout-out!
Starting from i, huh...
Was there any long word
that started with i...?
She's going for another long one!
You can go shorter, you know?
She's going all out!
On the full offensive.
i-ki-ri-chi-ra-shi-ta-ko-yo-ri
(Enraged Koyori)
An enraged...
Hold on!
She's pointing to Koyori-san.
What did you say?
Isn't this an invalid answer?
As long as it's grammatical,
then it should be valid.
So this gets a pass.
She says it's valid.
How cheap!
So even this gets a pass?!
Okay then.
ri-ri-shi-i-fu-ri-wo-shi-ta-ru-i-ne-e
(Faux-elegent Lui)
A faux-elegant...
This is threading the line
between praise and insult.
It's praise! Praise!
You sure?
I definitely don't hear it as such!
Are there still enough kana?
Okay, I'll go for it.
e-ga-o-de ko-u-ha-i-wo
(Juniors swooning before)
This is bad...
Aren't you going too hard?
Wait. Stop! Hold it!
Are you sure about this?
You'll be the one blowing up.
o-to-shi?
Will she make it?
o-to-su
(the smile)
o-to-su!
ro-bo-ko
(of Roboco)
Roboco! Okay!
You've pushed it way too far!
That was a long one!
I made it!
That's 44 kana filled up!
This ain't good.
We're in trouble.
Okay.
Let's do this.
This is in Lui-san's hands now.
I believe in you, Lui.
Remember our bonds as holoX!
Who will she pick?
You have my back!
One or the other
Our bonds!
ko-o-ri
(Ice)
Huh? What?
ri-ku
What happened to our bonds?
Landmass...
Wha...
We've already filled up 49 kana...
Any last words, Koyori-san?
It's your turn, Koyori.
ku-ji-ke-na-i-ko-ko-ro
(An unfaltering spirit!)
Bomber!
LuiLui! How could you?!
Blowing up felt
really good, though.
Look at this masochist!
Bomb Disposal
Final Round
For our final game, let's go with
Lui-san → Robocosan → Koyori-san.
The order's been mixed up, huh?
Yep.
You can start anytime, Lui-san.
If there's one person
in hololive with
a really long name,
it has to be our Founder,
ra-pu-ra-su-da-a-ku-ne-su
Oh, I see!
So long!
Laplus Darknesss, with no spaces.
Damn, it's long.
We'll take it.
Hmm, well then.
su-ka-n-ku
Skunk!
It sounds as if Lap-chan
smells like a skunk...
Nah, it's just her room.
I blew up with this phrase last time,
but in order to face this bomb head-on,
I must have
ku-ji-ke-na-i-ko-ko-ro
(an unfaltering spirit)
An unfaltering spirit!
That makes sense.
Hmm...
Oh.
Ah.
Huh.
Okay.
I'll be going for this.
Is that alright?
Sure.
Sure thing.
She got it.
ro-bo-ko
Don't forget the san!
That's my answer!
She wants the san at the end!
Though I kinda like
this level of intimacy.
Oh, you like it?
She looks happy.
In that case, I'll go with
ko-yo-ri
My, oh my!
Right?
Mutual no-honorific policy, huh?
How sweet!
How sweet.
Hmm, ri?
Yep.
Hrmm.
ri-su-se-n-pa-i
That works!
Taking from
Ayunda Risu-san's first name.
Dropping honorifics here,
but I'll go with
No problem with that.
i-nu-ga-mi-ko-ro-ne
I'm sure Risu-san
will be delighted with this.
They actually link well!
ne-ne
Nene!
That's a pretty short answer!
Was that a good choice?
Nene-senpai!
Are you sure about this?
Let's do this.
This is fine.
We can do this.
I'll go for it.
What's your pick?
This should be good!
Go!
ne-po-ra-bo
Oh! It's NePoLaBo!
At this point,
which of the two
will get the bomb?
Remember our bonds?
Hey, stop that!
Hey!
Stop!
Time out!
Well then.
It's time to leave them...
bo-c-chi
(alone.)
Alone!
Oh, dear!
Robocosan, this really
All alone, with one slot left.
suits you the best!
chi-ku-shi-yo-u
(Damn you all!)
Bomber!
That was a nice and vibrant explosion.
How did it feel having
to do bomb disposal?
She cornered me at first,
but LuiLui and I managed
to form a trustworthy bond after.
That you did!
So I'd say I had a lot of fun!
Great to hear!
Hmph, well, I got
a bit closer to Lui too,
so I guess I had fun too.
Am I the rope in this tug-of-war?
Seems like it.
Not that I'm complaining.
If you enjoyed this video,
please consider leaving a like
and subscribe to our official
and talent channels!
Starring
Hakui Koyori
Takane Lui
Robocosan
Shiritori Bomber was
brought to you by Hakui Koyori...
...Takane Lui, and...
...Robocosan!