This is a recap episode?
Why don't we take a look back
at hologra over the past six months?
Without further ado,
Top 10 hologra Scenes That
Caught the Viewers' Eye starts now!
Enjoy!
Number Ten!
Get your beast face on
Polka...
Nu-Perezzorcjunmunospolkos...
Let us be one again.
Combine!
Highlight Scene in:
Polka Sushi, good to go!
Polka Sushi
Whoo! Hot rice!
Hold it! Get away from that, Okamew!
I see white...
Omnomnom.
Gaaaaargh!
Oww!
Number Nine!
Sushi comes in
all shapes and sizes
Here you are.
Highlight Scene in:
Hmm?
Number Eight!
It's actually tuna
Uh, yikes. What?
Highlight Scene in:
I fished up a yellowtail!
It's you! NeneRose!
Yay, yay, yay!
Yel-low♪ Yel-low♪ Yel-low♪ Yel-low♪
Ugh, this fishy smell...
Number Seven!
Did you figure out who did it?
Highlight Scene in:
One of you has swapped out
my broth for barley tea.
Huh?
For real?
No way...
Who would do that?
Whaddaya think?
Dunno.
It wasn't me!
Or me!
Trust me...
Psst, go ask who did it.
Why me?
...Uh oh.
Number Six!
Vintage Tsunomaki Watame
Q2. The top three delicacies of the world
are foie gras, caviar...
Highlight Scene in:
and...?
Watame.
She's not food!
Next!
Number Five!
Who shows up like this?
"The Steam and Eat hololive Members'
Pillow Covers Syndicate"
Highlight Scene in:
Uhm...
Now that you've seen it,
you can't escape the White Death!
Shirakami!
"The Steam and Eat hololive Members'
Pillow Covers Syndicate,"
or "The Steam-and-Eat Cover Syndicate,"
can't be stopped!
Syndica-ha-ha!
What a misleading short form.
Number Four!
You reap what you sow (with interest)
Highlight Scene in:
Number Three!
Ringmaster lives off pure vibes
Hey, Mio-sen!
Highlight Scene in:
Hmm?
Aah.
What's this? Playing Merlion?
Ew! Gross!
C'mon...
Number Two!
Getting a license is hard.
Had to compromise.
Let's hit the road!
Hit the road? On our beasts?
Highlight Scene in:
Aw yeah, the wind feels hella good.
You guys feelin' it too?
A... Aye.
I-It feels great.
Number One!
AZKi, diva of the virtual world,
makes her debut!
Give me one last chance!
Highlight Scene in:
I promise I'll do this right!
Oh no! I'm late for school!
My name is AZKi-chi.
Condenser mics are the love of my life.
But this one's a five-eight.
A dynamic.
"What's a condenser mic?"
Allow me to explain!
Prof!
Nobody cares!
Man...
That was crazy, huh?
If any of the scenes interested you,
you can check out the episodes
from the description!
Next week,
the usual hologra returns!
Look forward to it!
hologra's pinch hitter is back?
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!