Speaking of, we call each other Honey & Darling.
Huh? First I've heard of that!
Really?
Bang! Bang!
That's dangerous!
Subaru...!
Must this be...
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Must this be...
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Out with the demon!
Wait, no, she's a devil!
In with the fortune!
Devil, begone! Devil, begone!
What?!
Devil, begone!
Why?
Calm yourselves!
Shut up!
Shut your trap!
Yikes! She's rampant!
C'mere!
She's possessed! Calm yourself!
Okay, with that out of the way—
Hey!
'Tis the season of Setsubun.
Listen, listen!
Huh? What is it?
Yes, Marine-chan?
Listen!
Out with the years!
In with the youth!
I dunno about that one...
That's so old-timey...
Years?
Oh, those kinda years?
How very senior citizen.
Years, huh.
Her old's acting up...
I'm in agony...
You don't really use "years"
like that on the regular,
Soz.
Oh, out of juice?
so I was wondering what she meant.
Sorry.
Okay, let's open up the store!
Welcome, welcome!
Oh, come on in!
Let's have our guest come in!
Yay!
Our guest has arrived!
Sweet bites!
I'm Yozora Mel, a vampire prodigy
from the Underworld!
Welcome!
Mel-senpai!
Yossan!
It's Yozora Mel with her super cute fangs!
About her: Scenarios using ad-libs!
Finishing Move: Playful nibbling!
MENT
LUCK:
A vampire prodigy of the Underworld
who loves acerola juice!
What concern does she have today?
Which gen are you in?
She's our senior.
1st Gen!
Wow! An OG!
She's our senior!
Wow!
Yossan!
Nobody calls her Yossan!
Yossan here!
Yossan?!
Nobody calls you Yossan!
Don't let her get away with that!
Oh, nobody calls you that?
Yeah, nobody does!
I'm the only one.
Yeah, just Subaru.
That surprised me.
Mel-chan!
Yeah!
Her wisdom stat is 5 stars!
Wisdom, huh.
Huh?
Can't help it, I am the wisest.
Yeah, no!
Excuse me?
Wait, what?
Hey! Got a problem?
Quit that! Yossan's 1st gen, you know!
Hey!
I'm 1st gen, you know!
You rebelling against a 1st Gen?
But you're a total klutz.
Yeah.
She's wrong. I'm very much a prodigy.
So, you say improv is your special skill?
Is that true?
Yes, that's correct.
Oh?
Really?
Towa-chan's groaning.
Try doing it by yourself!
Wait.
I wanna see you do it alone.
Okay...
Alone?
Yeah!
What? Everyone's a participant!
Let's do it together!
I'm not doing it!
Why? I dunno if I wanna...
Do you have a scenario ready or something?
Scenario? Let's see...
I'll play the part of a posh
young lady living in a mansion
with the rest of you as my maids.
How about that?
Uh-huh.
Everyone's a maid?
I'm good!
But what exactly's going to unfold from that?
My imagination's failing me.
That's what makes it improv!
That's what it entails?
A wild drama appears!
Posh Young Mel and her Improv!
Good luck, you three!
And...action!
[opens door]
I'm home!
Welcome home!
A-quality afternoon! I'm Minato Aqua!
Your friendly marine maid!
Oh, Aqua Marine.
A-quality afternoon! Marine maid here!
Huh? Is everyone Aqua?
Hey! I'm the real—
No, I'm the real one!
There's no way I'm a fake!
Wai—
I'm the real one!
Hey!
Focus on serving me!
OH! HO! HO! HO! HO!
Save me...
Something's happening.
The Mel before you is an impostor!
You figured it out, huh...
She admitted it?!
I knew it.
You leave me with no choice
but to see you to your death!
Who would've known...
Bang! Bang!
That's dangerous!
Subaru...!
Bang! Bang!
Must this be...
I've reached the end of my road.
Everyone, please take care of the rest.
Don't shoot corpses!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Let's start gaming already.
Let's play a game already.
Let's move on! Come on!
You wanna save round two for another day?
Let's game!
Let's hear out the request Mel-chan has for us today!
Okay!
Go ahead!
So, I'm in hololive's 1st Gen,
and I really want to get closer to the gang!
Leave it to us!
And there we have our request!
We have just the thing!
In short, Yossan's request
is to party it up and befriend everyone!
Yeah!
Leave it to us!
We have just the perfect game for you, Mel-senpai!
Woohoo!
The game we recommend for today is:
WarioWare: Get It Together!
It's time!
A new game in the WarioWare franchise:
WarioWare: Get It Together!
Instant action, using just two controls!
You can play this game with up to four players!
There are over 200 completely new microgames,
and you can play as quirky Wario
and all his quirky chumps.
Each character has different
quirks you can master!
Have a go at all of these microgames
with your family and friends!
Well, then! Now that we can play with four players,
let's have a go at WarioWare: Get It Together,
and get the joys of gaming together!
Oh, that was a good segue.
Nice segue!
Good job executing that without getting embarrassed!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
What's the plan today, Subaru?
The title is:
Enemies yesterday, friends today!
Maruyama All-Out BFF Battle!
BFF Battle!
We'll be playing the Variety Pack
in WarioWare: Get It Together!
The four of us will be having
an honest-to-goodness competition today!
An honest-to-goodness competition?
Yossan, so today, there's no going easy on you
just because you're 1st Gen.
I'm going to beat all you punks here to a pulp!
Get your ass ready!
Come at me!
Let's start with the first contest!
The first minigame is: High Five!
Come on!
In High Five,
you hit the ball as many times as you need
and make use of your character's special skills
to try to get the ball into your opponent's court!
If the ball falls in your court
or if the five-second countdown expires,
you lose the round!
Whoever loses six rounds first, loses the set!
Each match is worth one point,
and whichever team wins two points first, wins!
Got it!
Let's start with team formations.
Don't you want to team up
with Yossan, Subaru-senpai?
I do!
Let's do it!
I wanna team up with Yossan!
Speaking of, we call each other Honey & Darling.
Huh? First I've heard of that!
Really?
Just saying it as it is.
Yeah. We go way back.
Yeah, we go way back.
Way back, huh?
Are you good at these games, Mel-chan?
Mhm, I'm pretty good.
That's the response of a weakling! I can tell!
Nuh-uh!
Her expression kinda gave it away.
How would you know?
The teams are split as shown! Let's start!
I'm picking Ashley!
Wow, you picked fast.
I'm picking Jimmy T!
I'll pick...
You guys pick quick.
Kat!
Mel and Marine picked Ashley!
Who can use her the best?
Let's play High Five!
Looking good!
Don't forget, you need to get the ball into
the opponent's court before the timer expires!
Warning, it says!
An event will occur!
It's completely stuck in their corner!
We need to get it over!
This isn't good!
The countdown—
That was quick. Time for round 2!
Like this?
Good job!
Woot!
That settled it!
You're good!
Good luck!
Four seconds, three—
Watch out!
It hit the ground! It's in!
Mel-chan, you good?
Honey!
You just ended it yourself.
This character can't shoot left!
Ah! Sorry!
Nice!
I just did it myself, too!
This is intense!
What's that?!
Oh, that is—
Oh no!
Good one!
There's a wall—
Get going!
Nice one, Honey!
No!
Oh crap! Sorry!
Just a bit more!
I'm so sorry!
Don't worry!
It's match point!
We can do it!
It's our match point!
For Subaru and Mel's team!
Soz!
Yay! We can do it!
We're still in the game!
It's a deuce!
I'm so sorry!
Our last chance!
Let's go!
Captain?
Cap'n?
Wait—
I wanna win!
Keep calm!
From the side!
You should probably send it over soon!
Come from the side!
The side—nice!
That was close.
Good one!
Terrifying...
Nice receive!
From the side!
Good going, Cap'n!
Nice!
And the captain sends it over!
Send it back!
Oh no no no!
It's almost—!
Woohoo!
Yes!
The winner is...
Subaru and Mel's team!
Can we change characters?
Feel free to change your character!
Oh, we can!
There might be someone stronger—
Oh, Wario! Someone use the protag!
I'll use the protag, then.
I'll pick Dr. Crygor.
Thank you for using the protag.
I'm going to pick the mommy, then.
Guess I'll go with this.
The mommy!
For the second match, everyone changed their character!
Will they be able to make use of their special traits?
The overall victor will be Subaru and Mel if they win this!
Give it your all
Let's do our best!
Can't lose here.
That was a good fight!
What can this character do?
I know nothing.
This guy's slow af!
Crap!
Whoa!
What?!
He's so slow!
That's so OP!
What was that?
Settled via Towa-chan's smash serve!
What an opener!
Hey, hold on!
Not like this...
Hold up!
That's too powerful!
It's too powerful!
My dude's super duper slow!
Oh no!
The mom's doing nothing!
Oh no...
No...!
Towa-chan does it again!
Wait up...
Three consecutive smashes!
We're screwed!
Per! fect!
Can you believe it! Marine and Towa are already
at match point without losing a single one!
Good one!
Perfect, soon?
I don't want to lose to a perfect!
Oh no! It'll be over if she gets this one in!
Anything but a perfect!
Perfect!
Good one!
Straight!
Send it over!
Hey now! Was that all talk earlier?
Not at all!
We were just playing around.
The next match will decide it once and for all.
Someone I haven't used? Orbulon, I guess.
Uh-huh.
Orbulon?
Then I'll—Nobody's played this one, right?
Nobody's used Mike.
Someone I haven't used? Then...
I'll be this robot, then.
Good.
This guy, I guess.
Cute.
The mommy!
It's time for the third match!
Mel is using the mommy character
Marine used earlier, 5-Volt!
Focus on your inputs!
Ready, go!
What is this?!
Not again...
Honey, the mommy looks complicated.
The mommy is complicated.
This mommy's hard to use.
Hey!
Good going!
The boomerang's bad news.
She threw it into her own court!
You use the boomerang like this!
Nice, nice.
With this boomerang—
Oh, I get it now!
Send it over and—
Send it!
Yes, just like that!
What astounding force.
Return it!
Nice!
Let's go, Honey!
Attack!
Warning! An event's gonna get in the way!
Character swaps?!
This event's absurd!
You're kidding me!
It's gonna get stuck!
What is this guy, even?
Will it get stuck?
Crap!
This character's pretty good!
That character's good.
I'm back to my old character!
They're back to their regular characters.
The bound—
Nice!
It's match point for Subaru/Mel's team!
Here's our chance!
Oh no!
Another self-own!
To finish it off, even, can you believe it?
Self-own, really?
Now then! With two points,
the victory goes to Subaru and Mel's team!
Woohoo!
I'm so happy!
Dang it!
Don't you have something to say?
Yeah!
I had a blast.
I just had fun as usual!
I had fun!
2 Sore Losers
It was fun!
Fun, fun!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
The next competitive game is:
Sly Angle!
Now, all four will be battling it out!
Whoever wins a microgame gets to place a flag.
The objective is to make triangles with the flags!
Whoever takes up the largest area at the end, wins!
Let's get started!
Let's go!
Start!
Ball Blast!
Ball?
Is that how it works?
Whoever gets the ball with the prize, wins!
Let's gather as many balls as we can!
What is this?
That doesn't tell me much.
I don't get it.
I guess you have to find the good one?
Hey, what are you shooting at?
I want that one!
In short, you just collect balls.
I caught like zero balls...
Whoa! You picked up a lot!
The one with the most is—
Oh no.
Marine?
Is this the prize?
Woohoo!
What! Why?!
It went to Towa-chan!
I picked up so many!
She picked it up...
So this is how it works.
So where will she put it?
Try to cover up the most space.
There must be a strategy for this.
Yeah...
Let's make it very wide.
Okay, here!
Oh! She selected a point!
I got it.
Okay.
Good going.
Now then!
Round 2.
Contemporary Art?
Wait, if...
If I win this, I can make a triangle!
Like the title implies, you just paint all over.
How do we paint?
Paint the world away!
I just have to paint, right?
Keep painting and cover up everyone else's paint!
I get it.
Mhm, okay.
Whoa.
Oh, I get it.
Like that, huh?
Someone seems to be doing a good job!
Isn't green kinda OP?
Green seems to be doing good!
Your efficiency's wild!
Towa-chan?!
This might be close.
This one also goes to Towa-chan!
Two victories in a row!
Hey!!
Oh no!
Here? No, here!
You can form a triangle now!
You have to make the biggest shape.
Here it shall be.
Good going!
Isn't that a colored contact?
Let's go! Three, two,
Two, one...
Start!
Nobody knows when the eye will open!
This is really hard!
That's some apprehensive movement!
This is tough!
It's gonna open!
And Towa-chan gets three wins in a row!
What in the world?!
So annoying!
Towa's so good!
This game must have been designed for Towa-chan!
Can I?
Sorry, guys.
Someone handicap Towa!
We've gotta handicap her!
Let's handicap her!
Don't pop?
Don't pop? Our own, I guess?
Give it your best!
Why's this girl—
Don't let anyone else burst yours!
That hurt!
Ah! Mine burst!
Yes!
There's a wind blowing...
You have to aim for your opponent's balloons
without getting yours burst.
Down to 2P and 1P...
Wait, I lost?
Marine's dead!
What's this?
The stage will also target you, so watch out.
Mel-chan, you gotta aim for the blue balloon.
Okay!
Oh no!
I did it!
Place it wherever? Okay, then...
Wait a minute, if you place a triangle on top, then...
The one who makes the biggest area—
You can overlap other folks' spaces, yeah.
Oh, and it'll take space away?
Yep.
That'd reduce the opponent's
conquered area, yeah?
Oh, I see.
Don't do that...
Oh we gotta avoid hitting them.
This is a dodging game!
Dodge!
Just dodge.
Don't get hit? Got it.
This is scary.
They're coming!
Watch out!
This game's fun.
Gotta find a safe spot.
Crap, it's getting smaller!
It is!
Can you get in the way of others?
Wait, can you?
I dunno.
Can we?
Can you?
Oh I got hit!
I can't believe it.
This isn't good.
It's getting smaller!
It's so cramped!
This is bad news.
Oh man, where's the safe spot?
This is bad!
Woohoo!
A win for Subaru!
Dang it!
I did it!
I lost...
Am I the only one who's not using a person character?
Oh yeah.
You're right.
Hey, I'm the only one who hasn't won yet...
There's more, right?
Okay, how about here?
Right?
Do we just catch a lot of fish?
Attach six?
Attach? What does that mean?
Attach?
This is hard.
Oh, they attach to your body.
Basically, just collect them.
You're so fast!
But this annoying urchin...
The urchin's bad news.
...will take away your fish, I think?
4P's movement is kinda fishy.
Towa's too good...
You're good, Towa-chan!
If Subaru-chan takes this spot,
Oh, yeah.
she'll take over my triangle.
Strategizing time.
So I'll pick this spot.
That's how it is, huh.
Meta it up!
That's right!
No!
Focus.
Okay.
Where could it be?
Ah, crap.
Shoot.
Oh no.
This is too hard.
Where the heck?
This one!
Nice!
Wai—
Yay!
Towa-chan was fast!
She's too fast!
Towa-chan!
Is it her youth?
She's too fast!
Too fast!
The locks have been unlocked!
What are your thoughts, honey?
This isn't looking good.
Win already, my seniors!
It's a turtle.
The turtle is...
The turtle is...?
Are we peeling an egg?
Really?
They all look the same!
Which one's the same?
They're the same thing!
I can't tell.
This is all luck.
Oh, huh.
Please be mine!
Please!
Whyyy?
You're kidding me!
Winning even the luck game...
What's going on, guys?
Are your controllers connected?
The locks were unlocked,
so you can plant flags in more places.
Is this platforming?
Climb!
Climb?
Climb...
Climb.
Is it better to go through the middle or the right?
So fast.
Oh, I'm 2P.
Happens.
Get outta my way!
Oh, so the edge of the screen follows you.
Oh no.
She's climbing up!
Towa-chan is strong.
Darn it!
She's wiping the floor with us.
That reminds me of something.
Oh, what?
First to stop it?
It's a reaction speed one.
Ah.
Huh?
I hit it by accident.
Ah!
Ah. So you're out if you push it before it goes off.
Yeah, it seems like it.
Alright!
Subaru kept her composure and won!
Darn it!
Subaru got one before, so...
I choose you!
Wait...
The biggest one you can make.
Nah, nah.
Okay!
Ooh!
Let's go!
It's toilet paper!
Two rounds left!
Is this a mashing game?
Mashing?
Mash it as fast as you can!
What the heck?
Whoa, Towa-chan's fast!
What am I supposed to do?
I'm so confused.
Whoa, already?
Thank you, Mommy! She never disappoints.
Captain wins! It's a cat hand.
Yay!
Is there a hole I can use?
It's a cat!
Where do I...
You can only go here or there.
Where do I put it?
What do I do?
I dunno!
Last round.
What the heck is this?!
Waxing?
So we gotta pluck hair.
I got you.
50 strands?!
It's not good to pluck too much, though.
2... 1...
You can grow that much?
Start!
Oh, this is a stubborn one.
Okay, okay.
Ah... I see.
Take this!
Towa-chan, your character is insane.
This seems good!
They're too stubborn.
Doing good, doing good.
Ahh!
You're way too fast!
The character was good for that.
I didn't get much at the end though.
You already got too much!
That's right!
It's a lawn already.
Like a golf course, right?
It's a golf course.
We ain't here to play golf!
That means Towa-chan has won!
Sorry about that, lassies!
Final thoughts, Towa-chan?
My seniors were total noobs.
Shut yer trap!
Ow!
Mess her up!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
The last game will be...
Frenemy Frenzy!
Yaaay!
An intense battle to the death between four players!
Their characters will change randomly during battle.
Whoever remains standing until the end wins!
First to three wins is the victor!
All right!
Let's do it!
We'll start with "Desktop."
Okay!
What a cute stage.
Who was that?
It's the mom!
Beat them up good!
What do we do here?
Beat 'em, beat 'em, beat 'em up!
Where's Tokoyami?!
She's dead, I think!
Have you gotten your power-ups?
Mel-chan is out for the count!
Captain takes the win!
All that Smash practice really
paid off, Marine. Good play!
Will Marine-san be able to keep her crown?
Let's go!
The match has started!
That one's Subaru, right?
It's meeeee.
Almost swapping time!
Swap? What's that?
Your characters are gonna change!
I'm a ninja now.
Shuriken! Shuriken!
Player 4 still has a lot of HP!
It's gotten easier to move around.
I should get this.
I died!
Subaru and Mel-chan are down!
Now at a 1v1 between Captain and Towa!
Who will take the last hit?!
Captain wins a second time!
So good!
Great play!
That was so close!
Your Smash training is finally showing its fruits.
Damn it.
Now then,
if Captain wins the next round,
she'll be the overall winner.
Gotta go for the win!
Which do we pick: Sweet Shop or Pinball Machine?
Let's go for Sweet Shop.
Sweet Shop it is!
Let's do this.
Wait, this is difficult.
Oh? It seems like Subaru-san
has decided to just wait out the fight!
No one seems to have noticed...
Who's your pair?
I'm a ninja, so...
it's Mel-chan, I think.
Oh, yeah.
The mom's really hard to use!
She is!
The mom?
Mel-chan is mowing everyone down
with her power-up!
It's so hard playing as the mom!
Towa is out!
Subaru-chan still has a lot of HP!
Oh damn!
They've seen through my plan!
With Captain out...
The winner is Subaru!
That's unfair!
Perish in your petty squabbles!
Gah! Dirty play!
But that's another way to win, huh...?
So that was your plan!
GG.
We're down to the last match!
Will Subaru-san be able to win and
force a tiebreaker with Marine-san?!
There's a shield! A shield in the middle!
Which of them will last?!
Subaru-san is down!
You're almost dead, Towa-chan!
I'm not gonna hold back for you, Mel-chan!
Captain takes the win!
Winning a total of three matches,
Captain takes the crown!
I'm sorry, Mel-chan!
And that's the end of today's matches!
Please tell us who you think deserves
the title of Twin-Crew for today!
Hmm...
Darling! Darling! Darling!
I guess...
It has to be my darling!
Thank you so much!
She's clearly biased!
Yeah!
I mean, you really should put
fun first when playing games!
That's true!
Whoooo! It was fun!
I had fun!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Challenge From The Boss:
the Maruyama Championship Season 2!
At this point, we'll have our customers
try their hand at a minigame.
The one who finishes the season
on top will receive a trophy!
Season 2's minigame is
SEGA AGES Sonic the Hedgehog.
Players will compete in
Green Hill Zone Act 1's time attack mode!
The clear time shown on the
results screen will be your record.
By the way, the one with
the best time currently...
is Suisei-chan, with 36.56 seconds!
Whoa...
It's a pretty fast record.
Amazing...
How confident are you?
Zero!
No confidence at all.
None.
Just gotta dive in.
But I'll pull through since I'm a genius.
Oh, we have a genius!
I'll do my best!
That's pretty cool.
Give it your all!
Go for it!
Good luck!
Get over the Towa Line!
Let's go!
Go fast!
The rings are vital here.
That crab was a hassle...
Gotta keep track of my rings, right?
Yep, you should!
Do I need to sprint through this?
Nah, you can do it slowly!
Seems like Towa-sama's saying stuff
to keep her record unbroken!
Get past Towa's record!
Waaaaaaaaah...
There's her record!
And so, we have our time!
The time is 53.48 seconds!
53 seconds...
This places her...
in between Subaru and Towa!
Even my seat is right in the middle.
Actually!
So, how do you feel, having tried it out?
I had a lot of fun!
Glad to hear!
Will a monster appear
and beat the high score?
Thanks for coming, Mel-chan!
Tune in next time and see if the record is trumped!
Look forward to it!
Thanks for having me!
Thanks for coming!
See you again soon!
See you next time!
Until next time!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
After Closing
So, I've had the self-proclaimed advice master Subaru
stay around for today.
Yep! I never said I was one!
Oh wait, I did.
Sorry, I did say that.
Yep, you did.
But anyway.
Let's give our viewers some advice
for their worries.
Sure!
This is one from @hrmy_3522!
Thanks for the mail!
Thank you for the mail!
Let's see what they wrote...
"I'm a middle school girl in my 2nd year.
I changed classes this April,
and I thought it'd be a good chance
for me to make new friends.
However, I've only made three friends
by the end of the 2nd term.
Those three friends said
that I give off an intimidating vibe
whenever I just sit around silently."
I feel for her!
Yeah.
"Is there any way for me to make more friends?"
They wanted advice on this.
What do you think?
You felt for her, right?
You see, for some reason, I've also been seen
as the intimidating one in hololive.
Intimidating?!
Yes!
They think I'm expecting them
to do a funny when I'm around.
That's the sort of treatment I get!
Even though I'm not that kind of person at all!
So that's how everyone sees you.
Yes!
I wonder why.
There's a way to solve this, though!
There is?
You just have to be nice to people!
If you do that,
they'll start having a different impression of you.
And if you started out with a negative impression,
it might eventually even out into a neutral one,
but everyone else will see it as a net positive!
I see!
It's pretty common!
Overall, it's a positive!
Yes!
An excellent answer!
It's like Gian in the movies!
Be like him and be kind to others!
Be kind to a fault, is what you're saying.
Yeah.
Anyway, we're accepting requests for advice from you.
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique, personally-signed
request fulfilled sticker!
So please send in your submissions!
Keep 'em coming! Keep 'em coming!