It's time...
...to decide...
hololive's fastest
Winking Queen!
She's fast! She's taking the lead!
SHE'S SO FAST!
GO FOR IT! WIN!
Wow, she's speeding!
🎺🎺🎺🎺🎺
🥁🥁🥁🥁
🎺🎺🎺
🎺🎺🎺🎺
🥁🥁
The day's finally here!
It's time for our
#1 Winking Championship:
The Wink Derby!
Yaaay!
Yaaaaay!
So... what's a Wink Derby?
It's a Wink Derby!
You don't know what it is?!
Huh? You don't know?
You really don't know?
You making fun of this race?
A-Are the both of you...
It's a famous race
within hololive where
Uh-huh.
we measure how fast
a member can wink 100 times.
We had such a race?
Yup! By the way,
we actually got an AI
to make a racing video
based on the time
the members took to wink 100 times.
A racing video?!
Exciting, isn't it?
Oooh!
I see!
The three of you will be guessing
who's going to take the crown!
We just need to guess
the winner for one race, right?
We're not guessing
who'll win three in a row, are we?
No way.
We're not, right?
Okay, got it.
Let's introduce our runners!
We have Yuzuki Choco-san,
Yozora Mel-san,
Shirogane Noel-san,
Himemori Luna-san,
Sakura Miko-san,
Tokoyami Towa-san,
and Yukihana Lamy-san!
The seven of them will be
duking it out for the victory!
Let's introduce the three runners
competing in our first race!
Our first runner! With her trademark
stacked pecs and powerful muscles
which give her an edge in her blinking,
it's Shirogane Noel!
Here's our second runner!
The raw destructive power of her winks
is a force to be reckoned with!
No one can resist folding
to her pretty eyelashes!
It's Yozora Mel!
Finally, our third runner!
Charming unending waves of people,
is the raw power of her winks
#1 in hololive?!
It's Yuzuki Choco!
Whoa!
Okay.
Oooh.
We have a stacked
cast of runners here.
Yes, indeed.
They sure are stacked.
Amazing, isn't it?
Okay.
Everyone seems laid-back, don't they?
You're right!
Yeah!
Everyone's pretty laid-back.
Hmm...
Okay, I've decided!
You did?
Me too.
Me three!
Oh! That's great.
Uh, for this race...
I'll bet on Shirogane Noel!
Oh! Noel-san, huh.
She's got the most
developed chest among the three,
so I hope the Commander can assert
dominance over her opposition.
Okay!
As for me, I pick Yozora Mel!
Ooh!
Oh?
Mel's a girl who gets going
when the going gets tough.
Ah, true.
I'm betting on her
wiping out the opposition
with her full-power winks.
Uh-huh.
And as for me,
it's gotta be Choco-sensei!
Oh! It's a three-way split!
Take a good look
at our three runners, girls.
Choco-sensei hasn't
unleashed her full power yet.
Uh-huh.
Huh?!
Her full power?!
She's going to in a minute, eh?
What?!
Whoa!
They're gonna have to deal
with her hands, huh?
Oh my!
We have our predictions,
so let's start the races!
Wink Race Derby: Race 1...
Begin!
And they're off!
Oh! OH!
They're out of the gates!
Whoa, amazing!
Oh, Choco-sensei's fast!
Go for it!
WHOA, SHE'S FAST!
SHE'S FREAKING FAST!
She's taking the lead!
Choco-sensei's freaking fast!
OH NO!
Wow, she's really fast!
Yozora!
Oh my! Do your best, Mel-san!
Mel!
Do your best!
MEL!
Go, Mel!
I knew it!
Mel!
Keep it up, Commander!
Noel-san's surprisingly trailing behind.
MEL!
Did I make the right choice?
Catch up to her!
Oh! Mel-san's getting serious!
Commander!
Oh? AH!
You can do it!
Mel-chan's speeding up!
Keep up the pressure!
You're lagging behind!
Push past her!
OH NO!
She's going all in!
Do it!
She's gaining on Choco!
NO! Keep it up, Choco!
Overtake her!
Commander!
It's a neck-and-neck battle between Melkiss!
Keep pressuring her!
Wait, Noel-chan!
You can do it, Mel!
You can overtake her!
Mel!
Who will win?
You can do it!
Oh, Choco-san's out of juice!
You can do it, Mel!
YOU'RE ALMOST THERE!
You're neck and neck!
Mel-san took the lead!
Go, Commander!
You're overtaking her!
AH!
Last spurt! Come on!
GO GO GO!
This isn't good!
Will she get a straight shot to the finish line?
Push past her, Mel!
This is NOT good!
You can turn this around!
Do it!
Will Mel take first place?
This is REALLY bad!
Yozora's taking the lead!
And Noel-san!
She took it!
She took the lead!
Noel-san's pecs are
weighing her down to last place!
YEEES!
All riiight!
Nooo!
Oh my!
Shirogane Noel takes
second place!
And Choco-sensei's
cutely winking away!
She steadily blushes her way
past the finish line!
Yeees!
Okay!
First place is...
Yozora Mel-san!
Congratulations, Fubuki-san!
All right!
I won!
I knew Yozora Mel was the right choice!
Indeed!
She actually turned things around midway.
Nothing less from
the Underworld's genius vampire!
Yup.
Let's introduce the four runners
competing in our second race!
First up, the princess who combines her
adorable looks with some big surprises!
Those winks look gentle,
but they won't lose out in speed!
It's Himemori Luna!
Aiming to take the crown
with her high-speed blinking,
our second runner is Yukihana Lamy!
Her hidden potential for blinking
is impossible to uncover!
Show everyone your
last-ditch horsepower,
our third runner, Tokoyami Towa!
This girl needs no prayer for victory
because she'll grab it
with her own winks!
Our fourth runner, Sakura Miko!
Uh-huh...
Yup.
Ah, okay...
I see...
This is a tough one!
These are some hard choices.
They sure are.
I mean, with Luna-chan...
She gets the job done
when the time calls for it.
I've decided!
Oh! Aqua's decided.
Hmm...
Do I take a bet? Let's do it.
Okay, I've decided!
Me too!
Okay!
This time,
I pick Tokoyami Towa!
Oh, you're picking Towa-san!
Oh?
Towa-chan games a lot
Uh-huh.
and I think she's a tough person,
so she's probably ready
to wipe the floor here.
I see!
When it comes to races and gambling,
there's only Sakura Miko!
Ah, Miko-san!
Bet it all on that one chance!
And my one chance is Sakura Miko!
I'm going with Yukihana Lamy!
Oh! Okayu picks Lamy-san!
Ooh.
Lamy-chan's definitely
Grr...
gonna use her twintails at the end
to drive the competition off course!
Drive them off course? lol.
What?!
But Lamy-chan might
be having a hangover,
Ah...
so that's something to consider.
On such a day?
She might have taken a drinking.
That's definitely something
to watch out for.
While all that's happening,
I think Luna-chan's gonna
come in out of left field.
Ah, good point.
You're right!
She's also a threat.
This round's really tough!
This race is really tough!
Keep your eyes glued!
Wink Race Derby: Race 2 starts in...
Ooh!
Go!
Keep it up!
Okay, she's off!
Ah!
You can do it!
Yukihana Lamy's edging
towards the lead!
You can do it!
Take the lead!
Mikochi!
Come on! Take the lead!
You can do this, Mikochi!
They're all lined up!
Mikochi's pretty fast too!
'Cause you're Miko!
You can do it, Towa-sama!
You can make it!
The race only just started!
You'll make it!
You're doing good, Mikochi!
Oh! Is she gonna show us her eliteness?
Take the lead!
Nice job, Mikochi!
Keep it up!
TAKE THE LEAD!
You're in the lead!
Miko's taking it chill!
GO!
Go!
No!
She's swaying her head!
You can still win!
She's swaying her head a ton!
Oh no!
You can do this!
Keep it up, Lamy-chan!
Oh! Tokoyami Towa's fast!
You can't lose here, Mikochi!
Drive them off course!
Contestant Tokoyami's bolting off!
No!
You have to win, Mikochi!
Leave 'em in the dust!
Oh!
You still have a shot!
Luna-san's caught up!
Mikochi!
Go on! Finish it!
It's the last spurt for Towa-san!
Whoa! Towa's fast!
No!
What the heck?!
WHOA, SHE'S SPEED!
She reaches the finish line with a clear lead!
Seriously, Towa?!
Mikochi!
At least take third place!
What'll happen next?
Damn!
B-Both Luna-san and Miko-san
You can't place last, Mikochi!
You can't lose!
are swaying their heads for some reason!
Come on!
And Lamy-san reaches the finish line!
Mikochi!
Mikochi... you're freaking slow!
Will Luna-san take third place?
You're so freaking slow!
What about Miko-san?
You're a freaking snail, Mikochi!
Miko-san!
Miko-san's lagging
towards the finish line!
Miko-san was doing
so many pointless movements!
Ugh...
Yeah! There was so much
pointless head swaying!
Okay!
The one who nailed their prediction
of Towa-san taking first place
is Aqua-san!
Congratulations!
Ooh!
Yes!
Ugh...
What a dominating victory that was.
I knew Towa-sama would win.
Yeah! That was a dominating victory.
Indeed.
Believe in Towa-sama, everyone.
The Mighty-angelic Towa-sama.
And now for our final race!
It's a one-on-one between
the winner of the first race,
Yozora Mel-san,
and the winner of our second race,
Tokoyami Towa-san!
Ugh...
Whoooa!
Whoa! It's finally time!
This is a tough decision.
It really is a tough one.
It sure is.
Mhm.
I've decided.
Oh? You did?
Same here.
I'm going to go with
Tokoyami Towa for this one.
Oh?
Mhm...
Two times straight, I see.
I gotta go with Yozora Mel for this one.
Oh? Fubuki picks Mel-san!
Ugh...
As for me,
I pick Tokoyami Towa!
Oh?
All right, it's off to the races!
Let's take a look.
And they're off!
Ooh!
They're neck to neck.
You can do it!
You can do it, Towa-sama!
Leave her in the dust!
Both of them are really fast!
Looking good, Mel!
Towa-sama!
This is a good match.
Keep it up!
Oh, Mel-san has a slight lead.
You're doing great!
Go, go, go!
Whoa!
She's got a slight lead.
Towa's hugging the inner line hard!
It's okay, she's only just started!
Oh! Towa-san might overtake her!
Go for it!
This is where the comeback happens!
Oh no!
Wait, it's okay!
You can still do this!
What's it gonna be?
Keep going!
You can still turn things around, Mel!
Hang in there, Mel-san!
Oh? OH?!
You still have a chance!
Overtake her!
Can she take back the lead?
OH?!
Do it!
Towa's in the zone!
Towa-san establishes
a slight lead near the end!
Oh no!
She's winning!
You can still do it, Mel-chan!
Things can still turn around!
You're doing great! Keep it up!
Yes!
It's not over yet!
Keep going!
You still have a chance!
How will it end?
Who's faster?
Keep it up!
You can still make it!
Finish it, Towa!
Clinch it!
Who will reach the finish line first?
Yes! Finish it!
Gooo!
Who is it? Who will take the crown?
Oh my!
YEEES!
Nooo!
Towa-san takes the crown!
Meeel!
Yaaay!
Yeees!
Ugh...
The person with
the most accurate predictions is...
Minato Aqua-san!
Congratulations!
All right!
Ooh!
Argh!
Thank you so much!
All you need is Towa-sama.
Uh-huh.
That was really great.
Towa-sama's the best.
This was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
It was!
Really? That's great!
It really was, yeah!
It really was a lot of fun.
It'd be great if we got pre-race info.
Ah, I see!
Yeah!
I do wanna see you three with pens
in your mouths while scanning the papers.
That'd be cool.
I'd love to do that.
Yeah!
If you liked and enjoyed the video,
please subscribe to the
official hololive YouTube channel
as well as our talents' channels!
Well then, let's meet again
at the next Wink Derby!
Bye-bye!
Ah! 👏👏👏
Starring
Nekomata Okayu
Shirakami Fubuki
Minato Aqua
This video was brought to you
by Nekomata Okayu...
...Shirakami Fubuki, and...
...Minato Aqua!