February 20XX,
11:30 AM
You sure love talking
to strangers, Akane.
Well, we got off at the same station!
Why not have a chat?
Speaking of which,
what brings you here to Aogami?
Actually, I'm also curious about that.
I'm moving here this summer,
so I wanted to get a feel for the town first.
I'll be staying at the hotel
near the station for about a week.
Lucky us, running into a future neighbor.
We'd love to show you around town!
I'm sure of it...
I've seen this girl before somewhere...
Hm? Hey, it's Akane-chan and Yuka-chan.
Oh? It's Kaoru-san and the girls.
Hey there!
Hey, who's the girl with you?
Oh, get this!
She's gonna be moving
to Aogami this summer!
My, is that so?
But then, what brings her here now?
Ah, well, you see...
2:00 PM
I see!
So now you're gonna
show her around town!
Is there anywhere in particular
you would like to visit?
Well,
if there are any
lively spots around town...
If you're looking for a shrine,
I recommend Aogami Shrine.
That would be the name
of the local shrine.
I see.
Do you all go to the same school?
We sure do.
Same class, as a matter of fact.
Though a lot of people in my class
have been absent lately.
Might be a summer cold going around.
No one can even
get in touch with them.
I... I see...
Huh, what's the matter?
You don't look well...
What was that memory...?
It's weird that nobody
can get in touch with them.
I agree, Yuka-chan.
Come to think of it,
there have been reports of
missing persons in Aogami...
The rumor is,
all of them were last heard from
near Aogami Station, right?
What if our classmates
aren't out with a summer cold
but are among those missing persons?
It's a summer cold.
Huh?
What was...
C'mon, let's get going.
We'll show you around...