I have no idea!
No way! Where?!
Wait, wha?
Where? Where?!
Find the hololive members
hidden around the world!
holo Bird Watching!
Good evening to our guests
from the Wild Bird Society!
Tweet tweet tweet tweet tweet!
Flap flap flap flap!
So, you're the actual birds?
I'm holo Bird Watching's
elite shrine maiden,
Sakura Miko.
What I'm searching for now...
is a blonde girl with pigtails.
If she's a tsundere, then that's even...
Even better?
Even more wonderful.
I see...
Officer, over here...
but nice to have you.
I'm holo Bird Watching's devil,
Tokoyami Towa.
What I'm searching for now...
is the thing that I'm searching for.
Huh?
I'm holo Bird Watching's
Wild Bird Society's
newest addition,
Yukihana Lamy, I think.
What do they think
a Wild Bird Society actually is?
"I think"?
"You think"?
Who are you even?!
No, I am Lamy!
What I'm searching for now...
is a one-liner that I can use all year.
Thanks for having me.
Doesn't "liver face" work?
That is not a gag.
It's not?!
That's just part of her self-introduction.
Oh, yeah.
Please don't tease me about it!
So we've got the perfect
people-hunting game
for all of you, who are
currently looking for something.
I wonder what it is.
What kind of game is it?
This seems like it'll be fun.
So, things are going to be like this
for the whole show, yeah...
One of you will be
hidden in each image
that we're about to show you,
so good luck finding them!
I'm really good at these!
I'm really, really good at these!
You might say that I'm
nothing but good at these.
You've all got no source though.
Source, please.
So basically, it's a race to see
who can find them first.
Well then, let's get started on the first one.
There's no button to press,
but if you see it, put your hand up.
Now, let's start.
Who's hiding in the picture?
Huh?
So yes, see if you can find them.
I see.
It's cool to answer
as soon as I see it, right?
Of course. Just go ahead and answer.
Understood! ♪
Go ahead!
Let's zoom in a little bit.
Ooh!
Oh, we're zooming into this side...
Me!
I see it!
That was fast!
Towards the bottom right,
there's a white car...
Sakura Miko of
the Wild Bird Society is there.
Let's get a little closer
and see if that's the right answer.
She is there!
Ooh!
She's looking right at us!
So, Towa-san was right!
Sakura Miko is in the white car.
Yay!
Wow!
That was quick!
Ooh!
Oh yeah, I actually do remember
being around there.
You were actually there?
So this picture's of that one time!
Alright, let's move on
to the second one.
Who's hiding in the picture?
See if you can find them.
Huh?
Me!
You're too fast!
That quick?
Is it alright for me to answer
twice in a row, though?
Wasn't that too quick?!
I can't see it at all...
Ah, I see it!
Ahh!
There it is!
Do you girls see it?
In the top left, I can kind of see...
Tokoyami Towa-sama peeking out
from between the leaves.
I see.
Let's get a little closer and see.
She's hiding there.
Let's zoom in a little more.
She is there!
What a wonderful peace pose!
So, Miko-san was right,
Lamy-san was right,
and Towa-san was right too.
It's Tokoyami Towa,
living deep in the jungle.
Hey, don't you think
this is a little too easy?
Are you looking down on us?
The staff were actually
pretty confident about these,
so I'm getting a little worried now.
Is this going to be okay?
Okay, onto the third one.
Who's hiding in the picture?
Whoa! What a view!
Let's get in closer.
This one's hidden pretty well.
Let's see.
Let's zoom in.
Hmm...
Zoom in even more...
Hmm...?
Yup!
You've found it?
In the top right, where the clouds are...
I can see Yukihana Lamy lying down.
Let's zoom in and see.
They probably thought
we wouldn't be able to find her
because the blue and white blends in...
but you can't trick Miko's eyes.
...and zoomed in on the top right.
It's Yukihana Lamy, far out on the horizon.
I've ascended to godhood.
So, Miko-san got this one.
That was quick!
Yay!
Wow!
I'm just lying there having fun
checking out what people are doing.
As gods do.
This isn't looking good...
That was over in a flash.
But apparently, the
next one is actually hard.
We've kind of got a management vs hololive
vibe going on...but is that really okay?
Yeah, they're starting to get
a little serious about this too.
Let's continue!
Who's hiding in the picture?
Here we are.
They gave us a really
colorful one this time!
This is really colorful.
How about this?
This one should be a little harder.
Let's zoom in a bit.
It's so colorful, it makes it
kind of hard to focus.
Zoom in...
That's true.
Huh?
Yeah, the colors...
The colors definitely...
Ah, there...!
I found it.
Really?!
No way! Where?!
Where?
Sorry!
In the bottom left, under the
bright green beach parasol...
She's right!
all three of us are there.
Yeah, she is!
I see!
Let's get closer and see.
Let's zoom in...
A little more...
We're really enjoying the
summer, aren't we?
We're buried in the sand!
We are!
That is an interesting pose.
So, it's the three of you
buried in the sand at the beach
on a hot summer day.
We're buried in the sand?!
So Towa-san, you were right!
How amazing!
Uh...
Don't you think this
is a little too easy for us?
Yeah, I kind of feel sorry for them...
They're saying,
"Wait until you see the next one!"
So, that wasn't the last one?
They're starting to get a
little frustrated, aren't they?
They want another chance.
A new challenger appears!
Alright, this is the last one.
Who's hiding in the picture?
Oh wow!
This one seems pretty difficult.
There's so many people!
The staff are definitely
feeling smug about this one.
My eyes are getting all blurry.
Good luck! It's definitely
hidden in there!
Huh?
Is it really though?
Ah!
Sorry, but I found it.
But you can keep going.
That was quick!
"But you can keep going"?
She's letting them keep going.
Yeah, you can keep going.
By the way, who is it?
I think it's me.
And you two still haven't
spotted her yet, right?
I have no idea!
Let's keep looking a little longer.
Let's have Miko-san and Lamy-san
keep looking.
Yeah, good luck!
So with stuff like this, searching
in order is usually the best way...
There she is!
Really?
Which half of
the picture is it in?
The left side or the right side?
Umm, this is...
The left, I'd say.
I see. Stop right there!
The left...
Stop right there...
Lamy-san, good luck!
So it's up to me to finish it, right?
That's right!
This is kind of...
Once you see it, it's pretty obvious.
Yeah, it is...
Ah, I see it now!
Lamy-san has found her too!
I see her now.
Around the middle of the left side...
there's a cutout of Towa-sama's face...
It's full-on staring at us.
Let's zoom in and see.
Our eyes met!
So, everyone got it right!
It's Tokoyami Towa, hidden in a crowd!
Wow!
She's packed in super tight!
I've never seen anything like this before!
So, our most brilliant
holo Bird Watching master today
was definitely Tokoyami Towa!
Congratulations!
Wow!
Thank you so much!
You were so fast!
There are always people after my life...
That's probably why
I'm good at finding people.
You were super quick!
That was amazing!
Management must be feeling
really frustrated about this right now.
They're probably grinding
their teeth in frustration.
If you enjoyed this video,
please like and subscribe to
the official hololive channel,
as well as the channels of
our Wild Bird Society's members!
We hope to see you again in
the next Wild Bird Society episode.
See you!
Starring
Tokoyami Towa
Yukihana Lamy
Sakura Miko
This program was brought
to you by Tokoyami Towa...
...Yukihana Lamy, and...
...and Sakura Miko.