9:00 AM
I feel like...
I was having a strange dream.
9:00 AM
I fell asleep as soon as I got back
to the hotel last night.
That's right. I made plans to meet up
with Yuka-san and the others today.
I'd better get ready.
2:00 PM
They should be here soon...
Oh!
Wait, where are
Yuka-san and Akane-san?
They aren't with you?
Is there anywhere in particular
you would like to visit?
Um... But the other two...
If you're looking for a shrine,
I recommend Aogami Shrine.
Huh? Um...
That would be the name
of the local shrine.
Wh-What's going on...?
This isn't right.
What are you saying?
We sure do.
Same class, as a matter of fact.
E-Excuse me!
Where are Akane-san and Yuka-san?
Akane-san should be here soon enough.
Yeah! I think so too.
R-Really?
Then let's keep waiting.
Right, but what I wanna know is...
Who's this "Yuka" person?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Friend of yours, Miku-san?
No...
Well, whatever.
We can show you around today.
Let's go!
Um... I'm sorry.
I'm going to go look for Yuka-san.
No... You can't go that way.
Let go of me!
What's gotten into them?!
Yuka-san... Akane-san!
11:30 PM
Why...
I can't find them anywhere...
And I really should
be heading back.
11:30 PM
Wait, isn't that...
Akane-san?
Wait up!
Oof!
Ow!
Ouch...
Watch where you're going.