After school,
the transfer student heads home
with her new friends,
Touka-san and Inari-san.
Have you gotten used to this town?
Yeah. It's a gradual process.
Um...
Have you been to Aogami 2nd Park yet?
No, I don't think I have.
Hanabi-chan and I used to play a lot there.
It's a really nice place,
so please visit if you have the chance!
Sounds good.
I'll definitely stop by!
It seems the transfer student
is starting to get comfortable
talking with them.
This river truly is beautiful.
As are the flowers that bloom
along its banks.
Wow,
Aogami is sure full of surprises...
If you keep following this path,
you'll arrive at Aogami Shrine.
Aogami Shrine is another lovely place.
By the way, I noticed that
more people were absent today
in the class next door.
So it seems.
Plus, no one can
get in touch with them.
Do you still think it's just
a stubborn summer cold?
Yes, I believe so.
But a cold wouldn't
make them unreachable...
Could there be
another explanation?
It's a summer cold.
The Following Day
The town of Aogami is experiencing
quite the heavy rainfall today.
I can't stop thinking about yesterday.
I wanna ask someone else
about the class next door...
It's just...
Something tells me
I shouldn't bring it up.
Oh! Hey!
So, I was just talking with Suzune.
Right.
Aogami's got a festival coming up, see.
They're pulling out
all the stops this year,
so let's go together!
Wow, really?
Sounds fun!
What do they have there?
Well, there's all sorts of stalls and stuff.
Heh-heh.
Cool. What else?
Oh, you know...
There's supposed to be
something special going on,
but I don't really get it.
Either way,
we should totally go together!
Yeah! I'd love to!
Don't forget about me!
I'm coming with!
Oof!
Don't worry, I haven't forgotten.
Of course you're invited, too.
Huh?
Wh-What?
H-Hey!
Did I do something wrong?
N-No, you didn't!
...things will happen.
Huh?
I-Inari, that's just a rumor.
Transfer students must be treated well,
or bad things will happen.