Sing and cheer
utae sawage
The party goes on
utage wa tsuzuku
Break out the Oni'n'Furball Dance
mae onikemodansu
ha!
ONIKEMODANCE
Lyrics: PandaBoY
Vocals: Nakiri Ayame
yo yo yo yo
Composition: PandaBoY
Vocals: Shirakami Fubuki
kon kon kon kon
Arrangement: PandaBoY
Vocals: Ookami Mio
mion mion mion mion
Oni, fox, and canine, in the shrine!
oni kitsune inu jinjaa!
Take on a new avatar on the count of three
hifumi de shichihenge
Gather on the internet for another night
koyoi mo tsudoe intaanetto
With blessings for your fandom
oshigoto ni sachiare
This here is paradise
koko wa marude tougenkyou
One, two, and a hop, step, jump
isseeno de yoi yoi yoi
These horns light up the shadows of the night
ukiyo ni kakure tsuno hikaru
Doesn't matter where it leads
docchi demo yoi yoi yoi
Walk your own path
waga michi o ike
Swaying, yearning
yura yurari koikogare
My passions flared up in an instant
setsuna ni moyuru kono omoi wa
They are yet a fragmented message
mada wakaranai kedo
May they mature one day
minorasete
And burst out in bloom
sakimidareyo
Humans and beasts, right this way
ohito mo kemono mo tooryanse
hai hai!
Shrine dogs and foxes, jump and fly away
komainu kitsune mo tobimaware
hai hai!
Life is so very short
inochi wa mijikashi
So leave a mark, any way you can
gamushara ni kizame
A parade of good fortune, backed up by an Oni
ichi fuji ni taka de hyaku wa oni
hai hai!
Hear ye, hear ye, come one, come all
senkyakubanrai oidemase
hai hai!
It's a festival for the ages
appare omatsuri ja
Shoot for the stars
uchimakure
Sing and cheer
utae sawage
The party goes on
utage wa tsuzuku
Break out the Oni'n'Furball Dance
mae onikemodansu
ha!
yo yo yo yo
kon kon kon kon
mion mion mion mion
Come, come, let me borrow you for a minute
saa saa ote o haishaku!
Will-o'-the-wisps as my pranks
onibi tobashite itazura shitai
I want to mess and play with my dear humans
ningensama to dajare asobi
(Ready? Yo!)
(ara yo tto!)
Making a Too Sweet sign with my hands
oya ni kusuri to nakayubi tsukete
What I wub most is inari sushi
sukoru wa gekikara inarizushi
(Kon!)
(kon!)
Nothing ventured, nothing canine'd
inu mo arukeba uranai ataru
So I summon you, Hatotaurus!
ideyo shoukan Hatotaurusu
(Yikes, that made me jump!)
(uwaa! bikkuri shita!)
Enough Super Chats! Stop, stop, stop!
suupaachatto mou yoi yoi
I feel the hopes vested in those coins
koban o nagete atsu kakeru
So precious, those sweet fools
menkoi aho teetee na
Dreaming the most innocent of dreams
amaki yumemishi
Drifting in the gentle breeze
fuwa fuwari yasashii kaze
Like the falling of petals in the spring
karei ni hana ga chireru youni
As sad as it is
sukoshi setsunai kedo
Watch it unfold
mitodokete
And bloom in its place
sakihokoru wa
Specters, idols, or the gods divine
mononoke aidoru kamihotoke
hai hai!
Virtual or real, no borders within
baacharu riaru mo kakinenashi
hai hai!
Wagging our tails
shippo o furimawashi
Let's conquer it all
tenka tsukamou ze
Streaming the world I envision
shinshoufuukei namahousou
hai hai!
No borders, only broader horizons
saku wa naku tomo kisaku wa ari
hai hai!
Load your soul into the barrel
tamashii o komete
And fire away
uchimakure
Sing and cheer
utae sawage
The party goes on
utage wa tsuzuku
Break out the Oni'n'Furball Dance
mae onikemodansu
ha!
I have something to say to you
iitai koto ga aru n da yo
Animal ears sure are the bomb, yo
yappari kemomimi kawaii yo
Wub, wub, wub, wub, big wub
suko suko dai suko yappa suko
Finally, I've found you, my princess
yatto mitsuketa ojousama
Linking the past to the future
kako to mirai o tsunaideku
Pursuing dreams to the ends of the earth
yume o oikake doko made mo
I love you more than anything in this world
sekai de ichiban, aishiteru
I love you so much!
a i shi te ru!!!
Jumping, from one calling to another
shana shanari totsuideku
After the rain falls in the fox's wedding
kitsunenoyomeiri no ato ni wa
A rainbow will form
niji ga deteiru kara
Bring it all together
tsumugasete
And shine forevermore
sakitsuzukemashou
Dance forevermore
odorimashou
Humans and beasts, right this way
ohito mo kemono mo tooryanse
hai hai!
Shrine dogs and foxes, jump and fly away
komainu kitsune mo tobimaware
hai hai!
Life is so very short
inochi wa mijikashi
So leave a mark, any way you can
gamushara ni kizame
A parade of good fortune, backed up by an Oni
ichi fuji ni taka de hyaku wa oni
hai hai!
Hear ye, hear ye, come one, come all
senkyakubanrai oidemase
hai hai!
It's a festival for the ages
appare omatsuri ja
Shoot for the stars
uchimakure
Sing and cheer
utae sawage
The party goes on
utage wa tsuzuku
Break out the Oni'n'Furball Dance
mae onikemodansu
ha!
yo yo yo yo
kon kon kon kon
mion mion mion mion
Oni, fox, and canine, in the shrine!
oni kitsune inu jinjaa!
ha!