Ouch...
Watch where you're going.
You'll hurt someone otherwise.
I-I'm so sorry...
What's this girl doing here?
But I don't have time for that!
I-I gotta hurry!
She does realize the
last train left ages ago, right?
A train, at this hour?
Akane-san...
What is this?
Can't pass up a good photo op!
Whoa!
You're the girl I met
outside the station...
Call me Uzuki.
Who were you chasing after, anyway?
Oh, I know Akane-san.
We're in the same class.
Really?
I'm sure I saw her board this train.
Maybe she went to that end?
So... do you enjoy photography?
Yeah. I'm in the Photography Club.
I've taken pictures
of Akane-san and Yuka-san, too.
Huh?
You remember Yuka-san?
Huh? Well, yeah,
she's in my class.
Akane-san?!
Uzuki-san!
Tell me more about Yuka-san later!
Always in a rush, huh?
Wait up, Akane-san!
Yuka-san's disappeared!
Found you.
Huh?
Akane-san...?
Found you.
And now you're not getting away.