Oh, but you know what?
aa nandaka
The most mundane of days have started
to take on a brilliant hue lately
kawaranai hibi mo doko ka tokimekashikute
The most mundane of days have started
to take on a brilliant hue lately
kawaranai hibi mo doko ka tokimekashikute
The most mundane of days have started
to take on a brilliant hue lately
kawaranai hibi mo doko ka tokimekashikute
The most mundane of days have started
to take on a brilliant hue lately
kawaranai hibi mo doko ka tokimekashikute
The most mundane of days have started
to take on a brilliant hue lately
kawaranai hibi mo doko ka tokimekashikute
The most mundane of days have started
to take on a brilliant hue lately
kawaranai hibi mo doko ka tokimekashikute
The most mundane of days have started
to take on a brilliant hue lately
kawaranai hibi mo doko ka tokimekashikute
The most mundane of days have started
to take on a brilliant hue lately
kawaranai hibi mo doko ka tokimekashikute
The most mundane of days have started
to take on a brilliant hue lately
kawaranai hibi mo doko ka tokimekashikute
The most mundane of days have started
to take on a brilliant hue lately
kawaranai hibi mo doko ka tokimekashikute
The most mundane of days have started
to take on a brilliant hue lately
kawaranai hibi mo doko ka tokimekashikute
The most mundane of days have started
to take on a brilliant hue lately
kawaranai hibi mo doko ka tokimekashikute
Wait, what?
Upsy daisy.
Loves Singing
How do you think this episode
should go from here?
Hmm...
Don't start thinking about it!
*mumble mumble*
What?!
This is a holdup!
Gimme all yer health insurance IDs!
You got until I finish singing!
Yay!
Wait, no!
Not this one, the B-side!
Uh...?
Top Tier
WEE   B   C
WEE  B   C
I was trying too hard to show a new side of me.
You know, I was young and stupid.
My dream?
To create music that lives on in people's hearts.
Forever and ever.
What are you even trying to do?!
Tapping out?
Give me one last chance!
I promise I'll do this right!
Oh no! I'm late for school!
My name is AZKi-chi.
Condenser mics are the love of my life.
But this one's a five-eight.
A dynamic.
"What's a condenser mic?"
Allow me to explain!
Prof!
Nobody cares!
When are you gonna sing?!
I'm going to perform
at Makuhari Messe at 7 PM on March 19.
Please watch and enjoy.
What was all this for, then?!
A how-do-you-do from the idiot box!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!