It's been two weeks since the new girl
moved to the town of Aogami.
Today is her first day as a student
at the local Aogami High School.
She seems excited to make new friends,
but she's already running late.
Didn't get much sleep, it seems.
Hm? Isn't that...
That looks like the girl I saw
when I first moved here.
Oh! But I don't have time for this!
And so she rushes to Aogami High School.
Aogami High School: Classroom
Heya! Gotten used to Aogami High yet?
Oh, well, not quite...
Come on, Suzune-san.
Today's her first day here.
Yeah, give her time.
Oh, we haven't even introduced ourselves.
My name's Karamomo Suzune!
Nice to meetcha!
Suzune-san seems like
a candid and curious girl.
I'm Ibara Saki.
I'm on the Groundskeeping Committee,
where I tend to the flower beds.
Saki-san is a pillar of the class,
on whom everyone relies.
Her family runs the local florist's,
and she has two younger sisters.
My name is Yukihara Touka.
Welcome to our class.
Touka-san is the top student in their grade.
It seems she's very good friends
with Suzune-san.
My, but you are a pulchritudinous one.
Pulchri...
Wha? What's that mean?
It means she is very beautiful.
I agree. Why, she's like a porcelain doll!
Th-Thank you.
It would seem
she's unaccustomed to compliments.
By the way, did you see
the flower bed by the lockers?
No, not yet.
I hope you'll take a look
on your way home today.
It's a bed of red spider lilies.
Quite unique.
Red spider lilies?
That's certainly unique.
Many people find them unsettling,
but they're very beautiful flowers.
You simply must have a look.
Wh-What was that?
Those two were acting strangely...
One Hour Later.
With first period over,
the transfer student has started to relax a bit.
But just then,
two more classmates come to speak to her.
Hey there, transfer kid!
Hello...
The name's Hanabi!
And this here's Inari!
U-Um...
I-I just want to say...
If you ever need anything, please ask!
Whoa!
I-Inari!
T-Take it easy!
You're startling the transfer kid!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
You see, I'm the class representative,
and...
Inari! You gotta speak loudly and clearly!
Th-That startled me.
I gotta say, Hanabi-san seems
more like a class rep than Inari-san...
Inari's an earnest girl.
She just gets ahead of herself sometimes!
She used to be super quiet, though!
I-I wanted to become more self-reliant.
So I've been making an effort,
and...
So, hey!
I wanna know all about you,
so tell us about yourself!
H-Hanabi-chan,
you take it easy, too.
It's okay!
I wanna get to know you two, too!
Glad to have you!
Transfer kid!