TONIGHT
♪ On a path with blooming flowers
AT LONG LAST
♪ To the sky of our dreams☠
THE TONE-DEAF QUEEN WILL BE DECIDED
"Damn, this dogfight's hard to watch..."
It's the show you've all been waiting for!
Our new music show,
Right-on Rhythm Cinderella, starts today!
I, Yozora Mel, will be your host!
And our guests today are...
Known in hololive for
my song of ruin,
I'm Yuzuki Choco!
All hustle, all muscle!
Known in hololive for my baby voice,
I'm Shirogane Noel.
We have two of hololive's famed
tone-deaf members here with us today.
Wha, did you just say tone-deaf?
No!
I'm not tone-deaf!
I'm not!
They told me I'd get to
become a Cinderella if I came...
So, in this show, we're going
to see if you can sing
a song a capella, with perfect timing.
We'll play the beginning of
the song for you as a hint,
then it's up to you to sing it to the beat.
The person who wins today will be
our Right-on Rhythm Cinderella,
and our loser will be
our first-ever Tone-Deaf Queen.
Those are the stakes today.
So it's sink or swim?!
And there's only two of us,
so it's one-on-one!
Let's hear the first song.
Music...
Start!
It's "I Met a Bear"!
Do you know it?
I've heard this before!
I guess it is a pretty commonly-known
song in the human world.
So, "I Met a Bear" comes to 17.6 seconds.
First up, let's have...
Noel-chan!
Oh!
Really, me?
Get right on rhythm!
Shirogane Noel gives it a shot!
Who's going to become our
Right-on Rhythm Cinderella today?
Music...
Start!
♪ The other day, out in the woods, I met a bear
♪ On a path with blooming flowers
♪ I met a bear
Okay!
That was perfect, wasn't it?
I might sing off-pitch but I'm pretty sure
my sense of rhythm is pretty good.
So, Noel-chan's time was...
16.8 seconds!
That's a difference
of just 0.8 seconds!
I did it!
Yes!
I see...
I'm not going to make this easy.
I'm probably the same.
My pitch is pretty off
but I think I'll be okay with this.
I'll have no trouble beating
a small-fry like Noel-sama!
Winner if within 0.8 seconds!
Yuzuki Choco takes the stage!
Music...
Start!
♪ The other day, out in the woods, I met a bear
♪ On a path with blooming flowers
♪ I met a bear
See? I told you.
That was...
16.6 seconds!
That makes it a difference of 1 second!
YES!
Aaaaaah!
No way!
That means that the winner
of our first round is Noel-chan!
One more! One more, please!
ONE MORE, PLEEEASE!!
Everyone watching this
is probably thinking,
"Damn, this dogfight's hard to watch..."
The second song is...
Music...
Start!
Are we doing "guess the song"?
I know!
I-It's "Yumemiru Sora He"!
It is "Yumemiru Sora He"!
♪ Holding one another's hands and never letting go
This is a hololive song, so obviously
that means that there's no excuse
for not getting it perfect.
So, "Yumemiru Sora He" comes to
9.1 seconds!
I'm going to count the beat on my fingers.
Let's do this.
That's so low-tech.
Revenge using old-school tactics!
Yuzuki Choco stands strong!
Music...
Start!
♪ Holding one another's hands and never letting go
♪ Here we go! (Let's go!)
♪ To the sky of our dreams☠
And your time was...
8.7 seconds!
That's a difference of 0.4 seconds.
Seriously, 0.4 seconds?!
Darn!
Wow!
You did well, Choco-sen.
Dammit, that's pretty good...
Sorry, Noel-sama.
Thanks for letting me take the lead.
Cross under the 0.4-second barrier!
Shirogane Noel perseveres!
Music...
Start!
♪ Holding one another's hands and never letting go
♪ Here we go! (Let's go!)
♪ To the sky of our dreams
How was that?
That was decent, wasn't it?
So, your time was...
9.0 seconds!
Huh?!
That's a difference of just 0.1 seconds!
Seriously?
YESSS!
Seriously?!
That's amazing!
Oh no.
Has my tone-deaf cover been blown?
You were just faking it?
Dur-hur-hur!
Results
That means our first
Right-on Rhythm Cinderella is...
Noel-chan!
Congratulations!
Yay!
I'm going to call myself hololive's
"Right-on Rhythm Cinderella" from this day forth!
Which also means,
that our loser, Choco-sensei...
Congratulations!
You're our first-ever Tone-Deaf Queen!
That doesn't make me happy at all!
Why "congratulations"?
You should do a singing stream
with the Tone-Deaf Queen some time.
If you enjoyed this video,
please like and subscribe to
the official hololive channel.
Same with our channels as well!
That's it for now.
We'll see you next time!
See you!
Starring
Yozora Mel
Shirogane Noel
Yuzuki Choco
Right-on Rhythm Cinderella
was brought to you by Yozora Mel...
...Shirogane Noel, and...
...Yuzuki Choco!