Riririri
Volume lowered
for your sanity
SHUT THE HELL UP!
Hype Meter
Good morning, girls!
Good morning!
A-chan!
Yes?
What are we doing today?
The four of you will be answering
some of my questions today.
It's a very simple episode!
That's it?
Sounds super easy.
Aren't you just making fun
of vawiety shows?
Ooh, Director Luna weighs in!
Were they that big of a deal?
I've got the "good stuff" with me today.
Something valuable?
No, it's not.
Let me explain!
The "good stuff" I have with me
is this Hype Meter!
It's a fun item that lets me control
the hype levels of everyone around me!
I snuck it into the studio
to use on a bunch of people!
Let's get straight to it and
try cranking this up to 100%.
100%... there we go.
All right, girls! Go all out and
give us your best self intros!
Let's start from Subaru-san!
'SUUUUUP!
From hololive 2nd Gen...
It's me, Oozora Schubau!
Ooh!
You can't do anything without POWER!
Thanks for having me today!
She's flexing her guns.
Okay, next!
LA-LION!
I'M SHISHIRO BOTAN FROM
hololive 5th GEN!
You sound a lot like a cheer captain.
THANKS FOR HAVING ME!
MAXIMUM EFFORT!
Maximum effort, indeed.
I'll do my best!
You sound a lot growlier!
Thanks for the intro!
Yup!
A-quality day to you all!
I'm Minato Aqua
and Aqua's gonna aqua
you all in her aqua.
Don't screw with us!
GAAAAAA!
hololive 4th GEN'S
HIMEMORI LUNA
WUVS YOU
ALLLLL!
Thank you so much!
THANKSIIIES!
Yikes.
I'm worried that Luna-san's
stamina won't hold out.
Anyways, thanks for
being here today, girls!
THANKS FOR HAVING US!
Questions from A-chan
Favorite Food
So, girls!
Can you tell me
what your favorite foods are?
Watermelon for me.
Ah! Watermelon, I see.
For me... meat!
As a carnivore should.
I love omurice!
Ah, that's cute.
Takoyaki for me!
That's nice!
How adorable.
You girls do mention your favorite foods
quite often, don't you?
Okay! Let's do this... and...
All right! Let's check again!
Can you tell me what your
favorite food is again, Subaru-san?
Uh...
Water.
That's not a food.
Is water considered food?
Well...
I just drink water
when I can't eat anything.
(Survival PoV)
Ah, you mean that... yeah...
Ah, to survive
as long as possible, I see...
Good point.
Okay, how about Botan-san?
It's meat, right?
You love meat, don't you?
Uh...
Miso soup, I guess...
It tastes too heavy if you
add meat and the like and, uh...
I like my meals simple.
"I like my meals simple." LOL
Okay, thanks for that answer.
Then, uh... Aqua-san!
What's your favorite food?
Pickled food.
Pickled food, okay.
What kind of pickled food?
Just curious.
Radishes.
Radishes, I see.
Don't bring up anything but radishes.
Radishes are the best.
Radishes are the best? Got it.
Luna-san! What's your favorite food?
Sesame seed.
Sesame seed?
Wait, a single one?!
I stick a single one
to my finger and lick it.
That's kinda disgusting.
That'll get caught on your teeth, right?
There's a monster that does that, right?
There is, yeah.
What, the Sesame Licker?
I'm kinda tired now...
You're tired?!
Yeah.
We just started!
I wanna go home.
Come on!
We're Nonstop hololive!
Nonstop hololive!
Pitstop hololive!
Okay.
Yeah.
Nobody's saying a word. LOL
Questions from A-chan
Goals for the Future?
This question might get personal,
but can you girls tell me
your goals for the future?
They say you gotta dream big, so...
Uh-huh.
Okay! Let's get started!
Aqua-san!
What's your goal for the future?
Create my own nightclub, yo!
A nightclub, yo!
With champagne towers, yo!
Yaaay!
Let's all party the night away
with champagne towers, yo!
WHOOO!
PARTY NIGHT, YO!
Untz ♪
How about you, Botan-san?
What's your goal for the future?
Uh...
Live a long life.
LOL
Huh?!
Live a long life.
That's a long time, yo!
Live a long life?
How about you, Luna-san?
UOOOH!
MY GWOALS?
MY GWOAL IS...
What's she saying? LOL
WIVVING OFF PASSIVE INCOME!
Wow!
Our princess has no goals!
I mean it sounds like a goal
but doesn't seem like one.
IT'S A GOAL!
UOOOH!
Can I ask you for your future goals,
Subaru-san?
* This building is just a depiction.
I'M GONNA TAKE OVER HOLOLIVE!
Take over?!
What's gonna happen to YAGOO-san (CEO)
after you take over?
A PEACEFUL RETIREMENT!
How generous!
TO THE BOONIES!
That's really gene—
Let's try playing Shiritori
Okay! Luna-san, start us off!
The "Ri" from Shiritori!
Riiii
Riririri
Flow with the rhythm!
(Rizumu ni noru ze)
Flow with the...
(Rizumu...)
Flow with the rhythm!
(Rizumu ni noru ze)
She sounds like a cat that found treasure.
Yaaay!
"Mu!" "Mu," "mu," "mu"!
"Mu" next?
Oh, it was "Mu" from "Rhythm (Rizumu)," huh!
Got it! "Mu" it is, yes?
You're next, Botan-san!
Please continue from "Mu"!
Tasteless & Odorless!
(Mumi mushuu)
LOL
Oh! "Tasteless & Odorless"?
Tasteless & Odorless!
"Tasteless & Odorless", huh.
Why'd you go with that?
WHO NEEDS A REASON?!
IT'S SHIRITORI!
YOU WANT A REASON IN SHIRITORI?!
(Everyone: "Don't ask for a reason why.")
I'm sorry! I stuck my nose in too deep!
Okay! The "U" from
"Tasteless & Odorless (Mumi mushuu)" next!
Go ahead, Aqua-san!
Volume lowered
for your sanity
Huh? What's she saying?
Did her internet go bad?
Volume lowered
for your sanity
SHUT THE HELL UP!
(Uruseee!)
Okay, let's just roll with that!
ALL RIGHT!
Okay! That's a big success!
WHOO!
There's no such thing as
"success" in Shiritori!
Is it, though?
Ah...
It defeats the whole purpose.
You making fun of the game?
No, I'm not!
YOU GIVE IT A GO TOO, A-CHAN!
Girls, there's no need for that!
YOU'RE DOING IT TOO!
DO IT!
YEAH!
Come on, now. Wait just a minute!
The "Bu" from hololive (hororaibu)!
hololive's "Bu"?
"Bu"... uh...
COME ON, A-CHAN! SAY IT!
HOW HIGH DO I CRANK THIS?!
HOW HIGH?!
500%?!
HOW HIGH DO YOU WANT IT!
YOU WANT IT AT 500% RIGHT?!
OKAY!
I want to be proposed to
by a prince at the castle ball!
(Butoukai no oshiro de oujisama ni
kekkon moushikomaretai!)
(Desire for Marriage)
"I" next.
LOL
If you have a complaint, out with it.
An All-Out Message
To all the Fans!
Airs at 8 AM every Sunday
on the COVER-hololive Network
*Not an actual network
Guys! Thanks so much
for watching today!
Let's meet again
in the next video!
This sounds like an
anime for little girls... LOL
AND AFTER
YOU FINISH WATCHING,
TAKE A SHOWER,
BRUSH YOUR TEETH,
AND GO TO BED!
Do you wanna rap?
WHY NOT?!
Then I'mma go fer' it!
Why don't you just do it?
Go for it! We'll get
some good content!
Just do it! (lol)
I'll let Luna close us off, yo!
Three... two... one...
(Minato Aqua tossing
the mic to her kouhai)
The poor girl. LOL
The literal devil.
If y'all enjoyed the video,
like it & subscribe to all our channels!
Boom
Mic check ★
Drop all the likes and thumb-ups!
Sounds like some music
you'd hear at the supermarket.
Keep on coming back!
Like, at some random grocer's.
Let's all have fun!
She's a rockstar.
OH YEEEAAAH!
She's being a rockstar?
YAAAY!