So you... must be the transfer student.
Hee-hee.
W-Wait!
What I saw really happened, right?
There was a quake,
and then the ceiling collapsed...
But it's like nothing happened.
H-Hanabi-san!
I'm so glad you're okay!
Ha... Hanabi-san?
Something's not right. Her clothes are pristine,
and there's not a scratch on her.
What's more, she seems...
somehow... doll-like...
The name's Hanabi!
And this here's Inari!
Wh-What are you talking about,
Hanabi-san?
The name's Hanabi!
And this here's Inari!
Inari-san isn't even here...
The name's Hanabi!
And this here's Inari!
I-Inari-san?
A-Are you all right?
Transfer students must be treated well,
or bad things will happen.
What's that mean?
Is it my fault?
Did this happen because
I came to Aogami High School?
Why won't you talk to me?
We're friends... aren't we?
Ahh!
Hanabi-san! Inari-san!
Hang in there!
I'm coming to save you!
Having fun at school?
But it's time to go home now.
T-To go home?
What are you talking about?
Come, let's get going.
Now.
Please, wait for me!
I need to ask you something!
Ergh!
What's happening...?
What...
Where... am I?
What's keeping you?
Let's head back already...
transfer student.