how to be a better vampire big castle
big castle
That's it!
Want a Big Home? Call us!
Whoa!
Hmm...
What's up?
Which property
would you recommend, Sui-chan?
Oho?
I'm the
Executive Real Estate Master, Sui-chan.
Do you really have one
that'd meet my standards?
Ah, castles?
Yup. I want to be more vampire-y.
Look what this one has.
Furniture!
Appliances!
And bats!
Bath and coffin separate!
However,
it doesn't have a post box...
Oof, that's a nope.
And this one?
It has me interested.
It's a newish designer castle!
Friend A
Graveyard nearby. Little sunlight.
5 hour walk from the station.
Seems good.
Yeah, but...
It doesn't feel right.
You got a better one?
Yeah, here.
Say... what?!
100 rooms, and the rent's just 3K yen?
No churches nearby!
Plus all-you-can-read J*jo.
This is the one, Mel-chan!
Hello? Is this DEKADEKA?
I'd like to schedule a property visit.
You fool.
This castle is bait
to lure you vampires out!
I'm not a vampire.
I'm an umpire!
Strike!
Call DEKADEKA for all your castle needs.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!