All right, you maggots!
Listen up!
Huh?
What's going on?
What's happening?
You trying out a heel turn?
If they put their minds to it,
humans can do anything
in just 10 seconds!
So today, I'm going to be
your 10-second drill sergeant!
Now introduce yourself in 10 seconds!
Uh... okay?
Sure... I'll try.
Noerun, you start!
Ah!
Just like that?
All hustle, all muscle, everyone!
I'm hololive 3rd Gen's
muscle-brained knight,
Shirogane Noel!
Muscles!
Muscles!!
Yaaay!
I think that's just about 10 seconds.
That's okay, right?
Let's move on. Koyorin!
You're next!
Okay!
Ayo, everybody!
Coming at you from hololive 6th Gen,
I'm the brains of holoX,
Hakui Koyori!
Happy to be here! Yaaay!
Awoooooo!
That was pretty good.
It was. She even added in a howl.
All right, Sakamata!
You're next!
Snort snort...
Snort!
Hello!
Uh...
So, uh...
I'm holoX's... uh...
Well... screw it.
I'm Sakamata Chloe!
Thanks for having me!
Hey...
Come on!
How long have you
been here already?!
That's cause for
a performance review.
I blazed through my intro!
It's just a self-intro!
It ain't rocket science!
10-Second Pressure Survival
The three of you will be taking on
various different challenges
with a 10-second timer.
Every one of them
is suuuper simple!
What's this?
A duck!
However...
What's this?
If you fail...
A swan...?
This video will end instantly!
Instant End
What?!
Seriously?!
The whole video will end?
Yep. It'll end and that's no joke.
You better survive under the pressure
and beat that weak mind
of yours into shape!
It'll end even if we fail
just the first challenge?
OBVIOUSLY!
If you fail the first challenge...
The only thing that'll get uploaded
is a video with me
on some weird hype train
and your self-introductions!
Nooo!
Anything but that!
Spare us!
Let's hit the ground running!
Roger!
Dodger!
Pick the challenge you want
to take on from within this list!
Shiritori
One-off Gag
What's This?
Calculation
Kanji
Quiz
All right!
Which one would you prefer?
I'd like to let Noel-senpai pick first.
You mind?
That's a good idea.
Let's see...
She said they're all simple,
so maybe Quiz is
an easy one to start with...
Good point!
Let's get an easy dub!
Yup!
You're all sure, then?
I'll provide the question for the quiz.
The correct answer will
always be 3 syllables.
For example, if the answer is "Fubuki,"
Who comes to mind when
you think of hololive and foxes?
Noerun will write "Fu,"
Fu
Koyori "bu,"
bu
and Chloe-chan "ki."
ki
The three of you must match your
answers perfectly, or else you will fail.
Arrange the answers perfectly to pass!
Oh, okay!
Yup.
So it's a test of our friendship...
Okay, let's get straight to it!
Here's the question!
What's the name of the type of bear that has
characteristic white and black fur and mainly eats bamboo?
Okay! Countdown starts...
Now!
Really? This simple?
This is too easy!
I was worried for nothing!
Noel will write the first syllable,
Koyorin the second,
and Chloe-chan the third.
Oh, right!
Crap!
All right, time's up!
What happened?
Let's take a look at your answers!
What did you do?
Chloe-tan?
Chloe-tan...?
Is everything okay?
Chloe-chan?
Let's not waste any time!
Let's look at the correct answer!
Here it is! Reveal it!
Pa
n
Panda
Pan...panda.
WHAT THE HECK'S A PANPANDA?!
Hey... are you kidding me?
HEEEY!
The show will end shortly.
Thank you for supporting us
throughout the years.
Were you even listening earlier?!
DAMMIT, SAKAMATA!
I got confused!
Your writing's a mess too!
My writing's got
nothing to do with this!
This is an epic fail!
And that means...
It's the end of the show!
Goodbye everyone!
Please like the video
and subscribe to everyone's channels!
THIS CAN'T BE REAL!
I'M SORRY!
I'M SO SORRY!
DAMMIT, NEWBIE!
Hey, Sakamata?
I'm sorry. I really am.
I'm truly sorry.
Please!
I don't want it to end like this!
I said one syllable per person.
I'll cry as much as you want!
Can we get just one redo...?
You'll cry for us? Okay.
You get 10 seconds.
Yeah...
Okay...
Beg for that second chance
with sincerity.
Are you ready?
We'll begin now, okay?
Got it...
Ready? Start!
Um, well... it's really...
It's really because
of my newbness
that we ended up like this.
Please give us one more chance!
I'M SO SORRY!
Perfect!
All right, let's give it
one more try then!
Very good indeed.
I'm really sorry! 😭
That's great!
Second Wind from Crying!
It's your comeback!
Thank goodness!
All right!
I'm so happy...
This is your last chance, got it?
Yes.
It's all over the next time you fail.
Chloe-tan, do your best, okay?
I will!
I'm sorry!
I really am!
Let's pick a challenge then, shall we?
Shiritori
One-off Gag
What's This?
Calculation
Kanji
Quiz
Something that
we can't fail no matter what
would be nice.
Yeah!
I don't wanna end too soon.
I wanna play for a bit longer.
How about "What's This"?
It seems simple enough, right?
That's true!
Good point!
If it's as simple as the quiz earlier
we'll definitely be fine!
Yeah!
Is that your pick, then?
All you need to do
is name the object shown
What's this?
Carrot!
Bamboo shoot!
Onion!
to clear this challenge.
Challenge Cleared!
The objects shown are
all common, everyday objects.
There's no way
you can't answer these.
Turn Order
Koyori
Chloe
Noel
Okay, let's begin!
Ready?
What's this?
Kendama!
Takoyaki!
What's this?
Camel!
Challenge Cleared!
We made it! Phew!
That's great!
Good job, girls!
That was perfect!
You passed!
In what world would
camels be an everyday sight?!
Good point.
I had to do a double-take!
Let's move on to
the next challenge, shall we?
If you pick Shiritori,
you just need to complete
1 round in 10 seconds.
It's pretty simple, actually.
That makes things a lot easier!
We'll probably be fi—
Never mind. I'm not one to talk.
Emotional Damage
Have faith in yourself!
Stay strong!
Chloe-chan!
We'll go in this order:
Noel, Koyorin, then Sakamata.
Ugh...
Okay!
Got it!
You took a deep breath there, didn't you?
Guess I'm the anchor...?
Are you sure you'll be fine? I heard that!
I'll do my best!
Turn Order
Noel
Koyori
Chloe
The first character is hololive's "Bu"!
Warrior (Bushi)!
Uh...
Shi... shi...
Whitebait (Shirasu)!
Sushi!
Challenge Cleared!
Ooh!
That was close!
Great job!
You had me worried there
for a sec, Koyorin.
I couldn't think of anything
when I got "Shi."
I could've just said
"Happiness (Shiawase)"
and yet I went with
"Whitebait (Shirasu)."
And you ran with it!
Sounds delicious.
What do you girls wanna pick next?
There's Calculation...
...Kanji...
...One-off Gag...
You're squeezing that one in.
Anything but One-off Gag...
Anything's fine but that.
How about we go with Kanji?
Let's run with that, then!
Yeah!
Got it!
Kanji, it is, yeah?
Same as earlier, each of you
just needs to read 1 kanji
within 10 seconds to pass.
The kanji I'll be throwing
are 5th grader level.
How do you read this?
Weather
Wea・ther
We should be fine!
I'm sure you can
definitely read them.
Turn Order
Chloe
Koyori
Noel
Okay then! Are you ready?
How do you read this?
Single
Sin・gle
White Horse
White ・ Horse
Lively
Live・ly
Challenge Cleared!
You're all correct!
Phew! That was easy!
I'm so relieved!
Those were all level 1 kanji, after all.
You're too lenient.
I suppose the next challenge
is Calculation?
Any one of you feeling confident?
Me!
I'll definitely be okay!
Trust me, I'm a scientist!
Turn Order
Noel
Chloe
Koyori
Without further ado...
The answer is...?
9 divided by 3 is...
Huh?
Oh? Was that...
What?
Challenge Cleared!
Nope, it's a pass!
All right!
That was cutting it close.
That question was way
harder than I expected!
Yeah!
It sure was hard!
No more division-based questions off the bat.
That spooked the heck out of me.
You pretty much used
half of the time given.
5 seconds
Yep, sure did! Even so...
Koyorin is just way too good.
She saved our bacon!
Yeah! She really is!
I definitely didn't think the
equation would get swapped around.
If we had failed just now
and it was on me,
I'd probably have been
bashed for mouthing off!
Regardless, that was
a fine play from you.
You did great!
Great job!
Okay, next challenge!
Personally...
I think the three of us
can all agree on wanting
to pass the quiz
at least once, right?
Well, that's true.
You're right!
Yeah!
One syllable per person, okay?
Got it!
ONE. SYLLABLE. PER. PERSON. GOT IT?
The order will be
Noerun, Koyori, and then Sakamata!
Panda
She's reminding me twice!
Turn Order
Noel
Koyori
Chloe
Okay! Here's the quiz!
In the French novelist,
Maurice Leblanc's pièce de résistance,
What?
Huh?
the protagonist is a thief named Arsene XXX.
What is his surname?
lololol
W-W-Wait up.
Hang on. The difficulty's spiked!
Let's do this!
That spike came outta nowhere.
Isn't that just weird?
Come on...
But it's a piece of cake, isn't it?
What?
It's basically the name
of a famous thief!
Ah!
It's probably...
It's Arsene...?
Actually,
never mind.
Oh, is this the answer?
I have no clue!
Put your pens down!
Let's look at those answers!
Lu
pi
n
Lupin! That's correct!
That was so close!
All right!
We got it!
My gut feeling was on point!
We passed the Quiz challenge!
You finally synced your answers!
I'm so proud of you three!
Thank goodness...
I'm just so happy!
(Tears of Happiness)
Okay! I'm sure you'll be
able to clear the next challenge.
You've only done "What's This?" once.
Do you wanna do it again?
Good point.
That's true...
So you're picking "What's This?" then?
Turn Order
Noel
Koyori
Time for the What's This? Challenge!
Ready?
What's this?
Huh?
What the...?
The heck...
Noerun?
Uh...
Um...
Scarecrow...?
Wait...
A torii gate...?
No...
TIME'S UP!
That's a fail! Okay!
The video's gonna end here, BUT!
Is there anyone here
who knows what this is?
Me!
I think it's...
Go ahead, Koyorin!
What is this...?
...a Totem Pole?
That's correct! Goodbye!
Please like the video
and subscribe to everyone's channels!
Wait, it's over?!
No! It's over!
Bye-bye...
It's the end!
Bye-bye!
Nooo!