I—
I can't bear this!
Okay!
Delish-horse!
No good!
Why?!
Time to play the game where
your reactions trump all!
Extreme Reaction Word Coliseum!
Yay!
Wowowow!
Wow wow wow!
In this game,
Extreme Reaction Word Coliseum,
we will give you a situation,
and we'll see if you can react
with a word that perfectly fits!
Oh! How does this work?
What do we do?
For example, if someone messed up
and drank 100°C tea,
they could say like, "Tea-owch!"
Heh
Or, if someone ran into a fish from behind,
they could say, "Glub, glub, I'm so sorry!"
Is this hell?
I'm getting some brimstone vibes.
Is this the game from hell?
Find the perfect words to react in a way
that wouldn't make the listener think twice.
I'll be judging them based on
whether or not I like them.
Questioner and judge
Sakura Miko
For those who fail a reaction,
If they mess up, they'll be
struck by lightning and shrink!
Three lightning strikes and you're out!
you'll be struck by lightning!
And you'll become smaller and smaller.
What?!
So everybody be careful!
The official channel sure has been unsafe lately.
Right?
Lightning
Guillotines
Exploding balloons
That's true. A lot of
unsafe things happening lately.
It's time to start reacting!
Okay!
Let's start with Lamy-tan!
Your reaction when a cow's horn
pokes you in the butt!
Ready, go!
Hey, moo-ve it!
Oh, nice. That was cute.
Botan-tan!
Your reaction when a cat bites your hand!
Ready, go!
Ow!
Stop it myooow!
Okay!
Yeah, that works.
Aki-chan!
Your reaction when a bear suddenly appears!
Ready, go!
I—
I can't bear this!
Okay!
Now, next...
R-Really?
Are you sure about that?!
Lamy-tan!
Yeah!
Okay!
Your reaction when you eat horse meat! Go!
Delish-horse!
No good!
Why?!
I have no idea what the criteria are!
Why not that one?
It was a bit too simple,
and...
I just didn't like it!
Isn't that just
your own personal opinion?!
She did say it was
based on if she liked them.
Tell that to the person
who made the situation!
You've got a point.
I guess I'll look past it and let it pass.
So it's okay to complain
about the judgment?!
Next!
Botan-tan!
Your reaction when you get hit by a car!
Ready, go!
Screech!
Aaahhh!
Bam!
Crash!
Well, that's a lightning strike.
Yeah, that was definitely
a little too relaxed.
When you're getting hit by a car,
I'd want to see a louder reaction there.
I see. Huh, okay.
Now it's time for you
to take your lightning!
I'm chargin' up!
Hah! She shrunk!
I shrunk!
This is what happens when you shrink,
Cute!
so you two also better be careful.
You might just end up
as a speck of dust, in the end,
Oh no!
so this is a game to the death.
Uh-oh!
Okay, here we go!
Two more and she's gone.
Next! Aki-chan!
Your reaction when you see
a fly flying at an incredible speed!
Ready, go!
B—
Bzzzoooom!
Okay!
Let's move on!
That was okay?!
Lamy-tan!
Okay!
Your reaction when you see a clock stop!
Ready, go!
Um!
Uh, uh...
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick...
Sorry! I've got nothing!
Lightning!
For when a clock stops?!
What should I have said?
For this, let's see...
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick...
Oh, that...
It's time for a snack!
Ahh! I want pudding!
Yeah!
So where was the relevant reaction?
It was, "I want pudding."
Certainly a unique reaction!
I'm not sure we can
let that one slide, Mikochi.
I think you should get a lightning strike
along with Lamy-chan.
No way! I'm the host!
They shrunk!
Oh my.
So small.
This makes no sense!
Two more and they're gone.
Okay, next is Botan-tan!
Okay!
Your reaction when you drop some money!
Ready, go!
Clink clink!
Oh!
My Benjamins!
That was the sound of Benjamins?!
I don't think so!
Benjamins make noise, too.
I guess that's an okay.
Nice.
For the Benjamins.
Aki-chan! Your reaction when
you're kicked in the shin with high heels!
Ready, go!
Y—
You spotted a sensitive spot!
Spot! Spot!
Okay!
You're just okaying whatever!
Lamy-tan! Your reaction when
a gun is pointed at you!
Ready, go!
Waaah!
I'm...
I'm gunning for a long life,
so I beg you, please!
I've had enough of this!
So having a gun pointed at you,
you're going with gunning for a long life?
Can I go now?
You just wanna eat that lightning
and get outta here, huh?
Sometimes a lightning strike
can be your salvation.
Next!
Two more and she's gone.
One more and she's gone.
Botan-tan!
Yeah.
Your reaction when a squid approaches you!
Go!
Oh man! Are you squidding me?!
Okay!
Great! That's what I want!
That's the good stuff.
Like that, huh?
Aki-chan!
Your reaction when you bump into a mouse!
Go!
Squeak, squeak!
That squeaking hurts!
Just give me that sweet salvation.
Please!
You want the lightning?
This is the first time I've seen
someone be so happy for it.
This game is getting weird.
Next!
Two more and she's gone.
One more and she's gone.
Lamy-tan!
Your reaction when you
get splashed with water!
Go!
Wah! Splash!
Ahhh!
It's cold! Feels great!
Whoaaa...
-ter slide!
Lightning, get her!
Thank you!
See ya in the afterlife!
Lamy-tan!
She disappeared!
Yukihama Lamy
w a s t e d
Well then, what did you think about today?
It seemed like the situations
that were given to me,
the ones like "I can't bear it,"
were all pretty obvious to work with.
I couldn't really do
anything more with them,
and actually, I'm still a little unsure
about what you wanted.
Thank you very much.
I also...
Desk: -10 HP
Miko-senpai!
Where's the emotion?!
I mean!
I'm the most confused one here!
Judging these is way too hard!
S-Sorry!
Is Lamy-chan coming back or not?
There she is!
Just barely there!
Yep. This one's definitely
going down in infamy.
Thank you very much!
Thank you, everyone!
If you liked this video,
please hit the like button
and subscribe to the official channel and
the channels of today's participants!
We hope to see you again!
See ya!
Starring
Sakura Miko
Yukihana Lamy
Shishiro Botan
Aki Rosenthal
Today's program was
brought to you by Sakura Miko...
...Yukihana Lamy...
...Shishiro Botan, and...
...Aki Rosenthal!