I want a quirk!
Where did that come from?
I mean, you know... I only have two ears,
and I talk normally...
Pekekeko!
I don't think she's a good point of comparison.
I'll give you just what you need, then.
Listen up, Sora-chan...
I think she's fine as she is.
Dammit... Dammit!
And here we have Sora
grabbing tissues with hate.
The hell you making her do?!
Yeah, that won't do.
...This belly button's kind of a nuisance.
Less is more, as they say!
What now?
Okay, let's do a comedy routine.
Your fault for giving her stupid ideas!
I'll be the straight man.
Give me some material.
Uh... Uh...
I'm Tsunocandy Watame!
Actually, my horns are croissants.
Mimicry time.
A pteranodon drumming!
Ain't you a sheep?!
You both have issues!
Sora-chan, I think you're plenty quirky...
No, no, this isn't good enough.
I need to broaden my horizons!
Look what I found!
You there. Do you have express permission?
For what?
You must submit a formal request to play this.
Wild pianos are an endangered species, you see.
Oh...
Then I should help preserve them!
Please donate!
All for pianos,
pianos for all!
This isn't enough. I need a better plan.
Oh, I know. I can just become a piano myself.
So
La
I feel like this piano's tuning is a bit off.
Sorry, I don't have perfect pitch, only relative.
Some piano you are!
Boo!
Gwaaargh!
Uh... That's hella quirky.
More of the same in 2022!
Here's to another year together!