We raise the cubs with the pluck
to claw their way back up.
That is how we lions roll.
Uh... since when have I been
your cub?!
Don't take shortcuts!
Ma!
Get back up here on your own two feet.
Oi!
Quit ruining
the lore!
Pa!
Whoa!
Raising a child this wa...
She trying to say something?
...so last centur...
Hmm?
Positive reinforcement work...
Screw this! I'll go over there!
Whoops, broke the trampoline.
Huh?
Where's Shishiro?
Holy...
Real lions are a different beast, huh?
...rr...
What?
Grawr! Rawr!
She's returned to lion.
And there you have it.
O...kay?
What now?
Grrr...
Cho cute!
Where do you want to be pet?
Grawr...
There, there.
Do you like it here?
Or is this better?
Gah...
(Stop it!)
Rawr...
(Don't touch me!)
Guess I'll call the doggo police.
Gimme da finger!
Korone-senpai, you're a canine too.
Got any ideas?
Lions...
are felines!
Rawr! A wild Shishiro Botan appeared!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!