This hot spring is really hot!
I'm driving my UFO right now.
I'd like to hear about
today's special at KFP.
What?!
Now?!
Surprise Calls Minus the Surprise
La-lion!
On the main channel, la-lion!
Anyway, good morning!
I'm Shishiro Botan.
And here I am in a video
on the main channel
doing the opening all by myself.
This is giving me a bit of anxiety here.
Well, to explain what we're doing today,
it's an official surprise call program!
Yay!
By myself, yay!
Yay yay yay yay!
Peace peace!
We're going to surprise call
these three people today!
From 4th Gen, Tsunomaki Watame!
Next, from ID, Airani Iofifteen!
And finally, from EN, Takanashi Kiara.
Making surprise calls all over the world!
This should be fun!
A-chan
But!!
Actually, these aren't
regular surprise calls!
We told these three in advance
that they'd get a call today!
They're ready and waiting
to have a little fun with the call!
A-chan
And also!
Botan has been acting like she doesn't know
anything about this, but she does!
Basically...
it's all a put-on!
Now then, how will these surprise calls go?!
Okay! Who's our
very special first participant?
It's 4th Gen's Tsunomaki Watame!
Watame-senpai is first.
I wonder what she's up to.
Let's give her a call!
Surprise call starts now!
Exciting.
I really do wonder what's she doing.
Excitement. Excitement!
Hello?
Hey!
How are you doing?
I'm good!
Yeah? What are you up to right now?
I was just about to get in the bath.
You're gonna take a bath?
Right in front of me?
Yeah.
You sure about that?
Where are you?
Getting in the bath, so at home?
No, I'm not.
I'm at a hot spring!
I'm naked as a jaybird right now.
Really?
I'm gonna get in now, okay?
You're naked?!
Oh, sure.
Yeah, can I?
I'm gonna hop in.
Sure.
Splash!
Hey, did you rinse yourself first?!
Huh? Do what now?
You gotta rinse yourself before you get in!
What now?
Bath Manners
Before you get in, use a bucket of hot water
to rinse your body of excess dirt.
You gotta rinse your body to
get rid of dirt before you get in!
This hot spring's kinda brown and murky.
It says...
Oh, one of those.
Ow!
Hot!
It's... huh?
What?
This hot spring is really hot!
There are green onions
and stuff in here! Weird!
Sounds like a boiling issue.
Is there anything else in there?
Let's see.
Tofu...
Okay.
Shirataki noodles...
Shirataki noodles?
Are the benefits of the hot spring written?
Yeah.
- Health Benefits -
Highly nutritious.
Packed with protein.
- Health Benefits -
Highly nutritious...
Weird, huh?
- Watame Stew -
Wait, ain't this a stew?!
The protein they mentioned...
they probably mean you.
Oh my god!
Yeah, I'm getting out!
Out!
Yeah, get out!
I'm outta here!
You're in trouble.
I think I got a little bit scalded.
I bet.
My body's stinging a bit.
Can I dry my hair now?
Oh, sure.
It's soaking wet.
The way this is going
I'm expecting some sear marks.
Everything should be fine now.
Ow ow ow ow!
Is that actually a hair dryer?
Oww!
I don't think it is.
This is different from
any hair dryer I know!
Ow ow ow ow!
This thing's a blowtorch!
For cooking
It's a blowtorch! A blowtorch!
(the sound of meat sizzling)
You really are getting sear marks!
Blowtorch! Owwie!
Anything weird with your body right now?
Anything weird?
It's getting harder to move, I think.
Crispy texture achieved.
You're on the verge of becoming a meal.
There's a plate on this conveyor belt, so I'm
gonna get on that and head over your way.
Really? I'll await your arrival.
Okay.
What a crazy place to be in.
A food processing plant.
I'm back!
You were at a hot spring?
Sure was.
More like sure wasn't!
And that's the end of the surprise call!
Now Watame-senpai is here!
How was it?
What's your rating?
60 out of 100, I guess?
That low?
Lower than I thought!
A sixty, I'd say.
It's a tough one.
I mean,
I'm an idol,
so having to act like a comedian
wasn't in my plans.
What? I thought you were a meal.
You went there?!
The next surprise call is going to...
Airani Iofifteen from hololive ID!
Ohh! Iofi!
You do a lot of collabs with
Iofi-senpai, don't you, Watame?
Yeah!
What is Iofi-senpai normally like?
She's cute.
Cute, huh?
I wonder if we'll see that cuteness today,
when we surprise call her.
Let's go!
Let's see what Iofi-senpai is up to.
Surprise call starts now!
Ring ring ring ring! Ring ring ring!
Ring ring!
Oh?
Huh? Who's this?
At this hour?
Hello!
Is this Iofi-senpai?
Yeah!
It's me, the biggest brain alien, Iofi.
Whatcha need?
Hello.
This is Shishiro Botan
with Tsunomaki Watame.
Oh, you two!
It's been a while!
Yes, it has!
Iofi-senpai, what are you up to right now?
Right now?
I'm taking a little drive.
A drive?!
A drive...
Yep.
Where are you driving to?
Space.
Driving in space...
It's very pretty.
I'm driving my UFO right now.
Oh, that's so romantic!
Wow!
Do you have a driver's license?
Do you need a license for a UFO?
I do!
You need one!
Oh, you do.
So you need a license!
Seems so.
Definitely.
I'd say it's harder to drive than a normal car.
Oh, like a special heavy vehicle license?
You probably don't know that.
What's a special heavy vehicle license?
Special Large Motor Vehicle License level?
Medium
vehicles
Heavy special
There's like a special license you need
to drive some large vehicles.
Yeah, yeah!
Something like that?
Yeah.
So it's lumped into that class.
Like that.
How far from Earth are you right now?
I can see the constellation Leo.
Really?
It's so pretty.
Woohoo!
Oh yeah!
You wanna go there?
So you're millions of light-years away right now.
Leo
A constellation 80 light-years from Earth.
Right? Just how far away are you?
How many years should we wait for you?
How many years?
I'd say about twenty minu—
Nah,
I'll just head there immediately!
You can make it?
Yeah, I can.
You're coming back? You sure?
Should be right away!
Just wait for me!
Now, this is a surprise call.
Now arriving
Right?
Totally.
She's here!
See!
She made it!
Fast, ain't I?
And now Iofi-chan is here!
Hey, there!
Iofi-senpai, have you ever done
any surprise calls like this?
No, I don't think I've ever done any.
I see!
I asked some pretty crazy stuff.
Were you okay with that?
Easy-peasy!
On the easy side, huh?
I mean, for me, every day
is nothing but chaos,
so this was no problem.
Every day is chaos!
Every day is chaos for you!
Yeah, every day is just chaos upon chaos.
Sounds rough!
So this was nothing!
Bring it!
On to the next one!
This is the last surprise call.
Last but not least is
Takanashi Kiara from hololive EN!
Thoughts?
About Kiara?
Fried chicken!
You wanna eat Kiara?
A fellow food friend?
Continuing our cooking (?) special,
we'll see what Kiara's up to.
Let's find out.
Surprise call starts now!
Ring ring ring ring!
I wonder.
Ring ring!
Kikkeriki!
The president of KFP, though
they call me the manager,
hololive EN's Takanashi Kiara here!
What can I do for you today?
Hello? It's Shishiro Botan.
Hi!
I'm here with Watame and Iofi.
'Sup!
Hello!
Ohh!
My senpais!
My senpais, huh?
Yay!
I'm a little busy at the moment,
but if it's you guys,
I can make some time.
What were you doing?
Busy busy!
Right now,
I was just chewing out my KFP employees.
KFP: The fast-food chain that Kiara runs.
Oh? What happened?
They're having a little meltdown
over their salary.
Should you be telling us this?
How much do you pay them?
Uh... well...
It's a... at-will.
The paycheck is...
also at-will (free).
The paycheck is also at-will (free).
So the people who show up
just really wanna work for you?
That's right!
But after that,
the chickens—
all my employees are chickens,
by the way.
But chickens have a birdbrain memory.
They keep complaining to me about it!
Right.
So they forget.
Really!
What? What? Don't bother me!
Pay us
I'm on the phone right now!
Don't bug me.
I'm talking to my senpais right now!
Don't touch me!
N-No touchy!
Hey!
Pay us
Hey! Hey!
Uh oh!
Wait!
Wait, don't...
Don't touch me!
Stop!
Where are you carrying me?!
Stooop!
Is she about to get fried?!
Oh no!
Should we help her?
Don't touch!
Ahhh!!
It's so hot!
She's been taken away.
Help me!
Help me!!
By the way,
I'd like to hear about
today's special at KFP.
What?!
Now?!
I'm quite hungry, so yeah.
Do you have a Kiara burger?
New menu item: The Kiara Burger!
New menu!
Yeah!
We aim to please!
Hot!
I wanted to have you, uh...
I'm exhausted.
come by after this.
But are you okay? Can you?
If you want me there, I'll be there!
Yeah. I'll come by!
Okay, we'll be waiting.
We'll see you here!
Okay!
Freshly delivered.
Fresh 'n' hot.
Made to order.
She's here and ready!
Kikkeriki!
She's ready!
Pipin' hot Kiara?
I am not!
Pipin' hot!
I'm not, seriously!
Do you always get fried up like that?
No, that was the first time!
First time?!
Really?
First time!
It's usually the opposite!
The other way around!
So then...
Yeah, they're tasty.
You feed your employees
to the customers?
It's a lucrative business.
The Dark Side of KFP
A cruel work environment.
So-called
KFP president
Selling your employees as food.
How did you like
doing this in Japanese?
It was fun!
Fun!
I'm looking forward to more!
I'm happy to hear that!
I wanna do more of these!
Let's have some fun again sometime!
Yeah, let's have some fun!
Let's do a collab!
Yeah!
Absolutely!
Let's do another cross-border
collaboration sometime!
Yeah!
Bye-bye!
Please like this video and subscribe to
this channel and the talents' channels!
Bye-bye!
Byebyebye!