My friends,
do you enjoy manga?
Heya! Omaru Polka here!
hololive 5th generation
Omaru Polka
We have with us today some of
the biggest manga buffs in hololive!
Together, we have
a super exciting project
for you all today!
Yay!
hololive Generation 0
Hoshimachi Suisei
hololive 3rd generation
Shirogane Noel
Secret Society holoX
La+ Darknesss
That's what I like to see!
Lots of excitement!
You're way ahead of me.
So, ladies,
Shueisha is currently holding
its spring manga festival,
"Haruman!! 2022"!
And to help promote this campaign,
we're here to bring you...
"Straight from the Shueisha
Editorial Department: hololive Branch"!
Yay!
SED: hB!
Say what?
Everyone gathered here today
has received the honor
of being appointed by Shueisha
as One-Day Editors-in-Chief!
Wow!
At last! Shueisha, too, shall fall
under the dominion of holoX!
Uh-oh, do we have an instigator among us?
Sure, she wishes.
Our One-Day Editors-in-Chief
Uh-huh.
will select three ongoing manga series
that they consider absolute must-reads
and give a presentation about
what makes them good
and why they love each series so much.
We're looking forward to
your selections, Editors-in-Chief!
This is your chance to create
the manga magazine of your dreams.
Awesome!
I've always wanted to do this!
I'm ready.
Heck yeah!
What's more, they've made us
custom magazine covers.
Let's take a look!
Here they are!
Ta-dah!
Whoa!
Look!
Gosh...
Is this for real?
They look so legit!
No kidding!
Very legit.
We're not messing around.
Bookstores, here we come!
Yes, please give us shelf space.
Honestly, they wouldn't look out of place.
Just look at them!
They'd fit right in!
They certainly would.
In fact, these original manga magazines
will actually be made
available in e-book format
on all digital services
that carry Shueisha manga.
For real?!
Seriously?
That wasn't in the script!
Surprise announcement
We want lots of downloads,
so you Editors-in-Chief had better really
sell those titles in your presentations.
You betcha!
I'm itching to get started!
Best of luck!
Okay, so you ladies will be taking turns
introducing one title at a time.
And our first presentation will be from...
That's right!
Editor-in-Chief Shirogane Noel!
Take it away!
Okay!
Ooh!
Editor-in-Chief Shirogane Noel
Manga No.1
I'm hololive 3rd Gen's muscleheaded
knight and editor-in-chief,
Shirogane Noel!
My magazine is called
Shonen Muscle!
Keeping with my image,
I chose to feature works
under the theme of "power."
There's definitely some
muscle in that selection.
Oh, they're packing, all right.
The first manga I'll be
talking about is this one!
🥁🥁🥁
🥁💪
Mashle: Magic and Muscles!
Starting off with
It's Mashle!
a muscle manga right off the bat, I see.
Yes!
Mashle began its serialization
in February 2020
in the Weekly Shonen Jump magazine.
There are currently 10 print volumes,
with Volume 11 going on sale this May!
Can't wait.
Next month!
It's a very popular work,
with over 3 million books sold!
So onto the meat.
This is a fantasy work
set in a magic realm where
the mystical arts are commonplace,
but strangely,
the tagline shown
on Jump's official site for the manga is
"Power is everything!"
"Twisted Magical Fantasy!"
Wait, this sounds like...
Did you write this, Noel-san?
Unfortunately, no.
The guy on the cover
of the 1st volume
is the protagonist, Mash Burndead.
That's his name.
The thing with him is that
he might be a resident of the realm,
but he can't use magic at all.
Yeah!
On the other hand, though,
he has his well-trained muscles.
Like, he's ripped as hell.
Whoa, that's buff!
See?
He's jacked!
See now?
He gets things done one way or another.
A true musclehead.
He is truly my spirit animal.
Your spirit animal...
Of course, it can't be a
shonen manga without battles!
Right?
Gotta have the intense fights.
That's true.
It's a clash of magic and muscles.
I'd also like to highlight here
the unique style of the fight scenes
not seen in other works.
As expected,
the foes that appear here are all
fearsome mages in their own right.
Of course!
They're all gonna be strong.
But with a slam, and punch!
And a whirl!
And a c-c-c-crackle!
And all of that.
You get to see how strong he is!
Definitely a musclehead.
Truly powerful.
His muscles pull through for him.
When he goes to fight
a puppeteer mage,
He sounds tough.
you'd think he'd be in trouble, right?
Yeah, he's in a pinch.
Right?
What do you think happens next?
Doesn't he get thrashed?
Does he get mobbed?
Mash-kun fights them like this.
Mash rips the head off of
one of the puppets.
And then,
he swings the ball,
sending them flying.
Bowling...?
Bowling, exactly!
Strike!
Just like that.
Sounds fun, right?
Now I'm interested.
That was cool!
Same here.
You'd want to see more.
I could read this.
Some other things he can
do include morphing his wand
through sheer power,
like into a tennis racket.
He changed his wand into a racket
and fought with that.
How?!
Exactly!
You'd hear it and think "How?!"
You really need to see to believe!
Damn it, now I really wanna see it!
Wanna know more?
Yeah...
With that said,
all I've talked about so far
are the funny things.
Allow me now to introduce
my top highlight for Mashle.
The floor is yours!
What is it?
The staple of shonen manga:
fire-forged friendships!
Ahh, friendship!
Behold, this cover!
From Volume 3!
Striking, right?
That... thing he's holding
in place of a wand...
He's carrying that for a wand?!
He's carrying a dumbbell
instead of a wand!
A dumbbell...
Mash makes allies by
gaining the respect
and trust of his rivals
and former enemies
through the language of battle.
That's a staple, yeah.
That's intense!
That's cool.
Mash-kun very much
cares for his friends.
Whenever one of them gets hurt,
the way Mash shows his anger
is really awesome.
Can I show you a sample?
With that deadpan face?
That's unexpected.
WHAT?!
Here it is!
Whoa!
See?!
Compared to the
comedic Mash-kun we saw earlier,
here he goes,
"Come at me. Scumbag."
Biting words.
That is so cool!
It's that switch!
That sudden switch
He's got me all tingly!
I mean, he goes on
gets you all tingly, right?
to beat them after, right?
He's perfect!
Exactly!
With his muscles, too!
All muscle, no magic!
Just beats them straight up.
I can't ask for more.
Yep, pretty much.
Look at him go BAM!
Man, seriously.
It never fails to be
both funny and cool.
Whenever I sit down to read,
my heart and other muscles―
Yeah, all my muscles just
start flexing and getting gains.
If you want hearty laughs
and manly tears,
this work is right for you.
Please give Mashle a try!
You have definitely
piqued my interest.
This is a real solid recommendation.
Yeah.
Our first Editor-in-Chief made her passion
for the work show in her pitch!
Thank you!
What's our next presentation about?
Our next speaker is
Editor-in-Chief La+!
The floor is yours!
Yeah!
Editor-in-Chief La+
Manga No.1
Heed my call!
Founder of holoX and editor-in-chief,
La+ Darknesss here!
Yamada! Yamada!
Don't call me Yamada!
You're very persistent with that...
I've granted my original magazine
with the name of...
Lap LOVE Darknesss!
That sounds familiar.
Ah...
Don't say it out loud!
I've picked out some manga that
will give you the warm fuzzies!
Huh?
You're a shoujo fan?
You like those cute stories...?
No—
I-Is there a problem
with me liking them?
That's cute!
I should be allowed to
read shoujo manga too!
Here's the first manga I'm showcasing!
Okay!
2.5 Dimensional Seduction!
Oh!
It's been serialized in
Shounen Jump+ since June 2019!
Oh!
It currently has 13 print volumes on sale.
That's a lot of volumes.
Wow, that's a lot.
Yeah, there's lots of volumes!
You won't believe
how many views it has on Jump+...
It's a super popular manga with
over a hundred million previews!
Yeah?!
For real?
I'm deeply intrigued!
By all the skin on the left!
Oh my, how lewd.
Heh, my bad!
What...?
In the story, there's a
two-dimensional character called Liliel.
Okay.
It all starts when Okumura,
a manga club member who loves Liliel,
meets Amano Lilysa,
a new student joining the club.
Oh...
So Okumura has a good time?
Actually, Okumura here doesn't care
about the three-dimensional.
In other words, he has
absolutely no interest in real women.
Nice.
He doesn't show any interest
even in a girl as cute as Lilysa.
What?!
Or so he thought!
What?
But!
He gets a bad case of the hnghs!
Ah...
Oh my!
She's in cosplay!
Whoa...
When Lilysa reveals
her cosplaying hobby to him,
he thinks, "It's Liliel!"
Oh no...
He falls super hard
for a 2.5-dimensional girl.
Right.
His childhood friend,
who has an unrequited crush for him,
Wha-?!
also makes an appearance!
Oh!
Wait, wait, wait!
Oh my!
She reminds me of Choco-sensei.
I see it!
It's her wings, right?
From what I've told you so far,
this sounds like your usual
suggestive romantic comedy.
Yeah.
I bet you thought so too!
Okumura has a good time...
Is it not?
Yeah.
It's that kind of story, right?
It has to be...
The main thing I wanted to
show all of you... was this!
Hm?!
A rival cosplayer appears!
And it turns into a
super hype battle manga!
What?!
Oh?
There's a rival?
Really?
That's right!
It's a battle manga?
There's a rival cosplayer?
This is the rival, Nagomi.
What?!
She does cosplay for a living.
Nagomi?
She's a professional cosplayer.
Oh!
She's one of the elite four
legendary cosplayers.
There's four of them!
She goes right for Lilysa after
meeting her for the first time.
"You're cosplaying as a means to an end
just because you like Liliel, right?
Cosplay is my passion,
my end goal,
and my means.
So which one of us
loves cosplay more?"
Wha—?
Whoa!
Wow...
After being lectured to that extent,
Lilysa-san started doubting
her own love for cosplay,
and gets so depressed
she can't cosplay anymore.
Oh no...
She gets depressed?
Yeah...
The one who supports her
during her slump
is the terminal geek
who's having a great time,
Ugh...
Okumura!
He's taking all the best parts!
For real?!
"I know you can do it!
You can become Liliel, Lilysa!"
"...Yeah!"
This is intense!
With Okumura's support,
Lilysa regains her confidence
to cosplay again!
Oh!
Oh...
Whoa!
Just take a look at this!
Oh!
Her aura's totally changed!
This is how it begins!
Oh!
This is it!
This is totally the start of a battle manga!
"Liliel!"
This is where it starts...
Yeah!
It becomes a battle to see
who can charm the photographers more
and who can enjoy cosplaying more!
It turns into a battle of passion!
Wow!
I can't believe you can
fight battles with cosplay.
That's right.
Nice!
Right?
There are tons of
cute cosplayers other than Nagomi.
What?!
Oh!
They're so cute!
Look at all of them.
The middle girl in the top row
looks like the type of girl
that suddenly turns really cute
after she cosplays.
That's right!
I'm really interested in this girl!
The story is full of both
intense and touching moments
for all of these girls on the covers.
Right, right, right.
Witness the passionate friendships
between cosplayers
and the sweat they pour
into perfecting their craft.
It's truly a Jump classic.
Whoa...
What happened to the warm fuzzies?
Well, you know...
You can get the fuzzies real quick
with one of the many sexy scenes.
We have different definitions of that word.
Sexy scenes?
That's different!
Take a look at this.
What?!
Huh?
Oh my god!
How crazy is this?
Is this allowed?!
Hold up!
Just...
Look at all this skin!
It's so— Whoa!
Whoa!
Wait, they're totally exposed.
You can totally see it!
You can see it.
Don't you lot want to see this too?
Hey, you lot watching this video!
A semi-colored version
with the sexy scenes colored
is currently on sale!
Definitely go and buy a copy
if you're interested!
It starts from cosplay, gets all intense,
then it gives you the fuzzies
and sexy scenes.
Wow.
Next to present is...
Editor-in-Chief Suisei!
It's all yours!
Editor-in-Chief Hoshimachi Suisei
Manga No.1
It's your shooting star,
your diamond in the rough,
idol VTuber and
one-day editor-in-chief,
Hoshimachi Suisei! How do you do?
That intro got long.
Thanks for coming to my presentation.
Sure thing.
Wow.
Okay!
How I've looked forward to doing this!
My original magazine is
Comic Comet!
ComiComet. I like it.
It's a mysterious one.
I chose manga with
"secrets" as the theme.
Doesn't just a glance
at the cover fill you with suspense?
Yeah.
Wondering what you're going to see?
The first manga I'm introducing is...
OSHI NO KO!
Wow.
Yay!
Ooh.
The writer is Aka Akasaka,
the author of "Kaguya-sama: Love Is War,"
and the illustrator is Mengo Yokoyari.
What a dream team!
Mhm.
Whoa!
It's serialized in both
Weekly Young Jump and Shonen Jump+.
I read it in Jump+.
Ooh.
Ahh.
Mhm.
There are seven volumes out so far,
Seven volumes?
with over three million copies sold in total.
Crazy.
Whoa.
Sheesh.
And it won first place
in the Next Manga Award.
They already awarded it,
right? In 2021?
What? Wow!
Yeah, big time.
It already won.
It's a mystery that takes place
backstage in showbiz.
It's a mystery.
It's a mystery?
She looks so cute, right?
I mean, you know how we're idols?
Yes!
Well, yeah, if you say so.
Mhm.
I got curious, so I read it,
and it was seriously good.
Ooh.
So I want all of you—
I want everyone
watching this to read it,
so I've laid out my talking points.
If you would.
Here they are.
Anything I say is a spoiler.
I can't give a presentation on it! 😭
Done!
Sob!
So I can't say anything!
That's tough!
This is a tough one!
This manga is full of secrets.
Right.
Mhm.
It's more fun if you go in completely blind,
so all you viewers at home
who haven't read it
are super duper lucky.
Yes, indeed, true, ma'am.
Don't I sound like an informercial?
Yes, and that's fine too.
But not tossing the viewers
a bone is, well, yeah.
Yeah.
Mhm.
So I'll share the summary with you.
If you would.
"In the world of showbiz,
lies are weapons."
Ooh.
This is the blurb tagline.
Cool.
Cool...
This is the blurb from the first volume.
It's publicly available info.
It's pretty short for a blurb.
Ohh?
And now!
How to read it!
Suisei Points!
Number one!
Okay!
Okay, that's random.
It says that "In the world of showbiz,
lies are weapons," right?
What is it?
Mhm-mhm.
Yeah.
And the girl on the cover is the
idol Ai Hoshino from the blurb.
Right.
That's her.
The blurb also says,
"Ai Hoshino has begun her climb to stardom."
And that means...
Right.
Hm...
The idol Ai Hoshino
is a liar.
What?!
And...
I see.
Right from the start,
she's holding one heck of a secret.
We all know.
We're all reading it.
We're reading it.
Wh-What?!
We've all read it.
I mean...
What did you all think
when you read the first chapter?
I was like, "Yes, 'Destiny's Child'"!
I was like, the title's perfect!
That title!
Isn't it great?
My favorite scene is...
Oh?
The title's OSHI NO KO,
so when they reveal
why that's the title...
Yeah! Yeah!
It happens two or three times.
Yeah, that's right.
Now, the title OSHI NO KO
has a secret behind it,
but has a lot of different meanings.
Mhm.
So every time they reveal
why it's the title...
Ah...
Ahh...
There are no words.
That's all I can think.
Seriously.
Yeah.
Mhm.
The story is full of twists and turns.
If I've piqued your interest,
I hope you take this opportunity to read it!
Mhm.
You really haven't given
any info about it at all.
Editor-in-Chief Shirogane Noel
Manga No.2
I'm going all-in on power!
Okay!
The second title to be featured
as part of Shonen Muscle
is this one!
Ooh!
Dandadan!
That's right.
Yep.
Let's go!
It's Dandadan!
Dandadan?!
Dandadan is published
in Shonen Jump+.
It began its run in April 2021
and is currently ongoing.
It's drawn by Yukinobu Tatsu,
and print volumes up to
Volume 4 are currently on sale.
Volume 5 is coming this May.
It was selected by
bookstore employees nationwide
as their number 1
most recommended manga of 2022.
Ooh!
Oh, wow!
This is a series that
everyone's talking about right now!
Then it must be good!
It stars high schooler
Ayase Momo-chan
and Takakura Ken-kun.
Takakura Ken-kun?!
I know, Takakura Ken?
Takakura Ken!
That name sounds familiar.
Takakura Ken-kun, huh?
Takakura Ken, I see.
Anyway, they battle spirits,
aliens, and cryptids
in this action-packed paranormal
and supernatural action manga.
Sounds cool!
I see.
It really fits the zeitgeist!
And here is the reason
I chose this title!
The incredible art!
The power of the art
is simply OP!
OP!
That's right!
And I think it'll be easier
if you see for yourselves.
Let's take a look!
Here.
Whoa!
Giant enemy crab!
Crab!
Cool!
Wow.
It's so detailed!
That's really good.
Right?
The art is so good!
Next, take a look at this.
Here.
Whoa!
So good!
What's the deal with their getups?
I'm sure you have many questions.
Quite a lot.
Can you believe this is a drawing?
Amazing.
It's a drawing, but the action is
so dynamic, it looks like it's moving!
Yeah, it's so cool!
It leaps off the page.
Totally!
It's like a movie!
So good!
Man...
Amazing, right? So detailed!
Wow!
Do you notice anything,
looking at this art?
Huh?
What is it?
They're on a train!
Wait, what is it?
To give a hint,
they're missing something that you'd
expect to see in almost any other manga.
Huh?
Oh, I've got it!
Oh!
Huh?
Yes?
It's the, uh...
The sound effects!
Like "dah-dah-dah-dah."
Ah!
Oh!
Onomatopoeia?
Exactly!
You're spot-on!
No "BANG" or "rrrumble" or "SMASH!"
You're right!
Not a single sound effect at all!
Wow, I just noticed!
Yet you can still hear the scene.
Whoa!
The art alone is enough
to express everything.
It is!
I've got goosebumps.
I didn't notice till you said.
Yet the title's a sound effect.
Dandadan!
Yeah, it's Dandadan!
Yet it's Dandadan!
It's Dandadan!
On the topic of this
overwhelming art quality,
the genius behind one of
Polka-san's favorites, Chainsaw Man,
Tatsuki Fujimoto, had this to say:
"Among the best art
in all of shonen manga."
Whoa!
Ooh!
Right?
Tatsu-sensei used to work
with Fujimoto-sensei
as his main assistant.
Yeah, those detailed backgrounds.
Rumor has it that Fujimoto-sensei
was influenced by the art
of his assistant, Tatsu-sensei.
Really?!
That's how good his art is.
The student becomes the master!
That's cool.
That's so neat!
What a connection!
Amazing, right?
And that was Dandadan, featuring
some of the best art in shonen manga!
Okay!
Thanks for the presentation!
Your passion really showed!
Talk about power!
Editor-in-Chief La+
Manga No.2
The second featured work
on Lap LOVE Darknesss is...
This one!
Mei's Butler DELUXE!
Deluxe?
Cute!
Deluxe?!
Yes.
You all have heard of Mei's Butler?
Yeah.
Yep.
I've heard of it.
Serialized in Margaret since 2006,
this is the sequel to Mei's Butler,
It was known for that.
which had also had a live-action TV show.
Yeah, it was.
The OG had a total of 20 volumes.
DELUXE is currently running at 17 volumes.
That's certainly deluxe!
Wait, currently?
Yes!
Yep!
It's still ongoing!
Yeah.
The series has sold a total of
over 7.5 million copies!
Wow!
Running for 17 years and counting,
this manga is a timeless classic.
The all-girls school Mei-chan goes to,
St. Lucia Academy,
has an annual tuition fee
of 100 million yen.
Students get assigned a butler
to serve them.
Oh my!
This is what gives this manga
its warm fuzzies!
You get to squee to
Mei's butlers, the Shibata brothers!
There's two of them?!
Yes! There's two of them!
They're handing out rings?
Two?! WHAT?!
How does this work?!
Remember, girls,
they're brothers!
The first and elder butler
is Shibata Rihito.
He's the guy on the left with the black hair.
He holds the highest appraisal
in the butler industry, Rank S.
He's a man with no flaws
to him whatsoever.
The butler industry has ranks...
There's a butler industry...
Yes!
The blonde guy on the right
is the second and younger butler,
Shibata Kento.
The number two...
He's Mei's childhood friend
who has a crush on her.
Oh?
His butler rank is A.
Aww!
Yeah.
I might break down if
Kento-san ends up dumped.
He still has hope!
The series is still ongoing!
Actually, yeah!
Nothing's set in stone yet!
You serious?!
Here in DELUXE,
Mei-chan's already 18 years old,
so the sequel is a bit
spicier compared to the OG.
You all are expecting me to
show some sexy scenes, no?
Your idea of "the warm fuzzies"
No way.
is a bit off, Lap-chan.
Actually...
There's an off-chance
this is too risque for YouTube,
so here it is for your eyes only.
Ooh...
HOLD UP!
Is Rihito-san like...
a lowkey pervert?
He's totally a
lowkey highkey pervert.
But... But you can see it!
You can see right through it!
W-Well, instead of talking
about it further,
everyone should just
buy it for themselves.
I want to contribute to its sales.
Please buy it!
All right!
Okay.
Okay, then.
Man,
"The petals are dancing in the air."
Editor-in-Chief Hoshimachi Suisei
Manga No.2
The theme of Comic Comet is "secrets"!
And for my second presentation,
I've picked this manga.
Hana wa Saku, Shura no Gotoku.
Sounds fancy.
Yup!
I've never heard about this one!
It's totally understandable if
you're just finding out about this.
That's because it was serialized
in Ultra Jump starting in June 2021!
Yeah?
Ultra Jump, huh?
Oh!
That's recent!
It started very recently.
The first volume is currently on sale!
Oh!
The second volume comes out in May.
The first volume came out really recently.
Oh!
You might know about the novel series Sound! Euphonium, which received an anime adaptation.
And this is its author Ayano Takeda's
first original manga series!
Oh!
The manga is illustrated by Musshu!
Really?
Wow...
Yup!
Musshu has done a lot
with hololive before as well.
Right.
Yeah.
You can tell just from
the cover how cute their art is!
Yeah, it's so cute.
Yeah, it is.
My favorite character is
the girl on the top.
She's called Mizuki-senpai.
Wait, that's a girl?!
The blonde one.
That's a girl?
She's a girl!
Yeah, she's a girl!
Really?
Wow, she looks really bishie.
That's amazing.
I'm suddenly really interested.
Yeah, it's great.
I want to read this right now.
I'm currently obsessed with this manga
and really want to recommend it to you.
You might be wondering what
the secret to this manga is.
There's a secret?
It's actually...
What?
Believe it or not!
Hoshimachi Suisei is featured in
Volume 1's special comment section!
Uh, what?
What?!
This is a secret?
Whaaat?
There's a Suisei comment in it!
"It feels like you can hear
the voices of the characters
just by seeing their
expressions and dialogue.
These two artists have created
a masterpiece that
manages to express
the art of expression."
Oh!
How was my recitation of that?
Recitation?
It was pretty good.
It was pretty nice.
Yeah.
That's right.
It's a manga about recitations,
a rare topic for this medium.
What?!
Recitations?
That seems hard to show.
That sounds hard.
Wow.
Even though this is a manga,
you really can hear the
sounds and recitations.
What?!
Here's a scene you can really hear.
Oh!
Wow...
Whoa!
How amazing is that?
By portraying the scenes in the
recitations through drawings,
What?!
the readers get further
immersed in the story
and start hearing the recitations
not physically, but in their minds.
This is really nice.
That's so cool!
I especially like the usually soft
Hana-chan's expression here.
This expression!
Wow, it's totally different.
Her face when she's performing is amazing.
She's a different person!
Also!
I'm sure everyone who watched
Sound! Euphonium would know this,
Yeah?
School clubs, the passions of youth, and girls.
There it is.
Ayano Takeda is great at
writing about these topics.
Yeah.
The protagonist, Hana-chan,
loves recitations.
She's cute!
She joins the broadcasting club
upon starting high school.
The reason Hana-chan
joins the broadcasting club
Yeah?
is because Usurai Mizuki-senpai,
the president,
very assertively drags Hana-chan
around with her.
She's so cool!
Hana also grows as she learns to love
recitations because of Mizuki-senpai.
The story's full of the
emotional roller coasters of youth.
I'm sure that this is going to get
even more buzz in the future,
Right.
so please have a read through it!
Now's your chance to be caught up with it!
True!
Thank you!
Great presentation.
I expected nothing less from Chief Suisei.
Thank you!
Yup.
Editor-in-Chief Shirogane Noel
Manga No.3
Awright!
Power!
The third title to be featured
as part of Shonen Muscle
is this one!
Right!
Yep!
'Tis Time for "Torture," Princess.
I love this one!
That's right.
You do?
Yay!
Looks tasty!
I realize, the title sounds
rather problematic at first.
Sure does.
This series is published
in Shonen Jump+.
It began its run in April 2019,
and is currently ongoing.
I see!
Uh-huh.
Right!
Print volumes are
available up to Volume 8,
with Volume 9 coming this May.
Everything's coming out in May!
No kidding!
It's a jam-packed month.
The heroine is the commander
of a knightly order, like myself.
She's a princess.
Really?
She's a knight commander?
A princess knight commander
who's been captured
by the Demon King's army,
and who will now be subjected
Gasp!
to cold-blooded torture.
That's the premise.
Sounds scary!
But the cover's so bright and cute!
What's the deal?
That's true!
Indeed.
What could this big, tasty-looking
bowl of ramen be about?
Wait, is that pork broth?
"Cold-blooded torture"
sounds scary,
but I'm sure you're curious
what it involves.
So I'd like to show you all
what those scenes are like.
Okay!
Let's have a look!
Voilà!
Ahh!
Fresh out the oven!
What's the meaning of this?
Well, you see,
the Demon Army's torture
mostly consists of
scrumptious food.
Food!
In order to extract the
secrets of the Royal Army,
the Demon Army uses the
princess's appetite to torture her.
Uh-huh.
Of course, the princess does her best
to endure the torture.
You can do it!
Princess! Don't give in!
Alas...
Don't give in!
in the end...
Don't you break!
she completely breaks.
But she does!
And as a matter of fact,
How easily tempted.
this happens every time.
Wha?
This keeps going?
Every time, the princess
gives in to the torture,
much to the reader's amusement.
It's a wholesome and
hilarious comedy manga.
Cool!
As for why I chose this manga.
Uh-huh.
Well, there can only be one reason.
Oh?
Tasty power!
Power!
Yes, power!
Who could resist?
Now, I'd like to present the top three
best "torture" scenes that most vividly
displayed this tasty power.
In third place,
da-da-dum!
Apple pie!
That looks so good!
That crust must be so flaky!
Right?
Despite that, the princess puts up
a good fight resisting it.
Wow. Good on her.
Yeah.
She resists this tasty-looking apple pie.
That is...
Nice going.
until the Demon Army brings out
their coup de grâce.
How come?
What?!
Pie... à la mode!
Now she's in trouble!
Oh, wow!
And with that finishing blow,
the princess goes...
"Let me eat it!"
Can you blame her?
She broke!
She did.
She gave in.
Let me eat it, too!
In second place,
da-dum!
Sushi!
Right!
Ooh, sushi!
That's right.
"Yep, I give in."
Already?
That was fast!
The face of acceptance.
I mean, how can you resist sushi?
Looks so good...
For me, the thing is,
I don't really like wasabi.
So I think I'd ask them
to hold the wasabi.
Hah! You're such a kid!
Wasabi's good, too!
And in first place,
everyone's favorite,
da-dum!
Pork cutlet bowl!
"Yep, I give in."
Reminds me of you, Noel.
"I give in!"
And she breaks.
I wanna see what's in there!
Yes, I'm sure you do.
Yeah.
Even if I know it'll make me hungry.
But you're not allowed to eat
until you divulge some secrets.
Oh, true.
So, anyone got a secret
they wanna share?
Don't got any.
I don't have any secrets.
I'm an open book.
Really?
Nope, none from me either.
None at all.
Got nothing.
How about you tell us one,
Commander?
True.
Me?
Well, the truth is,
I like beef bowls better than
pork cutlet bowls.
We know!
Oh, you knew?
Then no pork cutlet bowl for you!
Yeah, we know.
You knew?!
Your pork cutlet bowl privileges
have been revoked!
Well, whatever.
Let's take a look inside!
Sure!
Let's look anyway!
So with that said, here we go!
It looks so good!
I can't take any more!
I'm getting so hungry!
I'm running away!
It's too much!
Don't run!
I want that in my mouth!
This is killing me!
As for our princess,
through the course
of all this torture,
she is completely won over
via her stomach,
and ends up becoming friends
with the Demon Army.
She just accepts it?!
That's right.
Can't blame her!
I honestly wouldn't mind
being constantly subjected
to such "torture."
Agreed.
And that was 'Tis Time for "Torture", Princess,
a manga full of tasty power!
Okay! Thank you
for the presentation!
So hungry!
That was great.
Let's just go home.
I'm so hungry now!
I love this kind of stuff.
I'm so hungry.
Editor-in-Chief La+
Manga No.3
The third warm-fuzzies feature
in Lap LOVE Darknesss
is this!
Honey Lemon Soda!
Cute!
It's all the rage now.
I've seen ads of it!
That's right!
Honey Lemon Soda!
It's been serialized
in the magazine I so love, Ribon,
since 2016.
Wow! Cute!
As for print volumes,
19 volumes
and one side-story volume are on sale.
It's a long-running series.
It has over nine million copies total in print.
What?!
So popular!
No way!
It also got a live-action
movie adaptation last summer.
Oh, right! That one!
Makes sense.
Yep!
Nice.
The two characters on the cover
are the protagonist,
Ishimori Uka-chan,
and Miura Kai-kun,
and their bittersweet romance
takes the spotlight in this
classic fuzzies love story.
How very honey-lemon.
I just know it's got all the fuzzies.
Yeah.
I just live for this stuff.
My highlight point...
is this!
Read this, introverts!
The MC's personal growth
is bound to leave you in tears!
She develops as a person!
That introvert feel!
So let's take a looky-look.
Together.
The protagonist, Uka-chan,
due to her withdrawn nature,
was bullied in middle school.
So in order to change herself,
she enrolls in the free-spirited
Honey HS, a private school,
and begins her journey
of self-discovery.
Her gradual growth in the story
really gets you in the feels.
Bold move, going to a school like that.
Yeah, well, this is Uka-chan's
initial step forward.
But take a look at what
Honey HS's students usually look like.
Yeah, like...
So showy!
Strong!
They're totally normies.
Normies!
And obviously, the shy Uka-chan
doesn't fit in in her class at first.
But whenever she needs help,
she gets it in the form of
the hottie life-of-the-party prince,
Miura Kai-kun!
The hottie life-of-the-party prince?
Oh!
Life-of-the-party?
What the hell?!
What a ladykiller!
What's gotten into him?
"Well done."
Normally, he's cold
and expressionless,
but he always helps out people in need.
This boy's almost like a hero.
Uka-chan was bullied and
given the nickname "Stone."
But when he talks to her about it,
you get to see what makes him tick,
and I want to showcase that scene, but...
Say, Polka-san?
What's up?
Could you read out Uka-chan's dialogue?
Huh? I'm Uka-chan?
I'll read out Miura Kai's.
Okay, got it.
Don't let your past self
dictate who you are.
A stone you may be,
but you are a gemstone.
Show more desire.
Take a step forward.
And do it like you're
prepared to look down
upon all the people you've ever met.
You don't know it,
but your life of happiness
is already here.
That painful nickname
just became very precious to me.
Huh?
Who was that?
I just gained a new dream.
It probably won't
come true anytime soon.
But...
I swear I won't be
a burden to you!
To anyone who sees this,
it probably looks like
I bullied and made you cry.
Really?
I can't!
I can't take this anymore!
What's so funny, huh?
Wasn't that just so cool?
Well? Got the fuzzies?
Seriously, turning the "Stone"
to "gemstone" was genius.
Crazy, right?
Yeah.
So freakin' good.
It's insane.
Kai-kun's such a poet!
Poet?!
Love them poets.
With Kai-kun's help,
Uka becomes friends
with her normie classmates
and starts to lead a glittering school life.
Seeing that, I start to feel,
"I gotta do my best too!"
It gives me the motivation to keep going.
Really?
Cute.
That's cute.
Ah.
Lap-chan cute!
Nice, nice!
Why me?!
But how will Uka's love end up?
Everyone, buy it!
Read it!
Talk about it!
I'm counting on you all!
Editor-in-Chief Hoshimachi Suisei
Manga No.3
Now for the third feature in Comic Comet!
If we're talking secrets,
then this has to be the manga
that comes to mind!
SPY x FAMILY!
There it is!
There it is.
I love this one!
I've read this too.
Are you reading this, Noel-san?
I am!
Reading this, La+-san?
I read it every time!
Do you read this, Polka-san?!
Heck yeah.
As you can see, we're all reading it!
Moving on,
SPY x FAMILY started to be serialized
in Shonen Jump+
back in March 2019.
There are currently 9 volumes on sale,
and it won 1st in the
Kono Manga ga Sugoi! 2020 awards,
under the male readers category.
And of course, the anime is airing
starting this April,
so this manga is without a doubt
going to get even more
popular from here on out.
This is a comedy about a top-class spy
and his family full of secrets,
made to face
both world-breaking threats
and school-ending tests.
Tests...
Threats and tests, yes.
Gotta deal with both, I see.
The tests are important too.
Yeah, agreed.
The main point I'd like to
highlight is this one.
The appeal of having
every single member of the family
hold a Hollywood-tier secret.
Hollywood-tier...?
It's very...
...very awesome.
Let me explain this in detail.
A top-class spy
codenamed "Twilight"
is tasked with extracting information
from a particular person of interest.
He is to do this by
infiltrating the elite school
attended by the child of that person.
In order to carry out the mission,
he needs a family.
As you can see here, he is to
"get married, and raise a child."
So simple!
Those were his higher-ups' orders.
And he only had a week to do all of it.
So he ends up making
Too fast!
this false family in a hurry,
and every member has
very unique quirks to them.
The father is the
above-mentioned Loid Forger.
His public persona is of a psychiatrist.
His other persona is that of the
meticulous intel agent
"Twilight."
Damn, cool!
He's a master of disguise
That's real cool.
with a hundred faces.
That's the dad.
Nice.
He's a really cool guy.
The mother is Yor Forger.
What a cutie!
Her other persona is that of a highly-skilled
assassin, codenamed "Thorn Princess."
Assassin!
She's frickin' strong.
She's really damn strong!
Yeah, she is.
She's ridiculously strong.
Super-duper strong.
Their daughter is Anya Forger.
Her hidden identity is that of an esper.
Cool!
And the dog!
The dog!
He's Bond Forger.
The dog has a secret too?
On the surface, he's just the Forger dog.
But he's actually a military experiment
possessing the power of clairvoyance.
Yes, even the dog
has two sides to him.
Anyway, so.
Every one of them has the
makings of a Hollywood hero,
don'tcha think?
I can see it!
Everyone here
is working so hard to
hide their own secret
that they don't even
notice each other's.
Yes!
They don't know each other's secrets!
Good point.
I'm pretty sure if Twilight was
working as his usual self,
he would recognize Yor
as an assassin from a mile away.
True!
But he never notices. At all.
Only the daughter knows everything.
That's what's so good about it.
Nice.
There's this one scene
in the manga which I think
captures a lot of what's good about it.
So while Loid was
in the middle of
making his fake family,
he thought of taking a ring
he stole from a previous job,
and gifting it to Yor.
And he did get it,
but he then lost it
while being chased around.
But since he needed to get the
engagement done and over with,
he took the pin of a grenade
and tossed the bomb aside.
Yeah, he just threw it!
Yeah, exactly!
He took the pin and
slid it on Yor's finger,
while saying, "Let's get married!"
That entire scene was just
mind-blowingly good.
And the background just goes BOOM!
Boom!
That's pretty much the entire series.
That was so good.
It's really damn good.
That scene encapsulates
the manga so well.
This is SPY x FAMILY.
Without a doubt.
I loved this scene so much,
so I decided to show it here.
All right!
Yeah.
The secrets hold the key!
This has been SPY x FAMILY!
Okay! Thank you very much!
And that's it for the presentations!
Yay!
Any final thoughts on today?
How was it?
Well...
It was so fun getting to
talk about my favorites.
Yeah.
Ah, the joys of manga.
I felt like I was dragging new fans
down the rabbit hole.
I know, right?
I gotta say, I was blown away
by the sheer intensity
of your presentations.
I'm sure the audience is
dying to read these titles.
As mentioned at the start,
you can! But to recap,
you can read the titles our
One-Day Editors-in-Chief selected
in these original e-book magazines,
available Monday, April 25th,
for free! On all digital services
that carry Shueisha manga!
Please check them out if you're interested!
This is so exciting!
This was news to me.
We seriously didn't know!
What a surprise!
Crazy, isn't it?
I can't get over it.
I still can't believe it!
That's so cool!
I didn't present this time,
but I actually compiled
my own magazine, too.
So if you'd like,
please check that out, too.
For real?!
What's in it?
Yeah, I'm not sure when
that happened myself.
The titles I selected are
Debby the Corsifa is Emulous,
Kaiju No. 8, and
Takopi's Original Sin!
I've got kinda a variety set,
from current hot titles
to modern classics.
Please check it out
if you're interested.
Okay!
Sure thing!
Here's to lots more fun times
reading Shueisha manga!
Yeah!
And with that...
goodbye!
Bye-bye!
Thank you, Shueisha!
Thank you!