Well if you don't wanna
end up like this,
you better follow
the rules in this village.
Frustrating, isn't it?
The fact that I'm the CEO!
Oh!
The goddess is laughing!
I am the goddess
who lost her smile,
Aki Rosenthal.
I'm here today to regain my smile.
The Harmonica Goddess &
The Picture Fairies
Fairies?
My dear fairies?
Here!
Present!
I'll allow you
to introduce yourselves
along with your most recent
memory of laughing.
My most recent memory of laughing?
Don't have any.
hololive 4th Gen's Himemori Luna here.
Thanks for having me!
F-Fairy Polka...
I'm a fairy!
Uh... my most recent memory
of laughing is...
...from waking up
to my own snoring.
I'm Omaru Polka from hololive 5th Gen.
Happy to be here!
Could you demonstrate
what sort of snoring it is?
*Snort*
That's too real, milady.
My most recent memory
of laughing, huh...
Let's see...
I got my sauce containers mixed up
and put vinegar on my shrimp.
I'm the hololive 6th Gen's bodyguard,
Kazama Iroha.
Thanks for inviting me today, milady.
Well then. I'll explain what
the three of you will be attempting today.
First, please take a look at this.
I've prepared a lot of picture cards
with a single letter attached.
The three of you must try and amuse me
by coming up with a line for the situation
in the picture using the attached letter.
What?
In reality, you just like these kinds
of things, don't you, Goddess?
Before you start answering,
let me add just one more thing.
Huh?
Add what?
Add something?
No way! Seriously?!
Whaaat?!
Goddess, what IS that?
The basis for
whether I laughed or not
will be decided by this divine—
*Pfft*
The basis for
whether I laughed or not...
You just did!
Yeah, you did.
You just laughed!
...will be decided by this
divine item, the harmonica.
The harmonica...
Raise your hand once you've come up
with something and answer away.
Uh, okay.
Got it!
Understood!
Well then, girls...
Amuse me.
Reveal... the picture!
Huuuh?
M
Now, then.
Come up with something.
What? U-Using this picture?
Do your best, fellow fairy!
You can do this, Fairy Luna!
Here I go.
You already have something? Wow.
Cue the princess' answer
in three... two... one...
Goddeeess!
Does this make seeense?
Huh?!
Oh?
Was that a laugh?
I was just yawning.
Whaaat?!
Was it maybe because
You yawned?!
the first word didn't start with "M"?
This is getting interesting.
She hardly budged.
Yeah, it wasn't really that good.
It was absolutely lackluster.
Reveal... the next picture!
D
That's cute.
What is THIS?!
HUH?! Hang on!
D-Did you just laugh?
I did not.
We can only take
the picture for what it is.
We don't get any context at all!
If that's the case—
Okay, then.
Three.
Two.
One.
Derpy Doggo.
HUH?!
Reveal... the next picture!
C
Now, come up with something.
Oh, me!
That was quick!
Go ahead.
Okay! Here it goes!
Crap, this sucks.
The cat's definitely
in a crappy situation.
Oh! She's blowing
into it quite a bit!
I've got another one!
Crikey, did you get dropped
into this world too?
Fairy Luna, do you
have anything to add?
Can we change the picture?
The heck is that?!
O
Oh?
Oh!
Oooh!
Okay, I'll go!
Oh!
Go ahead!
Oi, oi...
Please stop fighting
over me!
That's good!
It really is! She's blowing
into the harmonica!
That's a good reaction right there!
I'll give it a go too!
Sure!
O...
Old man...?
Old lady...?
Your old man and your old lady, huh.
It's gotten louder!
Ch-Change the picture, please.
W
"W"...
"W" is a tough one.
Okay, I'll go.
All right.
W—
What the heck is this?
That sounds so scuffed.
That's just your thoughts!
I'll go next.
Oh, please do.
Well, dear me,
is this the carnival?
No? Neither one of us
was good enough?
Not even a peep!
Is there anything sadder
than this treatment?!
I'll try again.
Go for it.
Well, if you don't wanna
end up like this,
you better follow
the rules in this village.
Scary.
That's so scary!
Was that—
Did you just laugh, Goddess?
No, I did not.
Huh?
Come on...
Just admit it already...
You've already laughed a ton!
Let's change the picture!
Let's keep going!
H
I'll go!
Okay!
Hoshimachi Suisei's
my fave, yo!
He's one of
the Hoshiyomi (Stargazers)?!
He's a fan?!
I'll go next!
Sure!
Hah!
This is the last thing
you'll ever see!
I guess I'll go last.
Oh?
Hey, hey!
I've got stars for eyes!
Adorable...
PLEASE FORGIVE ME!
SHE'S NOT AMUSED AT ALL!
COME ON! BE AMUSED!
GODDESS?!
WHY WON'T YOU LAUGH?!
H
Seriously?
What the heck
is this supposed to be?!
We need to use "H" for this?!
Oh, I've got one.
Really? Go for it.
Hey, Siri.
What kind of picture is this?
Sorry, I couldn't get that.
Could you try again?
I'VE GOT AN ACTUAL
SIRI REPLYING TO ME!
(PolPhone)
F
What the heck is this?!
I'll handle this.
Okay!
Frustrating, isn't it?
The fact that I'm the CEO!
THE GODDESS IS LAUGHING!
I was amused!
Goddess'
Divine Smile
Thanks to your efforts,
I'm finally able to smile again.
Ah, dear goddess!
That's great.
There's life in your eyes now!
The fairy that
amused me the most is...
Who?
Fairy...
...Polka!
Fairy Polka
Whoa, what?!
I knew it!
It's an honor.
Hm?
Yeah, it's an honor.
Do you truly think that?
Yes, I do!
The reason why I chose you
is because you hogged the spotlight.
(Reason)
Because she kept
hogging the spotlight.
"Because she hogged the spotlight."
Don't say that!
You showed me an amusing time
and I thank you for that.
And for those of you
in the audience who enjoyed this video,
prithee give it a like and subscribe to
the official hololive YouTube channel
as well as our individual channels!
Prithee subscribe!
Wait, were we that sort of character?
Fare thee well!