If you
fail this quiz,
you'll get guillotined?!
What are their fates?!
Guillotine Quiz
Redux!
Spring is in full bloom!
How do you girls feel?
Yaaay!
Spring is here!
Spring is the season
for new beginnings
and also the season of endings!
With that said,
look up above you, girls!
Up?
What the heck are these?!
Holy!
Whoa!
I knew it!
We've prepared some custom-made
guillotines fitting for
the season of endings!
Woo-hoo!
"Woo-hoo," my foot!
What do you mean by "endings"?
Are you taking it literally?
Well, this is the situation
you're in now,
so let's start off by
introducing ourselves!
'Sup, groupies!
Behold your Tokoyami Towa-sama
from hololive 4th Gen!
You can sic a guillotine on me
but I'm a devil, so try as you might,
there's no way you're beheading me!
Try as we might, huh?
See me, hear me!
My name is La+ Darknesss!
Your intro's the weakest of them all.
Yeah, that's true.
SEE ME, HEAR MEEE!
Did I Luive you all waiting?
I'm Takane Lui, from hololive 6th Gen,
and XO of holoX!
Drop a guillotine at me all you like.
I'll send it back up with my loud voice!
Yeah,
you are the loudest.
How powerful.
I'm Kazama Iroha, from hololive 6th Gen,
and holoX's bodyguard!
Guillotine? Psh.
That's nothing compared to
my trusty partner Chakimaru, miladies.
Snip snip!
Obviously, 'cause
you're a ninja.
Snip snip!
Wait a minute!
Time out!
Hold on!
Stop!
I am NOT a ninja, milady!
Bodyguard
This is our 2nd time doing this,
but the mastermind sent a letter again,
so I'll read it out.
The curtains open
on a blood-filled spring!
What are you doing?
What a heel turn.
The four of you will
have to take on a quiz!
You've fallen low,
Lady A-chan.
She sure has.
You're not
that sort of character!
Can the peanut gallery
pipe the heck down?
You're noisy!
Sorry...
If you get five questions wrong,
a guillotine will drop and you'll go bye-bye!
This is basically a death game
that you need to escape from.
So we get to go home?
Is that head of yours for show?!
However, we've planted a traitor
among you who knows the
correct answers to every question!
That traitor is our demonic Joker!
Say what?!
Don't call me out like that!
Now they all know I'm the Joker!
Wow, this brat is annoying!
Do your best to answer
every question and find the Joker
to survive this quiz!
HAHAHAHAHA!
Really? Laughing twice?
First Question
You often see sakura trees
when you walk around town, right?
Yes.
Yup.
Yeah.
Okay, which of these is a sakura tree?
Look at the pictures and pick!
Whaaat?!
Huh?!
Seriously?!
It feels like the angle of the pictures
is meant to throw us off!
Yeah! The way they're
presented is kinda evil.
Isn't this question
too easy?
Is that so?
Aren't sakura trees a
common sight around schools?
Ah... that's true.
The answer's very obvious.
Really?!
I see.
Looks like everyone's locked in their answers,
so let's show them all at once!
Go ahead!
B, C, B, and C...
Oh my, a 50-50 split!
What a split!
We're split up!
I think the leaf in B looks like
the leaf wrapped around sakura mochis.
The pictures are so over the place
I didn't look at the leaves.
I was focusing on
the tree trunks, milady.
Deciding based on the trunk, huh.
Sakura trees are
hard to climb, milady.
So that's your perspective...
How about you, La+-san?
Why'd you pick C?
Well...
I just went with my gut.
With your gut?! What?!
Gut instinct?!
The correct answer is...?
B!
Oh, yeah!
Ah, it was B?
Yeah! B's the obvious answer!
The leaves might have been a small hint.
It does make sense
now that I look at the leaves.
Huh. I never knew
sakura trees had leaves.
What?
Are you for real?
Hang on...
Are you really the Joker?
She might be doing that
on purpose to throw us off.
Second Question
Okay, next question!
Please listen to this first.
Feels like spring is just around the corner
when you hear this cry, right?
Yeah.
Which bird cry is this?
Another easy one?
There's no way
you can fail this!
What do you take us for? Fools?
My pen is down!
Isn't it a bit
early for that?
Seems like you're all done,
so let's have a look at your answers!
Nightingale all around!
The correct answer is...?
Nightingale!
Anyone would know for sure!
Isn't it weird that you're the only one
who answered in katakana, Lui?
Yeah! I was thinking that too!
Isn't it weird that only you
answered in katakana?
You saw the cheat sheet written in katakana
and did the same, didn't you?
Uh-huh.
I didn't!
I definitely didn't!
You girls are way more sus
for writing it in hiragana.
Uh-huuuh.
Third Question
This question involves games.
In shooter games,
you have the genres FPS and TPS.
What does the T in TPS stand for?
Me! Me!
Are you sure the questions
should be stacked in my favor?
You do play a lot of
shooters, Towa-senpai.
Exactly!
I wonder what would
happen if you didn't know.
What does TPS stand for?
Oh, wait...
That's the very question
being asked!
Oh, right!
Let's look at all your answers!
Towa-san says Third Person Shooter.
Lui-san says Third.
Iroha-san says Third as well.
The three of them answered similarly,
but what's with the "Top," La+-san?
What's "Top"
supposed to mean?
It's referring to me.
Uh-huh...
I only play, like, 2 games, so...
The correct answer is...?
It's "Third"!
Yaaay! "Third"!
Yaaay!
By the way, FPS stands for
First Person Shooter.
As expected!
The difference is the
First or Third Person POVs.
Well, well.
You have three lives left, La+-san.
It's fine!
I'm perfectly okay.
Everything's fine!
I have a trait where
I can do my very best
the closer I am to certain death.
Fourth Question
Please listen to this.
Another one?
Again?
Got it.
Hmm?
Uh-huh...
Give me the title
of this famous song.
What?!
Seriously?!
The song title, huh...
I'm sure you've all heard it
at least once in your lives.
Yeah, I've heard
this before!
I've heard it before
but I don't know the title!
I know who made the song
but not its title!
This might've been played
at your schools.
Based on the previous questions...
Uh-huh?
This question might have
something to do with the season.
Understandable.
Everyone's got an answer,
so let's take a look at them!
Go ahead!
"Spring," "Waltz of the Flowers,"
Oooh!
"The Four Seasons,"
"The Four Seasons: Spring."
I was thinking "Spring" or "Canon."
"Canon," huh.
Ah, understandable.
I see...
But I think "Canon" went like,
or something like that.
Ah, okay.
That's why I scrapped that
and went with "Spring."
I wasn't sure if it was Vivaldi's
"The Four Seasons: Part 1"
or Mozart's "Spring"
and it was a toss-up
between the two for me.
I wasn't sure if I should go with
just "The Four Seasons" or "Spring."
Ah, I see!
And I realized they
might be part of a set.
How about you,
Miss "Waltz of the Flowers"?
Gut instinct!
That's from
"The Nutcracker," right?
Yeah!
You know nothing at all!
You should call yourself
Le Mess Darknesss instead, milady.
The correct answer is...?
Vivaldi's "Spring," which means...
What? The song's from Vivaldi?
Towa-san, Iroha-san, congratulations!
You both are correct!
What?!
Yaaay!
It's Vivaldi!
You answered "The Four Seasons," Lui-san,
but the actual title is "Spring"
("The Four Seasons" is the generic title
used to refer to "Spring," "Summer,"
"Autumn," and "Winter.")
so it doesn't count
if you don't write it down.
What?!
Oh, really?
What a shame.
Okay!
She might be the Joker!️ ➡️
The fact that you knew
the answers up 'til now
yet got this one wrong
makes you kinda sus.
What?
Now hold right there.
That makes sense.
⬅️ She might be the Joker!
The fact that you're choosing to
Oh?
attack me now, Towa-senpai, is kinda...
Is this where it starts?
There's no way
Towa-sama is the Joker!
Because I know who it is!
You do?
Who is it?
She's DEFINITELY
the Joker! ➡️
Iroha's the Joker.
What?
She IS the most sus.
Uh-huh.
No matter how you look at it,
I'm not suspicious at all!
⬅️ She might be the Joker!
On the other hand, Lui-nee's
been pretty spot-on with her explanations
and I think we're overlooking that.
That IS true...
(holoX Civil War Outbreak?!)
Very good, holoX.
Let the hate flow through you!
Fifth Question
This next question's
a drawing-based one.
What? Crap!
What shape is the
Japanese archipelago?
Please draw it out!
Ahahaha!
I might be in danger!
Huh?
I'm absolutely horrible at this.
Can't draw to
save her life.
I can draw, yeah.
I've got this. I'm a pro!
This is perfect.
Okay! Let's see those drawings
all at once! Open them up!
Ah... okay.
So those are your results.
Mine's just doomed, isn't it?
Our drawings are
pretty much the same.
Indeed. Your drawings
are quite similar.
The members whose answers
have been marked as correct are...
Everyone except for Towa-san!
Congratulations!
OH, COME ON!
Why am I
the odd one out?!
Mine's pretty close, isn't it?
Well, uh...
Despite everyone's drawings
being similar,
yours was above and beyond
in how bad it was.
It's because your drawing of Hokkaido
looks like a throwing star.
It looks like the one
Kanata-senpai wears on her head.
That IS true.
I see you also have a
somewhat big island up top too.
That's Okinawa.
That's supposed to be Okinawa?!
Okinawa?
I wasn't sure where Okinawa was
so I just plopped it down up top.
Really?
That's just wrong.
Sixth Question
Here's the sixth question!
The essential item for moving house:
the cardboard box!
When you think about it,
which industry invented it?
Whaaat?!
Huh?!
Hold on...
A. Transportation
B. Fashion
C. Sports
Is this about why the
cardboard box was invented?
Yeah. Basically, it's about the
origin of the cardboard box.
So basically something like,
"Why was it made?"
Exactly.
What sort of
question is this?!
This is totally
out of my league!
The straight answer
would be A, right?
But I wonder...
But think about it.
The hololive staff love
throwing curveballs, right?
That's true.
Good point.
Indeed.
But they also throw
curveballs into curveballs.
Oh, yeah! They do!
That is true. Yikes.
Oof...
Let's see your answers!
A, C, C, and A...
Okay...
Another perfect split.
Oh?
Come on, it's only ever
used for transportation, right?
So something like
"Cardboard Boxes = Moving"?
It's an object for holding
other objects, after all.
Uh-huh. How about you, Lui-san?
Why'd you pick C?
The shoes you use for sports
are extremely precious things, right?
That's true.
Yeah.
Uh-huh...
Like, when you need
to go somewhere,
you put them into a tough
cardboard box and bring that with you.
I think "Transportation" is
a bit normal for a reason so I picked "Sports."
I see.
The correct answer is...?
It's actually B. Fashion!
What?!
No way!
Seriously?!
Really?!
That means you all got it wrong!
How is it B?
Cardboard was originally used as
a material for lining the insides of silk hats—
Heeey!
Isn't it wrong to put it as
the fashion industry then?!
It really is the fashion industry!
(It was created as a lining material
for silk hats in England back in 1856.)
Putting that aside,
you're in trouble, Lap!
You've got
one life!
You only have one life left!
Last Life
Whoa. The next mistake
will be your last.
At this rate...
Okay, let me say this in advance!
Sure.
I know you'll all accuse me
of being the Joker.
Yeah!
Uh-huh.
But I'm telling you this!
You're seriously gonna regret it!
That's something only
a Joker would say.
This is just her
desperately defending herself.
For all you know,
La+-san might be the actual Joker!
Yeah, as if.
There's no way it's her!
Every time I play these kinds of games,
I'm always labeled as innocent...
I even tried to act sus too...
That seems both
encouraging and depressing.
I wonder why...
We can just shoot
for the end now, right?
Sure!
You might end up with a
different fate for all you know.
Seventh Question
Here's the question!
The famous movie Yojimbo (Bodyguard),
directed by Kurosawa Akira,
is beloved by many
throughout the world,
and even had a big influence
on Spaghetti Western movies.
Now then! Why are
Spaghetti Westerns named as such?
Darn you, staff!
Don't go and toss out questions
that make it seem like
I know the answers!
You ARE a bodyguard, after all.
This might be your chance to recover!
Stop that! Seriously!
Is Spaghetti Western
the name of a movie?
You know all your cowboy films?
Those are classified as Western films.
The question is why's there a subgenre
called Spaghetti Western.
Well, I'm gonna just
apologize in advance.
Sorry, girls!
"Sorry," she says!
What're you on about?
Can we avoid the
"Any last words" situations?
Everyone's locked in their answers,
so let's have a look!
Let's start from La+-san.
I mean... this has to be
the answer, right?
Because the people
in Western flicks
eat a lot of spaghetti (?)
Westerns. The land where
spaghetti lovers gather.
I was thinking that
maybe it's because
Because they
ate it often?
there were scenes
where they ate spaghetti.
Uh-huh. I see.
Come on, girls!
This question's just pain!
It really is!
Okay, last up is Iroha-san
who's under some heavy suspicion!
I was freaking out over an answer
but then I wondered
what spaghetti reminded me of
and I realized it's
pretty similar to a katana.
Maybe it's because the people
wandered around protecting—
That's way too dumb.
What a weird way
to play the fool there.
Well then!
Let's reveal the correct answer.
The correct answer is...?
They're called Spaghetti Westerns
because they're Western movies produced in Italy.
That's literally it?!
Yup!
I should've just written that!
Unfortunate as it may be,
you've failed five questions, La+ Darknesss-san.
It's time to feed you
to the guillotine.
Soz! I done goofed!
What happened to your initial drive?
Good point.
Okay! Time until the guillotine drops:
Three.
Two.
One.
Goodbye!
Aaahn!
Bye-bye!
All right!
Our splendid cast of survivors are
Towa-san, Lui-san, and Iroha-san!
Yaaay!
Yay!
However, one of you three
is the Joker who knows all the answers!
Please discuss between yourselves
and name one person who you think is the Joker.
Who's the Joker?!
Honestly...
Yeah?
I feel like it's Iroha.
Mhm...
So you'd think.
I'm telling you,
you're definitely wrong!
Okay then,
who do you think is the Joker?
I think Lui-nee's the Joker.
She did write the answer for
Nightingale in katakana earlier...
Ah, that's true.
La+ pointed it out but
I think that holds some weight.
Actually, why doesn't anyone
doubt Towa-sama at all?
Towa-sama has common sense.
Ah... right.
That's true.
The fact that you could answer
all the earlier questions, Iroha,
but got the first question wrong
was what sealed my decision.
I think the Joker
would feel like it's easier
if they went and
failed out of the gate.
Uh-huh...
Mhm. Okay.
That made me suspicious.
Okay! Let's look at your guesses!
Show those answers!
Okay!
Everyone voted for Iroha-san,
and Iroha-san votes for Lui-san!
All right!
See ya, Iroha.
If Towa-senpai's the real Joker,
all I can say is that she's amazing
and I'm sorry, Iroha.
Okay.
Painful is this life
for knowledge was my bane.
Okay!
If you're all correct,
the Joker will be guillotined.
But if you're wrong,
everyone but the Joker
will be guillotined.
Nooo!
Oh, really?
What?!
Please no!
Come on over!
Spare me!
Time until the guillotine drops:
Three.
Two.
One.
GOODBYE!
Goodbye.
I don't wanna!
Now for the results!
The last one standing is...
Tokoyami Towa-san!
WHAAAT?!
She was the Joker all along!
Congratulations!
What a magnificent win!
Seriously?!
Yaaay!
Holy...
I had no idea what
TPS stood for at all!
What?!
I didn't know
but I just talked a storm
like I actually knew.
That was
masterful!
The fact that you three
overlooked that
is why you ended up
where you are now.
Victory belongs to this Towa-sama!
You're so cool, Towa-sama!
I wuv that part about you! ❤️
You're supposed to be on our side!
Okay, Towa-san!
You've scored a magnificent victory in this quiz
so please close us out!
Got it!
Okay! If you enjoyed
this video, please like it
and subscribe to the official hololive YouTube
channel as well as my own one too!
Oh?
Ooh?
Well then, everyone!
Please enjoy a nice spring!
Let's have a refreshing farewell!
Bye-bye!
They're not even on the screen!
We're not on the screen!