Sigh...
Suba vrooming in!
Look, Miosha, new face!
Sigh...
Oh...
Hey, Subaru.
What's wrong?
My fortune telling's hit a rough patch.
Nothing comes naturally.
Oh, yeah?
Try telling my fortune, then.
That's a bad idea.
Look, just do it.
Fine.
Tonight, you will...
Sleep. Probably.
Scared, are we?
Be more aggressive, come on!
But...
Rest assured! I will make it come true!
So bring it!
That's some backwards logic...
Subaru...
You will ruin something that
people worked together to create.
98...
99...
What's so fun about jumping at fixed intervals?!
This was your damn idea!
Grawr!
I've even got heels on!
Fun! Fun!
Don't jump rope indoors in the first place.
See... it came true.
You can't call that fortune-telling.
But all my effort!
I'll pwedict the future too.
That's for magic tricks...
I-Is that really it?!
This...
It's yours twuly!
It's Miocha!
This...
It's The Fool!
The Fool, huh?
Hey, it's not a bad card.
Are you dispweased?
Aw, chill out.
Let's give it one more shot, then.
Who ever said there had to be a punchline?
We're having one of those days.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!