Everyone!
Do you love
getting praised?!
We dooo!
Showering praise upon praise
until you're happy!
It's the start of our Praising Grand Prix!
Yeaaah!
Yaaay!
This is what I've been waiting for!
I'm Shirakami Fubuki from
hololive 1st Gen & GAMERS
and I'll be your MC today!
Thanks for having me!
Let me explain the rules for the
Praising Grand Prix!
All right!
Okay! One of you will be
selected each round
as the person to be praised.
The rest of you will be given a theme
on what to praise about the person.
You have 30 seconds to heap as much
praise as you can following the given theme!
Cute clothes!
Nice hairstyle!
Looks good in black!
That horn looks
good on you!
It's a competition that's simple
and makes you happy!
The three of you are the
Silly Sisters, aren't you?
That means you know each others'
good points, do you not?
Well...
Leave it to me!
You girls okay?! What was that pause?!
Of course!
Obviously!
Oooh!
Oh?
What's with the pause?!
Let's start with our first player:
Himemori Luna!
Your theme is...
Cuteness!
Huh? What?!
Oooh!
Really?!
There's nothing but praise
for my cuteness!
Without further ado, let's begin!
Shower praise on Luna-chan
until you're out of them!
Ready?
Start!
You're peppy and cute!
You're a real princess!
That's so cute!
You have a crown!
Your hair color's so adorable!
It's just so cute!
I love the gradient on your hair!
Yeah! Wait,
what's with that crown?
(2nd time)
It fits you to a T!
You're so adorable!
Where'd you buy those clothes?
Heck, where are you from?
Uh...
Are you flirting?
Are you praising her or hitting on her?
Huh?
Ten seconds left on the clock!
Those clothes look great on you!
You look good in anything!
Ah, okay!
You're a genuine princess! (2nd time)
That's so cute!
Yeah!
You're s-super, uh... c—
Cute!
Super cute!
Absolutely adorable!
Time's up!
How did you feel, Luna-chan?
Hm...
Both of you were praising me... right?
There's so much to praise about you
that I wish we had another five minutes.
Yeah!
Did you really have that much to say?
We had so much more to say!
I'm a little concerned given
that pause earlier, though...
That "hard to get" act you put on
from time to time is cute, too...
Next up, Aki Rosenthal!
Ooh!
Wow!
Yaaay!
And your theme is...
Kindness!
Kindness?
It wouldn't be a lie to call me
the incarnation of kindness.
Incarnation?!
Without further ado, let's begin, shall we?
Ready?
Start!
Thanks for listening to me all the time!
You're so kind, Aki-chan!
Your very being is overflowing
with kindness, AkiRose-senpai!
Uh, that sounds kinda weird.
I wanna cover myself up in your kindness and
broad-mindedness whenever I have food issues! (?)
Thanks for everything!
Food issues? Um... okay...
Honestly, AkiRose-senpai, I'm covered by
your kindness just by standing near you.
You're overflowing with it!
Ov—
Over—
Ove—
You're overflowing with it!
Five seconds left!
Overflowing. (lol)
You're stuttering hard!
Well...
Aki-chan, your motherliness is overflowing!
You're overflowing with it! It's like a flood!
TIME'S UP!
No!
In any case, the word
you two kept pushing out
was "overflowing."
You're right!
Her kindness was so overwhelming that
my brain could only come up
with the word "overflowing."
Your brain overflowed.
Well...
You tried your best, I guess...?
You did, right?
That follow-up is really kind
of you too, Aki-chan!
Moving on, Robocosan!
Your theme is...
Brains!
Oooh!
Wow!
Ah, I see!
It's "Brains"!
I have a lot of that!
Leave it to us!
Give us 5 minutes― err, hours!
Wait, 5 minutes?
5 minutes?!
Don't think!
Feel!
Let's get straight to it, shall we?
Ready?
Start!
You're a klutz and that's adorable!
Wait, no.
You're amazing!
The theme is "Brains," girls!
Did you get everything wrong?!
It's "Brains"!
Your thumbnails!
You're really good
at making thumbnails!
Oh, thanks!
Yeah, she is!
You're awesome!
Does that have anything
to do with "Brains"?
Um... you're high-spec!
That's so cute!
You're great at taking selfies!
You're a quick calculator!
"Brains," girls, "Brains"!
10 seconds left!
The theme is "Brains"!
You're a pro at math!
A pro... probably...
You're great at FPS games!
You're great at them!
Uh... um... uh...
Uh...
Ah! Um...
Let's see...
You're probably good at cleaning.
You're good at—
Bad at...?
Bad at cleaning...??
I'm wondering if...
...these two even know what
the word "Brains" means.
Were the gears in your head spinning?
Well, um... obviously,
my brain just can't compare
to Robocosan's high-spec brains!
How about you, Luna-chan?
How were the last 30 seconds?
Uh...
Well...
I used my bwain a ton...
Y-You exhausted your own brainpower!
All right, then!
Your next theme is...
This!
Luna's "Gaa"!
Okaaay!
Oooh!
Ah!
Really?!
"Gaa"?
Don't you think it's adorable
when she does it?
Gaa
She's doing it even now.
See? She's doing it now!
Yeah, she is!
Gaa
She's doing it!
Let's get straight to it then, shall we?
Gaa
Ready?
Start!
It sounds really nice!
It does!
And on top of that, it immediately
makes us think of you, Lunacchi!
How do I put it...
Uh, what's a good way to put it?
It's what defines you and you're really
good at it and I think that's really amazing!
Yeah! It's so Luna-like!
And it's also so easy to say
that it's contagious!
It makes you wanna go, "Gaa!"
Yeah, I think it's great
that others can mimic it.
And it really fits you because
your voice is so cute, Luna!
You sound like a baby!
That's really great!
That baby voice is so cute!
"Gaaaaa!"
TIME'S UP!
Huh?
That was a lot of praise,
but I heard someone say
"it defines me" and "I'm like a baby"
and that kinda stuck out to me,
but they were basically trying to praise me
so I'm really happy with that.
Was it you who said,
"like a baby," AkiRose-senpai?
Aren't you a baby, Lunacchi?
I'm not a baby.
Not only that,
you're also the one who said,
"it defines her" didn't you, AkiRose-paisen?
Well, I said that because
those are things that I can't do myself,
so I really respect her for
being able to do those things!
Hey!
I wanted to say "Gaa!" too!
Really?
Yeah!
Okay.
Try saying it then, Aki-chan.
Gaa ♥
HEY!
That's sexy!
What's with the added sexiness?!
Okay, now for Aki-chan's second round!
Your theme is...
This!
"Half-elf"!
Is that okay?
Won't we get in trouble for this?
Moving on!
The one word to describe you,
AkiRose-paisen,
Who's suggested this?
has to be "Half-elf"!
Well, then...
Ready?
Start!
Your elves are—
Ears! Your ears are long and cool!
It's awesome!
My ears are normal, though...
She's got no elf ears.
The word "Half-elf" itself already speaks
loads about how cool and cute you are!
Word...? It's a concept.
And it's a concept that really fits you!
A concept that fits her?
Concept?
Rather than a concept...
A w-word...
Half-elves are beautiful!
It's a fact that half-elves are beautiful people!
Uh... beautiful, yeah, sure...
And really smart!
Yeah! They're smart!
Half-elves are smart!
That's got nothing to do
with being a half-elf.
Time's up!
WHO CAME UP WITH THIS PLAN?!
SHOW YOURSELF!
The Culprit
D-Dunno...
I dunno who came up with the plan!
I myself still don't know any good points
about being a half-elf.
You don't know yourself?!
Half-elves HAVE a lot of good points!
I can list a ton of them easily!
Really? Then can you list some?
For example?
Sure!
Half-elves have a mythical vibe, right?
And your MV for SHALLYS
was very mysterious, Aki.
Plus, another good point about half-elves
is that they radiate motherliness!
You have some fantasy elements yourself,
Aki, with your belly dancing.
I love how your singing and dancing
convey that feeling of fantasy.
Whoa... what a run...
Oh my!
I'm really happy getting praise
from Fubuki-chan like that.
Huh?
This is turning weird!
How about us?
What about us?
Okay! Last for praising but not least...
Roboco-senpai!
Your theme is...
This!
"High-spec"!
There's nothing but praise for that!
Shower praise on Roboco-senpai
until you're spent!
Ready?
Start!
Being a klutz is high-spec,
don't you think?
A klutz?
Klutz? Huh?
You're a klutz AND high-spec!
That's cute!
I think it's high-spec how you
have so many friends, Roboco-senpai!
You're really great at talking
and I think you're over-specced in that regard!
Yeah!
You're cute no matter what you do
and I think the way you
consider a lot of things is high-spec!
Oh!
The way how you might actually be smart
might also be high-spec!
"Might actually"?
"Might actually"? Huh?
I think the way how you knock over
a camera and look cute doing so is high-spec!
DING DING DING! TIME'S UP!
Knocking over... a camera?
The "klutz" comments took
so much to process
that I couldn't register anything else...
"Couldn't register anything else"?!
Are you okay?!
Being a klutz is amazing and high-spec!
It's apparently adorable.
Everyone will love you for it.
I see!
YOU'RE OKAY
WITH THAT?!
Stop trying to sweet-talk her!
SHE ACCEPTED IT!
You're a one-of-a-kind klutz!
ARE YOU REALLY
OKAY WITH THAT?!
Maybe it's okay to be a klutz...?
Stop!
Don't write weird things
onto her memory chip!
Stop it!
Yes, it is! Being a klutz is
a very good thing!
But really...
I think each one of us, uhh...
saw how close the Silly Sisters
are with each other.
With that said!
I, Shirakami Fubuki,
would like to declare the winner
for this round's
Praising Grand Prix!
The one who stood out
above all others is...
Oh?
Me! Congratulations, me!
STOP RIGHT THERE!
Hey!
Congratulations, me!
Stop right there! Hey!
Thank you, everybody!
Thank you, truly!
Time out!
Well, girls...
You all fell completely short of the mark.
Please get along more with
each other from now on, okay?
Owkaaay!
All right!
If you enjoyed this video,
please like it and subscribe
to the official hololive YouTube channel
as well as to our respective channels!
Good boys & girls subscribe!
Yeah!