Hmph!
Uhhh...
What's up?
See for yourself.
She's been like that for a while.
Time to butter her up.
Aw, you're so cute!
Here's your expensive sake!
This one's ranked A5!
La-my-y!
Hmph!
Wha...↓
What now?
If you keep sulking,
we're gonna bounce, okay?
Hmph!
Smooth.
Seriously, what's the deal?
Whatever it is, I'm sorry!
Huh...
Huh? Hold up.
Do we just need to apologize?
Okay.
Sorry, Lamy-chan.
I'll tone down the horror gaming a notch.
Huh...
Get to it.
Fine.
Hey, I'm sorry I'm so touchy-feely.
You're just too cute, you see.
Huh...
My bad. But I named
my sumo wrestler Yukinohana.
I swear I'll make 'em
a top-ranked Yokozuna.
Let's sumo!
Hmph!
Square one?!
We give up!
Fine, I'll tell you.
I just wanted you to notice.
Notice what?
I changed up the angle a little, see?
That's too obtuse!
I won't tell you the answer again.
Be more perceptive from now on,
okay...?
Oops.
Whoops.
Hrmph!
I'm so sorry!
Nobody could've noticed that!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!