Kids these days have it too easy.
Al*xa, put on the AC.
Cruising through life!
This thing turned them into grannies at heart!
H-How do we fix this?
Go down to Ryugu Palace?
Glug! Glug!
Fishes in the sky!
Hi-yah!
Gah!
Wait, Fubuki-chan?
Nay, I am Otohime, if I may say!
All for fandom, fandom for all
Oh, I guess I had it wrong.
Uh, you're clearly her.
So, what brings you here?
Please help these two.
Sure, if you give me something in return.
I'll act out a person desperate for a bargain.
Here's an idea.
You can up the original price
and then give me a discount!
Fubuhime
Y'know how some things aren't too funny,
but you find 'em kinda amusing
and want to share 'em with friends?
This was not one of them.
Tough crowd!
But fine, I'll make you young again.
Yay!
Om nom!
Woooooooo!
Too young!
Woohoo!
Wait, Korone!
I shall take my leave, then.
Wait! How do we get
these two back to normal?!
Maybe look for the famed treasure box?
Korone-chan, find another one by its scent.
*sniff*
This way!
Yahoo!
Dig here, arf!
Aye aye!
Veggies.
Dig here, arf!
You got it!
Meat.
Dig here, arf!
Mew.
holo Curry
It's Pretty Damn Good!
Roux.
Yummy curry is served!
What about the box?
Keep calm and curry on.
Screw this crap!
Hear ye, foolish human.
Fubuki-chan?
No. I am the Goddess of the Lake.
Uh, you're clearly her.
LALALA!
Was this opened treasure box what you had lost?
Or was it this unopened one?
I know this fable! We can get both!
May be a case where
we only get back what we lost.
Yikes. Smart asses, much?
Wait, what?
So damn cute!
That ruse could also be a ruse,
and the liar gets both...
Hey!
Let me have those two,
and I'll give you both boxes!
Deal!
And that's how we got these treasure boxes.
Uh, what about Okayu-senpai and Korocha?
Erp.
Would be cool if Ryugu Palace were real.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!