I'm going for the 4th!
The time has come
Go for it!
to crown the strongest Lucky Queen!
Starting!
No panicking allowed!
Game of Chicken with a balloon!
I'm totally fine!
Hellobo!
Fridge stocked to the brim
with expired food and drink?
Not a problem for me!
That's nasty...
I'm hololive Gen 0's virtual robot, Roboco!
hololive 0th Gen
Robocosan
Did I Luive you all waiting?
I've lost count of
all my flukes on stream.
Since they're all flounders!
Secret Society holoX
Takane Lui
From hololive Gen 6, I'm holoX's XO,
Takane Lui!
Ayo, this is Koyo!
Secret Society holoX
Hakui Koyori
Coming from hololive Gen 6,
I'm the brains of holoX,
Hakui Koyori!
I had a moment when
I was gonna take out the trash,
but once I opened the front door,
I realized I only had one article
of underwear on me.
What?!
So uhh...
But!
No one actually saw me
and I closed the door ASAP,
so I was completely fine
and not traumatized!
She closed it ASAP, right?
So it must've been traumatizing for her.
She definitely felt trauma from that.
No! That's not it!
Let's announce today's challenge!
Take a Chance! Trust Your Gut!
Lucky Queen!
Yaaay!
So, ladies!
Did you all receive a mysterious item?
Item in Question
A balloon blow-up gun
Yes!
This looks pretty dangerous.
Received!
Dangerous!
A pistol!
Oh!
It's a pistol!
So, for this challenge,
Take turns pulling the trigger
you girls will be taking turns
inflating a balloon with a blowgun.
If you manage to either not pop
the balloon while inflating it
Who has both the luck and courage
to face a balloon that can pop at any time?!
or not be frightened
if your balloon does pop,
you'll be crowned
the title of Lucky Queen.
So the key here
is to not get scared
either way in order to win.
Pretty much.
Easy peasy.
Totally child's play.
Piece of cake.
You sure?
You have to declare the number
of times you'll pump in the air
Declare the number of pumps you'll do
and pull the trigger
that exact number of times.
That's how it works. Okay.
I see!
Yes.
The balloons are sure
to explode by six pumps,
Balloons guaranteed to pop by the 6th pump
so you'll have to choose
a number from 1 to 5.
Okay then.
Got it!
Scaredy or lucky? Which will they be?
Who wants to go first?
Oh? Okay!
I might as well start things off!
Let's have Koyori-san go first then!
Huh?
Wait, uhh.
Where are the...
Where are the other volunteers?
We're not doing that?
Go ahead.
Right this way!
First off, how many
pumps will you do?
I'll go with four!
Bold!
Hakui Koyori-san is first up,
declaring that she will
pump the balloon
a total of four times.
Well then.
Let's go!
Pop it.
One!
What?
Everyone went whoa.
Two!
Wow, really!
Good pace.
Wow!
It's not popping!
Th-Th-Third time!
Wha?
Wait, huh?
Hold on.
Koyori, don't tell me...
Could this be...
a rigged gun?!
Did you make it not pop?
It's not rigged!
How much did
you pay them?!
I didn't cheat!
I... I...
I'm going for the 4th and last one!
Go for it!
What?!
It didn't pop?!
Koyori!
How much did you
bribe staff with?!
I didn't!
What now?!
How am I getting pity points
now that it didn't pop?!
Needed the pop for sympathy points
To think Koyori-san's balloon
didn't pop at the 4th pump!
As expected of
our current Lucky Queen!
Where did my unlucky streak go...?
Always pitiful in her streams
How do I deal with this?
Of all the times, too.
Huh?
Anyway,
which of you two think
you can win against Koyori-san?
Me!
How many pumps will you go for?
Koyo went with four, so I'll go five!
Wait! Wait! Stop!
Are you guys sure about
what you're going for?
If this keeps up,
what will happen to Robocosan?
You'll be forced to go for six.
Forced by peer pressure.
That's just me defaulting!
Next up is Takane Lui-san!
She will be pumping
her balloon five times!
Start!
Starting with the first pump!
Ooh, we're safe!
Good.
Second round!
Starting!
Okay!
Alright!
It's not popping, huh?
That was easy.
EX Rank Luck
Is the goddess of luck on my side?
Very impressive!
It's not popping...
If she can do it three more times...
Let's go.
Wait!
Time out!
Oh? What's wrong?
Time out for a bit.
The heat's getting
to Robocosan!
I'm panicking.
I need to breathe.
Let's do this.
Wait!
I think I got it!
It's...
It's actually
already popped!
There's no way
it could've popped already!
I will finish this.
Pulling the trigger...
For the 5th time!
Hmm?
Is it really...?
What happened?
It hasn't popped.
Oh wow!
Why didn't it pop?!
Takane Lui-san is now
our Lucky Champion!
(Provisional) Lucky Queen
Hey!
Heeey!
Lui!
This is amazing!
Masters of Luck
Secret Society holoX
The holoX lucky charms
are quite effective!
I mean, holoX as a whole
is full of elites.
What a claim!
We all have the strongest luck!
How many pumps are you
going for, Robocosan?
Mmm, well, six is a guaranteed pop,
so I'll match Lui-nee's number
and go for five!
Five pumps, got it!
With that said,
Robocosan will pump
her balloon five times!
Begin!
Yes!
Round one, starting...
She's scared.
I'm totally fine!
You still have
four to go.
She's just
on her first one.
Going for it.
Go for it!
Second round!
I'm... still okay!
She's holding her breath there.
I'm okay.
Th-Third...
Third round.
Third round, got it.
Robocosan is eliminated!
It popped!
Seems like it popped!
I-It...
It totally hasn't popped...
And that shriek was?
That was a loud "KYAA!"
For the best set record,
the Lucky Queen title goes to
Takane Lui-san!
Congratulations!
Hooray!
So close!
You may call me
Takane Lui the Courageous.
Fantastic work.
Alright!
If you enjoyed this video,
leave a like and subscribe
to our official channel
and the channels of today's cast!
We look forward to
seeing you again!
See you!
Please leave a like and subscribe!
Please do!
Starring
Takane Lui
Hakui Koyori
Robocosan
This show was
brought to you by Takane Lui,
Hakui Koyori,
and Robocosan!