I came, I saw...
Where's the office?!
Hey!
Down 'ere!
Uh, what happened here?
Ya see...
I tried to stop 'em.
But they ran off to Makuhari.
Allow me to introduce
the crabulous band members!
Crabby
On guitar, Landmower!
Vroom!
Thwack
Thwack!
On Guitar:
Lawnmower
On vocals, Moai!
On Vocals: Moai
...
In photo frame, Tapioca!
In Photo Frame: Tapioca
Drums!
You need a backing band
for the concert?
No Sunday, No Life
We'll make it crabben!
Wait, do we need
a vocalist in a backing band?
Tapioca!
But how are we going to Makuhari?
We can't even open a door.
You good, or do you need a claw?
I'm good!
Croc'n'roll!
Stick to one tic!
Yikes! Everyone, freeze!
Hmm... What's with this mess?
Missy.
Eek!
Could you take these guys to Makuhari?
Who are you?!
The office.
Oh, the office? Need something?
You have this concert, right?
They wanna help.
Wow, but a lawnmower's too big.
I don't wanna carry it.
Then I'll go!
B-But then...
Roaaarrrggghhh!
You'll be torn apart!
Shaddup!
If we don't...
...help out...
...then who...
...the hell will?!
Go, Office!
Fubuki!
Groaaarrrrggghhh!
Thank you...
Yeah, no!
And so our office makes its Makuhari debut.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!