Rawr!
Help, Akiganger!
Speedy Gone-zales
Akiganger
Ganger! Ganger!
Akiganger!
...
I don't have all day!
Choke on this!
🍺
Th-That looks like
a brew-tal attack!
Hmm?
Oh, end of the workday.
Time to clock off.
Huh? Wait, hold up!
Shaddup!
Protecting Earth is my job,
not my purpose!
Blame yourself for calling me
just before five!
Like I could plan for this!
Rawr!
No... Is this the end of the world?
Don't you worry.
I am willing to work 24/7.
Overtime Cop
Maringer
You are...
All-Nighter Missile!
Last Train Punch!
What?!
Where...
Where'd my job go?
You're going to destroy yourself
if you keep working that hard.
Love yourself.
But work is all I have...!
You must find your purpose in life!
But can I?
Of course you can!
Because you have...
A-chan...
Always keep Akiganger in your heart!
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!