"Let's head back"?
Where is she trying to take me?
...
I can't just stand around here forever.
Where did she go?
I don't see her at all.
The classroom light turned on.
Did she do that?
What...
Wh-What... in the world...
Ahh!
What is this place?
How did I end up here?
It all started when she showed up.
Everything started
to go wrong after that.
Come on. Let's head back already.
Please, tell me. Who are you?
What do you want from me?
I'm not going anywhere with you
unless you tell me.
You won't come with me?
What are you talking about?
You have to come back...
You have to!
Stay away...
Please... just stop!
I need to get away from here!
What's the point of
continuing this charade?
I'll lose myself if I stay here any longer!
If I can just make it there,
I'm sure I can go back!
I just want to laugh
and talk with my friends
and have a happy school life together.
So you're running away again.
Isn't that just like you?
Always running away.
I'm going back to where
my friends are waiting.
So, goodbye.
Wait—
You think your delusions
will save anybody?
...
Enough of this already.
July 20XX
July 19XX