Pyup Pyup
Beam!
Pyup pyup!
Stuff it to the max!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Let's open up today as well!
Okay!
Towa is off today as well,
so work hard in her stead you two.
*Towa is on break for today.
Okay.
Also, today's customer set up
a reservation in advance.
We have reservations?!
For a run-down shack like this?
Run-down?! I mean, yeah, it
looks like a century-old candy store.
Stop dissing my store!
Boss, you really should treat
all your customers the same way!
She's right!
It's better if you don't discriminate!
What were all the previous customers, then?!
Yeah!
Forget about our previous customers.
Huh?!
Someone THAT important is coming?
Why the heck?!
We've got ourselves
a real customer today.
What's their name?
Who's coming?
I think their name was...
*whisper whisper whisper*
Wh-Wh-Wh-
What did you say?!
*🦆🦆🦆*
A-Wh-Wh-Wh-
What did you say?!
Right?
The guest that shocked both of them is...
I'm here!
Oh!
She's here!
Good afternoon!
It's Tokino Sora!
Give us a brief introduction!
Please!
Okay!
My name is Tokino Sora.
I'm usually on YouTube.
Thanks for being here!
I love singing songs!
Thanks for having me here!
Yay!
VVVVIP
The living legend is here.
She's legendary, huh?
She's a legend.
We're actually besties.
Huh?
So you two are really close?
Aren't we besties?
I guess we are? Somewhat...?
Are they really besties?
Sora...
Huh?
Marine-chan!
Scary...
Tried acting like her bestie
I-Is she angry? I can't tell.
Be careful with her!
Sora, so who's it gonna be?
Me or Marine?
Who's the real bestie?
Wait, can I only have one bestie?
Argh! Sorry, Sora!
She's a player.
My best friend, Sora,
is finally here at Maruyama!
Attractive features:
Finishing Move: Pyup Pyup Beam!
MENT
LUCK
Let's all pyup pyup together!
"As long as I pyup pyup,
I get the energy to do anything"?
Pyup pyup is the greeting on my stream.
My fans were hearing
my "yup, yup"s as "pyup pyup."
Really?
So it all started from a mishearing.
From then, they started
using it with an emote.
Really? That's cute.
Nowadays it's becoming
like an onomatopoeia.
I see.
When I calm myself down,
going "pyup pyup,"
even if I was a little down,
I can get over it by the next day,
It's a magic spell!
It really is.
I want everyone to know
how pyup pyup feels!
Pyup Pyup
Beam!
Pyup pyup!
That's scary!
Everyone going pyup pyup is scary!
Pyup pyup!
O-Oh...
Boss...
You have to play along!
I was pyup pyuping so hard.
Play along!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Sora-san has a worry
she'd like resolved,
so please tell us what that is!
Okay!
I get down over the slightest things.
Fortunately, I'm the type
that gets over it quickly,
but I get depressed so often.
I don't usually have the chance
to consult with other people,
so I want to build rapport with everyone
and have a place where I can
talk to people, just like here!
That sounds good!
I want besties.
Let's become besties!
Leave it to us!
There we have our request!
Thank you!
Sora's problem is, in short,
No honorifics?
to strengthen hololive's sense of unity!
Leave it to us!
We have the perfect game for you!
What did you say?!
Maruyama's recommendation
for you is... this!
Moving Out!
The first-ever game
to make its theme moving,
Moving Out!
The player plays as a moving company
and takes on the city's
furniture moving.
Can you efficiently complete a move
while dodging ghosts
and working with other players to carry
heavy furniture, among other challenges?
By packing furniture quickly with four people,
you're sure to strengthen your unity!
In Moving Out,
there's a set time you want to finish in,
so it's important to finish fast
by working together.
So it's important to be coordinated.
Exactly.
Starting from training!
Boss will be substituting
for Towa-san again.
Let's receive some training first!
Here's everyone's characters!
The yellow fried egg is me!
Cute.
She's not very cute.
Huh? How rude. It's cute.
No fried eggs for you forever.
Something's starting!
Wow!
It's a wedding!
It's like America a long time ago.
It ended so fast.
Wow, it's so stylish.
This game has a very definite setting.
"Mankind has been lifting objects
since the dawn of time."
True.
Smooth Moves.
It's a commercial for Smooth Moves.
We'll be working for them.
I see!
So we're getting a certification.
That's right!
Let's do this.
Let's do it!
Let's go!
Oh, it started!
We're moving!
Ooh.
What's this?
Pressing buttons at random
to see what they do.
Checking.
Come over here, everyone.
Okaaay.
Mr. Cat, come over here.
Wait! Uh... Marine's toast is flying.
What?!
Is it?
Aren't you just seeing things?
The toast was on the floor just now.
Don't be silly, toast don't fly. Ah—
It's flying all over the place!
Someone eat this part of me.
You're right! It's toast!
Put the thing over here.
Move the packages to the blue markers.
Over here, right?
You're all doing fantastic.
For this, we have to carry it together,
so form pairs.
Someone pair with me!
Stuff you can't move by yourself
can be moved with 2 people!
Hup!
Someone.
Right.
Sora-senpai, let's form a pair!
Bring it over just like that.
We did it.
Our teamwork is pretty great.
Going great so far.
There's something there!
It's a ghost!
Sora-senpai, you're good with those!
Beat up the ghosts!
We can beat it up,
so beat it up together!
Sora-senpai's beating it up!
She's smacking the hell out of it!
Leave the ghostbusting to me!
Go ahead!
Lastly, carry these inside.
Okaaay.
Everyone's so good!
You've got the sense for it.
100 points.
Yay!
Now that you've all finished
the tutorial, onto the real deal!
Show us how in sync you all are!
The first location is Holly's House.
There are three ranks to the time limit.
If you fail to load 24 pieces of furniture
in three minutes and forty seconds,
you fail the mission.
Let's get moving!
Let's go!
Sora-senpai, let's do this!
Boss and I...
I think we need two for the sofa.
I see.
Let's get the small ones.
Ready?
For the windows...
Someone's breaking the windows.
You can break the windows as a shortcut!
Someone's already breaking them.
Please follow the law.
By the way, you can take
a shortcut through here.
Let's leave it here.
Take the shortcuts as you like.
Next...
So, break the windows?
Let's take this.
Please!
Like that.
We have pretty good teamwork.
Doing good.
It's stuck...
Okay.
There's a backdoor too.
Try using it.
It's stuck...
It might be good to let go for a sec.
Let go...
Boss, you're quite good at this.
Well.
Do you have experience doing this?
I seem like I have, right?
Like, in the past.
Just a little.
Seriously?!
Hey.
Listen close.
When you press this button, it shows
you how many people it needs to carry.
Roger!
Thanks!
So you can know
what you have to carry in.
Double-check which ones you need to carry!
Ah, Sora.
Ah, crap. That's no good.
1:17! We're on good track!
Was the good one 1:40?
1:40 is really good.
I want to go for that.
Sora-Marine, I'll leave the
big bed in the back to you two!
Okay! Let's get the bed.
That was a bed?
This thing here.
Other than that, it's these over here.
Let's carry these over.
Ah, is that a TV?
Sora-Marine, get in sync!
Calm down.
We got through!
Let's go out this way.
Ready?
A little more!
It's getting stuck!
Okay! Okay!
Pull!
Crap!
Calm down!
Okay.
Now pull.
Nice!
Alright.
Okay.
The time...
How are we?
2:17.
They finished loading
the difficult sofa and bed.
Just a little more to go!
The fridge! Marine, let's go.
Let's do this!
Nice!
That's fast!
So fast.
Perfect!
Okay.
Ah, sorry.
Is there none over here?
Marine!
Okay!
With that, they finished loading!
A clean finish! Quite good for their first job!
They didn't get the gold, but that
was pretty good for their first job!
How in sync do you feel you two were?
You were carrying stuff together.
Well, I think we weren't very in sync.
You weren't?
Do you think so too, Sora?
Um... I thought we did pretty well...
Marine's in the wrong here, isn't she?
That's completely my fault.
Marine's in the wrong.
But...
we did get stuck a few times,
so I think we can
do it better next time.
Right!
Excited to see how they do on the next stage
Let's look forward to their improvement.
Well then, we're at our next project.
Ah, right here!
Right here?
Yes!
A farm?
Next up is Snottsberry Farm!
Oh!
Sounds fun!
The thing we're loading
into the truck here is...
animals.
Sounds fun!
Pay attention to the animals running away!
The moving animals will
run out of the truck.
It seems assigning roles
will be important.
I'll be keeping the animals inside the truck.
Everyone else, carry them over.
Roger dodger.
Okay.
What's going on with this farm?
Sheep?
They're so lively.
Let's-a-go!
Let's go!
Sheep.
They're so fast!
They're running!
Sheep.
They're fast.
Here's another sheep.
They're just running.
First, Subaru organizes the truck's inside
As per plan,
Subaru-san is organizing
the interior of the truck.
Chase them into a corner.
Sheep...
I'm ready whenever.
Please throw them in!
Oi, you're kidding me.
You're making a scene.
Sorry!
I'll throw it in.
Throw 'em in!
When you're holding the chickens, they cry.
Like, "Bwak Bwak!"
I can't catch any!
Ahh! Something hit me.
Ahh! The chickens are running away!
I threw it the wrong way.
Confine the animals with the straws!
Everyone struggles with
keeping the animals inside.
Marine's toast...
It's flying!
This way, cow.
This way.
I brought the cow!
Ah!
Cow, cow, cow, cow.
Cow, cow, cow, cow...
Cow, cow, cow, cow, cow, cow.
The Big Cheese going after big game
Cow?
Let's throw this one on three.
Sora and Marine capture the cow
This cow's pretty easy to...
Throw it inside on three.
Press that button.
I'm pressing it.
Nice, Boss!
Ready? One, two, and...
It's not going!
Ow!
This trap hurts.
Sora and Marine-san want to throw
the cow further into the truck, but...
It's not going!
The cow's not going in.
Facing Difficowlties
It seems you're lacking in teamwork.
Let's put the cow in last.
Let's get the small ones first.
Roger that.
Roger.
Only a little bit of time left.
Let's all go out to catch them!
This game is way too difficult.
Alright!
Cow?
Cow! Cow!
Stuff it to the max!
Just get them on!
Last spurt!
Put 'em in!
Cow...
Ah...
That's so hard...
It's so hard!
That was so difficult.
It seems the escaping animals
were a bit too difficult for them...
Clear failed...
Moving animals is a struggle...
Close but no clear.
Let's get back in gear and
move on to the next stage!
Next, I want us to play
this place called Dread Manor.
Dread Manor!
There aren't any animals this time,
but there are moving chairs,
ghosts, and pianos.
Wow!
Poltergeists!
No way.
Sent to the start
if you're caught by a ghost?!
If you're caught by a ghost,
you're forcibly teleported to the start,
so try to avoid them!
Ghosts are scary!
Ready, go!
Go, go!
I'll start from the stuff
around the ghost that's outside.
Okay.
Ghost right off the bat!
The chair is moving!
The chair!
I'm already carrying one.
So fast!
How do I get out?
It's not opening!
Is this the ghost's doing?
Oh, you can get on
from this side. Sorry.
Crap, it's running away so much!
Wait,
the chairs keep running,
so we need something...
Moving chair puts up a fight
Will it run?
...heavy to block it in.
Over here?
Let's carry this over.
This.
I'm coming over.
Please help with this.
Coming.
Like this...
Blocking the moving chair with the bench!
The chair's running!
The chair's running.
Let's put it on this way.
Ah, okay.
The chair's running.
The chair's finally sitting put.
Who's a good chair?
Nice chair!
I'm going upstairs!
Unintentional pun-off?
Let's take the fridge.
Okay!
Oh, it's a piano.
The piano's attacking.
The pia—
The piano's crazy!
They're being attacked!
Sora, the piano's insane!
Getting used to the job?!
While they're surprised
by all the contraptions,
they're working remarkably more efficiently.
There we go.
Everyone's working pretty swiftly.
We can totally clear this.
I'm getting used to the controls.
Wait, if I put this moving chair here...
Ah, we brought just the thing, Boss.
Let's block it in with this.
Let's block it with this bench.
That's okay, I restricted it.
Say what?!
Oh?
I blocked it off with another chair.
She's too competent.
Okay!
Ah! I'm in the way.
This time for sure!
Can they clear it this time?
Marine, let's take this!
Okay!
Let me reposition.
Thank you.
Okay. Nice!
You're all...
starting to play really seriously.
I just really want to clear this.
Serious Mode
I feel you!
I end up focusing.
Where are the last 6 at?
2 minutes left.
Press this button on top!
Okay, I got it.
Okay!
We can clear this! Let's go!
Let's do this!
How many left?
Three more!
And this!
Okay!
Ow, piano!
Marine got sent over.
Darn it.
The piano's insane.
That piano's tough.
Oh, there.
There!
Dodge the piano by
going clockwise first!
Roger that!
Clockwise...
Be careful!
Then...
Excellent!
Okay.
Nice!
Only 2 more!
2 left!
Only 2 left.
Wait, isn't it these?
I have one.
You can do it!
This is the last one!
Sora!
Go!
Put it on!
It doesn't fit.
You can do it!
Yay!
Nice!
We did it!
We cleared it...
Congratulations!
Clear!
Getting much better at doing work!
They cleared the
difficult location excellently!
They really showed off
their teamwork this time!
That was really fulfilling.
This game is really fulfilling to clear.
Now that we're more united than ever,
let's challenge this last stage,
Flamethrower Factory!
What the heck is that?!
That sure is a place name.
Master the conveyor belt!
The last stage is a highly difficult
one fitting of the finale.
It requires even more
unity from the players.
Until now, it was important to pack things
into the truck compactly, right?
Yup.
Here, you don't put
the stuff in the trucks yourself.
Oh?
In place of that,
there is a conveyor belt.
We load it onto the conveyor belt,
and that loads it into the truck.
That's right!
Once you bring the packages here
and flip the lever...
the packages will be sent
to the truck on the conveyor belt!
If the flames hit the packages,
they'll be sent back to their original location,
so you have to use the
two switches to divert the flames!
I'll stay over here, then.
Ah, okay! We'll leave that to you.
Ah, but someone else is on it,
so maybe I'll leave it to them.
You do it like this.
I'll do it, then.
I'm a little confused.
How do I do this?
We carry these, and
we go to this conveyor belt...
Come over here, everyone.
Go through this.
Oh, is that the entrance?
Jump past this.
And then place the package here.
Someone left their package here!
And you flip this to push them inside.
And what's this?
That one adjusts the speed.
It's going backwards.
Ah... I see.
Okay!
Now carry those over.
I'll just bring a bunch.
Then we use the...
Ahh!
Ah. It's burning.
We need someone
in charge of the flames.
We need someone on the other one.
Then I'll be in charge of this one.
I feel like we might not
make it in time then.
Maybe we should take
all the packages over there first,
then put them all in at the same time.
Ah... Yeah!
Let's bring everything over here first.
Gather all the packages.
Okay. Without putting them...
Ah, I put them in.
Absolutely genius.
It's burning.
Nice idea, Boss!
First off is gathering the packages!
Training holomembers' unity,
Maruyama Moving Center
Maruyama Moving Center,
open for business!
Bring on the packages!
We've got a fair bit
of packages here now,
so let's get to our switches
and send some over.
Subaru-san is in charge
of the fire switch #1.
Sora is in charge of fire switch #2.
And Marine-san and Boss is in charge
of putting the packages on the belt!
Everyone has a role
in this assembly-line setup!
Let's see if it works out for them!
Can we push these over now?
Sure.
I think you have to flip the switch first.
Yeah, like that.
Ah! It's going!
Going all at once might... not be good.
I see.
I think some burned just now.
Did it?
Is it fine?
It's okay. Now...
Okay.
AHHH!
Did you flip it too early?
I flipped it too early.
Sora tries it as well.
I did it.
We finally got one in!
Keep them coming!
Will our package spacing work out
with our flame switching...?
They're cleanly burning.
They're burning alright.
This spacing ain't good.
This isn't working out
so well for us.
Package spacing is important!
Looks like she'll need to figure out
the feeling with experience.
Maybe we just play the numbers game
and send a bunch at once.
I'll keep sending them as they come.
Yeah, do that.
Two at a time is really good!
Two at a time is good.
With my current feel.
Then, Boss, let's put down two at a time.
Two at a time!
Okay.
At the same time.
This is easier.
This is much easier!
We're becoming more efficient!
We're like factory workers now.
This is really good!
Oh?
We're becoming pro-like.
We've been just so focused at work.
Good pace.
There's...
eight more.
Eight packages left!
Eight, huh...
Let's throw this over.
One, two, and...
They're getting good.
Last-minute power-up?
There's... about 3 minutes left.
Can we make it?
Can we?
We can't afford any mistakes.
Me and Sora included.
There's more over here!
Do we need two for the water?
Let's move the water first.
Roger.
It's becoming tense.
We're starting to speak less
from the sheer focus.
This is nerve-racking!
The fire duty is nerve-racking.
The fire duty's so stressful.
Let's go.
Thank you.
It went!
Nice!
There!
I'll put it in.
Please do.
Two minutes left, do your best!
We'll clear this at all costs.
Go! Go! Go!
One minute left!
Bread flew over!
Bread!
The bread is being transported!
Mine too!
Ah, I didn't make it.
I think it should be fine.
Serious Mode: The Return
Was that bad timing?
It's okay.
Ah, the direction is reversed.
Believe.
Believe!
Alright.
Are we done?
Not yet!
We still have one more!
Can we throw this over?
If I stop concentrating
for a second, it'll burn!
Eek!
One, two, and...
There!
This doesn't seem to work.
Does it not?
Keep going! Last minute!
Maybe...
We still have a whole minute.
We have a minute!
Okay!
One, two, and...
Huh?
Boss.
Did she slap her?!
Calm down!
There's one more to the right!
Nice!
Nice throw!
You got that.
Okay.
There's more down there.
The right one.
Bottom-right...
30 seconds left!
It's heavy...
Go! Go!
Marine!
Ah, nice.
There's not much time left!
Do your best, everyone!
Just a little left!
Marine!
Not much time left!
Everyone carrying packages for the end!
Marine! Thank you!
Okay!
Okay, okay.
We could've done it together, sorry.
Ah.
Wait, where?
Crap!
Ah.
No! No!
No! No! No!
Nooo!
No!
Guys!
We almost had it!
But by the end, we had the
well-oiled beauty of a factory line.
It was wonderful to witness.
My brain was empty.
True.
We were hyper-focused on our own tasks.
I really like games with a timer like this.
Yeah.
So it was really fun.
That was certainly teamwork.
I think we got better!
Well, then.
That's it for our demo!
What did you think of Moving Out?
It was really fun!
Yay!
I wanted to play more,
and I wanted to clear that flame place.
That was a close one, right?
Finally, let me ask you a question.
Please tell us the member who shined
the most, the Twin-crew for today!
Okay!
The Twin-crew for today was...
Subaru!
Heck yeah!
Well, we're besties, after all.
She was quite the leader today.
Really?
True.
During the game,
she was giving out orders.
Yeah. She was taking the lead.
The image of a leader!
Yay!
Thank you!
I think
your bonds with your seniors
got stronger as well.
Yeah!
It did!
Now, hololive is more peaceful!
Yay!
Pyup pyup!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Challenge From the Boss:
the Maruyama Championship Season 2!
Yay!
At this point, we'll have our customers
try their hand at a minigame.
The one who finishes the season
on top will receive a trophy!
This season's minigame is
SEGA AGES Sonic the Hedgehog's
Green Hill Zone Act 1's time attack mode!
The clear time shown on the
results screen will be your record.
By the way, the best time is currently held
by Suisei-chan, at 36.56 seconds!
Sora-chan, how confident are you?
I'm not that good at action games,
so I'm not so confident,
but maybe...
You can do it?
I could get a decent record!
Do your best!
Nice answer.
You'll be worth cheering on.
Let's get right to it!
We're starting!
Do your best!
It's started!
Go, Sora-senpai!
Blaze through it!
Blazing through!
How are the controls?
Oh, there was an item up there!
A hidden item.
She's stuck!
I'm sliding back!
She's glittering...
She got stuck at the slope.
The glitter's invincible mode.
Oh yeah, it is!
I see!
The glitter means you're invincible.
Go go go!
The Invincible Sora!
Feeling fine?
It's really fun!
Right?
Yeah.
Aaagh!
This is bad!
That part's tricky!
It's a common choke point.
Oh, okay.
Got through with not a dent.
Not bad.
I wasn't that fast, I think.
Goal!
Okay!
Sora-chan's time is 47.14 seconds!
Isn't that pretty good?
That's fast for a beginner!
Where does she place?
How did I do?
She's in 5th place!
5th Place!
That's a great record!
Really?
We had Four-Second Retiree, so...
Yeah, actually.
Retiree? What?
While it was a great record,
you, unfortunately,
didn't beat the best time.
Any thoughts after playing?
It was actually really fun.
Now I want to go for a quicker time
and, uhh,
take the world record.
I believe!
Will a monster appear
and beat the high score?
Find out in the next episode!
Please look forward to it!
Thank you for coming today!
Thanks for having me!
Bye-bye!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
So, I've had Subaru
stay over for today.
After Closing
Yep!
Let's give our viewers
some advice for their worries.
Lesgo!
This one is from Toratora-san
(@2aMDOeKIKF9e5u)!
Thanks for the mail!
They wrote this.
"I am a first-year middle school guy.
I have a crush on a person,
and I want to confess to them
at the end of my 1st year.
Thing is, I have a mullet haircut
and I generally look scary,
so they think of me as a delinquent,
and avoid me whenever we meet.
Okay, I see.
What do I do in this situation?"
They wanted advice on this.
What do you think?
Okay!
What you should do is
you should
do a lot of good things
in front of them!
For example,
picking up their eraser
from the ground!
Or picking up trash in front of them
to show how good you are!
O-Okay then!
Gotta go with that approach!
It's a great idea!
People who pick up
random trash are pretty cool.
Exactly!
You gotta show that gap in personality!
By the way, if you were to
see a scary-looking guy with a mullet
go in front of you, pick up the trash,
and subtly show it off,
how would you react?
Hmm, well.
I'd probably be surprised
that they had that side to them.
Right?
Yeah.
If Boss says it, it can't be wrong!
Not wrong at all!
With all that said,
our solution to Toratora-san's problem is
to do good things
in front of your crush!
Yes!
Anyway, we're accepting requests
for advice from you!
If your request gets featured,
you get this!
A completely unique, personally-signed
request fulfilled sticker!
So please send in your submissions!
We're taking them!
Keep 'em coming!