Huh? What's this?!
Oh, shoot, shoot!
It's me?!
The Dick Mabbutt.
Hold up!
Hey!
*whistle*
Title drop coming up!
The Dynamic Vision Championship:
hololive Express!
I am your conductor on this twip,
Himemori Luna!
The hololive Express
will be departing soon.
Will the passengers
please state their names
and favorite trains in order, please?
Good day.
I am hololive's No. 1 Sexy Queen,
Aki Rosenthal a.k.a. AkiRose
from hololive 1st Generation.
My favorite train is...
Hmm...
Mm...
Mmm...
The Dick Mabbutt.
Hold up!
Hey!
*whistle*
I'm hololive's No. 2 Sexy Queen,
Omaru Polka.
My favorite train is... hmm...
The Super View Odoriko.
It's got a kids' area, you know.
This sensual lady
longs for the kids' room?
I mean,
when I was a kid,
I was all like, "I wanna play there!"
Okay, next up, Iroha-san.
Faster than a speeding Carzama...
Hello, I'm hololive 6th Gen
and holoX's bodyguard,
Kazama Iroha, I daresay.
I am coming to you with
my most ladylike voice today.
My favorite train
is the maglev Linear Motor Car.
It, too, is faster than a speeding Carzama.
Glad to be here today, I daresay.
Very well.
The scheduled time has come.
Our train that traverses
the stars at superfast speeds,
the hololive Express,
will be departing now!
It's like a theme park ride!
On this twip, you all will be quizzed on
the things you see outside these windows.
However!
We'll be traveling at
super-super-duper fast speeds,
so you'll only see them for an instant.
They may be hard to see,
so twy not to miss anything!
Without any further ado...
Here's Stage 1:
"How many passengers
are on the hololive Express?"
This train will soon cwoss another
hololive Express going the opposite way.
Ah, I see.
Please count how many of
your copies are riding that train.
Copies?!
Train incoming!
That was quick!
Already?
Too quick!
Three!
Two!
One!
Ready!
That's a lot of me.
Wait, AkiRose only?
Huh?
I have clones!
Okay, raise your hand
if you know the answer.
Me! Me!
Me!
Me! Me! Me!
Me! Me! Me! Me! Me! Me! Me!
There were seven!
How about the others?
I counted a lucky seven too.
I daresay it was a lucky seven too.
You know, did they forget
they're in outer space?
They're sticking their bodies
out of the train.
Are they even still alive?
Uh, we don't talk about that.
It's nuts.
Did anyone get it right?
Let's take a look in slow motion.
I sure hope we did!
Yeah.
One AkiRose,
two AkiRoses...
Alona! Alona!
Six.
Seven.
Seven alona!
Seven alona?
Alona! Alona!
Alona!
The correct answer is seven!
So, yes, all of you got it right!
Woohoo!
Yay!
Seven alona!
Stage 2:
How many *****s are in
the shooting stars?
You may spot your copies
hidden among the shooting stars.
Try and guess how many
of them there are.
Three!
Two!
One!
Oh, shoot, shoot!
They're zooming!
It's me?!
Fast. Too fast.
Pick me! I've got it!
That was thirteen Polkas!
I think I saw around
fourteen Polkas, I daresay.
I get the feeling
there were fifteen Polkas.
Wait a sec.
They're multiplying.
Polka-senpai's growing in numbers.
You all gave different answers.
Oh no...
Did anyone get it right, though?
Take a look in slow motion!
Okay!
I'm not sure even slow-mo will help.
We can check.
There!
I saw that!
Got Polka!
Got Polka!!
Five...
Got Polka!
Six...
Seven...
Eight.
Nine.
You're hidden behind all those stars...
Ten Polkas.
Eleven...
Twelve...
Thirteen...
Fourteen...
Fourteen!
The correct answer is fourteen!
Yay!
Well, I daresay my life in the boonies
has helped improve my vision.
Wow, nice.
How, exactly?
Okay, we'll be steaming into
another one of those showers.
What?
Five seconds to go!
Four, three, two, one, zero!
Why are you counting so quickly?!
Fast!
Too fast!
That's me, all right!
That...
was ten daresays.
What?
Ten... daresays.
Huh? Really?
But I counted nine daresays.
I saw ten daresays too, I daresay.
Ah!
Oh?
This is two versus one.
Yikes. I may have messed up.
Split answers!
Did anyone get it right?
Let's take a look in slow motion.
Okay!
This needs slow-mo.
One daresay... Two daresays...
How surreal.
Three daresays...
Her pose is so proper.
True.
Four daresays...
Cinco dare Sayo!
Seven daresays...
I missed the seventh daresay!
Got a ways to go, huh?
Ten daresays!
Oho?
AkiRose-san and...
Iroha-san!
You got it right!
Hooray!
Nooo...
Yay!
Stage 3:
How many members are hidden
among the countless aliens?
Countless?
What does that mean?
What do you mean, "countless aliens"?
This train will soon pass through an area
densely populated by aliens.
You may spot a bunch of members
mixed in with those aliens.
Try to guess how many there are!
Three! Two! One! Zero!
So fast!
Again? Seriously?!
I saw a Polka.
I saw an AkiRose.
I saw a Kazama too, I daresay.
The princess was there, too.
Yeah.
She sure was.
Huh? I was?
The conductor.
What's the correct answer?
Take a look in slow motion!
What was that?
Aliens... Aliens?
Polka-senpai...
Yeah.
That sure is densely popul—
Ah, there's me.
AkiRose-senpai!
There I am.
Smol!
Love this BGM.
Princess!
Oh, Luna-senpai!
Yay!
Was I in there?
We did it!
The correct answer is four!
We're steaming into another
alien area!
Are you ready?
I knew it.
On your toes!
This will be hard.
Let's go! Five seconds to go!
Four, three, two, one, zero!
Slow down!
Fast!
Wait.
Why was the last one alien-sized?
Yeah.
I saw someone really big.
I saw a female alien.
What did you just call me?!
Was that five AkiRoses?
One Polka-senpai,
one Kazama,
five AkiRose-senpai, I daresay.
Definitely. Maybe.
One princess, one Pol,
one Kaza...
and five AkiRoses.
So, eight?
I think my answer's
the same as Iroha-chan's.
One Pol, one Kazama,
five AkiRoses.
Did anyone get it right?
Let's take a look in slow motion.
Okay!
I'm so fast.
Whee, I daresay!
I daresay! Hey, it's Polka-senpai.
Got Polka!
Looks fun.
Alona! Alona!
Alona!
And this last one...
Huh?
So that means
the correct answer is...
Seven!
...seven!
AkiRose-san and Iroha-san got it right!
I dareyay!
Yay!
The person with
the most right answers was...
That's one hell of a drumroll.
Dun!
Iroha-san!
I daresay I did it!
Express Vision
Kazama Iroha
She got every single one right!
I did?
No way, really?
Did you enjoy your journey
aboard the hololive Express?
It was indeed, I daresay.
It was fun!
Yeah!
Are you always
the conductor on this thing?
Well, uh, we take turns.
Oh, you have shifts?
If you enjoyed this video,
please like and subscribe to
the hololive official channel
and each of our channels as well!
We're waiting for you!
Please!
Please do!
Indeed, I daresay!
It's time to say goodbye.
Let us meet again
aboard the hololive Express!
Yeah!
Indeed!
Okay!
Later!
See you!
Bye.
I bid thee farewell!
What a good train.