Multiverse of Promotion
May 3rd on the hololive official YouTube channel
#ホロストレンジ
Recap!
Get up-to-speed on Doctor Strange!
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness
Before you watch,
get up-to-speed on Doctor Strange!
Brilliant neurosurgeon Doctor Strange
injures his finest tool, his hands, in an accident.
Loses the use of his hands
But he finds new purpose in the mystic arts!
New purpose in the mystic arts
Reborn as Master of the Mystic Arts
Through intense training,
he is reborn as a Master of the Mystic Arts!
Prideful and arrogant,
but compassionate at heart,
Arrogant, but cares for his friends
Avengers' Master of the Mystic Arts
he's also a valuable member
of the Avengers!
He fights alongside his partner,
a sentient... cloak?!
Partner is a sentient cloak
In this latest installment,
the once Sorcerer Supreme
faces a new threat from the multiverse!
The Avengers' Master of the Mystic Arts,
Doctor Strange, opens the gate
From Marvel Studios,
the studio behind Avengers: Endgame
Master of the Mystic Arts
Doctor Strange
to a realm of infinite possibilities:
the multiverse!
Realm of infinite possibilities
The Multiverse
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness!
To celebrate the release of
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness,
the hololive Multiverse of Promotion...
Ready?
...is finally starting tomorrow!
Whoo!
Woo-hoo!
Yaaay!
Yup!
So, Multiverse of Promotion, a campaign
brought to you by hololive, is finally live!
Woo-hoo!
All right!
I, Master Korone, will be your MC!
Thanks for having me!
Yup!
And it's your first time MCing!
Any thoughts?
I'll do my best.
You're strung pretty high.
You're as stiff as a board!
I'm pretty nervous, but...
I'll be okay since I have you two.
Sure! We got your back!
Got it!
And presenting alongside us is...
Ancient Fubuki!
Open your eye.
Fwoosh!
Whoa!
Now all the viewers
are in their astral form!
Okay, what's going on here?
Calm down.
Koro-san? Koro-san!
I can explain!
Ancient Fubuki did the palm strike, so...
I can see that, but some of our viewers
might not know what an astral form is.
You all don't know what an astral form is?!
That ain't right!
Not everyone knows what an astral form is!
That's just strange!
Please watch the movie, then!
Yeah!
Please watch the first movie!
That was smooth.
The astral form is brought up
in this series quite a bit.
Anyway, it's in the title of this movie,
but do you girls know
what a multiverse is?
Of course!
What is it?
So a multiverse, put simply,
Tell me!
What is it?
refers to multiple other dimensions
that are different from our reality.
Yup.
Oh!
And the person who did
the "Open your eye" thing
is called the Ancient One,
who appears in Doctor Strange.
The Ancient One is a super amazing person
who taught Doctor Strange magic.
Really?
Yeah. Strange initially
didn't believe in magic,
so she did the palm strike thing
just now on him
and separated his spiritual form
from his physical form
and taught him how ignorant he was.
Yup.
Basically, she's the one who turns
his idea of common sense upside down.
Uh-huh.
Yup.
Do you two wanna give it a go?
I wanna!
S-Sure.
Here I go!
Okay!
Open your eye!
Fwhoom!
Whoooaaa!
Both Subaru and I have
turned into our astral forms!
Okay, let's not try to push this.
Let's stop. It's making us look crazy.
It's a no-go, huh?
You're making me sweat buckets.
I didn't expect to pull it off.
I guess my training paid off!
You're amazing, Ancient Fubuki!
Hard work really does pay off!
Okay!
Moving on...
What a sloppy segue!
Moving on... Subacilius!
Yo, I'm the villain!
Huh? Ms. Villain?
Wait, were you a villain, Subaru?
Come on! I haven't fallen to
Dark Dimension Magic,
and I don't have black stuff
all around my eyes!
But, uh...
There's such a character in the movie.
Let's just blame this on our producer
who wrote the script.
Quit getting all embarrassed!
I mean, come on!
"Yo, I'm the villain!"
It says that in the script!
Well, for those who aren't too
knowledgeable about the MCU,
to put it simply
in my words as a big fan,
Uh-huh?
I, or actually...
Kaecilius, a villain who appears
in the previous Doctor Strange movie...
He's basically one bad customer.
Ooh...
How scary.
The bad guys who appear in Marvel movies
have "villain stans" over here in Japan as well.
In fact, my absolute favorite character,
Loki... oh, wow.
I almost called him my Loki-woki.
My favorite character, Loki, is also a villain.
That's true.
Fubuki-senpai's favorite Loki-woki
Hey!
is one of the bad guys, but...
Okay, fine! He's my Loki-woki!
I won't deny it!
Yup.
Well, the characters that
appear in Marvel movies
are all fascinating,
be they heroes or villains.
Exactly!
Yeah!
In Marvel movies, character motivations are
super well defined, regardless of their alignment.
Like with Strange, for example.
He learns how to use magic
and fights enemies,
and he beats them up, right?
Yup.
But because he's also a proud doctor,
it causes him great internal conflict.
Yeah.
I love those scenes.
I totally get you!
They're just great, aren't they?
There's a segment after this where
Lui-nee, Schubau, and I rave—
Rave about Doctor Strange.
We'll go full throttle in that segment!
Yeah!
How nice!
And this show is—
You can do it, Korone!
I will!
I'll do my best!
Korone!
I'll do my best to read the script!
Hey! Don't say that!
Sorry!
The aim of this program—
The goal is to show all our fans
the joy and appeal of Doctor Strange
and convince you guys to hit the theaters to watch
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness,
which releases tomorrow!
Hit the theaters!
Yup! Hit 'em!
Please go watch the movie!
Yeah!
Okay!
We'll be covering
the media event which started in mid-April
as well as report on the currently ongoing
movie-inspired café in Roppongi Hills
created as a commemoration for the movie!
Woo-hoo!
Furthermore,
Subaru-chan, Fubuki-chan, and
Lui-chan will be doing a segment where
they'll talk about the previous movie, as well as
highlighting parts of the movie to rave over.
Yaaay!
The talk segment was recorded in advance,
but there's just so many fascinating
things about Doctor Strange
that we didn't have enough time
to highlight everything we wanted to!
There really wasn't enough time!
We talked a whole lot,
but I think it's all been edited down
due to time constraints.
A brief segment is just not enough time!
Exactly!
Yup!
Subaru, Lui, and I talked about
this in the segment,
but I'd like to ask you what the
Marvel movies are to you, Korone!
To me, the Marvel movies
are all about eternal heroes!
Ooh...
I believe that they really exist,
and I'd love to join their ranks.
And since Koro-san wants to do that,
let's take a look at Koro-san's hero pose!
Show it to us!
What?!
Ooh!
Hang on!
Three!
Two!
One!
Go!
Wow, that's weird.
That's out there!
Okay...
Isn't that more of a villain's pose?
If I had to say, yes.
Is it?
It's fine.
The villain Korone has appeared!
I feel like she'd bite people's fingers off.
Good point.
But I'm fine with being a villain too!
Really?!
Yeah.
Villains are cool too, right?
Yeah. They sure are.
Yup! I wanna be a cool villain!
Come to think of it, by the way...
Just last week...
Come to think of it...
Come to think of it, did you girls see that
when we announced this program last week?
That?
Huh?
And that would be...?
Oh! The poster?
You mean the poster?
Yeah!
Here it is!
Here's the poster!
Take a look!
Ooh!
Whoooa!
This poster's so cool!
The level of detail is just insane!
It's amazing!
Plus, the fact that we're officially
allowed to do this is just nuts!
Yeah, it is!
hololive has truly crossed dimensions.
It really has!
Right?!
Apparently, the hololive poster is jam-packed
with lots of insider references and jokes.
Do you girls know what they are?
Can I take a closer look?
We've got some insider jokes
I wonder what they are...
I suppose it's the obvious one?
The fact that La+ is
standing where Wanda is,
but she's so short that she has to
stand on a cardboard box.
Yup!
That's hilarious.
She's too short!
It isn't her floating,
but her standing on a box!
You're right!
Yup!
Wait. Did you two notice it?
Notice what?
Aki-chan!
The magic circles around her hands
have the same symbols from SHALLYS!
I'm surprised you noticed it.
That's amazing!
You can tell just from this?!
Awesome!
You've got some great eyes.
They drew the symbols in!
Really?
Plus the magic circles
are shaped like apples.
Yeah!
That's an important trait for Aki.
You're right!
That's cool.
Yeah. Plus we have the
shattered glass flying around,
but if you take a closer look,
it's the glass from our office windows!
You're right!
Right?
It's the window glass from our office!
I feel like there's a tendency
for our office windows
to get shattered every time
there's an announcement.
Yeah!
They get shattered all the time.
They're mass-produced.
Pfft... mass-produced...
Yup! Our office windows
are mass-produced!
Yep!
And the person who made this poster has
a specific part they want to highlight.
You see the crow on top of Lap-chan's head?
It's in the exact same position
as the Eye of Agamotto.
Oh, that's amazing!
It's perfect!
Oh, you're right!
Yeah. There's stuff like that as well.
Thank you so much for the poster.
So that's what the
cardboard box is for?
Yeah! Just for that!
Oh! I see!
It was needed to get her position just right!
I see how it is!
Basically, there's a whole lot
of thought put into this poster.
There's so many things to dissect.
Don't laugh!
Nice way to wrap things up.
Right?
And not only that...
Right!
Not only that, we also have this footage!
Roll the tape!
Footage?!
Whoooa!
Wooow!
Amazing!
That's so cool!
I swear, this reel is insane!
It's just like in the movies!
Yeah! Exactly!
It's instantly recognizable!
Oh!
Ooh!
That's so amazing!
It's so epic!
It's freaking awesome!
Multiverse of Promotion
May 3rd on the hololive official YouTube channel
#ホロストレンジ
It really is!
Wow...
There's also the hashtag #holoStrange!
That's so awesome!
It's holoStrange!
Whaddya think?
It's unprecedented!
Yeah!
Who would've thought that
we'd get to do a parody version
of Marvel's trademark intro reel
that's present at the start of
every one of their movies?!
Wow...
Did you ever see such a thing coming?
It's amazing.
I really didn't think
this would ever happen!
I know, right?!
It sounds like a dream!
Every time I saw the reel
I'd think, "Wow, that's so cool."
but I never imagined we'd get a hololive version!
Yeah! You'd always see it at the start
of every Marvel movie!
Yeah! With that timelapse
of different scenes.
Wait, you both never expected it?
Expected what?
This.
Whaddya think?
It's unprecedented, right?
Of course!
We already said that!
Was your head in the clouds?
We said it earlier!
You did?!
We did!
Great question there!
I think—
I think I'm still on edge!
Whenever you're confused, Korone,
you'll just do this!
Yeah!
Yep, this pose!
Okay, moving on!
Well, this might only give you a little push,
Yup!
but if you become interested
in Doctor Strange and
the other Marvel movies
after watching this show,
we would love that.
Yup!
Yeah!
All right!
This marks the end of
our opening segment!
Oh!
Next up, we've got
these three reporting on the
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness-
inspired café!
Yaaay!
Whoo!
Without further ado,
let's switch over to them!
You're still here?
You hanging around?
Go already!
Shoo!
Go, go, go!
Get a move on!
Move it!
Go, go, go!
Hurry up!
Yaaay!
This Golden Week, head to theaters
for an epic, reality-bending
cinematic experience!
Marvel Studios presents:
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness!
We're here, we're here!
Yay, we made it!
Yes, we've here!
So, what might this place be?
What might it be?
It's the Doctor Strange promo café!
You said it right!
In Roppongi, Tokyo!
It's finally begun!
hololive's special promotional campaign:
Multiverse of Promotion!
Three hololive members
have come to take a look at
a café inspired by
Marvel Studios' upcoming movie,
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness.
It's celebrating the movie's release.
The café is decorated throughout,
and the menu also features special items
inspired by the world of Doctor Strange!
The three of us got a special invitation
to visit this promo café.
It's an honor.
That's so nice of them!
There's already huge posters
right at the entrance.
Wow!
Look, Aki-san, your beloved Wong is here too.
I wonder if they put up
all of the characters.
Looks like it.
I'm so much looking forward
to the movie.
All these people that we know and love.
I can't wait to see it!
Ah! Strange-san, good to see you.
Ooh, look at him.
He looks so cool.
He does, right?
They have big posters
from the movie too.
"Enter the multiverse,
a world of infinite possibilities."
That's so cool!
Hey, look at this.
Check it out.
Yes?
Wow!
Wait, he's right here in this café!
It's an honor to meet you.
He's looking me in the eye.
No, no, he's looking at me.
No, it's definitely me.
I'm not sure if you noticed,
but he's actually looking at me.
And in the end,
he's not looking at anyone.
Look at him float.
He's floating with his cloak.
WOW!
I want one too!
The inside of his cloak
looks amazing too.
Oh, look here!
Wow, it's so detailed.
Right?
Oh! Look outside!
What a pretty view.
This looks amazing at night.
Would be perfect for a date, no?
Don't say that.
You're just making us feel lonely.
But look, there's tables
right by the window too.
It's nice of them to put
those round tables there.
You can also come alone that way.
Ah, you're right.
You can come as a couple,
or with the whole family,
or on your own.
Of course.
Well, shall we go ahead
and try out the food?
Yeah!
Yes, please.
Let's go.
All right. I guess I'll be going first.
Not fair! I'm hungry too.
The dish I'll be having is called
the One-eyed Creature Seafood Pasta!
Yay! That looks delicious.
The pasta represents the creature, see.
Right, I can see that.
That's pretty straightforward.
It is.
Honestly, it smells great.
It does!
I can smell it all the way over here.
Mix, mix, mix.
Hey, stop that!
Where will you start?
The eye?
Start from the eye!
But if you eat the eye,
it won't be a creature anymore.
It'll just be a tasty-looking
pile of spaghetti.
I'm starting!
How is it?
It's proper pesto spaghetti!
I'm getting worried
about your food reviews.
The noodles are nice and thin,
and the parmesan cheese
with the roasted squid
gives this crispy texture. I like it.
That sounds delicious.
I couldn't really place
the taste of the eye, though.
Here's my Cheeseburger That
Got Teleported From New York!
The design on that plate
looks so dynamic.
Let's see how it tastes.
Here we go!
Enjoy!
It's super big.
The patty is really thick,
and I love the taste.
It's a bit different from
the hamburgers you usually get.
Like a new experience that
you can't have anywhere else.
It tastes super good.
And here's mine.
It looks so fancy.
Oh look, it comes
with potato chips too.
Nope, can't have 'em.
Come on, you can
give me one at least.
I'm starting.
This tuna is great.
You like the tuna?
This tuna sandwich is great!
I... suppose it is.
It has tuna and tomato and...
There's tomato and egg and tuna in it.
I love it.
There's one more dish
you can order right now,
so let's get that one
for the three of us.
This is the Sanctum Sanctorum Window
with Nepali-style Chicken Curry!
We saw this on the internet!
Yes, this is the one!
I was so curious about this one.
Yeah, me too.
Let's give it a try, then!
Enjoy!
You too.
Enjoy.
Whoa, it smells great.
It's taking me to another country.
It's spicy.
It takes you to Nepal.
It does.
It has this subtle spiciness.
What's the red slice? Radish?
Radish?
Radish maybe?
It looked just like his cloak
when they served it.
This is the taste of the Kamar-Taj.
Maybe Doctor Strange had this too.
Right?
They made him drink tea
at the start, though.
Yeah, they did.
Maybe he didn't get this after all.
I'd say we try out the drinks next.
Time for drinks! I'm thirsty!
Personally, I ended up choosing
the Multiverse Tomato Smoothie!
Check it out.
They really went all out in
making it multiverse-themed.
Right?
The rim has a
"portal made of popping sweetness."
So it's a portal!
Sounds mighty dangerous if you ask me.
Better not touch it.
"It'll take you to another dimension."
I'll go ahead and take a sip!
What's it like?
Wait, it's making noise!
It's popping!
Scary!
Are you okay?
You're not going to
another dimension, are you?
It feels like I am.
I quite like the taste.
It's a smoothie, so I think it has
a bunch of other things besides tomato.
Does it?
I still hear it popping!
Do you want to try it too?
I'm getting... pulled away...!
What is this stuff you gave me?!
This is bad...
That's the candy portal.
It's just a tomato smoothie, okay.
I can't... It's dragging me in...
This is the kind of fun drink that you can
only get at themed cafés.
Yeah, that goes for
all the dishes here, really.
You can tell they wanted
to make something unique.
All right, here's the next drink they offer.
The Magic Circle Smoothie.
Ooh, looks cool.
So they designed it
to look like a magic circle.
Right? Looks just like it.
It's a "refreshing smoothie
based on oranges and mangos."
Let's give it a try!
Here we go.
Delicious! I love it!
It's great.
It mostly tastes like mango,
but it really is refreshing.
It's delicious, I'm telling you.
You should try it too.
The taste is just right, not too sweet.
Ah, you're right!
The lemon scent freshens it up.
You could have three or four glasses
of this without a problem.
So, the description says it represents
Doctor Strange's
magic circle of Eldritch Light.
Makes sense.
I can see it.
It's a glass of Eldritch Magic all right.
Look at this.
They brought the next drink.
That looks so cool!
It looks super classy.
It does. What is it?
It's called "Sorcerer's Grape Juice."
"A beverage representing a world
that was altered by the multiverse."
It's jumping right out of the glass.
Another amazingly dynamic design.
It's a... pretty crazy concept for a drink.
But it's the multiverse.
I'll go first, then.
How will you tackle it?
With my teeth, that's how.
You're starting with the candy?
I am! Here we go!
*crunch crunch*
Oh wow.
How is it?
It's great!
I wonder if they make
each of these by hand.
Yours look slightly different, don't they?
They do, they do.
I wonder how the staff does it.
I just realized why they look different.
They're different worlds
from the multiverse.
Good one!
That must be it.
You're getting good
at making these comments.
I'll have the grape juice too, then.
Ah, delicious!
The grape flavor in this
is pretty strong.
You can really tell what it's made of.
Hey, why am I the only one drinking?
Get to it, will you?
I'll take the juice first.
Oh, you prefer it that way?
You were right!
Grape juice through and through, right?
Really tastes like grapes.
The perfect grape juice
for grape juice lovers.
Not watery at all.
It tastes fruity.
But hey, about this candy bit on top...
Each one of these is unique, isn’t it?
It does feel like
they made each one by hand.
Yeah, they all looked completely different.
That's the multiverse for you.
It's the multiverse!
Bottoms up!
And that concludes the report
about this promo café.
Tomorrow on May 4th,
when the movie gets released,
the One-eyed Creature Seafood Pasta
and the Star Portal Sandwich
will be added to the menu.
This themed café
celebrating the movie release
will be open to visitors until June 19th.
Be sure to come check it out!
After the break:
"What We Love About Strange"!
This segment is part of
hololive's special promotional campaign,
"Multiverse of Promotion"!
Yay!
Whoo!
Yeah-yeah-yeah!
It's finally habbening!
It's habbening!
Witness the action in Marvel's
most unpredictable and epic entry yet!
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness,
coming to theaters on May 4th!
Yay!
Whoo-hoo!
So excited!
So exciting!
After opening the door to the multiverse,
a realm of infinite worlds
and infinite possibilities,
Strange faces an entity
of unparalleled magic and evil:
an alternate version of himself,
in this magical action epic!
Say what?!
We'll be discussing what makes
Marvel movies so great
and what to look out for
in the new film
in a way that even
new viewers can understand!
Yup!
Further, we'll be delving into
what makes Doctor Strange,
the brilliant but arrogant neurosurgeon
turned Avenger and Master of the Mystic Arts,
such a compelling character.
Yay!
Right! So, the three of us
will be the panel for this segment.
Yep!
We'll take turns...
And who are we?
Glad to be here!
Who, indeed?
Let's take turns introducing ourselves
What do you mean, who?
and saying what Marvel movies
mean to us!
Let's start with
the most habbening member.
Okay!
Right!
'Sup!
I'm the habbening one.
It's good to be here.
To me, the MCU is
a deep, deep rabbit hole.
The name's Oozora Subaru!
Yay!
Okay, next up...
To me, the MCU
is a world that sparks the imagination
and makes you wonder
if superheroes could be real.
Did I Luive you waiting?
Takane Lui here!
It's an honor to be here!
Yay!
And finally,
to me, the MCU is a world of
endless possibility and imagination!
It's me, Shirakami Fubuki!
Yay!
We'll be the ones
bringing you this segment!
Hope you enjoy!
Please enjoy!
Enjoy!
Actually, Fubuki-senpai and I
have been vocal Marvel fans
for quite a while now,
but we found out recently that
Lui-chan's quite the fan as well!
That's right!
It's true.
In fact, Doctor Strange
is what got me into the MCU.
Ooh!
I'm a huge fan of
Benedict Cumberbatch-san,
so I originally watched the movie
because he was in it.
That's how I became a Marbel fan.
Yeah.
Nervous?
Oh, absolutely!
I was like—
You're nervous?
Do I really get to be in this?
Oh?
You sure do!
I do?
You should be more vocal!
For real?
Wait a second.
Before we started recording...
About your love
for Benedict Cumberbatch-san!
Right?
Gosh, I wanna marry him.
You were like, "I'm gonna—"
I love him so much, I wanna marry him.
Okay, that's a little...
That's going a bit too far,
isn't it, Fubuki-senpai?
It is, but I understand the feeling.
I'm glad you do.
I just love him so much.
So I really love him as Doctor Strange too.
I see.
That's right.
I gotta say, I'm with you on that.
I normally don't go into this much,
but can I have a moment to rave
about Marvel, Fubuki-senpai?
Go for it! I know there's a lot
you love about those movies!
Gosh,
"a lot" doesn't even begin to cover it!
One of the main draws of Marvel films
is that they're easy to get into
and easy to understand
even for people who
don't usually watch movies.
And they're just tons of fun!
Right?
Of course, each movie has its own theme,
be it magic, technology, or so on,
but they all feature
spectacular action scenes
and tons of cool and cute heroes!
And more than anything,
just watching them gets me so pumped up
and hyped up and souped up—
Wait, not souped up.
"Souped up"?
Pumped up, hyped up, and souped up?!
Come on! I'm nervous too!
Oh, you are?
Yes, I am!
Nerves, huh?
Can nerves make you mess up like that?
Sounds sus to me.
I wouldn't joke around at a time like this!
So it gets you pumped up and hyped up,
and the design of the vehicles is so cool,
and their bases and buildings!
And the gadgets, like with Iron Man and stuff.
Not to mention,
the romance subplots that
show up every so often.
So good!
I know what you mean.
Gotta love that.
It's just the best.
Sorry, are we still good on time?
We're fine!
We've got plenty of time.
You really made your passion clear.
Seriously, though,
the Marvel movies are all so good.
Right.
The thing with Marvel movies,
is that the relationships and connections
between the characters are so complex.
I couldn't have said it better!
Exactly!
Right?
And there's no better example
than the Avengers movies.
The Avengers, like Iron Man and Cap,
first starred in their own films,
but then they got to team up.
That includes Doctor Strange, the Avengers'
own Master of the Mystic Arts.
Right.
Exactly.
There's just nothing cooler than seeing
the heroes of different series
fight alongside each other.
You can say that again!
It's so cool!
It's like the best thing ever.
For the people who think that the MCU
might be too complicated for them,
please, just turn your brain off and
give Guardians of the Galaxy a watch.
Man, Fubuki-chan, you're
so obsessed with Guardians!
I love it so much!
It's so hilarious!
There are so many great quips.
It's like they can't go a minute
without a zinger.
Seriously, Guardians of the Galaxy
is such a good movie to start with.
Seconded.
Exactly.
Plus, the Guardians of the Galaxy
eventually cross paths with the Avengers,
which provides a good segue into
watching Avengers and other Marvel films.
That said, putting aside the Guardians of the Galaxy,
my favorite Marvel character is Loki.
There it is.
Show some love for Loki Laufeyson!
I swear, Fubuki-senpai...
I can feel the intensity...
I mean—
I'm a bit intense about this.
This girl's such a huge Loki fan,
she's got like, the cup
that appeared in Loki...
Right, I also collect lots of merch.
That's right.
You sure do.
I'm a collector.
Yeah.
I've got a bunch on my desk,
heh-heh-heh...
...as a matter of fact.
Just so you guys know,
Fubuki-senpai only giggles like that
"Heh-heh-heh!"
when she's genuinely enjoying herself.
That was the giggle of a true fangirl.
Right, when I'm fangirling.
Fubuki-senpai and Subaru-senpai,
what's your impression of Doctor Strange?
My impression of him?
Such a cute and mischievous gentleman.
Can't argue!
Totally.
Right?
Seriously, in the movies,
he just breaks all the rules.
He sure does.
Like, honestly.
But that's also what's great about him.
Like, it shows his curiosity.
He really is adorable.
It's like, go on, break those rules!
I know what you mean!
Who are you, his doting mom?
Right, like he's conceited
and kinda insufferable,
but that's part of his appeal.
He's like a naughty child.
Exactly!
You nailed it.
That, and also,
he seems really cold at first, right?
Right.
For sure.
The cold, detached, genius neurosurgeon,
who seems really self-centered.
But then he gets in his accident,
loses everything, hits rock bottom,
then goes through all that training.
Right.
And you get to watch him
grow as a person
while getting hints of
his future friendship with Wong
Right, right.
through their snarky conversations.
Like the Beyoncé scene.
Gotta love that.
Right, Beyoncé!
Plus, when he gets in his first battle,
despite his cool demeanor
when he was a neurosurgeon,
he's totally flustered, because
he's never been in a battle before!
Like, he grabs a random pot in his panic.
It really humanizes him, you know?
You don't even know how to use that!
Exactly!
Yeah, just grabs some random pot!
"Sure, this works!"
Right!
Throughout the movie, you catch glimpses
of that very human side,
beneath his cold, arrogant exterior.
I really love that.
Same!
Also,
his self-assuredness that comes
from being a genius
Uh-huh.
is really fun to watch.
Oh, man...
You really nailed it.
I just can't stop nodding.
Seriously, Strange is really
self-centered and impulsive,
and sees everything as "himself"
or "the rest of the world."
Impassioned speech from Lui-chan...
Buthetrulycaresforthoseclosesttohim,
evenifhe'snotgoodatshowingit.
Thatmakeshimsuchahumananddeepcharacter,
andreallymakesyoulovehim.
And it's just like, gosh,
I love this Strange character so much!
It just drives me wild!
Easy, there!
Like, gosh, I'm so in love
with you, Cumberbatch!
I see.
That's right.
Have I sufficiently expressed my love?
More than enough.
You sure have.
That you have.
Such a good character.
So great.
Got it all out of your system?
You just said your bit and
breathed a sigh of satisfaction.
I know I need to explain myself clearly,
but I keep worrying
that I'll start rambling.
I know that feeling!
Same.
Us geeks can't help
but ramble about what we love.
I'm afraid I'll become a runaway train,
just barreling on forward,
with no way to stop.
Good job putting on the brakes.
But I'm glad I was able
to express my feelings.
So, by this point,
I think the viewers have gotten an idea
of how much we love this franchise.
Now, let's take a closer look back
at the first Doctor Strange.
Ooh!
We'll be looking at some of our
favorite scenes that we selected beforehand.
One of us sure picked
an awful lot of scenes.
So I think this should be
a very lively discussion.
Oh, crap!
Okay!
Favorite Scenes Watch Party
Try to guess the scene!
So, what do you think of this
ragged and dirty Doctor Strange?
So hot.
Hot?
Try to guess the scene!
I get it, though.
The disheveled hair and all.
Exactly!
That, and also,
it really shows he's
at the end of his rope.
Right, exactly.
Yeah, definitely.
And you can tell just by looking at him.
It's such a good scene.
And he's still wearing that watch!
The fact that he's kept that watch
with him this whole time...
I know!
I was like, "STRAAAAANGE!"😭
Ah, so good.
So like,
if you learned how to do magic,
you'd definitely want to use it, right?
I mean—
Totally!
For sure!
Like, picking things up.
Right.
Yeah.
Like, let me grab this book.
What would you
use it for, Fubuki-senpai?
If you learned how to do that.
If I learned that?
Gosh, I dunno.
Go peep on you at home, maybe.
I have some objections to that.
Like peep on you in the shower?
I object!
In the shower!
"Sorry, I didn't know this led here!"
A likely story!
No, come on,
I wouldn't abuse my power!
Ooh, the apple!
The apple!
This part is so exciting!
Yeah, I love this scene!
Ooh!
Right here!
I like how he starts by testing it
on something small, like an apple.
Right?
Wow...
You gotta start somewhere.
The design of the Eye of Agamotto
and the way the magic circles form
around their hands...
I know!
They're just so...
They're so cool!
When I first saw them,
they were so cool,
I was like,
"Are you kidding me?!"
And then...
Novice sorcerer Strange,
you've got this!
You can do it!
Yes!
So cool!
I seriously love the part where Strange
floats up from below with his cloak.
I know, it's so great!
I've seen a lot of movies,
and I'd never seen anything like this part,
even in other magic-themed movies.
I was like, "Wha..."
"This hurts my brain!"
It really throws you for a loop.
It's trippy, but not
completely incomprehensible.
Yeah, exactly!
Right, and you lean in while watching.
Here we go!
Whoa...
So freaky!
He's so huge and scary!
There's no way he can defeat Dormammu,
yet he wears him down...
wears him down into submission...
Where he's like,
"I'll keep doing this forever!"
It's basically a comedy sketch
with Dormammu, not a battle.
I see what you mean.
He's like, "Stop coming back!"
Exactly!
The way Dormammu's like,
"I can't take it anymore!"
It's such a unique scene.
Even though he's so huge!
It's such a funny scene.
I laughed when I first saw it.
Like, "Oh, that's how we're doing it?
That's how we're fighting
this thing, huh?"
This scene is the best.
It's a really great scene.
Yeah!
End of Watch Party
And there you have it!
We had quite a lot to say
about those scenes.
I wish we had more time.
Recording time: 2 hours
We'd need at least three or four hours...
No kidding.
There's so much...
I wish we could talk more.
Right?
I wanna watch more and talk more!
They probably condensed all that
into a reactions montage.
We've been recording
for quite a while at this point.
We sure have.
We've just been watching scenes,
going, "So good..."
Hard to believe
it could be so condensed.
So excited for the new film.
I know, I can't wait!
Wanda's gonna be
in the new movie, too.
Really?!
That's right! It's so exciting.
Wanda from WandaVision will be co-starring.
Holy cow!
That's right, she's been through a lot
and gotten a lot more powerful.
Now she's meeting Doctor Strange.
I just can't wait to see how they'll interact
and where their stories will go.
I can't wait!
He fights himself, too.
That's right!
It's a mirror match!
Totally!
It's like, what's going on,
what's gonna happen?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm just dying to find out.
Can't wait.
Absolutely.
If we get into that, I'd have to start talking
about What If...? and everything.
That's true.
So, if this has caught your interest...
Hopefully, we've gotten some more people
interested in Doctor Strange.
That concludes
"What We Love About Strange"!
The Avengers' Master of the Mystic Arts,
Doctor Strange, opens the gate
From Marvel Studios,
the studio behind Avengers: Endgame
Master of the Mystic Arts
Doctor Strange
to a realm of infinite possibilities:
the multiverse!
Realm of infinite possibilities
The Multiverse
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness!
"Operation: See Us, Hear Us Interview"!
Well, your name for this segment
is definitely unique
and so cheesy.
What are you laughing at?
Got a problem with it?
Anyway, witness the action in Marvel's
most unpredictable and epic entry yet!
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness is coming to theaters on May 4th, you louts!
Yay!
After opening the door to the multiverse,
a realm of infinite worlds
and infinite possibilities,
Strange faces an entity
of unparalleled magic and evil:
an alternate version of himself,
in this magical action epic!
This program is meant
to introduce hololive fans
to the magic and madness
of Doctor Strange,
so that when
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness
finally premieres tomorrow,
you louts will flock
to the theaters to see iiit!
See iiit!
Why did you draw out the last word?
Furthermore!
Keep it together!
A part of this project,
Right.
the voice cast interview, has been left
in the hands of us,
Secret Society holoX!
That's right!
I had the privilege of attending the voice
cast announcement event on April 18th!
The event featured Mikami Satoshi-san, the voice
of Master of the Mystic Arts Doctor Strange,
Matsushita Nao-san, the voice of
Strange's ex-girlfriend Dr. Christine.
as well Kitou Akari-san,
voice of newcomer America Chavez,
a young girl who holds
the secret to the multiverse.
These Japanese dub
cast members took the stage
to discuss the many mysteries
surrounding the new film
and what each of their characters
brings to the table.
Gosh,
the anticipation is killing me!
And I myself, believe it or not,
got to interview Mikami Satoshi-san,
voice of Doctor Strange,
and Matsushita Nao-san,
voice of Christine Palmer,
where I asked them all sorts of things!
Whoa, that's so cool!
I even got to take a picture with them.
They let you?
And here's that special picture!
Ta-dah!
Would you look at that!
It was such an honor!
You're grinning ear-to-ear!
Of course I'd be happy!
Mikami-san is so handsome.
He is!
Mikami-san is so handsome and
Matsushita Nao-san is so beautiful.
There was so much star power there,
it made me a stammering mess.
I'm so grateful to them.
Did you even conduct
a proper interview, Sakamata?
O-Of course I did.
Piece of cake.
I'm honestly a pretty big fan of
Mikami-san and Matsushita Nao-san.
Gosh, was it okay to leave them
with this girl?
Here's the footage. See it, hear it!
See it!
The truth is,
I really don't like bathing,
so there's something
I simply have to ask you two.
In short: Do you like bathing?
Bathing?!
What?!
Wait!
Hold up, hold up!
Stop the video!
What, why?
Huh?
Wha...
You... You asked if they liked bathing?!
That's right.
Ohhhhhh boy.
You've done it now.
What, why? What did I do?!
The first thing you ask them and you—
Ask them about the movie, you dolt!
Okay, hear me out!
You see, this was all
part of my strategy.
Really?
Your strategy?
Perhaps this is too advanced for you,
Strategy?
but when you first meet someone,
they'll be nervous,
so you gotta put them at ease
with something lighthearted.
It's called an icebreaker.
Okay, hold up.
The point isn't to make friends!
This is an interview!
Okay, but still...
Mikami-san was totally taken aback!
"B... Bathing?!"
My apologies.
In that excellent voice of his.
He did seem taken aback.
I would imagine so!
Indeed.
Okay, but there's more to it! Let's watch!
Here we go!
Seriously?
In short: Do you like bathing?
Bathing?!
Well, I certainly wasn't a fan
when I was a young boy.
What a gentleman.
We didn't have VCRs back then,
so when I'd be watching TV...
He went along with you.
"Come on, it's bathtime!"
"No, after I watch this show!"
So I'd drag my feet
and refuse to go bathe.
That's so adorable, Mikami-sama!
I wouldn't say I love bathing.
I tend to be quick.
I don't really read books in the bath
or watch movies or videos or anything.
I'd rather bathe quickly
and watch afterwards.
I knew it! That's so her!
Do you do anything in your
personal lives to help get in character?
Nice.
Including, I suppose,
your bathing habits.
But do you change
any of your daily habits
or pay particular attention to anything
Ooh, I'm curious.
when deciding
how to play your character?
That's a good question.
Well, this is less about the character,
but we have to take care of our voices,
to ensure they're in good condition
when we go to record.
So that includes things
like bathing, so that the steam
can help keep our throats
from drying out.
And of course,
if I have work the next day,
I make sure to get plenty
of sleep the night before.
Well, for me,
just because I'm playing
a gloomy character
or a character who isn't very cheerful,
that doesn't mean I have
that mindset in my personal life.
In fact, I make sure to
separate myself from the role
so that the character and
my personal life don't blend together.
Talk about some great answers.
For sure.
The part about taking care of your voice
applies to us, too.
Right.
We should follow that advice.
Yeah.
If a professional voice actor says so,
we'd better pay attention.
Exactly.
Bathing aside, the part
about keeping your throat moist...
Seriously, though, just take a bath.
Nah, I dunno...
It's that simple.
Let's move on to
the next interview question.
I still have my doubts...
How come?!
My last question was good!
Anyway, here's the next question!
A lot of hololive fans are
college-age or in their early 20s.
For first-time viewers of Marvel movies
or the Doctor Strange series,
do you have any favorite parts or things
you'd like them to watch or pay attention to?
Well, the visuals are stunning.
There are showings in 3D and even 4D,
so you can experience the movie
like an amusement park ride.
For college students and young people,
I think this is a perfect date movie.
Why don't you try asking your date
if they'd like to come watch this with you?
Well, first,
I would recommend they watch
the first Doctor Strange on DVD.
Once they've done that,
I'd invite them to come watch
this new film when it comes out on May 4th.
Speaking as a woman,
Marvel movies can give the impression,
with the action and aesthetics,
that they're mainly for guys,
which might drive women away.
But that's not the case at all.
I think that's one of the great things
about Marvel movies.
They're not bound by gender.
They tell stories that anyone can enjoy.
And as Mikami-san said,
they're perfect for dates.
You'll definitely have plenty
to talk about after the movie.
Yes, absolutely.
Sharing your thoughts afterwards is
part of the movie experience, isn't it?
Yeah.
With Marvel movies.
I could keep talking forever.
I bet watching Doctor Strange
in 4DX would be amazing.
I know, right?
With the incredible visuals and all.
Exactly!
Like in the last Doctor Strange,
remember the scene where
the city folded in on itself?
Yeah, the Mirror Dimension.
Yeah, exactly.
Those parts are seriously so good.
Parts like that.
You've gotta experience that.
Okay, let's check out
the next interview question.
Next, next!
It's been five years since
the first Doctor Strange was released.
Five years?!
At the time, you stated in an interview
Sheesh!
that your impression of Strange
was "a conceited and arrogant character."
Time sure flies.
After playing Strange in this new movie
and his other appearances,
have your impression of him and
how you approach his character changed?
Ah, yes.
He definitely had that arrogant
and self-important attitude,
which to some extent hasn't changed,
but after Endgame,
That's what makes him great!
as well as Spider-Man,
he's definitely gotten
a bit more friendly and approachable.
Yeah, for sure.
Definitely felt that in Spider-Man.
So I definitely feel like
he's grown as a person.
But some parts haven't changed,
and I think it's quite fun
to be able to see those aspects.
Yeah.
Yes, of course.
With each new movie,
Strange's character gradually develops.
As Mikami-san said,
you can see him grow as a person.
Yeah, his heart got bigger.
Yes, well, that's a simple way of putting it.
It really has.
Well then,
shall we move on to the next question?
Go, go, go!
Let's go!
Matsushita-san,
you also said five years ago
that Strange's arrogant and self-centered side
was part of what made him so attractive.
When playing Christine again this time,
did your impression of Strange
and what makes him appealing change?
Well, he's certainly
become a true superhero.
In the first movie, you could tell
he still had a boyish, immature side,
which made him quite cute.
But this time around,
I'm sure that any woman who sees him
would find him quite desirable.
Thank you so much for the response!
Boy, I know what she means.
She really nailed it.
The thing with Strange is
he's got those hidden depths.
On the surface, he looks like
a no-nonsense doctor,
but he's actually got quite
the mischievous personality.
He sure does!
How could you not fall for him?
Lastly, I asked them both to give
a message for our viewers!
For real?!
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness
is finally coming to theaters!
To all you hololive fans,
we hope you'll come out and watch it!
So nice!
It's such an honor to hear
these two say that.
Not to mention...
"To all you hololive fans"!
Sh-She actually said that...
Hard to believe, isn't it?
It's seriously unbelievable.
So unbelievable,
I'm at a loss for words!
Do...
She's in fangirl mode.
Do we deserve this honor?
Please, everyone.
You gotta go out and watch this.
Right?
Please do!
And another huge thank you
to our lovely interviewees!
Seriously, thank you so much!
Once more,
Right.
you can witness the action in Marvel's
most unpredictable and epic entry yet!
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness,
coming to theaters on May 4th!
That's right!
And all you louts
watching this program
had better go see it
and hear it in the theaters!
See it, hear it!
Recap!
Get up-to-speed on Doctor Strange!
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness
Before you watch,
get up-to-speed on Doctor Strange!
Brilliant neurosurgeon Doctor Strange
injures his finest tool, his hands, in an accident.
Loses the use of his hands
But he finds new purpose in the mystic arts!
New purpose in the mystic arts
Reborn as Master of the Mystic Arts
Through intense training,
he is reborn as a Master of the Mystic Arts!
Prideful and arrogant,
but compassionate at heart,
Arrogant, but cares for his friends
he's also a valuable member
of the Avengers!
Avengers' Master of the Mystic Arts
He fights alongside his partner,
a sentient... cloak?!
Partner is a sentient cloak
In this latest installment,
the once Sorcerer Supreme
faces a new threat from the multiverse!
The Avengers' Master of the Mystic Arts,
Doctor Strange, opens the gate
From Marvel Studios,
the studio behind Avengers: Endgame
Master of the Mystic Arts
Doctor Strange
to a realm of infinite possibilities:
the multiverse!
Realm of infinite possibilities
The Multiverse
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness!
Would you look at that!
It's time to wrap things up already.
Although, we're still quite pumped.
What you saw just now was a Doctor Strange
recap video dubbed by Fubuki-chan!
Amazing, isn't it?
Wow!
That's right!
The official version is dubbed by Spider-Man's
Japanese voice actor, Enoki Junya-san.
It was played right at
the start of this show.
And guess what!
I had an opportunity to dub the recap video
exclusively for this show!
Thank you so much!
Fubu-chan, how did you feel when
you were asked to do an official dub?
Exactly how you would feel
when you get asked to do an official dub.
I was sweating buckets
while recording it.
I see.
It was an honor.
Thank you.
Thank you so much!
Nice interview!
Okay!
Celebrating the release of
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness,
our special program, Multiverse of Promotion,
is coming to an end.
Subaru-chan, how did it go?
It was quite short, but I hope we managed
to show all the various sides of Doctor Strange's appeal
through stuff like the café review
and interviews with the voice actors.
And so!
To all hololive fans!
I'll put it bluntly!
I'd like you to watch the previous entry,
Doctor Strange,  on Disney+!
And, of course, go and watch
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness
in the theaters!
Let's go!
We'd be glad if we managed
to show Doctor Strange's charm
even a little bit to all our hololive fans.
Right?
That's right.
We made this such a fun program. So good.
All the segments were too good.
We outdid ourselves today.
It still doesn't feel real, though.
It was like living a dream.
Yeah, I agree.
It was like a dream come true.
Well, it's time to go now.
Guess I just have to do this...
Hey, what are you doing?
Like that...
Hey, Fubuki-senpai?
Fubuki-chan, what's going on?
I want to go home.
Go home? Why?
What do you mean "why"?
The show's over, isn't it?
You're a fox, not Strange!
Get it right!
I want to go home and watch it again!
I'm gonna review the previous
Doctor Strange movie again!
It's not appearing...
Well, I mean...
There's a slim chance
that it will appear...
Really?
Like...
No, no.
If you do like that...
There are no slim or fat chances!
What, really?
Of course!
Nonsense, watch me go!
Just try it yourself!
Okay, let's see if it works.
You want to open a portal? Okay, then.
Stretch out your left hand
and go counter-clockwise with your right.
Okay.
Got it.
I want to go home...
"I want to..."
Open, the gate to my home!
"I want to go home..."
We're still live, you know?
Well, whatever.
Open, the gate to my home!
You have to believe in it
or it won't work, Subaru-chan.
I see, but...
That's right!
A portal to the convenience store
nearby is fine too...
Hell no, it's not!
We don't know magic,
so I doubt we can do it.
Okay, let's end the show
and go home, then.
Hey, why am I the only one doing it?!
It won't open after all, huh.
You gave up too fast!
Guess we aren't fit for it.
It won't open, huh.
It just won't open.
Anyway, we hope you enjoyed the show, and...
Witness the action in Marvel's
most unpredictable and epic entry yet!
Open sesame!
Doctor Strange in the Multiverse of Madness
is finally out in theaters tomorrow!
Please go watch it!
Double!
There is no "double" spell.
Never heard of it.
Is that a new Mystic Art?
Well, then...
Bye-bye!
We're closing with that?!
See you soon!
And, we're clear!
Good job, everyone!
Good job!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
There was so much going on today,
but I glad we wrapped it up nicely in the end.
Yeah.
That was quite nerve-racking.
I'm glad it went well.
Let's actually head back now
and have a movie party.
Yeah, let's do it!
Off to watch Doctor Strange!
Go, go, go!
Okay, let's open the portal.
Oh?
Okay, let's go!
Forward!
Let's go!
I'm Doctor Stephen Strange.
At last, a portal to this universe has opened.
I speak for myself.
Because the warnings...
The warnings come after the spells.
The multiverse... It's life or death.
No pressure, then...
All right, let me ask you this one time.
I need you to come with me.
To protect our world.