Passionate! holo Voice Acting Workshop!
Yay!
First of all, everybody please introduce
yourselves using your best voice!
I'm hololive 1st Generation's
comfy half-elf,
Aki Rosenthal, a.k.a. AkiRose!
Thanks for having me!
All hustle, all muscle!
I'm hololive 3rd Generation's
meatheaded knight, Shirogane Noel!
Nice to be here!
Hoof, hoof! Helloof!
I'm hololive 4th Generation's
Tsunomaki Watame!
Thanks for having me!
Good voices indeed, everybody.
Good to be here with you.
Since last summer, hololive, in collaboration
with Yoyogi Animation Academy,
has been offering voice acting lessons to
any talents who have wanted to take them!
Today, we'll be doing
a lesson in workshop form.
And I hope this program
will be able to show everyone
what kind of lessons are being given!
Let's get going!
Now I'm a little nervous.
I'm getting nervous!
Let's go ahead
and introduce today's teachers!
First is a vocal coach and voice actor,
ERIKO-sensei!
Hello! I'm ERIKO-sensei!
Nice to meet you!
I haven't seen you all
in quite a while!
Long time, no see!
Sensei!
Let's work hard today!
Yes!
I will!
We will!
And our other teacher today
is a vocal coach and former TV announcer,
TAKAKO-sensei!
Thank you for being here!
I'm TAKAKO-sensei,
a vocal coach.
It's been a long time, everybody!
Yes, it has!
Have you all been doing
your daily vocal training?
Erp!
Uh, um...
Umm...
You have, right? Right?
But really, I'm looking forward
to today, so let's have some fun!
Yes, let's!
We're welcoming these two teachers in
to hold our workshop today,
so please work hard
all the way through!
Okay!
Passionate!
holo Voice Acting Workshop
Our first lesson is...
What will change? How to change it?
Enunciation and articulation training!
Yay!
This enunciation and articulation lesson
is not just important for voice actors,
but for all of you streamers working hard.
TAKAKO-sensei will be instructing us for this!
Okay!
Thank you!
All I want is a proper cup of coffee,
made in a proper copper coffee pot.
She sells seashells by the seashore,
and the shells she sells are seashells.
He thrusts his fists against the posts
and still insists he sees the ghosts.
Okay then, each of you please read
one of those lines out loud.
None of these are gonna be simple.
Let's start with AkiRose-chan.
All I want is a proper cup of coffee,
made in a proper copper coffee pot.
Here I go!
All I want is a proper cup of coffee,
made in a proper copper coffee pot.
I'd say you did well, but I'd be lying.
Harsh!
Okay, Noel-chan!
Okay.
She sells seashells by the seashore,
and the shells she sells are seashells.
She sells shells by the shore,
and the shells she sells are shells.
Where'd the sea go?!
That's an almost.
And now Watame-chan.
He thrusts his fists against the posts
and still insists he sees the ghosts.
Here I go!
He thrusts his fishts
againsht the posts
and still inshists
he shees the ghosts.
I could say I'd give you
a pass on cuteness,
but I can't accept that!
You can't, huh?
For those who want to share
their voice with others,
they've got to be able to manipulate
the inside of their mouths a little bit better.
We do actually have muscles
around our cheeks.
These are called mimetic muscles.
Athletes warm up with stretches, right?
Right.
I'd like you to do
some facial stretches as well.
Oh! That's a thing!
It is!
Face Stretch #1:
Lip Trill
Put your lips together
and breathe out, vibrating them.
Face Stretch #2:
1 minute of vowel calisthenics
Repeatedly vocalize "a i u e o" for one minute.
Relax.
By doing these, your mimetic muscles
have been loosened up.
It's a good idea to do these exercises for a few moments
before you have to talk in front of others.
Next, what's important for reading lines well is
the placement of your tongue.
Your tongue!
Can you all move your tongue?
We did the lip trill like this earlier.
Now the tongue!
Tongue Stretch:
Tongue Trill
Vocalize while vibrating your tongue.
Can you do it?
Give it a try!
This is pretty difficult.
La la la la la la la...
Huh? Noel-san, um?
La la la la la...
Oh?
Noel-chan, wait a moment!
We've been halted.
Noel-chan, you can't do it?
I've tried so hard and
come so far, but in the end...
You couldn't do it, eh?
Yeah.
Crying won't solve anything.
Try again.
How Spartan!
Those who can't do a tongue trill
have weaker tongue muscles.
Please work hard to strengthen them!
Okay!
Now we've gotten a little bit
of vocal training in.
I think if we go back to those
earlier practice lines,
you'll be able to move
your mouths a little bit better.
Shall we try?
Okay!
All I want is a proper cup of coffee,
made in a proper copper coffee pot.
Nicely voiced!
Oh, what a difference!
Well done!
Nicely voiced!
Good, good! You pass!
It helped.
Yay!
She sells seashells by the seashore,
and the shells she sells are seashells.
Here I go.
She sells seashells by the sheshore,
and the sells see sells sea...
Maybe I can pass you on cuteness?
Not a chance! Again!
How about you repeat after me?
She sells seashells by the seashore,
and the shells she sells are seashells.
She sells seashells
by the seashore,
and the shells she sells are seashells.
Oh, perfect!
Well done!
You did it!
Next is Watame-chan!
Okay!
He thrusts his fists against the posts
and still insists he sees the ghosts.
Oh, very nice!
You pass!
I did it!
As long as you keep practicing hard
on your enunciation like this,
you'll be able to read lines very well.
Since you're all such fast learners,
it makes me want to keep
teaching you more and more!
Thank you!
I'm grateful!
I want you all to continue to work hard while
taking care of your voice and your throat!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
That was TAKAKO-sensei!
She gave us some enunciation
and articulation coaching.
Thank you!
Passionate!
holo Voice Acting Workshop
Here's our next segment!
Basics Matter! Dubbing Lingo Quiz!
Ooh!
Yaaay!
In the lesson for this segment,
we taught you all about
the mics you're familiar with,
as well as VA industry lingo
that you'd do well to memorize!
You all definitely paid attention
and remembered the lesson, right?
Well... don't worry about it...?
Well...
Of course...?
Of course...
Your replies are a bit concerning,
but let's get right to it!
Okay, ERIKO-sensei!
Please start the Dubbing Lingo Quiz!
Yes?
Got it!
Let's begin, girls!
Okay!
Lip-sync!
If you know what it means...
...please do raise your hand!
Yeah!
Me!
Is that the sound you make
when you're eating delicious food?
Huh?
Buzzz!
Is that a joke?
Didn't I often tell you girls,
"You didn't really lip sync that well."?
The answer refers to matching
the length of the line being spoken!
Ah...
Oh!
Continuing from the previous question,
what's Off-sync?
Which one was it again?
I don't remember if
it was longer or shorter,
Uh-huh.
Longer, I guess?
but I know it refers to the reading
not matching the line well.
Uh-huh.
Which one was it?
When we go "It's completely off,"
it means you read the line
faster than intended.
So it's shorter!
I see!
Yup.
Okay, next question!
Whispering!
I guess it has something to do
with a whispering voice?
Indeed!
So a whispering voice is...
That's right!
A soft voice?
That was pretty sensual.
Basically, it refers to speaking
in a hushed tone.
Doesn't a hushed tone make you girls
think of a secret conversation?
Yeah.
But, with whispering,
you're still speaking in a hushed tone
but you have to convey
what you want to say to your audience.
So you can't just
speak softly, is that it?
Makes sense.
Yup.
Let's try voicing your vowels
in a whispering voice.
Okay!
Got it!
AEIOU
Okay!
Now try voicing them
as if you want them to be heard.
Your attempts just now are more on
the "secret conversation" level.
Let's start! Ready?
AEIOU
Okay, okay, okay!
That's the spirit!
Next question.
Okay!
Sure!
Blowing!
Blowing...
Blowing?
Just what does it mean?
Well, it's exactly
as the word implies.
Just what are you blowing into,
is the question.
You're blowing into... the mic.
Ding ding ding!
That's right!
Remember, you must not
blow into the mic!
It'll ruin the mic!
I see.
It'll ruin them?
It really will!
Remember the whispering exercise
you did with the vowels just now?
Voicing those vowels makes you
exhale more than consonants.
It's very easy to exhale with vowels,
so watch out for that, girls!
I see!
That's cool.
Wow!
You girls have your own mics as well,
so take good care of them!
You'll make the staff cry otherwise.
They sure will.
They'll go, "Those were expensive as heck..."
Okay!
That's it for the Dubbing Lingo Quiz!
Thank you so much!
Thanks so much!
You've all studied pretty well!
Oh, thanks for the praise!
Thank you!
That was a good lesson from ERIKO-sensei!
Good job, girls!
Passionate!
holo Voice Acting Workshop
Now for our last lesson!
Hands-on Dubbing!
How exciting.
Very exciting!
Since the three of you
took actual lessons,
we obviously want to show our fans
the three of you doing your best
to voice a character on screen!
Since we're cooperating
with Yoyogi Animation Academy,
we've borrowed their animation
for Yuke Smash!!
which is widely used
even in actual voice acting lessons!
Thank you!
Thanks so much for sharing it with us!
That's so nice!
Yuke Smash!! is a sports anime about the protagonist who is a ping pong athlete and a zashiki-warashi.
Sports, huh...
Yup!
We'll be using 3 scenes from Yuke Smash!!
for the three of you to dub over.
But first!
Let's start by watching the already
dubbed version of the 1st scene.
Ooh, looks nice.
How nice.
I wanna go there.
Oh, the ping pong table's roughed up.
A'ight! It's a showdown!
She's cute.
She's adorable.
How cute.
And then a shot of the boy.
He seems very much
like the protagonist.
I'mma serve, 'kay?
Yeah.
T-Time out!
She's holding the paddle
with a penhold style.
You're right!
Um... uh... who are you?
You're pretty well informed.
What? Ya din' know?
I'm the zashiki-warashi who lives here!
She's got an accent.
Yeah!
Seems like they both just met each other.
Huh?
This is what the first scene looks like.
The three of you will be
dubbing over this scene in a bit,
but can you highlight some points
for this scene, ERIKO-sensei?
Sure!
First off, anyone here
ever played ping pong?
Oh, good point.
I have.
Me too.
Oh!
You have?
This show is sports-based,
so there are a lot of action scenes.
People who've played a sport before
can make it more realistic.
Good point.
I'm excited to see
your performances today, girls!
Good point.
I see.
I'm excited to see
your performances today, girls!
She's setting the bar high!
There are comments and directions
written on the script.
You'll be reading
those comments and directions
and then do a cold-read
based on them.
Right! We'll also need to do the casting.
So we have Zashiki-warashi
and Taku-kun appearing in this scene.
Who wants to play Zashiki-warashi?
I guess I'll go for it!
Oh, the senpai!
Okay!
What a senpai!
Thanks, senpai!
Okay, who wants
to do Taku-kun then?
I'm also a senpai here,
so I'll play Taku-kun!
Do your best!
Awesome!
Nice!
All right! Watame-chan!
Yes?
Can you read the comments
and directions on the script?
Sure!
Okay.
Once Watame-chan reads
the comments and directions,
the both of you try
reading your lines based on them!
Got it!
Please begin.
Zashiki-warashi stands straight with her hand on her hip and poses with her paddle at the ready.
Try imagining yourself in her position
and read your lines.
Go ahead.
A'ight! It's a showdown!
That's a bit too cute.
Be more spirited.
She's itching for a battle.
I see, so a bit more fire.
More fire, got it.
Yup. Give it another try.
Okay!
A'ight! It's a showdown!
Nice!
Okay, next line!
Taku's so confused
that he's shocked into silence.
You need to ad-lib this part.
He's absolutely dumbfounded there.
Nice one.
Huuuh...?
That was very realistic, Noel-chan,
but this is an anime.
If you do it realistically,
it won't get picked up by the mic!
That's a thing, huh...
I see...
Because the voice is too low.
You need to give it a bit of an
upward inflection and raise the volume a little bit.
Upward inflection, got it.
Give it another try.
Got it.
Huuuh?↑
Okay, that's good!
Let's move on to the next line!
Zashiki-warashi is ready to serve the ball.
Okay, you're in a serving pose. Read your line!
I'mma serve, 'kay?
Okay. Your voice sounded
floaty just now.
You need to give it some oomph,
like you're energizing yourself.
Huh...
Okay!
Yup.
I see...
Give it another go.
Got it!
I'mma serve, 'kay?
Just like that!
Ooh...
Uh-huh...
That sounded very spirited, right?
Okay, next line!
Camera cut to Taku.
By that, it means
Taku's now in the shot.
He's in the shot, okay.
Go ahead!
T-Time out!
That didn't feel like he
"entered the scene."
He comes into the scene out of nowhere.
There's momentum to it.
Uh-huh...
Momentum, okay.
Ah, I see...
T-Time out!
Okay!
That feels more like it.
Uh-huh...
Okay, next line.
The dumbfounded Taku raises his hand and
scratches his head with a troubled expression.
That's a pretty long one,
but give it your best shot.
Um... uh... who are you?
Okay.
When you make a troubled face while
reading the lines for a character who's troubled,
the line will sound sad,
Oh...
Really?
so try saying it as if
you're smiling wryly, for example.
A wry smile...
Yup.
Your own expressions
are important too, huh.
They are!
A voice actor's expression is
clearly conveyed in the line they read.
Wow...
Ah... okay.
Try again.
Um... uh... who are you?
That's a lot better!
Really?
It feels a bit more comedic now.
Ah...
Expressions are important, aren't they?
They are, yeah...
Next one.
Zashiki-warashi stands up
straight from her serving pose.
What? Ya din' know?
I'm the zashiki-warashi who lives here!
Your dialect sounds really good!
Yeah! It's kinda cute.
It's cute!
It's adorable!
I think it'll be a hit.
I guess I'll speak
with an accent from now on!
Adorable!
It's very cute!
It's adorable!
That's cute.
Okay!
Last line, please.
Taku with a suspecting look.
Suspecting is pretty tough.
What kind of voice should I do?
Okay, try doing 3 variations
of just the "Huh?"
Okay.
Huh?⤴️
Huh?↘️
Huh?↗️
Okay!
So...
Personally, I like the first one the most.
Ooh.
So something like that.
Got it.
Yeah. Try going with that.
All right! Taku with a distrusting look! Go!
Huh?⤴️
Good! Very good!
I'm sure someone's
excited from that.
The fans will definitely love that.
I think that's great.
Okay! Now that the three of you
Uh-huh.
did a proper cold-reading,
Yup!
Yes?
let's start dubbing!
Okay!
How exciting.
A'ight! It's a showdown!
I'mma serve, 'kay?
T-Time out!
Um... uh... who are you?
What? Ya din' know?
I'm the zashiki-warashi who lives here!
Huh?⤴️
That was beautiful!
That was great!
That was really great!
That felt amazing!
That was amazing!
You really were!
You both were awesome!
Yeah! Noel-chan,
you did so well that
there's nothing for me to nitpick.
Really?!
Whoa!
Thank you!
And as for you, Akirose-chan,
I was really impressed by a few things.
Oh?
You put some proper oomph in
with the "I'mma serve, 'kay?" line
and you ad-libbed and did a small laugh
at the line where she goes,
"Ya din' know?", didn't you?
I did, yeah.
Ooh!
I think that was great.
Wow.
Great job!
Ah!
Amazing!
I can't pull that off that well myself.
Ooh!
Really? Thank you!
Yup.
You did really well!
That's cause for celebration, isn't it?
All right!
Both of you acted this scene perfectly!
Oh!
Yes!
All right!
A certified pass!
Yay!
You all passed that first scene
with flying colors,
so let's move on to the second scene.
No more...
Huh?!
He's crying pretty hard.
He's crying...
Erika-chan is retiring...
and now this weird kid is teasing me.
My life sucks...
Is this Erika?
It's so over the top.
Why do you have that?!
It was just lying there.
Oh, so that's his oshi.
Give it back! That's mine!
I thought it was a naughty video...
Don't say that!
That's inappropriate!
Finders keepers!
Okay, so there's our second scene.
Sensei, can you give us
some pointers for this scene?
First of all...
Crying is hard!
It does look hard!
And on top of that,
the character's a boy!
What do you think a boy
sounds like when he cries?
That's true.
Now, let's pick our cast
while keeping those points in mind.
Yes, please!
Alright, who'll play Zashiki-warashi?
I will!
Watame-chan!
Good stuff!
And who'll do Taku-kun?
AkiRose might give it a go...
Give it a completely different
feel from before, okay?
Okay.
Yay!
Finders keepers!
Take a deep breath
before saying "Finders keepers."
Alright, let's give it a go!
Yeah.
No more...
Huh?!
Erika-chan is retiring...
and now this weird kid is teasing me.
My life sucks...
Is this Erika?
Why do you have that?!
It was just lying there.
Give it back!
Yaaay!
Stop that!
Finders keepers!
Great work!
That was very well done.
Thank you!
So, I think that in anime,
there are voice actors
who act and voice actors
in charge of character voice.
I see...
I think that with this combination,
with AkiRose-chan's strong acting
and Watame-chan's cute voice,
you'd have a really fun show.
We make a great pair!
Wanna do it?
Yeah! Shall we?
Let's do a show!
Please feel free!
Yeah.
Shall we do one more scene?
Yes.
This last scene might be
a little more difficult,
but let's go ahead and take a look.
Here it is.
Ah!
It's an action scene!
How was that?
This looks hard!
It's pretty fast too.
You're such a cheeky brat!
You don't even have that yet!
That?
I'm talking about a finishing move!
A finishing move?!
She was talking about a finishing move.
Take a good look at this!
This is pretty tropey.
Yeah.
Here it is!
It's her finishing move!
The air around her's changed!
You have to voice this part
where she's charging up as well.
Finishing move: Yukemuri Smash!!
Wow!
That's dangerous!
It missed him!
And he gets cut!
Nice!
This bit is a little over the top.
That's dangerous!
It's could be some kind of ping pong
with superpowers though.
That's scary!
It turned to ash!
It burned up...
Yeah.
That's not a smash.
That's a serve!
That's all you've got to say?
I mean...!
Are you trying
to kill me or something?!
And then you've got
this reaction at the end too.
There's a lot going on in this scene.
This is really hard!
This is hard!
So, this scene is quite
long and difficult...
Sensei, can you give us
some pointers for this scene?
So, Zashiki-warashi has action parts...
and she yells quite a bit in this scene...
I see...
That's true.
You need to have energy!
Energy!
Let's do our best!
So, who wants to play
Zashiki-warashi in this scene?
Yes! I will!
And what about Taku-kun?
I... will!!
I haven't played him yet,
so it's my turn.
Please do.
Watame-chan, you have a really cute voice,
but can you do a boy's voice?
I can!
That's so funny!
She nailed it.
She sounds like a hot guy!
Let's give it a go then.
Ah!
Haha!
Ah... I messed up!
You're such a cheeky brat!
You don't even have that yet!
Shall we start over?
That?
Let's start over!
Let's pretend this never happened.
I was surprised when Watame
suddenly appeared in the show.
I'm sorry!
That "Haha!" just came out!
How was that?
You're such a cheeky brat!
You don't even have that yet!
That?
I'm talking about a finishing move!
A finishing move?!
Take a good look at this!
Finishing move: Yukemuri Smash!!
That's not a smash.
That's a serve!
That's all you've got to say?
I mean...!
Are you trying
to kill me or something?!
Thank you both!
That's it for that scene.
My heart's racing!
I stuttered!
You did great!
Great work!
Thank you!
To be honest, I didn't think
Watame-chan could pull off a boy's voice.
But you did really well!
I tried really hard!
Great work!
Thank you so much!
It really is about that energy.
Energy really is important there,
isn't it?
And with the part where she throws
the ball in the air and jumps...
Noel-chan ad-libbed
some grunting, right?
I really liked that.
Really?
Things like that
really show off your uniqueness.
It's a unique performance
nobody else can give.
Great work!
Thank you very much!
Very impressive!
Wow!
You all did a great job!
You all pass!
Thank you!
I think you were all able to do
so well because you first practiced
your enunciation with TAKAKO-sensei,
then practiced your acting.
That was great, wasn't it?
Your foundations are important!
Please keep up the hard work!
Yes!
Thank you, ERIKO-sensei!
Thank you all!
Thank you!
Passionate!
holo Voice Acting Workshop
And that's that!
This was actually just a little bit
of the entire lesson,
but the teachers from
Yoyogi Animation Academy joined us
and taught a workshop for us!
I'd like to hear from our teachers, ERIKO-sensei
and TAKAKO-sensei, about today's lesson!
Let's hear
TAKAKO-sensei's thoughts first!
Okay! I feel like I could cry
at everyone's improvement!
I'm glad!
You really worked hard!
Yes!
But...
Uh-oh!
What ERIKO-sensei taught you
was the equivalent of
being at the starting line
and hearing the pistol go off.
So that means that what I taught you was
what to do to get to that starting line.
I see.
That being said,
to be honest, whether or not
you're standing at that starting line yet
is a bit of a... hmm?
Still a long way to go.
I want you all to make sure
to work hard daily
so that you'll be able to stand
at that starting line.
Daily!
And I definitely want you
to take care of your voices.
I know I say it over and over,
but I really think it matters.
I really want you
to cherish your own voice!
Indeed!
Okay!
Thank you!
Work hard!
I will!
And now ERIKO-sensei,
if you please.
Good work, everybody!
You too!
You're all very popular VTubers,
and you have a ton of fans.
VTubers are always
the main character of their own story,
so, in a good way,
you get fawned over a lot.
But, you know, voice actors don't really get a ton
of attention if they don't play a major role.
So, while there are major roles,
there are also minor roles.
But those small roles
are also very important!
No matter how small the role is,
or how few lines you have,
giving it all you've got when acting them
is fundamental.
Lessons are important, too,
but even before that, as actors,
I want you to broaden your minds.
Oh, I see.
I know you all can do it!
That's reassuring!
Because you're all so very cute!
Thank you!
I've become a fan of all of you!
I'm glad!
Hooray!
Let's all work hard so that someday we'll be able
to voice an anime together in the studio!
We will!
Let's work hard!
Thank you very much!
To finish this up, let's use
your now-improved best voices
to end by saying, "Thank you very much!"
Ready, set!
Thank you very much!
Please like this video and subscribe
to the hololive channel and the talents' channels!