I'm the Sucker Punch Champ!
What was it again?
Uh...
Um...
Wha—
For me! 😉✨
"For me!" (lol)
Challenge everything!
holo World Records Episode 3!
Yaaay!
I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
The record I've held so far is, uh...
that blinking one!
Yup! 68 blinks!
A-quality day to you all!
I'm Minato Aqua!
A record I've had up until now, huh...
Uh...
How about the record for the longest
anyone wore a cap in their whole life?
That's just weird!
That makes no sense!
Om, nom, Okayu!
I'm Nekomata Okayu!
One of my records is...
Living on with the people around me
by absorbing their luck from them.
Say what?!
When Fubuki-chan was
trying to fish up a Shiny Magikarp,
Endurance streamed
for a Shiny Magikarp
I got my own Shiny off-stream in just one hour.
Yeah...
That's just crazy.
Your first challenge is the
High-Speed Blinking World Record!
This challenge will test you on
how many blinks you can do in just 15 seconds.
I'm blinking a ton as I explain this as well.
I, Friend A, will be counting your blinks!
I've always had
a tendency to get dry eyes,
so I practically blink a lot every day.
I see!
I'm confident in my chances!
Yeah. 'Cause like, when you game,
you need to keep your eyes
open the whole time.
With how much I game,
I've definitely blinked less than
everyone else in my whole life!
So you saved those blinks.
Yeah! I saved them up for this moment!
Ah, in that sense of the word. Okay.
I saved my blinks all for this moment!
As a fox, I'm naturally better
than the cats gathered among us.
Uh-huh.
I'm gonna need to show them who's boss.
Okay, got it.
You little cats ready?
Ha!
Is that so?
You sure I'm a cat?
The current record for
this category is held by Fubuki-san.
Her record is an astonishing 68 blinks!
68 blinks in 15 seconds?!
Oooh!
Wow... that kinda looks unbeatable now.
Come on!
You're giving up too quickly!
Hm? Huh?
She can't talk the talk but can she walk the walk?!
Nekomata Okayu takes center stage!
By the way, how many
blinks are you aiming for?
Hmm... 30, I guess?
Let's have a warm-up first.
Why?!
How slow are you gonna go?
That's pretty timid.
Well then, let's start!
Ready?
Begin!
Wow, that's fast!
Wow!
That's amazing!
Whoa, she's fast!
She's really fast!
Ten seconds left!
She's amazing!
Her ears are twitching!
The ear twitching is adorable!
Her ears!
Her ears are
twitching a ton!
Five seconds left!
Four!
Whoa!
She's too good!
Three!
Two!
One!
Time's up!
You're freaking amazing!
Fin
That was amazing!
Seriously, Okayu?!
That was fast!
Stop right there.
That was really fast!
Wow. Did she set a new record?
Really?
I thought my eyes popped.
Nekomata Okayu-san's score is...
Wow! 74 blinks!
She's our current queen!
I'm the champion!
No way!
On her first attempt too!
You faked us out, didn't you?! Dammit!
True.
I'm the Sucker Punch Champ!
You little—!
Next up, Aqua-san, who
wants to beat that record!
Please step up!
Do I even have a chance?
You don't need me to do this, right?
Come on, don't say that!
Aim to set a new record!
Minato Aqua sails into the fray!
Ready, Aqua-san?
Begin!
Oh, she's quick!
Oh, she's doing good!
That's really quick!
Keep at it!
Aqua-chan's really fast!
Slowly increase your pace!
She's breathing faster than she blinks.
That's some insane panting.
She sounds like a dog!
Didn't we have two cats?
Why's there a dog here?!
Were you a dog all along?
We have a dog here with us!
One second left!
Time's up!
She wasn't an onion but a dog.
Fin
You were a dog the whole time, huh.
My breath! I can barely breathe!
And Aqua-san, who can
barely breathe, got a score of...
Please be good!
Wow! 43 blinks!
Da heck?! You gotta be kidding me!
43 blinks!
Even without an example,
Okayu got twice my score, right?
Yeah, she did.
She's too good.
I didn't really notice myself, though.
Now for our last challenger, Fubuki-san!
Ready!
I'm gonna break that record!
Will she reclaim her throne?!
Shirakami Fubuki makes her stand!
Without further ado...
Let's start Fubuki-san's challenge!
Ready?
Begin!
She's FAST!
She's fast!
Freaking fast!
She's laser-focused!
Blazing fast!
Keep it up!
She's insane!
It must be tough
keeping count.
Yeah, I'm tapping the button
like there's no tomorrow.
Isn't she blinking
too fast?
True, maybe she's too fast.
You're right!
Her body can't keep up
with her blinking.
That's possible.
Ah! Time's up!
Fin
Okay!
*Huff*
Is that a new personal best, or...
I need air!
All right! Fubuki-san's result is...
Seventy...
...one blinks!
You were so close!
Nooooo!
Wait, I'm faster than her?
You beat your previous record
but not the current queen's!
Ugh!
Dammit!
You were so fast that some of your blinks
might not have been counted.
Not counted?!
Ah, I see.
Their battle is beyond our level.
Our newly crowned queen is...
Nekomata Okayu-san with 74 blinks!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Congrats!
Congraaats!
You were amazing!
Our next challenge is
the Tongue Twister World Record!
Oooh!
Okay...
Each member gets their own
custom tongue twister
and passes if they say it
three times without stumbling!
I'll be the one judging
if you stumbled or not.
Are the three of you confident
in your tongue twister skills?
Not at all.
Yeah, nope.
Oh, really?
Hang on, you two.
Are you gonna say that
and leave me in the dust again?
Come on! Stop it!
Everyone should run
a marathon together, right?
I'm serious!
We're gonna do
this together, okay?
Promise me?
The current record holder
for this category is
our Tongue Twister Queen,
Yukihana Lamy-san,
and she actually shares her throne
with Tokoyami Towa-san!
Both of them got 9.1 points out of 10.
What's with the 9.1 points?
Are there like, bonus points for presentation?
Yeah! You get extra points for presentation.
Seriously?!
You can get bonus points by doing stuff like
(Rules)
Presentation points are awarded for factors like
cuteness, etc. on top of how smoothly they can read.
winking at the end on top of
finishing your tongue twister.
Ah, okay. I get it now.
Will she claim a second throne?!
Nekomata Okayu makes her move!
Here's your
Tongue Twister challenge, Okayu-san!
Nekomata Okayu's kit,
the kit of the cat kin to the kit of that cat
is catnapping again.
Oh?
That's a tough one!
She's catnapping again?
In the end, it's just talking
about your cat, Okayu-san.
I wonder how I'll do.
I don't think I'll do well.
Are you sure about that?
Well, just give it a try for now.
She's doing it again.
Yeah.
She's at it again.
Well then, Okayu's Tongue Twister
World Record Challenge starts...
Now!
Nekomata Okayu's kit, the kit of the cat
kin to the kit of that cat is catnapping again.
Oh, that's fast!
Nekomata Okayu's kit, the kit of the cat
kin to the kit of that cat is catnapping again.
Nekomata Okayu's kit,
the kit of the cat kin to the kit...
Cata... catty... catter...
MEOW!
...of that cat is catnapping again!
And that's it!
Fin
What?!
Huh?!
She didn't stumble the first two times!
Yeah, the first two were perfect.
Seriously?!
Nekomata Okayu-san's score is...
8.88 points!
You got 8.88 points!
Whaaat?!
Amazing!
Your speed was pretty good
and you didn't stumble
the first two times.
And when you stumbled at the end,
you recovered with a big "Meow"!
Our next challenger is Aqua-san!
All right! It's my turn!
Chase their backs!
Minato Aqua charges forth!
Here's your Tongue Twister, Aqua-san!
Aqua in the aquarium
acquiring a quality cure-all
that qualifies for her qualms.
You getting a medical checkup?
Sounds about right.
What kind of situation is that?!
That's one messed-up situation.
How do you feel, Aqua-san?
I got it!
We can get extra points as well, right?
Yes, you can!
How you recover from a stumble
also plays a factor in your score.
Okay, got it!
Aqua's Tongue Twister
World Record Challenge starts...
Now!
Aqua in the aquarium acquiring a quality
cure-ball that qualifies for her qualms.
Aqua in the aquarium acquiring a quantity
curveball that qualifies for her qualms.
Aqua in the aquarium acquiring
a quality cure-all that—
What was it again?
Qualifies...
...for me! 😉✨
For me!
Okay, that's it!
"For me!" with the wink!
Fin
I did my best for presentation!
That was very adorable.
I really did!
How was it?
How'd I do?
Did I do well?
Okay!
The deliberations are over!
8.46 points!
That's a lot higher than I expected!
You got 8.46 points!
Is it really okay giving me
that high of a score?
Don't worry about it!
I even messed up at the end!
It's pretty hard to wink with both eyes
while you're reading the tongue twister
so your attempt at doing so
factored well into your score.
All right!
Thank you!
I did it!
Heck yeah! ♪
Now for our final challenger, Fubuki-san!
Are you ready?
Oh!
My turn, huh?
Break the record!
Shirakami Fubuki leaps in!
Here's your Tongue Twister, Fubuki-san!
Kissy killer foxes with faux pas
outfoxing cats
forcing foxy faces.
That's a pretty tough one.
What the heck is this supposed to be?!
They spiked the level up outta nowhere!
This level spike!
Right?!
Fubuki's Tongue Twister
World Record Challenge starts...
Now!
Kissy killer foxes with faux pas
outfocusing cats forcing foxy faces.
outfoxing cats forcing foxy faces.
Kissy killer foxes with faux pas
outfoxing cats forcing foxy faces!
Oooh!
Wow! Amazing!
Fin
You got the last one pretty well!
That was a pretty good attempt, wasn't it?
How was that?
Your score, Fubuki-san, is...
*Huff*
...9.09 points!
WHOA!
WHAT?!
COME ON! GIMME JUST A BIT MORE!
UGH! Just gimme a few more points!
You did really well, but...
Just where was I lacking?
If only you didn't stumble at the very start!
Aaaaagh!
That's the only negative point!
Ugh!
You were just shy of becoming queen!
Even so, you did great! Congratulations!
Uuugh!
Thank you...
That's all the challenges!
We didn't get to crown a new
Tongue Twister Queen this time!
Lamy-san and Towa-san's
double-wall combination was quite the hurdle!
Great job, the three of you!
It's a steep climb.
It sure is.
It really is!
Even for an otaku who speaks fast all the time,
the tongue twister hurdles are not a simple foe.
Please look forward to
future next-level battles!
If you enjoyed this video,
please like and subscribe to the
official hololive YouTube channel
as well as our talents' individual channels!
Please subscribe!
That's all for today! See you all again
on the next episode of holo World Records!
Bye-bye!
Starring:
Shirakami Fubuki
Nekomata Okayu
Minato Aqua
holo World Records is brought to you by
Shirakami Fubuki...
...Nekomata Okayu, and...
Minato Aqua!