Is your tongue bugged or something?
There was something like a sauce on it...
How sauce-spicious...
Odd One Out!
Food Review Detectives!
I greet you, the best of the best,
hololive's food review detectives!
In today's show, you'll all get
to eat delicious food!
Yay!
Thank you very much.
Quite lively today, aren't we?
Well then,
please introduce yourselves.
Sure! Nya-hello!
From hololive 0th Gen,
I'm your elite food review elective...?
I'm the first food review detective,
Sakura Miko!
I keep saying that
my favorite food is taiyaki,
but lately I've been hooked
on double cheeseburgers.
Man, I love junk food.
Junk food-loving elite
The second food review detective
Sakura Miko
Nakiri Ayame
from hololive 2nd Gen here!
I've come to liking salmon lately.
Ah, nice.
Shake!
Shake it up, baby!
The second food review detective
Nakiri Ayame
All hustle, all muscle!
From hololive 3rd Gen,
owner of the cast-iron stomach,
the third detective,
Shirogane Noel here!
Yay!
Nice to have you all here today!
Beef bowl!
I love beef bowl!
Owner of the cast-iron stomach
The third food review detective
Shirogane Noel
I heard that all of you
food review detectives
have not only reasoning skills,
but also outstanding
food review capabilities.
Well, yeah.
Now, you all will be required
to put on blindfolds
and taste food with them on.
Oh god!
Blindfolds?
You'll have to deduce
who is the odd one out
eating something different,
as well as what they're eating,
by using each other's food reviews.
I see.
Got it.
During your review, you cannot mention the name
of the food or any of its specific ingredients.
No saying!
Please show off your inner foodie
via all your eloquent descriptions!
Got it!
Food Review Detectives
Mission No. 1
Just for our viewers, we're gonna show
what our detectives are going to eat.
Here it is!
Takoyaki or okonomiyaki
What is it?
I can't see it...
Is everyone ready?
Yup!
I am!
Aw, how cute.
Miko-san, please say, "Ahh"...
* The food is invisible due to special effects.
Here it goes...
Nice.
What is it?
I wanna try it too!
I wanna too!
It's something especially magnificent.
Open your mouth...
* The food is invisible due to special effects.
Yum!
Yup! Very yummy!
Please open your mouth wide...
Just like that!
Okay! You all finished eating, right?
Yup!
Yes!
Well then, start the food review!
It's something salty, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
It's salty and quite...
Like, you know...
How's it called?
Sauce-y—
It's also chewy!
Oh right, it was chewy!
Oh, you know,
there were veggies inside, right?
They were kinda crunchy.
Yeah...
Huh? Crunchy?
Huh?
Wha? It was gooey, wasn't it?
Was it?
Yeah, it was...
There was some kind of
membrane... Some peel?
It was wrapped in it.
A membrane?
I see.
There was some peel...
Ah, a memb—
A membrane?
Oh? What do we have here?
So, the odd one out is Noe-san?
I, uhh...
I think the same.
It has to be her!
It wasn't crunchy at all.
Really?
As for the taste...
Rather than being a mix,
it was a single flavor.
Was it salty?
It was.
There was something
like a sauce on it...
Ahh!
So there was a sauce on it?
How sauce-spicious...
Huh?
Ayame-senpai?
Ayame-senpai?!
Ms. Detective?
Did the second detective
just say something?
Hmm?
Uhh...
I don't think there was
something inside...
It was a quite rich flavor.
A rich flavor?!
It was for me.
Were there any solid pieces inside?
Nope!
Nothing like that!
Nothing, I see.
There was nothing solid inside.
So what was the gooey part...?
That's it!
It was going quite nicely at the start,
but you all got a bit confused
along the way, huh?
We got so lost...
I lost all the leads...
Well then,
please deduce the odd one out
and the food they were eating
and write it on the panel
in front of you.
Okay!
Sure.
Hmm, what was it?
What did we just eat?
I have no idea...
Could it be...?
But... Hmm...
Seems like our food review detectives
have reached their conclusions.
Let's check your guesses!
One-two, reveal!
Noel
Soft roe
Noel-chan
(Salmon roe)
Me!!
(to be announced)
There we go!
All of you suspected Noel-san to be
the odd one out, but as for the food...
Yup.
Miko-san is thinking that it was soft roe!
I mean, soft roe has
a smooth skin on the outside
and sticky insides, so...
Ah, I see.
So that's what you meant.
I see, I see.
"It just has to be this,"
or so I thought.
By the way, what do you
think you were eating?
It was okonomiyaki.
Ah!
Yep!
Okonomiyaki?
Oh? Seems like
we are close to the truth.
Ayame-san thinks that
it was salted salmon roe.
Yeah! I mean,
it has a skin, it's smooth,
has a rich flavor, so I thought...
Right, it's pretty distinctive.
So Noel-san, you thought
you were the odd one out,
Yes?
but what do you think you ate?
A cream manjuu...?
But I'm not sure since
I've never eaten one before...
Oh, I see!
You said it was salty!
It was something big...
It had a strange texture...
A strange texture?!
It was quite hard.
I've never eaten it before!
Let's see the correct answer.
What was it?
The odd one out was...
Noel-san eating takoyaki!
Ah!
Ahh!
I even asked you if
there were solid pieces inside!
But there weren't any!
There really weren't any!
There were.
But hold on, cream manjuu
is sweet, you know?
Indeed.
Is your tongue bugged or something?
It tasted cheesy!
It was like a
Chinese steamed bun with cheese.
There was also sauce on it.
I guess that's what
takoyaki tastes like!
TIL!
Food Review Detectives
Mission No. 2
For mission No. 2
we want the people watching
to also guess
what everyone is eating,
and who's the odd one out!
Open wide! Here it comes.
Mmh! Mmh? Mmh! Mmh!
Alright.
Mmh?!
There we go.
Mmh?
Well then, start the food review!
It's fruity, right?
Yeah, fruity!
There's a bit of bitterness
in between the sweet—
No. Never mind that.
You don't need to lie, you know?!
Forget that! Forget that!
It's sweet. It's sweet.
Sweet? Alright.
Yeah. Sweet.
Sweet. Okay. Got it.
Yeah, yeah. Sweet.
Yeah, it's sweet, and, uh...
Sweet.
But it's also kinda sour, isn't it?
Oh, yeah. I can see that.
When I took the first bite
I thought, "Oh, that's bliiiss!"
Bliiiss.
Just a bit.
Bliss, huh.
They don't seem
very receptive to that...
Huh, wait!
No one relates!
J-Just a little bit!
Anyone home, girls?
That's interesting.
Excuse me,
can we go back to reviewing food?
It came in, like, parts,
and when you bite into it,
baaam comes the flavor!
Yeah.
Ah...
Right.
You felt that too?
I had that. I had that.
Yeah, yeah.
You'd eat it like...
when you're in a kotatsu.
Oh! I can see that.
Riiight...
Mmh...
In a... kotatsu...
Yeah, a kotatsu.
Huh?
Ayame...?
Kotatsu...
Mmh?
I guess they belong to the same family...?
Yeah, the same family!
What?
But...
Oh!
Also,
Yeah?
it was really watery.
Right. It contains a lot of water.
Yeah, that was a big part.
Huh?
Now everyone's confused?
It'd taste really good as a juice.
It would, yeah!
Yep, yep, yep!
Crazy example, but were this food
a hololive member,
it'd be Oozora Subaru
or Nenechi.
That's the feeling I got.
Oh, I can totally see that!
Mmh? Hold on!
Did anyone really get
anything different?!
Alright...!
That's it! Time's up!
Whaaat?
This is hard!
You were doing great at the start,
but everything got more
confusing than expected.
This was really tough!
It was really complicated...
That was so hard!
Alright!
Food review detectives,
please deduce the odd one out
and the food they were eating
and write it on the panel
in front of you.
Hold up, no...
I don't know!
This is so hard...
It is... mmh...
I... can't decide!
This will be fun!
Let's check their guesses!
Here they are!
Ayame-tan
Grapefruit?
Noel-chan
Mandarin
Ayame-senpai
Sweet Grapefruit
Oh?!
Very split!
Miko-san and Noel-san
say it's Ayame-san...
Huh?!
No way!
That's my guess.
and Ayame-san says it's Noel-san.
It's a split vote!
No way!
Let's first go over Miko-san's answer.
What caught my attention
was that she said it was bittersweet.
I really shouldn't have said that!
That really seemed weird to me...
Yeah, same here.
The bitter part seemed weird to me.
Come on!
Oh! I see!
I told you to forget thaaat!
Mmh?
What does the most voted person
have to say about this?
She mentioned eating it
in a kotatsu, so I thought...
Right. Right.
it had to be mandarin.
Got it, got it.
By the way, the one
who mentioned the kotatsu
was Miko-senpai.
Right.
Huh?!
WHAT?!
NO WAY!
Mmh?
This might change things!
Our last shared braincell is dying!
Shoot!
Alright!
Let's see the correct answer!
What will it be?
The odd one out was...
Who was it? Who was it?
Noel-san!
She had a mandarin!
Oh! I knew it!
I should've gone with that!
She was the odd one out,
and as for the other two,
they were eating oranges.
Yeah! I knew that was it!
Alright!
A lot of mistakes were made today.
Like blurting out bittersweet
and mentioning kotatsus.
Tell me, do you eat
oranges in a kotatsu?
Well...
I do think I kind of messed up there...
That's right...
Now it's time to announce
the real food review detective!
Who is it? Who is it?
Who is it?
Who could it be?
Tell us! Tell us!
Who could it be? Who could it be?
Maybe meee?
The real food review detective...
Who will it be?
It's me! It has to be me!
It's obviously me!
Who?
Is...
Who is it?
Who? Who?? Who???
Who could it be?
Whooo?
Who? Who? Who?
It's Ayame-san!
Yaaay!
Congraaats!
That's right!
Yay!
Thank you! Thank you!
Congratulations!
You're our food review detective!
Detective—
Detective Nakiri Ayame is at your service.
Detective Nakiri!
How'd the biggest airhead
of the group win...?
Wait, what?
Darn it!
She was the one
who gave the biggest clues.
Oh, that's right!
She was really good!
Even in pure darkness,
the flavors stand by my side.
That's the power of
my sharp taste buds!
Found myself a new talent.
Yeah, you can add that
to your repertoire.
A new talent for this talent!
A talent, alright.
Thank you!
Alright!
If you're here and enjoyed watching,
remember to like, and...
check out the official channel, and...
subscribe to all of our channels!
Please!
Thank you for watching!