July 19XX
I pray that I make many friends
and enjoy my student life to the fullest.
If only making friends were that easy.
I know I have to start
by changing myself,
but there's nothing special
about me to begin with.
I can pray all I want,
but that won't make me any friends.
*sigh*...
Sh-She's so beautiful...
If only I were more like her.
Then I'd have self-confidence.
But, wait...
I don't remember a girl
like her at Aogami High.
The Next Day
So the girl I saw
was our class's new transfer student.
That explains why
I didn't recognize her.
Her first day,
and she's already so popular...
Not like it makes
any difference in my life.
I know I have to start
by changing myself...
U-Um...
Excuse me!
Um,
if it's all right with you,
can we be friends?
Yes, of course!
The pleasure's all mine!
That was the turning point.
I gradually began to make more friends.
But there were some
who didn't look kindly
on my friendship
with the popular transfer student...
Several Days Later
Hey, isn't that so scary?
That rumor about the Art Prep Room?
It's quite fascinating.
Yae-san, you must have
heard about it from Honoka-san.
You know about it too, Sakura-san?
Of course. I was the one
who told Honoka-san about it—
and to keep it secret.
We Furukawas
built this school ourselves.
There's no way it's haunted.
Sure, whatever you say.
I'm just looking forward to
the test of courage tomorrow.
And the more the merrier!
We should invite Shino-san
and the new girl!
Misora-san's stuck to her
like glue again, I see.
Such a nuisance.
Aww, cut her some slack.
You're just jealous 'cause
you're into the new girl yourself.
I didn't ask your opinion.
My head hurts just
looking at Misora-san...
...
9 PM, The Next Day
This is so exciting...
Oh! This way, this way!
Well...
it looks like we're all here.
Let's begin.