How... did I get here?
This... has to be a bad dream.
This can't possibly be happening.
Please... You helped me
make all these friends...
I'm begging you...
Please, save them!
Please...
February 20XX
When did I fall asleep?
I feel like I was having
a strange dream.
Such a beautiful, idyllic place.
So this is Aogami, my new home.
Yuka, wake up!
We're almost at Aogami Station!
Mm... So sleepy.
I promise I'll wake up
when we get there, Akane.
You always say that,
and it never happens!
Come on, wake up!
Mm...
Oh, come on!
Wait...
Isn't that girl...
Hee-hee.
Say,
we're almost at Aogami Station.
July, 20XX
In recent months, there has been
a surge of missing persons in Aogami.
And they all have one thing in common.
Namely...
All those who have gone missing
were last heard from
when they were in the vicinity
of Aogami Station.