Nya-hello!
I'm the elite shrine maiden
Sakura Miko from hololive!
0th Gen
Sakura Miko
And we also have...
'Kay, see me hear me...
Hey! Be serious!
My name is...
Laplus Darknesss!
Secret Society holoX
Laplus Darknesss
May 5 is Children's Day.
hololive's child ambassador, Lap-tan, and I
will be your hosts today!
Quit joking around.
Huh? What do you mean?
How the heck am I a child?
It's just the way you look!
D-Don't look at me!
Okay.
Today, we're bringing you
Children's Day: Drawing Competition!
Woohoo!
Drawing—
So!
It appears that a bunch
of young hololive viewers
drew some pictures
of our fellow members!
Wow!
Wait, there are children
who know about me...?
Wow, it's like I'm *ikakinTV!
I'm so glad!
Our first entry is
from Hina-chan, age 6!
Thank you, Hina-chan!
Right over here!
Ta-dah!
Oh wow!
Ooh!
Wow!
Can you tell who this is?
Yes! It's Luna-san!
Gen 4
Himemori Luna
Yeah!
She drew Luna-tan for us!
Wow!
She's a good artist!
So this drawing appears to be
showing Hina-chan and Luna-tan
posing together
for a commemorative photo!
Ooh!
She's only six, yet her ambition
to share the same stage
as her idol's already forming.
That's quite something.
From the perspective of a six-year-old,
Luna-tan is a princess after all.
Yeah.
She's really pink and cute,
so she must be pretty popular.
True!
Thanks a lot, Hina-chan!
Thank you!
Our next one is
from Kanna-chan, age 5!
Thank you, Kanna-chan!
Here it is!
Who do you think
she drew, Lap-tan?
Gen 2
Minato Aqua
Aqua-san!
That's right!
Good job getting it right, Lap-tan!
Of course I'd get this right!
And, if you look
at her eyes and all.
She did a good job
trying to replicate Aq-tan's eyes.
I can see that!
Those eyes are pretty close.
She's even got the pose down!
She does!
Pretty amazing for a five-year-old.
Wow.
She's got talent!
I also really like how you can tell
Yeah?
that she's holding
all these hearts and stars and all.
The portrayal of her
holding them is incredible.
This is really, really cute.
So cuuute!
Thanks a lot, Kanna-chan.
Thanks!
Next up, we have one
from Reina-chan, age 7.
Let's see it!
Thank you, Reina-chan!
This shows Reina-chan and Moona
hololive ID
Moona Hoshinova
in the middle of making flower crowns!
Moona's outfit looks really cool!
Yeah, it's pretty cool!
Being able to draw things
like clothes is really impressive.
On top of that, the way
she fancied up the ponytails is a nice touch.
Yeah.
The ponytails are matching, too!
Right? It's so cute!
Wow.
I could only draw clothes
as triangles when I was little.
Thank you so much, Reina-chan!
Thanks!
We still have a lot more left!
Our next one is
from Rin-chan, age 6!
Let's see it!
Thanks, Rin-chan!
Thanks.
Wait, what?!
Oh!
Isn't this... a lamenting Pekora-san?
Gen 3
Usada Pekora
She's but a six-year-old, yet she's already
partaking in drawing Pekora cruelty?!
Who knows why,
but it looks like she decided
to draw a depekoed
and bummed out looking Usada.
Mm.
Wow.
Wow...
Rin-chan, you've got some taste!
She totally gets it.
Nice.
Rin-chan.
You. I like your style.
She's got talent, all right.
She does indeed.
Wow.
Thank you, Rin-chan!
Thanks!
Next up is
from Mio-chan, age 9!
This isn't from our Mio-chan, right...?
Gamers
Ookami Mio
Oh? Mio-san?
She does regress to being
a nine-year-old sometimes...
This must be a different Mio-chan, right?
Thanks, Mio-chan.
Thanks! Here it is!
What do we have here!
Wow!
Wow! This is really stylish!
Huh?
Wait a minute!
Isn't her cleavage pretty cray?
That's her cleavage, right?
Mhm, that probably is cleavage.
Mio-chan...
Cute...
So this one shows Choco-sensei
and Mio-chan taking a bat
Gen 2
Yuzuki Choco
and some cats with scary insides
out for a walk.
Wow, this one's totally my type.
I'm curious about
what she means by "scary insides,"
Me too.
Does she mean
like a Cerberus-like cat?
Yeah, something like that, probably?
How devilish!
Yeah!
Super cool.
Her imagination's wild.
I would've never thought
about catching a bat.
Same.
Wow.
Just wow.
She's got it leashed on a string.
And it looks like Mio-chan
sent in another one, too!
Oh? No kidding?!
Yep. Let's take a look.
Here it is!
Oh?
Who could this be?
Who is it?
She's got pink hair, so...
Well! This just happens to be...
me, Miko!
Yay!
Thank you so much!
In other words, you got drawn
by Mio-san, the child prodigy!
It looks like she used
some patterns in this one.
Your outfit's great.
It's super-duper cute!
Is this showing you two
trying to hold hands?
Yes.
This just means Mio-chan
sees me like a big sister!
Oh my!
You've made a mistake, Mio-chan!
She's more like the same age as you!
No way!
So cute...
Right? It's so cute.
This makes me really happy!
I'm happy that someone drew me.
You're all smiles, Miko-san.
I'm happy, I can't help but smirk.
You're beaming...
Thanks a lot, Mio-chan.
Thanks!
The next one is
from Hana-chan, age 6!
Here it is!
Oh!
It's Miko-san again!
Yay!
I'm so happy! It even has
my name written on it!
Thank you!
Is it just me, or are you
pretty popular with the kids?
Can't help it. It must be
that big sister charm.
Are you sure it isn't because
they think you're one of them?
That's not it!
Are these things cherry blossoms...?
Yes!
The highlight of this one is
its usage of actual flower petals!
Wow!
What an artisan!
Doing something like this...
That's not something you would've
expected a six-year-old to come up with.
You're kidding me!
I just noticed, but this is
you in your idol outfit, too!
Yeah! It makes me so happy!
Both of us are standing on a stage.
Hana-chan sees you
as an idol, Miko-san!
I'll do my best, Hana-chan!
Thank you!
Good for you!
Thank you, Hana-chan!
Thank you!
The next one is
our last piece of the day!
Already?!
Fear not, Lap-tan.
We most assuredly received
a drawing of Lap-tan, too!
What... did you say?
I'm honored!
I wanna see it!
What's more, this one
is by our youngest sender,
Haruna-chan, age 1,
One?!
O-Okay...
and her sister,
Wakana-chan, age 8.
They collaborated in
the making of this drawing!
A collaborative drawing? For real?
Let's take a look! Ta-dah!
Oh...
But!
This must be
what they call abstract art!
This is nothing short of amazing.
Her overflowing talent is
on explosive display here!
The one-year-old Haruna-chan
likes making dots—
she drew your tail
in the bottom right, for instance.
A pointillist drawing, I see.
Wow!
The older sister Wakana-chan
used a writing brush using water
Oh, it's even watercolor!
to slather in your hair.
This is the work of a pro!
Isn't this incredible?
I'm so glad.
By the way, I've been informed
that we also have
a photo showing Haruna-chan
in the middle of drawing!
What?!
A photo? Is that all right?
Oh my!
Ahh! She's so cute!
My, my!
She's even dual-wielding!
It says here that she drew
while dual-wielding purple
and blue colored pencils.
She's only a year old but she
already knows how to hold a pencil!
She's totally got the face of a pro.
Hey, Haruna,
would you like to
come work under me?
Hey.
Don't solicit her to
join your evil organization!
YAGOO—
I wanna keep her drawing!
I feel you! I want them, too.
I'd want to put them up in my room.
Thank you so much,
Haruna-chan and Wakana-chan!
Thank you!
Children's drawings are just the best.
They've given me life.
It makes me ecstatic to think about how they
drew these because they come to watch us.
I'll do my best!
Boom Boom Hello YouTube!
'Sup, it's Lapukin.
Hey.
Thanks to all of you
who came to watch me today!
I hope you keep watching
what I do over at LapukinTV!
Hi, all you good girls and boys!
Thanks for always cheering me on!
Your big sister was
really, really glad today!
If we get a chance to do
one of these shows again,
I'd love it if you could draw a bunch
and post it using the tag, #miko_Art.
It'd make me so happy!
I'm going to keep doing my best,
so please keep cheering me on!
With that out of the way!
We hope you'll keep
supporting hololive, everyone!
Please do!
Bye-bye!