I remember taking a stroll
in NY stark naked...
Riley's raring to go♪
Tee-hee.
This is hell. It really is.
It's April 1 today!
Which means?
It's April Fools' Day!
Yay!
Wrong!
Huh?
What?
Is there something else today?
I lied!
Ahh!
It is April Fools' today!
Today we're going
to have a show about lies!
hololive GAMERS
Shirakami Fubuki
SS holoX
Hakui Koyori
Sakamata Chloe
hololive 3rd Gen
Shirogane Noel
Who U? Rapid-Fire Lying!
Yay!
Yay?
Wait, what?
What does that mean?
Now, now.
I will be furiously
shooting questions at you,
Rules
What's your name?
and you have to lie to all of them!
I'm Suzuki Fubuo!
I wonder what will you all turn into
by the end of this show.
Let us begin, then.
Anyone want to go first?
Me!
Koyo-chan!
Hold on.
So be it.
I lied.
I lied!
I lied, you hear me?
Thank you!
You what?!
By all means, go ahead!
That was a lie!
Thank you very much!
That was a lieeeee!
What a nice kouhai we have.
Just wait a moment!
It was just a lie for the April Fools'!
I don't want to go first!
Hakui Koyori's Turn
I will be rapidly
throwing questions at you,
so answer all of them with a lie!
And please truly become
the character you're lying about.
Uh, okay... Got it!
Rapid-Fire Lying...
start!
What's your name?
Agatha Christine!
What kind of person are you?
I really...
love money!
What do you do for a living?
I... Uhm...
I j... J...
I sell land!
You're flipping land? Not bad.
So a landlord?
I own many high-class apartments.
What's the structure of your family?
Family structure? There's me...
and my... dalmatian!
A dalmatian?!
How nice.
Any pet sayings?
Pet sayings?
Très bien!
(TL note: Très bien means splendid)
Describe yourself in one phrase.
It's a sin to be this beautiful.
That's some self-confidence.
Oh, shut it.
Your biggest mistake in life?
I remember taking a stroll
in NY stark naked...
Murmur
Chatter
Noise
How are you not in jail yet?!
Murmur
Chatter
Hold on!
Rustle
You've got a few screws loose!
Murmur
Noise
Chatter
Rustle
Murmur
Noise
How did that happen, even?
Chatter
Noise
Anything you'd like to tell the crowd?
Why don't you
become my dalmatian?
That's it!
That was a lot of questions.
Scary!
What should I have done?
I'm now afraid.
Good job!
That was really nice!
That was amazing!
Was that more embarrassing than
walking stark naked in NY?
Walking naked was better for sure.
Walking naked is better?!
Your questions caught me off guard.
You haven't used your
pet saying at all. Is something wrong?
Gosh, what was it?
Très bien!
Don't go "gosh" now!
Please call her Christine-san
until the end of the show.
And here I thought
I was done with this hell...
Très bien...😢
Très bien!
Sakamata Chloe's Turn
Ngh!
Please no!
You can't run!
Do your best!
Nooo!
You shall not run, très bien.
Christine-san, do you have
any advice for Sakamata-chan?
Do not fret. Stay strong.
Très bien!
That's just head empty!
Well, then...
Who will Chloe-chan turn into
after being forced into lies?
Rapid-Fire Lying...
start!
What's your name?
A... A...
Ajino Shiroe.
Ajino Shiroe?!
Well, then, Ajino Shiroe-san,
how old are you?
32 years old.
32? I see.
What kind of person are you?
Well, you know...
I usually spend my time
at cafés reading novels.
My Childhood Friend
Has Animal Ears?!
Oh, a novel-reader?
I see, I see.
What kinds of novels
can you recommend?
Stuff like bank robbery, I guess.
Robbery?!
Do you have any other hobbies?
Well...
I also make games, I guess.
Dang!
You make games?!
Please tell us a title!
"Stop Staring! My Shameless♡Harem,"
or something along the lines.
That's R-18 for sure.
What do you want
the most right now?
A cat-eared maid, I guess.
So you want to make your
girlfriend a cat-eared maid?
Nah.
i wont go out with her and obviously
shouldnt try anything on her
but i want her to love me
thats a new low
take your pills
That's getting complicated.
Anything you'd like
to tell the crowd?
If anyone wants to lend me money,
send them to the number below.
Ajino Shiroe is looking for sponsors
080-XXXX-XXXX
How was it, Ajino-san?
This is hell. It really is.
I'd like to go home.
Noel-san, what do you think?
Do you really have to lie?
It's bad to lie, isn't it?
It's okay if it's nothing serious.
It doesn't harm anyone.
Right! It doesn't hurt anybody!
They hurt themselves!
EMOTIONAL
DAMAGE
Shirogane Noel's Turn
Let's ask Ajino-san
for tips this time.
Well...
Just be yourself.
I know how great you are. Yeah.
Do your best.
Well, let's see who Noerun will turn into
after drowning in lies.
Rapid-Fire Lying...
start!
Please tell us your name.
My name is Riley Att-a-way.
Att-a-way?!
What kind of person are you?
Well, many call me modest,
others call me bold.
So which one is it?
Modest but bold?
What kind of personality is that?
How old are you?
I, believe it or not,
am 102 years old.
102 she says...
Très bien!
Do you have an introduction joke?
Some joke you've been
fostering for 102 years?
Riley's raring to go♪
Tee-hee.
What do you think?
Do you have a husband?
I was unmarried my whole life.
But lately,
Unmarried, huh.
there is someone I'm interested in.
32 years old, single
102 years old, single
The cute 32-year-old boy over there.
Like...
Um...
I'm
You know...
Wai—
Hold on!
I just thought he was cute and all.
Sorry...
You're a bit out of my league...
Ehehehe...
102 is a bit...
Aww, he's blushing, how cute!
Not at all...
Nonononono...
Um, Noriko-san!
kuawsedrftgyfujikolp
Seems like he likes
cat-eared maids.
Are you okay with that?
Well, if that's what he wants,
I'll do my best.
Hell no.
Pfft...
Hey...
You don't want you though.
Don't get the wrong idea!
Anything you'd like to tell the crowd?
I'm a bit lonely at 102,
so if there's a gentleman out there...
Wait, that was
your phone number, right?
I completely forgot!
That was Ajino-kun's number!
Splendid!
No way...
All good now!
No way!
I solved my loneliness!
Time to change number...
Love me lots♡
Anything you'd like to tell Ajino-san?
Is Granny not good enough for you?
You're not!
Thank you very much, Riley-san!
How do you feel?
My body feels hot after a long while.
What could it be?
Excitement, maybe?
That's love!
A love for the first time
in 80 years...
I'm so glad!
That hit harder than I thought.
Good for you, Ajino-san!
That it! How did you
like it today, everyone?
Lies put your mind in disorder
more than I could ever imagine.
I'll start jumping
at shadows at this rate...
I can't trust anything anymore...
Oh no!
Your souls...!
Your souls are leaving your body!
Let's keep lies to April Fools'.
Yeah...
I agree! Let's keep it to that.
Let's live our lives honestly,
without a lie, starting tomorrow!
Sure! Same as before.
If you liked this video,
please click the like button and subscribe
to the official and our own channels!
Please do!
And don't lie!