Y'know, I've been hooked on okayu lately.
I totally get that! You've seen the light, huh?
This morning was the same.
The okayu (porridge) warmed me up.
Yeah, yeah, I know that feel.
Pay attention, girl.
Thinking about Okayu (Nekomata)
gets me all hot and bothered too!
Hmm?
What's there to think about?
Speaking of, what topping do you like?
Topping...?
Y'know, like bonito flakes or soy sauce.
Topping Okayu?!
That's making me somewhat itchy.
It made Okayu happy?
Huh? I don't think okayu has feelings.
Don't be like that!
Of course Okayu has feelings!
M-My bad.
Also, Okayu and rice balls go hand-in-hand.
Keep that in mind.
Rice balls and okayu...
Really? I've never eaten that combo.
Hold up!
What do you mean, "eat"?
Y'know, eat okayu (porridge).
Eat Okayu (Nekomata)?
Don't!
Mwahaha!
My breakfast today was okayu, too.
Sui-chan, you jerk!
Uh... what?
Nothing makes a chilly day better than "Okayu."
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!