(1. 2. 3. Hey Yeah!!!)
BABACORN - HappinessWorld
Lyrics: Yuki Houto
(1. 2. 3. Hey Yeah!!!)
Composition: Yuki Houto
BABACORN - HappinessWorld
Vocals: BABACORN
(Houshou Marine, Shirakami Fubuki)
Arrangement: Yuki Houto
All Instruments & Programming: Yuki Houto
BABACORN - HappinessWorld
Recording & Mixing Engineer:
Tsukasa Kikuchi (Arte Refact)
Art: BLADE, sameanko
Video: Yoshi
Cooperation: Ni-c
You there, young lady,
this will soon be paradise
nee soko no ojousan koko wa mousugu paradaisu
Turn that frown upside down,
don't be looking gloomy, gloomy
fumange na kao shicha dame da yo damedame
Your smile's your passport,
if you've got it, then it's all good
sumairu ga pasupooto sore ga areba moomantai
Make the most of this colorful life
tanoshindeikou yo barairo raifu
A little courage
honno chotto
(A little courage)
"honno chotto"
Muster it up and go on one, two, step out, yay!
yuuki dashite wan chuu suteppu iei!
(Yay!)
(iei)
yuuki dashite wan chuu suteppu iei!
All you've seen so far
ima made no keshiki to wa
Will pale in comparison
akiraka ni chigau sekai
So pump it up and enjoy it
furu buusuto de! tanoshimou yo!
(1.2.3でHappiness World)
(1. 2. 3 de Happiness World)
Now's your chance,
take it and seize your dreams
ima da Get a chance da yume o tsukamou
(Woohoo!)
(fu fu)
ima da Get a chance da yume o tsukamou
Outfox the bookies,
tomorrow will bring confetti fever
ashita kara kamifubuki fiibaa
(Fever!)
(fiibaa)
ashita kara kamifubuki fiibaa
Waiting for you are things
beyond your wildest dreams
souzoushita koto nai dekigoto ga kitto matteru sa
(Hey)
Sing a song and let your heart dance
Sing a Song de kokoro odorase
(Woohoo!)
(fu fu)
Sing a Song de kokoro odorase
Be positive and helm the wheel all right!
pojitibu ni saa omokaji ippai!
(All right)
(ippai)
pojitibu ni saa omokaji ippai!
And your feelings give you the all-clear
kimochi harewataru sono shunkan
Go full speed ahead
zensoku zenshin da
You are never alone
itsudatte hitori janai
Come with us
watashitachi to issho ni
And find a life full of happiness
saikou ni HAPPY na jinsei o...
(Yay!)
(iei!)
24/7/365, it's show time
nengaranenjuu It’s Show time
Come one, come all, it's all right
kuru mono kobamazu It’s All right
We're hitting peak vibes, let's all go, oh yeah!
baibusu wa saikouchou seeno de minna de Oh yeah!
(Oh yeah!)
Arms in the air, hip hip hurray
ryoute o agemasho banbanzai
Things aren't getting hype enough
madamada kore demo mono tannai
You there, the shy one, come join us
uchikina soko no kimi kocchi oide
For people of all ages, from far and wide
kokontouzai rounyakunannyo
Nothing beats having fun, right?
tanoshii koto ga ichiban desho
Try cutting loose once in a while
sukoshi taga o hazushitemimashou
Welcome to this wonderland
youkoso wandaarando
Keep moving forward, one day at a time
kyou mo ippo ippo fumidaseba kitto
And the XP you gain will take you miles
jinsei no keikenchi gecchu
Even random mundane happenings
futoshita nanigenai koto datte
Can put a smile on your face
tabun waraeru sa
Now!
ima da
Now's your chance,
take it and seize your dreams
ima da Get a chance da yume o tsukamou
(Woohoo!)
(fu fu)
ima da Get a chance da yume o tsukamou
Outfox the bookies,
tomorrow will bring confetti fever
ashita kara kamifubuki fiibaa
(Fever!)
(fiibaa)
ashita kara kamifubuki fiibaa
Waiting for you are things
beyond your wildest dreams
souzoushita koto nai dekigoto ga kitto matteru sa
(Hey)
Sing a song and let your heart dance
Sing a Song de kokoro odorase
(Woohoo!)
(fu fu)
Sing a Song de kokoro odorase
Be positive and helm the wheel all right!
pojitibu ni saa omokaji ippai!
(All right)
(ippai)
pojitibu ni saa omokaji ippai!
And your feelings give you the all-clear
kimochi harewataru sono shunkan
Go full speed ahead
zensoku zenshin da
You are never alone
itsudatte hitori janai
Come with us
watashitachi to issho ni
And find a life full of happiness
saikou ni HAPPY na jinsei o...
(Yay!)
(iei!)
A life full of happiness for all of us
minna de HAPPY na jinsei o...
(Yay!)
(iei!)