Damn sunshine!
It's too hot!
Can you like, chill?!
Nope, sorry.
You're going down.
Hello?
I want to make it so the sun never rises again.
Okay.
Get together at the club, okay?
Seen Rushia-chan around?
Here, Ru-Ru-Ru-Ru!
Ru?
Ru!
Found Ru-Ru-Ru-Rushia!
Crowds...
Socialites...
When in Rome, do as the Romans do!
Nom!
Nomnomnomnomnom
nomnomnomnomAmanom!
Critical hit!
You're not supposed to eat that stuff.
Haachamachama!
Necromancers can eat wraps, though?
You know...
That was aluminum foil, not wrap.
I'm so metal!
Farmable XP!
1350! 1350!
I'm up again!
Take this!
Ru... shi... a?
The Four Women of the Burnpocalypse
Teehee!
Attagirl, wearing that seatbelt.
If you enjoyed this, please subscribe for more!