I'm the wet Okayu!
Huh?!
Infusing lewdness!
Could you strip for me?
Oi! This is the official channel, you know!
hololive Lecture on Cuteness!
UwU
Good morning, everyoooooone!
Good morning.
Huh?
Hey, aren't you two
a little lacking in cuteness?
Like this: Good moooooorning!
Isn't...
Isn't Kanatan acting a little strange?
She's so cringe.
I've gathered you two here today
to lecture you two on thish and that
as the adowable, angewic professow of cuteness
in order to make the two of you even cuter!
You're painful to listen to!
Ow!
Owie!
What the heck is "thish and that"?
So mwean!
You're so mwean!
Are we allowed to walk away from this?
We're, uh...
We're not really aiming
for that direction.
The type of cuteness, yeah?
The first lecture is free of charge,
so don't fret!
Let's work on it together!
Professor
Amane Kanata
First Lecture FREE
Lecture on Cuteness
Sounds like a scam.
Leave it to the super-duper cute
and youthful me,
and you'll become much cuter,
so let's get going!
Now, do it with me!
Sparkle!
Don't drag us into it!
We never agreed to this!
No, I insist. Just do it.
Just fricking do it.
One more try!
Sparkle!
Time for suffering.
Let's start with the basics!
The basics of being an idol:
A cute self-introduction!
To start us off,
I'll do an example
just♥for♥you★
SMACK
Their envious glares are a little scary.
But let's push on!
My selling point is my 50 kg grip!
I'm gonna crush you... with LOVE!
I'm hololive 4th gen's Amane Kanata!
Nice to meechu!
"Meechu"?
Just like that, girls.
Was that cute...?
I thought my heart would pop
when she said "crush."
Cuuute!
Cuuuuuute!
Next!
C'mon, Captain Marine!
What, me?
A cute intro...
How do I...
Cutely, like mine!
Cutely?
Mari-Mari Mori-Mori
La-dee-la-la-la!
Magic power is flowing into me!
Turn back time 15 years!
I'm the Magical Magic Pirates'
Marine-tan, okay? Set sail!
Right. Okayu-senpai, you're next.
Okayu-senpai.
Ah... so she's just
going to ignore me...
This is a poor example.
Okayu-senpai is already really cute,
Wha?
but I'd like to see you even cuter!
Okayu-senpai's cute
self-introduction starts in:
Cue-te!
Um...
"Cue-te..."?
I'm the cat-cat,
wet-wet
"Wet-wet"?!
Are you wet, Okayu-senpai?!
"Wet"?!
You're wet?
I'm the wet Okayu!
Huh?!
That's...
That's too lewd...
But that was cute!
Splendid!
Aren't you being a bit too biased?!
Hey! Was that fine for you?!
It was different from this thing.
What the heck
did you mean by "wet-wet"?!
What's wrong with it!
Okayu is wet!
Cute!
But from my view, you two...
"still have a long way to go."
R*oma-kun?!
Well then!
Take this lecture on cuteness
and become even cuter, okay?
Flu-flu-flu-fluff!
🤮🤮🤮
UwU
Let's raise our cuteness gauge!
Act a Profession!
Yaaay...😑
We need more energy than that!
Yaaay...😔
Yaaay!
As you can see,
we have a new, red pad here.
We'll have each of us
act out a profession
and say a one-liner to get
the audience's hearts thumping.
This cute and adorable Amane Kanata
will now show how it's done.
The profession I'll be acting out is...
A flight attendant!
Oh, I see.
Marine-chan,
Yes?
could I ask you to do the countdown?
Okay!
Are you ready?
Kanata's one-liner starts in:
Go!
Attention, please.
Dear customer,
would you like to go on
a flight of love with me?
Are you okay?
You were losing balance there.
She's stumbling.
Can I break her kneecaps now?
I'm so cute!
Down we go.
She's stumbling.
That was so cute!
She was stumbling just now.
Well, that's how it's done.
Do we really have to do this?
Do you even have to ask?
You two will have to do it as well.
We signed up for hell, didn't we?
We chose the wrong lecture to attend.
The profession you two
will act out is...
A nurse!
A nurse?!
A nurse?
A nurse, yes.
A nurse, huh...
We sure got a lewd one.
Well then, you can go
as soon as you're ready!
Anyone got a one-liner?
Then, meee.
Ah!
Okayu-senpai, go ahyead!
So, first...
"Ahyead"?
On the platform, yeah?
Yes!
Hup.
Are you ready?
Yes!
Okayu-tenpai's one-liner starts in...
Go!
I'm Okayu, the nurse
in charge of you from today.
I'll take care of you anytime.
WHOOOA!
Huh?!
Professor?! Professor?!
I hope I can learn a lot from you, professor.
Hold up! Hold up!
Please take care of me.
I'm the professor! Hey! I'm over here!
Please teach me lots, professor!
I'm the professor of lewdness.
She's so sexy...
Time to get schooled
by the Professor of Lewdness♡
I'll take this course instead.
Prof. Amane, it's been short but...
Thank you for everything.
No, no. Stop.
It was a wonderful performance,
but it's lacking in cuteness!
This is the cuteness lecture, after all!
Cuteness, you say...?
Could you act out
a nurse for us too, Marine-chan?
I want to see it, too!
If Prof. Okayu says so...
I'll do my cutest one!
Infusing lewdness!
It's inside me!
No lewdness allowed!
Illegal. Not allowed.
Cooties! Cooties!
Infusing lewdness!
Give me some cute power then!
Cuteness power!
Ah! I can feel it flowing in!
I think I can do a cute one now!
Alright, infusing lewdness power!
Ah! No! No!
Ah! It's flowing in!
Cuteness power!
Now then,
Captain Marine's one-liner starts in:
Go!
Oh, no!
Ah...
Dear patient, I'm so sorry!
I accidentally stabbed your butt
with the syringe!
You can—
Oh, no.
Watch Your Step
I tripped off the platform.
You OK?
Did I fail?
Get back up there!
I accidentally stabbed your butt
with the syringe!
You can stab it in my butt too.
Disqualified.
What the heck was that?
UwU
The next profession is...
Ta-dah!
A teacher!
We got another lewd one.
Eek!
Is it a little lewd?
It might be a little sexy.
But I'd like you to
place emphasis on cuteness.
Captain, you want to try?
Uh...
Can I really do it?
You seem good at it!
At being a teacher.
A teacher...
Well, then.
Marine-tan's one-liner starts in:
Cue!
I'm your health teacher,
but I don't know much
about boys' bodies.
Could you strip for me?
Why you...
Oi! This is the official channel, you know!
Huh? What?
What's your problem?
We're on the official channel!
You're gonna get them banned!
Wasn't that cute?
It was cute!
It wasn't!
It wasn't cute!
You have to be more innocent!
Geez, you two just don't get it.
Infusing!
Wah!
Cuteness power! Become cuter!
Don't lose to her!
Waaah!
Become cuter!
Now that I've become half-cute
and half-lewd, I'll give it a go!
Go ahead, Okayu-tenpai!
Okay.
Okayu-tenpai's one-liner starts in:
Cue!
Hello!
We'll be reviewing
Japanese history today.
Let's learn the forty...
two?
three?
four?
prefectures of Japan today!
There's forty-seven!
Uh...
Teacher?
There's Aomori, Akita, Iwate,
and You♥
That made no sense.
What was that about?
I didn't understand anything
from beginning to end.
On top of that,
some prefectures
of the 42 got left out!
She's too irresponsible!
Stop being a Japanese history teacher!
She doesn't have the drive!
And that wasn't even history!
It was geography!
There's Aomori, Akita, Iwate, and You♥
Then, I'll do a math teacher.
A math teacher?!
Can I?
Okay!
Kanata's one-liner starts in:
Go!
I want to solve
the final theorem with you...
This is our farm―
Farm?
K-Kanata...
You totally...
Cut that take.
You totally flubbed there.
Cut. We're done here.
UwU
The next profession is...
Ta-dah!
An Ally of Justice: A Police Officer!
A police officer!
But first, I'd like to
show y'all how it's done.
I'll give an example.
Revenge
Alright.
The professor's...
...example.
The professor's one-liner starts in:
Go!
You illegally parked in my heart,
so I'll have to arrest you *wink★*.
So they parked in the streets, huh.
Your heart's a road?
That's right!
Oh, maybe she's saying it's flat...
I'm not flat!
It is like a road.
It seems like a road.
It's not like a road!
Is that the metaphor?
It is not!
It's like an expensive, paved,
No!
and completely flat concrete road.
It's not!
It's about how the person filled
the gap in my heart by parking in it—
A gap? So your breasts are caved in?
It's not like that!
Swish
Swoosh
Does anyone else have
a one-liner for a police officer?
Do you want to try doing
an interrogation together?
An interrogation?!
Yeah.
What?
A lewd one?
A lewd one.
No lewdness allowed!
Let's do it!
No lewd ones allowed.
Let's do it together.
It's so cramped, Okayu-senpai.
It sure is.
So cramped.
Okayu-senpai and Marine-chan's
interrogation starts in:
Cue!
So you're the one?
That did the bad-bad.
Do you want to eat a pork cutlet bowl?
Or do you want to eat me?
Don't worry, we won't tell anyone
for just a little fun.
Yeah.
Isn't that skewing a little too much
on the lewd side?!
What?! It's cute, isn't it?!
That's gonna get us banned for sure!
But it's not our own channels
being banned, so...
You're right!
It's on the official channel, so...
Oh, right.
I guess it's fine, then!
No, that's not fine.
UwU
Today's lecture ends here!
Thanks for coming, everyone!
It's finally over!
Welp, time to leave.
Let's get going.
Wait up!
How was it? Do you two feel cuter?
It was interesting.
Don't you dare leave!
See ya!
There's still more!
Get back in your seats.
If I feel that your cuteness
is starting to diminish,
I'll drag you back here
without a second thought.
So keep that in mind!
SMACK
UwU
Don't forget to SMASH that Like button
and SUBSCRIBE to hololive OFFICIAL
and the featured talents' channels!
Huh?
What?