You're pretty good, Marine!
It's a winner!
Please give us a good reaction! Firing now!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Hey, hey.
Yer givin' me my Valentine
chocolate this year, right, Marine?
Hey.
You'll give some this year, yeah? Towa?
Why don't you give me some?!
Hand over your chocos!
Where's my chocos?!
I knew it!
My worst fears have come true!
Jokes aside,
you've done so much for us and all,
so let's get the Boss a good gift this season!
Staff being considerate for the Boss♡
That's a good idea!
Huddle time!
Valentine's is over, you know?
What's the plan?
Sure!
So...
Chocolate would probably kill the Boss.
She is a cat.
Do NOT give your cats chocolate!
Please don't do this at home!
Okay, we're ready.
Happy Valentine's!
Wah!
I can't eat chocolate!
Come on!
Thanks for everything, Boss.
I can't have it!
You'd never know if you don't try it!
Not! Eating!
If the Boss dies, leave everything else to us!
Leave the shop to us!
Yeah!
We're not getting any work done.
Let's stop fooling around
and open up shop!
'Kay!
We're sorry!
Okay!
Let's welcome our customer!
Welcome to the store!
Mio-chan!
Whoooo!
Hype Meter MAX
Please don't make a mess in the store.
It's me! It's me!
She's here!
Ookami Mio is here!
It's her! It's her!
Finishing Move
Mio Hyper Beam
MENT
LUCK
Today's customer is Ookami Mio-san!
Effect:
Zaps chat into
a babbling mess
Her specialty is tarot reading,
a big hit with other hololive members!
Special Skills:
Tarot reading
Ukelele, howling
*These stats are self-answered.
Your special skill is tarot reading?
Yes!
Predictions through tarot cards...!
Does it work?
It's really accurate!
Yes, it does.
It does?
Last year, mine said,
"Take good care of your health
lest you have trouble while you're sick."
I thought, "No way that'd happen,"
but then I got sick during Golden Week
when there were no doctors around.
Oof...
I ended up going "gaaaaah..." in despair.
You predicted that just
from the tarot cards?
Well, it's more of...
The cards told us
she should take care of herself.
That's amazing!
My own health luck was a bit shaky,
and I did get sick.
Captain's checked out too!
Wait―Aren't these death...?
Death predictions?
That'd be scary!
Cause of death: Mio.
That would be scary!
You're all getting just sick lately.
That ain't good.
I heard you had a finishing move too.
Oh, my finishing move?
Finishing move?
I could show off for a bit...
You would?!
Really?
How does it work?
What is it?
Okay, hmm... Come here for a bit, Subaru.
She's calling for you, Subaru-senpai.
Huh?
Come forward.
We got a nomination!
A nomination!
Thank you very much!
Wait, no!
Why me?! I haven't done anything! Marine!
Nuh-uh, Subaru-senpai!
You said we'd be on the same boat, right?
Said who?
Hold up!
Okay, I'm ready!
Please give us a good reaction!
Firing now!
Bwoom-woom-woom-woom-woom!
Mmrghmgrmghrmrgh!
MARINE!
That didn't take long.
That was quick!
Wait a sec. Did it only hit Marine?
Marine died so I could live.
Thank you for your sacrifice.
She's doing the Krillin pose and all.
Don't you mean Yamcha?
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Mio-chan has some problems
she'd want resolved!
Yep!
Please tell us what they are!
Sure!
Lately, I've just been cooped up
in my house, all alone.
I just wanna let loose and
raise hell with everyone here!
Leave it to us!
And there we have our request!
There we have our request!
Oooh!
So Mio-senpai's request is, in short,
Hmm?
to go back to your roots
and blow off some steam!
Leave it to us!
We have the perfect game for you!
Yaaaay!
We have it!
The game we recommend for today is...
Our After-School Playtime!
Whoa!
After-School Playtime!
This is our after-school playtime!
The 4th game of this series
revolves around after-school play!
The afternoon town is your playground,
filled with fun mini-games
that would tickle your nostalgia!
There are over 10 game modes,
including cardboard sledding, and crayfish hunting!
Who will master the games and become
Maruyama's Chief of the Playground?
That's it for homeroom!
Class Rep!
Everyone, stand!
Attention!
Sit down!
Just go home!
What an old gag!
Why are you all sitting down?
Class Rep!
Ma'am!
Everyone, sit!
Stand!
Attention!
And say goodbye.
Goooodbyeeeee.
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
We'll now start playing
Our After-School Playtime.
And to go along with it,
we'll be holding our own Maruyama
Chief of the Playground Showdown!
Yaaaay!
Chief of the Playground!
Here are the rules.
This is a free-for-all fight via
the mini-games in After-School Playtime.
You will receive points in each match
based on your standing.
First gets 3 points, second 2 points, third 1 point.
No points for fourth.
The one with the most points at the end
becomes the Maruyama Chief of the Playground.
Whoever becomes the Chief of the Playground
will win a copy of Our School Battle,
a sports software set,
and a whole lot of other goodies!
I want that prize!
I want it!
It's not a participation gift?
It isn't.
Nope.
Gotta earn it.
You're not gonna be
Chief of the Playground at this rate.
That's harsh!
You have to fight for the title!
I guess that's true.
Time to take the win.
Okay.
Let's start off the games!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Begin the showdown!
Whoa, this is neat!
Character Select
Time to select a character.
I'll go with Rin.
For Marine.
That's clever!
Makes sense.
I'll go with Takumi since we're both purple!
You even look similar!
Cool pick.
Don't you think
the upper-right guy's for Subaru?
This guy?
Now that's a Chief of the Playground!
He does look the part!
Souta's a pretty fitting name too.
True!
I'll stick with him, then!
Got a pick, Mio-chan?
Black hair's one of my traits so I'm picking Akira.
Another cool pick.
Even your hair styling is pretty similar.
It's the kid leader haircut.
The hair style...
Now that they've made their picks,
it's time for them to choose from
the wide selection of mini-games!
They're all like a peek
into your childhood, no?
You can pick them from below too.
So much to choose from―!
But damn,
my character looks hecka unique!
He's very rugged.
Look at them corners.
You can see the title of each game
on the upper right.
Since we have a clear view
of our options below,
does anyone have a game
they want to play―?
Wait. I wanna go crayfish hunting!
I wanna catch some!
Gotcha!
I wanna go catching!
Great choice for a first game!
Let's go crayfish hunting!
The game is simple:
use the net to catch crayfish!
That's all there is to it!
Even if you can't see them,
look out for the bubbling spots
and try your luck there!
Some of them are glowing!
I'm gonna catch these ones!
Definitely these ones.
Oh, they're fading away!
They are!
Right here!
The bubbling spots have the crayfish!
Victory is determined
not by the number caught
but by the total weight of the catch!
While you should
catch as many as you can,
the size of the catch still matters!
The catch numbers are
on the left side of the screen!
Towa-sama's in the le― Oh?
The glowing ones are the good ones, huh?
Marine seems to be
taking a pretty good lead here.
She's doing quite well.
I think I'm just catching the small ones.
Not too confident about this lead.
Number-wise, though...
19?! That's a lot!
Nineteen?!
That's definitely a good catch!
It's the weight that matters!
The weight has the final say!
It's by weight?!
Whoever makes the heftiest catch wins!
Let's see!
Marine-chan is first place!
Isn't this a numbers game?!
This is totally a numbers game!
It isn't! I swear!
You tricked us, didn't you?!
Exactly!
I didn't!
I really didn't!
Damn you, brat pack leader!
Captain is 1st, netting her 3 points!
Our next game is...
What's at the bottom?
That one, with the shoe.
The one with the shoe?
Lower left.
That one's the...
Down.
Penalty shoot-out?
That one.
Oh, not that.
It's the one with the shoe.
There.
The orange one!
Right below you!
I know where it is!
It's that one!
Now, now. No fighting.
Where are you going?!
She's going back.
It's rock kicking!
Rock kicking race!
I wanna play this!
Rock kicking race, huh?
Let's do it!
Next up is the rock kicking race!
Kick your rocks to the goal!
It's a very straightforward race game!
The key mechanic is
to change your camera angle as you go!
Let's go and kick some rocks!
It's time.
Everyone's assigned a rock,
so please kick your own rocks.
So that's how it goes.
Crap, I went off-field.
We just started too...
Subaru's doing really well!
You see...
Subaru has really good ball control!
How do you move the camera?
Use the left and right directional buttons.
Like this?
I went off-field.
Marine is chasing from behind.
Who's in the lead?
Subaru is in the lead.
Subaru's in 1st.
Marine's slowly catching up to her though.
They're now neck-and-neck!
You're pretty good, Marine!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Get to the green spot to win!
Ah, I see!
Surf's up!
Crud, off-field again!
Off-field!
This might be your chance, Subaru-chan!
Get in!
YES!
Damn it!
I was so close!
Why did I panic near the end...
Y'all saw that?
Wait! Let me catch up!
This really takes me back.
The fight for 3rd place ends with...
Yaaay!
Ooh, game set!
Am I the only one left behind?
Yes.
Looks like it.
Is that so?
Okay, please wa―
Off-field again?!
You might never get out of here, Mio-chan.
Geez!
Do I just rotate like this?
Kicking rocks for all eternity.
Yep! Just do that!
So that's how!
Keep going!
Just a bit more!
I'll get there!
Everyone's waiting for me―
I really don't like how this is going!
Don't give up!
Painful.
COME ON!
LET ME FINISH!
Mio-san still has 0 points...
Please try harder on the next game!
Which should I choose...?
Just go for what you think looks fun.
What about pebble towers?
Let's go for that!
This one?
The next game is pebble tower!
You balance some pebbles into a pile!
Whoever has the highest tower wins,
so be careful not to let it all come down!
The directions are on top.
How do we do this?
Drop the pebble...
Like this?
The next one comes after
dropping the first one.
If even a single pebble falls off,
then it's game over for you!
This feels strange.
Pile them up!
Lechu go!
Okay.
Four, five.
Is that all?
It starts counting down if you take too long.
Right.
Wait. Wait.
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
AAGH!
Marine is out! Final height: 5.4 cm!
Okay, I see!
One of us here's
just breezing through this. Look!
The expert's right here!
She's good!
Have you done this before?
She's a pebble stacking pro!
Ah, wait!
It was piling up quite high too!
You did well!
What the heck are you building there?
Subaru...
Your pile's really messed up!
It's still holding up!
Not bad, Subaru!
Subaru-senpai looks like
she's on the road to victory.
Aaaaah!
Wha?
What?
Ah.
What's her final height...?
That's a wrap!
Great job!
She finally got 1st place!
Mio-chan is 1st!
She finally did it.
I'm really better at games
that require thinking.
Did we need to think for this one?
Mio-san gets her first win!
There's still a lot more games to go!
Let's go cardboard sledding!
Sure!
Have you done it before?
Yep!
Whoa! That means you've played all of these!
I have too!
You had a wild childhood, huh?
Yeah.
Cardboard sledding! Whoosh!
Everyone races on cardboard sleds
on this nature-filled course!
Speed up with the jump ramps
and dash to the win!
Ready to go!
Yep!
Start!
Let's go!
So fast!
Move over!
It's a roughhouse!
Outta the way!
Jump ramp, go!
Another jump ramp!
Out of my way!
Everyone's single-filed!
Marine's blazing through!
Towa-sama's getting better!
Towa-chan's now first!
Mio-chan's blocking my way!
What the heck?!
Left? Right? Where do I go?
Noooooo!
Towa-chan's currently leading!
We're on the last leg of the race!
Get outta my way!
I'm gonna go for a drift!
Isn't that the finish line?
1st place is Towa-sama!
Where's Mio-chan?!
Second is...
She's about to cry! She's gonna cry!
Yep.
The results are in.
Congrats!
Yeah!
Oh no, Mio-san is last again...
She's starting to fall behind.
The games that followed
were just as intense!
As everyone slowly regains
to their childlike innocence...
Before we know it,
the first half is done!
It's a fight for the top!
Let's keep our eyes peeled
on the second half!
On the other hand, though...
Mio-san still only has 3 points!
Th-Three?
Just three...
Hm?
I did win once, right...?
Just once isn't enough.
You're not childlike enough yet, Mio-senpai!
Really? Is that it?
You haven't fully embraced it yet!
Exactly.
Maybe I'm not cut out for that.
To help the girls reclaim their childlike innocence, we've prepared a little something!
Ta-dah!
An assortment of nostalgic cheap candy!
They can choose one after telling
a childhood after-school story.
I like Black Thunder... but Yocchan is also good...
Nah, it's got to be BigKatsu.
And... go!
Who wants to... Ah!
Me! Me! Me!
Me!
That was fast! Subaru, go ahead.
Whenever you're ready.
Okay!
I'm a master when
it comes to cheap junk food.
Oh?
A master?
I went to the junk food store
with 500 yen after school to live it up.
Isn't that a little too much?
So, I bought a truckload of snacks,
Living the life from childhood.
went to the top of a hill with my buds,
and ate them while staring off into the sunset.
That's so cool!
That's such a cool story!
You really made the most
out of your childhood.
That was a great story.
Yay! Can I eat some?
Sure!
Let's go!
Are you sure you want to
reward this self-indulging brat?
That was a great story.
I'm a little touched, honestly.
See that?
I'll go next!
Pick me!
Netherlands Candy
Next up: Captain Marine!
Go ahead, Captain.
I was actually the master
of cheap junk food, too.
She has the same story!
Don't steal my story!
For real.
Well, unlike Subaru-senpai,
I was actually one of the destitute junk food girls.
The destitute junk food girls?!
Yes.
Never heard of them.
So back then, on the show ITO FAMILY,
Uh-huh.
there was a trick to knowing
which butamen were winners.
You were cheating?!
We were all doing it in the store,
then the candy store granny
walked over and said,
"Are you doing that too?
Everyone that came here today was doing that.
However, that trick doesn't work here."
That was a good story.
Was it really?
You can have one!
Boss, you're too lenient!
When you talk about candy stores,
you can't leave out the granny.
When it comes to the candy store,
She's a mainstay.
It's been a while.
I'd go for what the show had: butamen!
Butamen Ramen
Who else?!
Me!
Hmm... Let's see...
Let's go with Towa-chan!
Yay!
This is a story from when I was a little kid.
My friend took me to this
"Secret Candy Store."
I had 50 yen in my hands
and bought a 10 yen gum that had jackpots.
Oh, yeah!
I remember those!
And, I also got this 40 yen... jelly?
The one in a tube.
Oh, those!
The one that's all twisted, right?
The tornado one.
Yeah.
I got that tornado jelly in a tube
and checked if I won with my friends.
That's a nice memory.
This brings me back!
The neon-colored ones, right?
YEAH! THOSE!
She's really hyped up. Take one!
Yaaay!
10-yen cola gum
It'd be great if I got a winner.
Can you wrap us up, Mio-chan?
My after-school story is...
Let's see...
I used to take the tadpoles
in the paddy fields home with me!
Really?
Tadpoles?
Wait—
Sorry for cutting you off.
It's a winner!
Oh!
She pulled a winner!
Take another!
You can take another one.
Sorry, Mio-chan, I interrupted.
Cut Yocchan Ika (squid)
Her winning pull drew us away
from Mio's story!
Was that a good story?
I honestly can't say...
Whaaat?!
Whyyy?!
Also, while I was on my way home,
um...
I used to drink nectar
from some red flowers, too.
I remember those!
You have to snap the thing in the middle off
and then suck from the bottom, right?
Yeah, those!
You can take one!
Yaaay!
Sudako-san Taro
Did you enjoy those snacks?
It was good!
Then, let's play some games!
Okay!
Time for the 2nd half!
Did those stories sound nostalgic?
Let's begin the 2nd half battle for the title of
Chief of the Playground!
Let's see...
The toy boat race sounds fun.
I want to do that!
That sounds fun.
I'm the Captain, after all.
That's true.
You're right!
Next up is the toy boat race!
A race with customizable ships!
I wonder what designs
everyone's gonna go with?
Let's start designing!
This is hard to choose...
I want to make mine
look like a pirate ship...
This looks cool.
It is!
Ah! They have a pirate ship! Nice!
Captain's ship is...
Of course, I modeled it off a pirate ship.
And Towa-chan's is...
I added a spring mechanism.
It looked like it'd make me faster.
It does have one.
True.
I thought it had that image.
I see.
It's cute.
Subaru's is...
For mine,
I thought water bottles are pretty buoyant,
and I added floaters on the sides
on top of that.
That's smart!
Big brain strats.
Mio-chan, you had those too, right?
I think mine's a mix of Towa's and Subaru's.
I can see that.
Let's get started!
Okay!
Let's do it!
Once you're ready to sail, let's start!
So it's down to skill anyways...
I wonder...
But is speed also...
Speed probably depends on, uh...
It probably depends on the customization.
Yeah.
Might affect maneuverability too.
There's a bunch of... trash? floating around.
She's fast! She's gaining momentum!
Yay, I'm in first!
How do you do that?
Ah, the current's dragging me along.
So far, Towa's pretty fast.
But Subaru-chan's right next to me!
It's a dead heat race!
That was close!
Who will get first?!
Go! Go! Go!
This is a close battle!
Yay!
Whyyy!
Everyone was pretty close except for me.
How did you do badly on your specialty?
My pirate ship ;-;
Captain unexpectedly gets
last place on her turf.
Well, let's make up for it in the next one!
Next up is a guaranteed hypefest...
the water gun fight!
The rules are simple:
Whoever lands the most hits wins!
Utilize the cover to reposition,
then unleash a torrent on your enemies!
We're on each cardinal direction, huh?
Ah, okay.
Oh no, that's bad.
Take this!
Ah, crap.
Mio-senpai!
Chill, chill.
Mio-san is locked onto Captain!
Take that! And that!
Mio-senpai!
What the heck?
They're face to face!
Mio-senpai! You're too close!
While Mio-san was chasing down Captain,
Towa-san lets loose!
Take this!
Wait! Subaru-chan!
Take that!
Melee distance!
Nooo!
But she's really...
Oh, no!
Take that!
Oh, so you have HP.
She's so good...
The one who hit the most is...
Wait, it's not me!
Yaaay!
The winner is decided
by how much they landed!
I thought I was being pretty aggressive...
We didn't hit as much as we thought.
I see.
I was so close up!
But I hit so little.
Time flies when you're having fun!
It's almost time to go home.
This next battle will be the last!
These are the current standings!
Will Mio-san be able to close
this overwhelming gap?
You can do it!
Hold up.
Oh, no.
Boss, she's gonna
file a complaint at this rate!
Rest assured.
Of course,
for the winner of the last battle...
will reward 20 points!
20 points!
The final battleground is
Noisy Crazy Sumo.
It tests to see if your physical strength
is befitting of a chief.
This will decide
Maruyama Chief of the Playground!
Those are some painful-sounding blows.
Get 'em! Push 'em out!
Oh, no!
Take that!
They're going at it.
Ahhh!
Oh, crap! I stepped out!
Oh? Subaru-san and Captain are out!
Mio-chan and Towa!
Mio-chan, you got this!
Yaaay!
I did it!
Congrats!
I did it!!
Yay!
That home-ground advantage!
V for Victory!
A huge turnaround!
The winner is Mio-san!
I suppose the Chief needs luck as well!
The comeback victory!
She had immense momentum.
That she did.
Those were some amazing slaps.
Yeah.
They hurt.
I felt those for sure.
For the winner, Mio-san,
we'll give her the School Battle game set!
You did it!
That aside,
did we manage to solve your worry?
That ending blew it all away!
Let us ask you one last thing.
Please tell us the member who shined
the most, the Twin-crew for today!
Mio-sha...
Don't let her trick you!
I cheered you on until the end, remember?
Mio-sha...
Don't let them trick you!
Mio-chan!
Mio-sha...
Let's see...
Let's compromise here and pick...
I suppose it should be Towa.
Yay! Mio-chan!
You fell for her tricks!
Captain, just as I expected,
Mio-chan has no judge of character.
Hey, you're indirectly dissing me you know!
What do you mean "as you expected"?!
We said we'll keep going at it together.
Right?
Who cares about these two losers.
She's suddenly calling them losers.
Let's settle this with a sumo bout!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
Challenge From The Boss:
the Maruyama Championship Season 2!
At this point, we'll have our customers
try their hand at a minigame.
The one who finishes the season
on top will receive a trophy!
Season 2's minigame is
SEGA AGES Sonic the Hedgehog.
Players will compete in
Green Hill Zone Act 1's time attack mode!
The clear time shown on the
results screen will be your record.
By the way, the one with
the best time currently...
is Suisei-chan, with 36.56 seconds!
Well?
How confident are you?
Uh... 36.56? How fast is that, exactly?
Ah, so you've never tried this before?
Yeah, never!
I see.
This should be fun.
Okay, let's get right to it!
That was abrupt!
Don't worry. Plenty of people
hadn't tried it before.
I'm in trouble!
But hey, y'know, Mio-senpai kinda has
a similar hairstyle to Sonic.
Yeah, might be some synergy there.
Oh, whoa!
She picked that up quick!
She seems good!
Pretty good!
That's some American reactions.
True.
She's aiming for it.
What's that mean?
You're good! Good!
That was a difficult spot!
She can do this!
She can do this if she keeps going!
And she got through that easily.
Keep going!
People keep getting stuck there.
What? Really?
So you're better than most.
Seriously?
This is looking good!
And there we have our time.
It's 43.24 seconds.
Which means...
Fast!
That puts her in third place!
Your Sonic similarity paid off.
You're right behind Captain Marine.
Oh.
Too bad, Mio-senpai. You couldn't beat me.
What was your time?
What was it?
Oh, 41.25 seconds.
Darn, so close!
Hopefully the next challenger
can beat her.
Okay, so...
Thank you for coming, Mio-san!
Thank you!
See you again soon!
Game Shop Maruyama!
~Game Over Your Worries~
Season 2
I've asked Marine to stay back
with me this time.
After Closing
Here I am.
Let's give our viewers some advice
for their worries.
This one's from @NaS_HOISSURU!
Thank you!
"Hello to the cast of Maruyama."
Hello.
"I have trouble turning my friends down.
Don't get me wrong, I truly am happy
that they invite me out,
but I usually end up regretting it the next day.
That said, turning them down
leaves a void in my heart.
Is there a good way to avoid
hurting myself or my friends?"
There we have it.
I often use my health as an excuse.
The Sickly Method
Your health?!
I see. They can't force you then.
"And lately...
My schedule...
Yeah! My schedule's packed!"
The Busy Method Also Works
How about you, Boss?
Don't you get asked to hang out?
Well...
How do you handle it?
Well, the thing is...
Yeah?
I turned them down so many times.
Yeah, really.
I'd just apologize to them, like,
"Sorry, I have to catch the last train home."
Are you sure that's a good idea in this business?
No! Absolutely not!
Oh, so it's not.
Yeah, so now nobody invites me.
So I think you should
absolutely go when you can.
In NaS's case...
Try bonding over drinks, or something?
It's complicated.
But don't push yourself.
When you don't wanna go,
say you're sick...
or that you're busy.
Yeah.
Oh, but here's the thing.
If you turn them down once,
go the next time.
You should maintain a balance.
Makes sense!
Don't just turn everything down!
Go when you can or should.
Like birthday parties, or special events.
Yeah, yeah!
Ah, so you can just go
when it's important!
That's a rather good solution,
don't you think?
Right?
Anyway, we're accepting requests
for advice from you.
If your request gets featured, you get this!
A completely unique, personally-signed
request fulfilled sticker!
So please send in your submissions!
Keep 'em coming! Keep 'em coming!