"There's a surefire way
to win this game."
They even added
an extra "!" for emphasis.
"No poking!!"
Ahh! I've completely cracked it—
Wait, that's not it. I got it mixed up.
Welcome to the show!
This is holo's Bonjour,
a variety and talk show
where one of the guests
changes every month!
Now then,
it looks like we have
three lovely ladies here today!
Allow me to introduce myself.
Hellobo!
I'm the virtual robot, Roboco!
Now, who might this young lady
looking high out of her mind
next to me be?
Ahahahah!
The name is Haachama-chama!
I'm Akai Haato, a.k.a. Haachama!
Your turn, Lapchamachama!
Hmph!
It's ten million years too soon for you
to even try to lay your eyes upon me!
Give heed!
La+ Darknesss
i-is—
the n-n—
name?
Stuttered
Did she just stutter?
I think she just stuttered.
That's my name!
Very well, then.
Uh—
Can I go back to normal now?
Everyone,
back to normal now, please!
All right then,
the three of us will be
bringing this show to you today!
Yay!
Woo-hoo!
I'll be your host for today.
Let's have lots of fun!
Okay, sounds good!
'Kay!
The three of us make
for a pretty rare combo, don't we?
Yeah!
Yeah, this is a new combo.
But...
We've talked quite a bit,
haven't we?
We talked about getting naked—
Stop, people are going
to take that the wrong way!
Friends who have conversations
that can't be shared
We did talk about getting naked, though.
We did keep on talking about
some slightly suggestive topics...
Yeah.
We have a totally
open relationship with each other.
But we're not even married?
I haven't even shown you that much yet!
We might get a bit closer in the future...
Will we really?
I don't want to meet
at Lap-chan's place, though.
Why?
Why not?!
Is it that filthy?
I hear a lot about it being dirty.
Nah, nah, nah.
For real?
Okay, it's true it was dirty.
But...
Some of my subordinates
came over to my place.
Kazama Iroha and
Hakui Koyori came over
and beat me down verbally.
"Disgusting." "It smells."
I was really hurt by their words
so I cleaned up.
My officer came over the other day,
and it was so clean she remarked,
"Wow, there's no smell!"
Wooow!
Nice!
Let's go mess it up some time!
Why would you?!
Sounds good.
I'll bring tons of snacks.
Oh, but you know...
I'm under the impression that
both Haachama and Lapchama rap a lot.
Nah, nah.
Haachama-san is the only one who raps.
You don't?
They might call me
Rap+ Dopenesss,
What?!
but that's just for show.
That battle with
Haachama-san the other day
was my first time rapping.
Wow!
That's really cool!
You were really good.
Right?
In order for us to get
to know more about Lap-chan,
let's move on to one of
our scheduled segments!
Let's go!
Random Rapid-Fire Interrogation!
Whoo!
🥁🥁🎉🎉
In this segment,
the two of us who've
been on the show before
will pelt the newcomer
Lap-chan with questions.
Very well!
Can you handle this?
Can you answer
all these questions?
Wha? Uh, yeah, totally.
You were kinda...
worried about stuff
before this, though.
Are you okay?
Really?
Don't talk about that!
Haachama and I will
hit you with our 20 questions now!
All right.
Yup.
Start!
Okay.
It's said that your place is a dump, but
where's the dirtiest in your house right now?
Under my bed!
Gross.
Your favorite recipe?
Omurice!
How cute.
What's your obsession?
Voices.
Any favorite phrases?
Because I'm the number one.
What's your motto?
The legend of I, the strongest.
Tell us how you feel
right now through rapping!
It's holo's Bonjour, these phrases are pure.
Tonight, you can call me the Maestro.
Streams on a new level every day,
the top is my dream.
Yeah!!
Did you have that written down?
Ayy!
Okay!
Next question!
What does it mean to be dignified?
To have my
overwhelming aura of power.
My head is...?
I'm not going to say that.
Lapchama...
I said, I'm not gonna say it!
That's all!
Very good.
Now that we're through with
pretty much all the questions...
She didn't do
the "chamachama" at all.
Why wouldn't...
Okay, wait.
You know...
she's been trying to get me
to say "Haachama-chama"
for so long now.
What?!
And have you ever said it?
No, never.
You said it earlier.
You said it before the stream!
Huh?
It just kinda
slipped out subconsciously,
but I took it back right away.
Why...
Why do you stop yourself there?
We'll take it step by step.
Ugh, my head...
Also, the question
about your obsessions.
Lap-chan has a huge thing for voices.
Everyone says that about you!
I'm super into voices.
What kind of voice
do you like the best?
Uh, Mimori—
Mimori Suzuko-san and
Sawashiro Miyuki-san's voices.
Ah,
something like
a mature older sister voice?
Oh, I see!
I see what you mean.
Oh, she's going for it.
She's doing the voice...
She just did some voice.
Oh my, I see.
I see what you mean.
Wow, that's kinda nice.
Oh dear.
Let's act like
mature older sisters today.
I wonder why Haachama-san's
voice just feels wrong to me.
Why would it?!
Oh, my!
Oh, but that's nice.
You still have a bit to learn.
Yes!
Can we get an, "Oh, my,"
from you, Haachama?
"Oh, my."
Oh, my.
Oh me, oh my.
That's an older sister?
Oh, my.
Older sister...?
An older sister?
Not a very mature
older sister, I think.
Yeah, I agree.
You can call me
Dearest Sister Roboco if you want.
Sister Robochama!
Dearest Sister!
Oh, my...
Oh, my, what a cute little devil.
Don't you have
an older sister voice, Lapchama?
I'm really good at it.
Do it, then.
Oh, my!
I'm so good.
Wow, that reeks of Haachama to me.
Doesn't sound that much
like a very mature sister.
Please don't compare me to her.
Just don't.
Our next segment is this!
Ta-dah!
Robocosan SOS!
Yay!
This segment is mine!
I'm a high-spec robot,
but I don't have much luck.
So, I'd like to train to improve my luck
by playing luck-based games
with everyone!
What're you giggling about?
I have really bad luck.
So we're gonna be testing our luck?
Yeah, precisely.
Please look over here!
Okay!
Okay.
Ah.
Robocosan!
Robocosan, how did—
Oh my!
Robocosan!
Welp, Robocosan's locked up,
so we might as well
go eat some meat.
Let's go, Lapchama!
Let's go get some yakiniku.
Stop kidding around, you two!
I'm your senior, save me!
As you can see,
I've been captured,
so you two have to
work together to save me.
In order to save me,
you two will have to press the symbols
on the screen one at a time.
However,
there's one button
connected to the bomb,
and if you press that,
the bomb will explode,
and the rescue mission
will end in failure.
If you can manage to press all the buttons
that aren't connected to the bomb,
you can save me,
so work together to save me!
Okay!
Moreover, there have been
no successful runs as of yet!
I'm counting on you two!
Well, the first one
only has one bomb,
so it should be easy.
However, we haven't had
anyone clear it yet.
Really?!
FYI, it's not a race to see
who can blow me up first.
So don't do that.
I see.
It's a streamer's nature
to go for the bomb, though.
Let's get started!
First stage: 1 bomb!
Well then,
start!
Which one of us first?
Uh...
Huh, which one?
Do neither of you two
have the power to choose?
I want to go first!
Haachama first?
Sure.
X! X! X!
You really like pressing X.
It's red!
I wanted to press that one!
Let's try it.
Okay!
There's no way.
Here goes nothing!
It's only the first one.
I'll be fine.
What's it gonna be...
Oh...
Well, yeah.
Management gets it.
That's too meta.
Lap-chan.
Lap-chan, your turn.
Could you petition to me
in a sexy older woman voice?
Will you rescue me, Lap-chan?
Ah—
I'd appreciate it if you
helped me not blow up here.
I'm goin' in!
That was easy.
I'll go with the circle.
The circle!
After the X, I'll try the circle.
Let's go.
We'll take this white circle...
and boop it!
I trust you...
That can't be wrong.
It couldn't be...
There's no way.
Ah, okay.
Oh!
You're such a good girl!
Piece of cake.
Next, I'll pick...
It's gotta be...
I should just let you make
all the decisions this time.
The yellow square...
Ohwaitnevermind.
The orange triangle!
The orange triangle?
Why?
Why did you chicken out
of the square?
Are you scared?
I'm not scared, it's just...
It's just gotta be a triangle!
Why?
Well, my lucky number is...
It's three!
Oh, really?
That's how this works?
When are you gonna explode?
Don't say that!
I knew she was trying
to blow you up!
You have to save me!
Boop!
Let's see...
I can't wait...
I can't wait!
When Haachama picks,
I don't feel like
it's about to blow up.
For real?
Oh!
Yay!
Whoa!
Is today...
the day...?
Looks like it might be...
I think it's about time for us
to set up some
unfortunate foreshadowing.
Lapchama...
I won't die here.
I'll survive for sure!
I want to live!
I want to survive!
Trust me, then!
I pick the green button
on the right.
The X is already taken
so we can't do
the One Piece thing
with all our fists up
showing off the
X tattoos on our arms.
Can't put our hands up now...
Can't do that anymore,
so green circle!
Boop!
What's it...
gonna...
be!
Was it really the best idea
to believe you?
Ugh...
Ay!
Whoo!
We're down to four choices now.
I pick the star!
And boop!
Which one?!
What'd you just say?
What was that?!
The white star!
The star.
I just heard a "boop"
outta nowhere.
I thought I was about
to suddenly drop dead—
She's making this
more nerve-racking.
Nooo!
Ro—
Robocosan!
Nice.
What do you mean, "Nice"?
What's...
What's nice about this?!
I didn't even realize at that moment
that I was about to die...
Not like this!
Not like this...
I didn't even know
I was about to die...
Hey, you can keep going though!
You're saying that
she has more lives left?!
I haven't become
a star in the sky yet.
I'm back!!
And I'm all blinged up!
I'm back! And so it's time
for the second stage,
where three out of eight buttons
are connected to bombs!
That's tough...
Well, you gotta have
at least three bombs or so
to really be able
to judge your skills.
We couldn't even succeed
with just one bomb, though.
The true battle begins here.
Why are you acting so confident
when you're trapped in there
with those bombs?
I don't get it!
Right?!
Lap-chan goes next, then.
Oh, are you sure?
Please rescue me!
This time, I'll save you and
we'll become comrades for real.
The EKS!
Push it, please.
EEEKSSS.
X...
And boop!
All right staff, take a hint.
There's no way it'd just
blow you up right away!
There's just no way.
AH!
No way!
Oh, man.
I'll bring the third Robocosan in, then.
That was too quick!
You accepted this way too quickly!
I already said last time
that the X was a bad idea...
Time to bring in the third Robosan!
And here's our next segment!
Quiz Time! Haachama Rap!
Whoo!
Ooh!
It's rap time!
This is Haachama's segment,
so please explain the rules!
Okay!
Quiz Time! Haachama Rap!
This segment is Haachama's—
Wait! Wrong line!
These are Roboco-senpai's lines.
In this segment, you'll all need to listen
to an original rap I came up with.
After that, you'll be quizzed on stuff
you can definitely answer if you listened to my rap!
This time around, I made a rap
using January 2022 as the theme!
Ooh!
Wow.
However, I went overkill making it,
so the rap this time
has some censored parts!
Isn't that all the time?
Doesn't this happen all the time?
There weren't any censors last time.
Really?!
It was really rough!
As for how the rap turned out, well...
Let's start off
by listening to the rap once.
Okay! Let's get to it!
Here it is!
Bring it.
To all the staff and all the members
I'm sorry for finishing this
after the deadline!!!
I'll kneel before you
so don't let go of my liiine!!!
It's pretty fast this time.
It's blazing fast.
Sounds pretty good.
Start of the year and it's bonjour and bye!
Same old <Redacted>, you and your passion!
Hey, Lapchama! You still kicking around?
Hey! What did you say?!
Haachama-chama's 10 feet underground!
I have no clue what she said there.
Took a big L playing VALORANT!
but let's finish duking
this through fiery raps!
May have been caught up in moving places
but Haachama's kicking
thanks to her parents!
Monetization?
That end with chamachama?
<Redacted>
Hey! What was that line?!
Little PC? It's busted AF, sadge!
The whole line got censored!
Keyboard? Drowned in pork broth, sadge!
Anything and everything busted up!
<Redacted>
I'm doomed! 😭
Stop, stop, stop.
Time out.
That's a lot of censors.
Did anything ever get
censored this much?
No clue.
There were some early on
and near the end.
I might be doomed.
The bleeps blocked out
everything else.
I can't remember anything at all.
All I can remember is
her spilling pork broth.
All I remember is
the number of bleeps.
Kinda amazing that
you memorized that.
It was all I focused on.
Here's the first question!
Oh?!
Q: What did Haachama spill pork broth on?
Wait.
I remember you spilling pork broth
on something but not what it is.
What was it?
Isn't it this item?
Robocosan, your doodles from earlier
are still on the palette...
*The doodles from their pre-stream
were still there on their answer sheets.
Robocosan...
I'll draw a bunch for you.
Hey! Stop that!
I'll draw you a bunch of them!
Me too!
Why?! Don't doodle on mine!
Okay!
Let's look at
Lapchama's answers first.
Sure!
I'll go first!
My answer is...
That's Robocosan's answer!
The staff's heads
all got Haachama-chama'd!
It's fine!
Just show either one!
The staff all got Haachama-chama'd.
My answer is "Desk"!
Oh!
Ooh!
Okay, I see.
How about you, Roboco-paisen?
Let's bring mine up, then.
Please do.
I saw a bit earlier but
wiped it from my memory.
Here it is!
Wait. Hang on.
When did you write this? You little...
I'm the greatest!
My answer is "Keyboard"!
I'm pretty sure she said that.
It's plausible.
"Keyboard" is a plausible answer.
Both our answers are plausible.
It's either her desk or keyboard.
If she spilled it on her keyboard,
it'd get her desk by extension, right?
True.
So my answer's the correct one.
Uh-huh.
Okay, then.
Time for the answer!
Here's the correct answer!
A: Keyboard
Ah! Dammit!
All right!
Hah! Got it!
Wow.
Dammit... I lost.
Looks like you need more practice.
I got it wrong, dammit.
Don't worry, there's still more quizzes!
Wait, there's none left.
What?
Wait... are there?
The heck?
Oh, there's still more?
Okay! Since that's the case...
The heck's up with you?
What should we do?
Do you two wanna listen to the rap again?
I wanna hear it again!
I'd like to listen to it again.
One more listen!
It was too overwhelming the first time!
They listened to it again.
Start of the year and it's bonjour and bye!
Same old <Redacted>, you and your passion!
Hey, Lapchama! You still kicking around?
What's she saying there?
Haachama-chama's 10 feet underground!
I'm really curious what got censored.
Like, uh...
Just one word will do.
I forgot.
You forgot?
You forgot, huh.
The staff are telling us
to avoid that topic!
Come on, girls?
There aren't any censors.
Ah, crap.
You're right!
The staff are on top of it, after all.
We have the staff on top of it, yeah.
But it really makes you curious.
Sorry.
They even added
an extra "!" for emphasis.
"No poking!!"
Why don't we show the question first?
Okay!
Staff, if you will...
Please bring it up!
Q: Why did Haachama tell La+ Darknesss
that they'll finish duking it out?
Hmm?
Huh? This one's...
Mhm?
Hang on...
This is the only answer.
I gotta put you in your place
'cause you're always such a cheeky brat.
I know the answer to this.
You do?
I only remember the other stuff.
Are those your final answers?
Yup!
This is my final answer!
Okay, let's reveal those answers!
What's it gonna be?
Which one first?
Ta-dah!
"VALORANT" and...
"Rap."
Rap...
Hmm...
I dunno anymore.
Looking at it, I think
Robocosan's answer is correct
but I dunno...
Maybe mine's correct...
I think the line was about
having you start rapping, Lap.
Our heads are getting
Haachama-chama'd.
OH?!
It's a tricky situation.
You said it!
No, I didn't!
We have video evidence!
No!
I said "Getting," so that doesn't...
Because I said that...
Uh... I phrased it differently
so it doesn't count.
You making excuses?
The way I phrased it was different
so it doesn't count.
Let's move on, then.
Here's the correct answer!
A: RAP
What?!
Ooh!
Exactly.
What do you mean, "Exactly."?!
Congratulations!
I thought I got it wrong
when I saw Lap-chan's answer.
Isn't it VALORANT?
I can squash you like a bug
better in VALORANT.
With VALORANT,
well... recently, I, uh...
I haven't been playing it much lately
plus I already lost to you there.
Don't hide from VALORANT.
So yeah.
Okay! Moving on,
our next segment is a new one!
Protect her Dignity!
Lap-sama's 10 Questions!
Yaaay!
B-B-B-Bam!
Surprise surprise!
This segment is Lap-chan's!
Yup!
Okay, please explain the rules!
Okay.
I'm the Founder of
the Secret Society holoX.
In other words,
I have to play a proper mystery—
mysterious figure flawlessly!
However, it feels like I'm losing my dignity
each passing day since I debuted.
With that said, I've prepared a segment that'll
help me regain my dignity as the Founder of holoX!
Feast your eyes on this!
Whoa! What's that?
Wow!
That looks cool!
It looks awesome!
Secret Society
Crow
Shark
hololive production
Wolf
Orca
Bodyguard
In this segment,
hololive production
I will pick one of the topics on the board
and both of you will have to guess
which one I picked by
asking me Yes or No questions.
Is it related to
the color blue?
Is it an animal?
Each person gets 5 questions,
which means you both get a total of 10 questions.
It's a guesting game!
Guesting game?
You okay?
Did you bite your tongue?
Guesting game?
Uh...
*Questions involving the
topic words are not allowed.
And of course, you can't directly
ask questions about the topics.
First off... do people
actually call you Lap-sama?
Nope.
I see people calling you
Yamada (a nickname) too.
I don't need people
calling me Yamada.
Guess I'll call you Yamada-sama!
Uh-huh.
Stop that!
That would kinda suck.
I said stop!
Okay.
The both of you
will need to ask me
10 questions total and
try to deduce the answer!
Y'know...
Mhm?
I figured out a surefire way
to win this. For real.
What?!
Really?
I'm not sure if I should use it
straight off the bat, though.
Yeah?
Wait, I can't see the
list of topics anymore!
Are you doing one of those,
"There's a surefire way to win this game." bits?
"There's a surefire way
to win this game."
We're not gonna show the topics.
Are we not allowed to look
at the topics, perchance?
What?!
I'm crippled if we're not allowed
to see the list of topics.
(Surefire Method: Crushed)
That's pathetic.
Can I have the first question?
Go ahead.
Sure!
Does it live in the sea?
No.
Oh, I got it!
Ahh! I've completely cracked it—
Wait, that's not it. I got it mixed up.
What? What'd you mix it up with?
We're coming up with questions?
Yeah.
What's the strongest being
in the world?
The heck are you saying?
*Only Yes or No questions allowed.
What the heck are you saying?
Wait, did I get the game wrong?!
You've got it completely wrong!
So wrong!
(Explaining the situation to Haachama)
For starters,
we know it's not a creature
from the sea,
so shark and orca are off the list.
Uh-huh.
I suppose we can use that logic?
Oh.
Go ahead and ask me
a different question.
Try thinking it over.
Is it the strongest in the world?
Obviously, yes!
Ohoho!
Ooh!
Does it have...
Yeah?
...anything to do with
the holoX members?
Good question, isn't it?
Ooh! Do we have it in the bag?
That narrows it down
significantly, doesn't it?
Does it have...
Uh-huh?
...anything to do
with you, Lapchama?
You already know
the answer to that!
Obviously, I have
something to do with it!
*It has something to do
with the holoX members.
Sheesh.
This doesn't look good for me.
Your partner's
a deadweight, Robocosan.
Crap.
Making her my partner
might've been a mistake.
What?!
I wanna ask for a partner swap.
Maybe you can try asking.
What?!
Seriously?
Can she? Can she change partners?
I need that swap.
Still...
Yeah?
It's the strongest,
yet it has nothing to do with the sea...
Yup.
Doesn't that narrow things
down quite a bit?
Yeah.
You getting this, Haachama?
We narrowed down our answers.
I've got a good question!
Can I ask it?
Hurry up!
Go ahead.
Is it something that
you put on your head?
You don't put it on your head.
You don't put it on your head...
Hang on.
Stop.
Wait.
Time out.
You don't have to do that...
You've got five questions left.
Five? That gives us
some decent leeway.
Can it be abbreviated?
Ooh, good question!
Ooh...
I think I know the answer!
Oh?
I wanna ask a question!
Oh, sure. Go ahead.
Is it a group name?
Ooh...
That's a yes.
Ooh!
You have three questions left.
Doesn't that pretty much
confirm it, Haachama?
I guess we can go for it.
Really?
You sure you don't wanna
ask any more questions?
You have three left, just saying.
Let's use them all up!
Let's do that, then.
It's not like, well...
They don't really have
to be about the game.
Oh, wait!
(And so it turns into a regular Q&A segment.)
I wanna have a go!
You sure?
I wanna ask her something!
Yeah. Go for it.
This is just simple curiosity, but...
Uh-huh?
Yeah?
Lap-chan...
Yes?
Wh-What—
What's your cup size?
That's a NO!
Hey!
Don't ask her that!
It's clearly endless!
That's sexual harassment!
It's not like it matters
what cup size I am.
It's endless, right?
Endless...
Possible, yes.
That's true.
It's already at its end.
No more, no less.
Shut yer trap!
"Already at its end."
That's our cue to stop.
Okay.
We'll show the answer in a bit,
so deduce away, you two!
Secret Society
Samurai
Hawk
Coyote
Crow
hololive production
Shark
Wolf
Orca
Bodyguard
Obviously, there's only
one answer here.
It's over.
It can only be that.
Wait.
Hang on.
Ah!
Right!
We had to pick from these!
Finally understands the rules.
What the heck did
you think you had to do?
Wanna answer at the same time?
Sure!
Okay. You ready?
Mhm.
Ready?
Secret Society!
Is that your final answer?
Yes, it's our final answer!
Let's show the correct answer then!
The correct answer is...
Secret Society!
Yaaay!
That was too easy, wasn't it?
10 questions is a bit too lenient.
You're both pretty good.
Personally, I feel like we
could've asked more questions.
True.
Oh?
On the other hand...
Since you say that,
Onwards to Round 2...
let's do another round.
Sure!
Ooh!
Extra
I can't trust anything anymore...
Come on, the X was just
begging to be pushed.
Trust in us, Roboco-paisen!
I can't!
She doesn't trust us one bit.
We killed her twice, after all!
About your tail, Lapchama...
Will it grow back if we cut it off?
Obviously NO!
Don't just whip up
a knife outta nowhere...
But it looks re-attachable,
doesn't it?
You're crazy!
If you're interested, check out the official fanclub channel on NicoNico for the full stream archives!
I don't wanna be
anywhere near you two!
You're both scaring me!
We're not scary at all!