Oh no!
I'm gonna be late!
Wait, this is a tome, not a toast!
Wha...
Out of my way!
My expiry date's almost here!
You what?
What was that all about?
And wait, I feel like I saw the future
when I touched this book...
hololive's 7th Generation is here,
and they're all toast!
Toasts
Make hololive Debut
A toast to all these toasts!🌟
That sounds awful! I gotta stop it!
I want no part of that cursed future!
Stop it, Kanatan!
You can't eat that!
Some nutrients I can
only get by eating Chronicle!
Cursed already!
The Fateful Choice?!
Stop Amane Kanata
Stop Shirogane Noel
Uh... er... This one!
Gimme your Chroniroll too!
Rochniroro! Rrrrro!
Why are you even
chasing after that crazy thing?!
Yeah!
Eat a toast, not a tome!
The Fateful Decision
Cross
Wait
Oh, you're actually waiting?
This isn't exactly
the safest neighborhood, yeah.
Kanata!
Why is nobody here?
We have an important stream scheduled!
But you got toast right here!
Beggars can't be choosers, I guess.
You'll do!
Toast
Egg on Toast
hololive 7th Generation: holoBread
Debuts Soon!
Oozora Subaru couldn't prevent
this cursed timeline,
but you can, in...
Sin Chronicle!