All the way into your heart.
Ooh!
F-Friends...?
Yes.
Friends...
Friends?
Welcome to the show!
This is holo's B-...
What are you laughing at?
Wow, I sounded like Sazae-san
for a second there!
Welcome to the show!
This is holo's Bonjour,
a variety and talk show
where one of the guests
changes every month!
Now then, exactly—
Er?
Now then, immediately,
let's introduce the guests!
Welcome to your rouge awakening!
This is Akai Haato!
And now the other two guests.
Why, how do you do?
My name is
Laplus Darknesss, indeed!
Who is this?!
Laplus Darknesss!
And now for our final guest.
Oh yes, hello, everyone!
Did I Luive you waiting?
I'm the XO of holoX,
Takane Lui!
What's with everyone trying
to act so charming today?
What? This is the same amount
of charm as usual!
Oh, yes, of course.
If we were to speak
about the relationship
between the three of us so far,
I'd call us a family,
wouldn't you say?
Nope.
Family?
Haato-san, you're our pet.
You seem like
you'd do some bad stuff,
No, I won't!
That's the image you give.
We'd have to put you in a cage.
You stay on the balcony.
The balcony.
The balcony?
The balcony?!
Am I not your beloved puppy?
The balcony seems like
it'd be a bit chilly,
so let's let her come inside.
Nice of you.
Yes!
So does that mean we can
sleep together on Mama's bed?
No way that's happening.
It's a cage for you.
Depiction of her bed.
No bed for you.
Okay, then, I'll settle for Lap-chan.
What? Don't use me
as the compromise!
You're the compromise!
I can't?
She said she'll settle for you.
Sure is hyper around here...
Right, you said that the pork cutlets
you ate didn't taste very good.
The katsudon I ate today
wasn't very good.
Not even the katsudon, huh.
My katsudon was terrible.
What did it taste like?
Kinda like plastic.
Plastic?! Really?
That's a rare flavor.
Okay, I'll make you some
delicious katsudon sometime.
Aw yeah!
Mama!
Wait.
I didn't say I was going to
make any for you, Haato-senpai.
Why?!
Make some for the two of us!
Fine, I'll make enough
for the both of you.
Yay!
And now that we all understand
what our relationship is like,
let's move on to the first segment!
Do we really understand?
Okay!
The first segment is called
Random Rapid-Fire Interrogation!
Yay!
In this segment,
Yay.
the two of us who've been
on the show before
will pelt the newcomer
Lui-chan with questions.
Lui-chan, are you ready for this?
What kind of questions
will I be getting?
Let's begin.
Here comes our barrage
of twenty questions!
I heard that you have
an impure image. Is that true?!
I'm a lewd and taboo type of pure.
Then can you please say, "Haachamachama!"
in a seductive, adult way?
Haachamachama!
Ohh!
How was that?
You're almost at four months
since your debut! How has it been?
Meant in a positive way, lately, I've been able
to take things a little less seriously.
Wonderful.
What do you do
as an executive officer?
I take care of Lap-sama.
Yay!
Can I call you
Taka-nerunerunerune?
Sure!
Really? Yay!
Taka-nee! Won't you please
make me some food, too?
You didn't even
call me Taka-nerunerune!
What do you like about me?
I like how you always
rely on me first thing.
Hey, wait.
What's that mean? (blush)
What don't you like about me?
When you message me first
and then leave me on read.
How awful!
Nooo! That's not it!
I just forget to reply!
How far can you see
in Hawkeye Mode?
All the way into your heart.
Ooh!
Something about that bugs me.
It's said that a capable hawk
hides its claws.
Do you have some sort of special talent
that you've hidden until now?
Hm, let's see...
If I go to an amusement park
with someone,
I can basically be like a staff member
and entertain them.
That sounds fun!
I wanna go!
Dogs, cats, or me,
which is your favorite?
Hm, I'll go cats...
Hey!
you acting as one, that is.
Oh nyo!
If you could become me
for one day, what would you do?
I'd do a super cute and sweet
ASMR stream.
Do not.
That does not need to happen.
I wanna see that!
Is that all?
That's all for the questions,
but there are
a couple worth revisiting
so let's go back and take a look.
Okay.
Lap-chan, was there anything
that caught your interest?
When I asked,
"What don't you like about me?"
I was expecting to hear,
"There's no such thing, dear."
I see.
But she sure answered.
What was it you didn't like again?
She'll start conversations with me,
and then she'll ignore my replies.
That's not good.
Like, she'll ask me about something,
and I'll reply,
and then she just ignores me.
I'm not ignoring you!
Not ignoring!
Well, this happens pretty frequently.
Yeah...
I'll be waiting for a reply,
but I don't get one.
And I'll be thinking like,
"I can go to sleep, right?"
"I'm good to go to bed, right?"
It's like I've said everything
I wanted to, so I'm satisfied.
Satisfaction is a two-way street!
Once she gets what she needed
to say off her chest,
she probably feels better
and that's that.
I see!
You're really letting her have it.
What was it?
The one where you
entertain your friend.
Yeah, the hawk
who thought she was
an amusement park employee,
right here.
I like it!
You really did?
It sounds so fun!
I wanna go with you.
I'll be like,
"And on your right, you can see..."
Can you do it right now?
Huh?
You do it when you're in line, right?
Yeah, I do it in line, but also like,
once we're in the attraction,
if someone says, "Watch out!"
I'll be like,
"Waaah! Everybody! Everybody!
Your heads! Your heads!
Are you okay?!"
Like that.
Oh wow!
Like at a certain land of the Mouse,
where you ride on that boat in the jungle
and see animals or something,
and they're like, "Watch out!"
You'll react to that?
Yeah, while reacting to that.
But my voice is loud,
so it makes the other customers laugh.
Really?
Your voice really is loud.
Oh, really?
I'll be like, "Is everyone okay?!"
Now for the next segment!
Ba-dum!
Quiz! Haachama Rap!
This is Haachama's segment!
Yay!
In this segment,
you'll be listening to an original rap
that Haachama wrote
and then taking a quiz
related to the rap!
The theme of this rap is
Haachama in February 2022!
So from February.
February, huh?
I have no memory of this.
The heck?
To start off, listen to the rap.
Haachamachama!
I went all in on spring break!
Ahh, vacations are the best!
Spring break?
Over hill and over dale
for miles and miles!
Danger in the boonies is big trouble!
Ane-chama was so mad,
she stomped in a circle!
Circle to the square to the triangle,
Yeah!
that's the story at any angle!
Hmm, for real!
The holoserver's so quiet!
Can't deny it, can only hear the trees!
Under the sea!
The plan's to befriend
all construction companies!
Don't care what,
just gimme some work!!
Enough with the mix-ups, hey, hey, hey!
Just a baby-chama
who loves a little prank, okay!
It's not about love or hate, hey, hey, hey!
I just wanna play with everyone, okay!
With TNT, it all goes boom!
And your mind goes blank
like an empty room!
Rat-a-tat-tat and a
Ratatatat!
Let's have fun in the holoserver!
Wow.
Yeah. It's amazing.
It is, but it's also full
of Haachama's feelings—
So what's with
the theme of February 2022?
Yeah, I didn't get anything
February out of that!
During this...
I thought maybe it'd have
something to do with Valentine's Day.
It's basically just
about fixing a problem
she caused or something?
During this time...
Haachama's fearsome.
During this time, it was
so lonely in the holoserver
and she just wanted
to play with everyone,
so that became
the theme of the rap.
Okay, gotcha.
That wasn't me, so I dunno.
The heck was all that?
So now we'll answer the questions?
Right!
Uh-oh.
Are you ready?
My mind went rat-a-tat-tat
and went blank.
Same here!
It did a number on you!
Now it's time for
the quiz based on this rap!
Here's the first question!
What was the plan that Haachama was
working on in the hololive Minecraft server?
What?
What was it?
Yeah, I'm with you.
We'll give you
some time to think it over.
I honestly have no clue, so I guess
this answer will be for the lols.
No idea.
I wonder.
I'm worried about my kanji.
Okay, let's take a look
at your answers.
Starting with La+-chan!
Sure.
Pa-pa-pa-pa! TNT world!
What's that supposed to be?
There were a lot of P sounds in there.
There were!
And something about
a world called TNT, maybe...
If I were to build a world like that,
would you help with me it, Lap-chan?
I'm not so sure about that.
Oh no, she's so lonely
she's started hunting friends right now!
Lui-chan, that's... enough of that!
Trying to make Minecraft friends.
What about your answer, Lui-chan?
Blow up some TNT.
Both of you have explosive answers.
TNT was the only thing
that stuck with me, too.
I see.
So if you're talking TNT,
I figured it's a plan to blow it up.
Exactly what would be accomplished,
I didn't really remember.
You too, Lui-chan. If I do that,
you'll help me out, right? Thank you.
She's so lonely that she's friend hunting.
Well, how can I say no to that?
Sure, I'll help you blow up some TNT.
Yay!
Haachama herself
gave an answer as well.
Let's take a look.
Ta-dah!
Construct civilization!
Was that in there?
Did she say that?
Was "construct civilization"
in there somewhere?
Was that said?
Did she really say that?
Now then, let's see the answer!
A plan to befriend
all the construction companies.
That was in there!
She said that!
I remember!
I was planning to become
friends with everyone.
I was listening to it thinking,
"Not a chance!"
What?! Why?!
No chance?
I was thinking solo construction
fits you the best.
No, no! It's lonely!
Harsh.
If we can do 30 minutes,
I'll play with you.
Not even a full hour?!
Because she gets motion sick.
I'd get the urge to throw up
if I go at it for too long.
Can't do anything about that then.
Okay. Let's move on
to the next question.
Before that, do you want
to listen to it again?
I will!
Can we?
Okay!
I remember nothing...
All I can recall is the TNT.
They listened to it once more.
Haachamacchama!
I went all in on spring break!
Ahh, vacations are the best!
So it seems we have
one last questi—hwaey!
Ok—hwaey!
So it seems we have
one last question!
Okay!
Let's see it, please!
Ane-chama became upset
for some reason.
What was that reason?
What was it?!
Wait. Ane-chama...
Was she in there?
Who is Ane-chama?
Haachama's real-life older sister.
She was there, I'm sure.
You're erasing her existence!
I think she was in the rap's prologue.
What was the reason again...?
Right. Right.
She's writing something.
How can she invade this space?
Let's start with Lui-chan this time.
Okay.
Because of the circle
to the square to the triangle,
story at any angle
nonsense gone-sense.
The heck is that?
I have no idea what that
super-long sentence is saying!
What's that nonsense?
You did say something like that, though.
Yeah, she's mad because it made no sense.
Triangle to the square
to the story at this angle or whatever.
That was basically playing
on repeat in my head.
Seems like your mind
went blank, Lui-chan.
Next up is Lap-chan. Let's see yours.
Okay.
You got a meeting time
wrong during the vacation.
Well...
She did talk about a vacation.
Yeah, and I was thinking
what would get someone
mad during a vacation.
And I figured getting the time wrong
or being late would do it.
You're on the right track, though.
Speculating!
Is she?
Let's see the answer.
Because we met
with danger in the boonies.
Ahh!
That was in there!
There was some danger.
What exactly is
danger in the boonies?
Was this danger your fault, Haato-san?
So yeah,
we couldn't wait
any longer for the bus,
so I was like,
"Let's just walk home!"
So we went walking
on this snowy mountain
where it was pretty slippery,
A snowy mountain?!
and my sister was like,
"I've had it!"
Yeah, that'll make ya mad.
Next time I was thinking,
instead of my big sister,
maybe I could find
a hololive member who
I can put into danger instead.
Why someone you can
put into danger?!
Try not to put them in danger!
Maybe the three of us
can do something?
Well, we are a secret society,
so we don't dabble
in any of that stuff.
If I touch anything cold,
I'll explode.
Apologies.
Don't go on
to expand your lore here.
That's not a thing.
Don't put out
blackmail material like that.
Time for the next segment!
Protect Her Dignity!
Lap-sama's 10 Questions!
This is Lap-chan's segment!
Why'd you say it like that?
You said dignity kinda trembly.
Introduction, please!
I'm the Founder of Secret Society holoX.
In other words, I have to play
a proper mysterious figure flawlessly.
However, it feels like
I'm losing my dignity each
passing day since I debuted.
You never had that to begin with.
I'm just reading this out.
I'm only saying this
'cause it's in the script.
I've lost no dignity whatsoever.
(Her view)
Stop mentioning the script.
With that said,
I've prepared a segment
that'll help me regain my dignity
as the Founder of holoX!
First off, please look at this.
Enough with the stiff-sounding recital.
What I Want to Eat Right Now
Hamburg steak
Miso soup
Stew
Yokan
Shortcake
Omurice
Fried chicken
Stuffed peppers
Takoyaki
Gyoza
"What I want to eat."
What's this?
I see yokan.
Yeah, I like yokan.
In this segment,
Secret society
hololive Production
Shark
Wolf
Orca
Bodyguard
Crow
I will pick one of the topics on the board
hololive Production
and both of you will have to guess
Has to do
with light blue?
An animal?
which one I picked by
asking me Yes or No questions.
Sounds fun!
It does.
And, of course, you can't ask me
direct questions about the topics.
What I Want to Eat Right Now
Hamburg steak
Miso soup
Stew
Yokan
Shortcake
Omurice
Fried chicken
Stuffed peppers
Takoyaki
Gyoza
Okay.
So nothing like, "Is it this one?"
Right. You can't do that.
Just yes or no questions.
Okay so, here's
an important change I added.
An important change? Go ahead.
So last time,
I allowed five questions
per person for a total of ten.
But it was just
too super-duper easy,
so now you may only ask
up to five questions per topic.
New rule:
Only up to five questions per topic.
What?!
Okay...
That's not fair!
That's not fair is what that is!
No, it's fine.
Because I am the law!
But you said ten...
I see, I see.
What I Want to Eat Right Now
Hamburg steak
Miso soup
Stew
Yokan
Shortcake
Omurice
Fried chicken
Stuffed peppers
Takoyaki
Gyoza
But you said we could
ask ten questions to you.
Got a problem?
Don't fret the small things.
Now it's time for the first question!
Change the graphic, then!
Now, the two of you,
please ask me your five questions!
Okay, I'll start.
My question is...
Does it have vegetables in it?
Wait, that was too easy.
I should have
narrowed it down more.
Actually, I think
you did that pretty well.
Really?
Yeah.
Now me.
My question is...
Does it go well with Japanese tea?
Oh, nice!
It's absolutely that one.
Yokan
But we can still ask
three more questions.
Three more.
Okay, then...
My question is...
Is it brown?
Is it one of Haato-senpai's
favorite foods, too?
I think we've got it.
Maybe we should move on
to another one now?
What should we do, Lui-chan?
May I, then?
Sure.
So this food...
During your debut, did you say
you wanted me to make it for you?
What?!
Huh?
It's a whole new ballgame!
That it is.
Or, maybe the person saying
it goes well with Japanese tea
is just really weird in the head?
Hey, what the heck
you talkin' about?
They totally go well together!
No more questions!
I got it!
What I Want to Eat Right Now
Hamburg steak
Miso soup
Stew
Yokan
Shortcake
Omurice
Fried chicken
Stuffed peppers
Takoyaki
Gyoza
That's it.
But does Haato-senpai like it?
It just might be that one.
Hold on! Hold on!
Thinking time is over!
She didn't ask for it...
You two!
It's time for you to reveal your guess
for which food I'm thinking of!
I know it.
Starting with the XO.
Okay!
The food that La+ is thinking of is...
fried chicken!
Hmhmhm.
And you, Haato-san?
Gyoza.
Don't gyoza have vegetables in them?
Does it have vegetables in it?
She forgot her own question.
The answer is...
fried chicken!
Yay!
Seriously?
So that means the (last) question
was a really good one!
Vegetables!
That's right. If it weren't
for that last question...
I would have went with yokan.
That was really misleading of you.
You two were the ones
asking the questions, you know!
Shall we do another one?
What I Want to Eat Right Now
Hamburg steak
Miso soup
Stew
Yokan
Shortcake
Omurice
Fried chicken
Stuffed peppers
Takoyaki
Gyoza
Since we went with fried chicken
for what I want to eat right now,
we'll make this one,
"What I want to eat for dinner tonight."
Okay.
Go ahead and ask away.
My question is...
Is it brown?
Why brown?
Do you have to get
that question in or something?!
Brown...
Oh, it is.
Could be brown
Hamburg steak
Stew
Fried chicken
Shortcake
Takoyaki
Miso soup
Yokan
Omurice
Stuffed peppers
Gyoza
There are quite a few
brown things, though.
Wait a sec...
I'm glad I picked this one!
Okay!
Is it a beverage?
Oh...
Not a beverage.
Do you cook it?
Wait, that's still a lot.
Could be cooked
Hamburg steak
Stew
Fried chicken
Shortcake
Takoyaki
Miso soup
Yokan
Omurice
Stuffed peppers
Gyoza
The heck?
My question is...
Does it use horizontal writing?
Is it written with katakana?
I've got it.
Have you now?
Yeah, I think I've got it.
Is it yellow?
She told you that it was brown!
I got it.
I screwed up again!
Why'd you ask that when—
This sucks!
I said it was brown!
I messed up!
You guys haven't really
narrowed it down.
What I Want to Eat Right Now
Hamburg steak
Miso soup
Stew
Yokan
Shortcake
Omurice
Fried chicken
Stuffed peppers
Takoyaki
Gyoza
No, I got it.
But which one is it?
Lui's guesses
I gotta pick one.
That one...
I forgot!
You mentioned yellow, but...
Hey!
Hey, hey!
Which is it?!
And she likes
both of these quite a bit,
so there's not much
difference there.
But you're eating it today, right?
You're eating it today?
I want to eat it tonight.
Okay.
So Haato-san, what is it?
Hamburg steak.
Hamburg steak, okay.
XO, what is it?
Hamburg steak.
You're thinking you wanted to make stuffed peppers today, but that you probably won't.
So if you order delivery,
you'll probably go for Hamburg steak.
So Hamburg steak.
Now that's metagaming.
A guess based on
the Society's kitchen status.
Shall I announce the answer?
Please.
What I want to eat today is...
Ta-dah!
Hamburg steak.
Well, yeah.
Yep, this one's Hamburg steak.
Woo-hoo!
You were deciding between
that and omurice, weren't you?
Oh, how'd you know?
If it's about you and food, I know.
Mhm.
Don't get all embarrassed.
No, I was just wondering
how you knew.
What a mood we've got in here now!
Sorry about that.
We're Founder and XO after all.
Parent-child bond
Sorry 'bout that.
Time for our next segment!
Teach Us, Lui-nee!
Hot-blooded Talk Seminar!
Yay!
Yay.
This is Lui-chan's segment!
No, wait.
Neruneruneru-Lu—
Lui-neruneruneru's segment!
What a pain!
Please explain for us!
Okay!
I, Takane Lui, a former
top-ranked businesswoman in Japan,
will teach you communication skills
with wide-ranging use
from business to just talking with friends.
With this segment,
hololive's communication abilities
will go through the roof!
The heck, you saying I can't communicate?
Well, you can't.
Hey, don't say that I can't!
What to say when you oversleep
and break a date with your friend.
Instructor
I'm going to throw out a situation,
and we'll test whether you can
give the best response to it.
As this is introductory,
I'll be giving you
the simplest situation:
One involving
communicating with your friends.
F-Friends...?
Yes.
F-Friends...
Friends?
Frien—...
Or hololive members.
Go ahead and think of
this situation like talking to them.
Gotcha.
Now then, please take a look at this.
How to invite someone to hang out
with you for the first time.
Okay.
In our case, it'd be like
how to invite another member whom
you've never collaborated with for one.
Okay, I see.
Got it.
And in everyone else's case,
how would you invite someone
to hang out with you for the first time?
Please think about it!
Okay.
Thinking time...
Starts now!
Yay!
Write it down.
Okay, okay.
I should, too.
Oh, the right answer?
Right, you have to give us an example.
Yes, the answer.
But I feel like...
I'm gonna give a better
answer than Takane Lui.
The heck you sayin'?
Mine's gonna be the best, of course!
Mine will be, of course!
There are many correct answers.
There are plenty of good ways to do it.
If I think that your answer is good,
then it'll be correct.
I'm seeing a future
of correct answers!
A future of correct answers?
You're quite confident!
Are you both ready?
Yes.
Yeah.
Thinking time is over!
Now let's look at
each of your answers.
Let's start with the answer from
the very confident Haato-senpai.
How to invite someone to hang out
with you for the first time.
Haato-sama's method.
In 3, 2, 1...
Go!
Good day to you!
Are you looking to
spend some time with me?
I would not protest!
How was that?
Goodbye friendship.
Pretty rough.
Why?! Why?!
You're really... really...
Why?!
You're really acting like
you're better than them!
I'm already fully aware that
everybody wants to hang out with me!
You're way too overconfident!
I can't believe you thought
that'd be a passing answer.
Really.
Let's look to La+'s answer
as an example, then.
Haato-san, please take a look.
La+'s invitation method
in 3, 2, 1...
Go!
Oh... hello?
Look out your window.
Get in.
Company car
This is the way.
Eww!
You're not thinking about
your friend's situation at all.
Indeed.
But wouldn't they be happy
to see me there so suddenly?
Maybe if it's a situation
where they already like you a lot.
I mean...
everyone loves me.
Okay, um...
how do you two want to do this?
Do you want points or like,
"I liked this part," or something?
Should I hand out points?
Well, uh, how about a Benz?
Company car
Benz...
I think it should be this
"good day to you" stuff.
Like based on how well it sounds.
How well it sounds?
The wording and stuff?
I mean, look at "get in."
That's no good!
I see.
Neither is "I would not protest!"
I'm going to judge by good or bad.
And I'd say both of them...
Well, they're bad.
What, why?
What?
Because one's acting
like you're above them,
and one's not caring about
their friend's situation at all.
They should match
their situation to mine!
At that point, it's already too late!
Now for my example answer.
I'll show my own answer
to this question.
Here's my answer.
Show me.
I want to OO with you, OO-san.
What do you think?
That's so ordinary!
There's a point to this!
For example:
"I want to play this game
with you, Haato-senpai."
I could say that.
And this will get across
the feelings that I have
of wanting to be friendly with,
to hang out with Haato-senpai.
Uh-huh.
Furthermore,
Point
Calling a person by their name
saying someone's name
gives them a feeling of closeness,
and it's the basics of the basics
of communication.
The more you call someone
by their name,
the more they'll start to like you.
Instructor!
Yes?
Instructor!!
I came up with something
from your example!
Oh? What is it?
I want to play Lap-chan with you,
Lui-san!
The heck are you talking about?
Yeah, what?
Instructor!
Yes?
What is it?
Can I say one
based on your example, too?
Go ahead.
Okay!
Hello?
Haato?
Look out your window.
Get in.
Company car
No way!
Oh, come on!
Isn't this the "so-called" way to do it?!
There you have it.
What did you think?
I had fun!
I feel like I learned something.
You had fun?
You learned something?
I feel like I've made more friends.
More?
Well, not like you two
had any to start with.
Yeah, I do?!
Now that your
communicative ability has risen,
I'd like to end the segment here.
We're looking for more situations
that you want to see next time!
#ルイ姉さトーク塾
Please tweet them with
the hashtag Lui-nee's Talk Seminar!
Thank you!
Thank you.
And that's all for "Teach Us, Lui-nee!
Hot-blooded Talk Seminar!"
Seems hard to say.
We've finally reached the wrap-up point.
This is the end of today's broadcast.
Your thoughts?
I really learned something.
You say you learned something,
but you're only talking
about the last segment!
But like, it was nice because this
grouping of members feels fresh.
You're right!
True!
Let's all do a collab together.
Yay!
You can make me some food.
I will!
Then we can chew the fat.
Chew the fat?!
You're not some backwater country
chick! Don't say "chew the fat"!
What happened to
being a high-class girl?
I just wanted to try using it.
If you join the official fan club,
you'll be able to view the full VODs
from all of holo's Bonjour broadcasts,
so please take a look!
And now for an important announcement.
This month, for fan club members only,
we will be distributing a calendar wallpaper.
This month features Yukihana Lamy,
Momosuzu Nene, Shishiro Botan, and Omaru Polka.
We offer a new calendar every month,
so please join to get yours!
Dang, I want that!
Wow.
Those are their stage outfits.
Next time, Lap-chan will be the host.
Give it your best shot.
Yeah, I'll give it a go, I guess.
A go, huh.
But now you're leaving, Haato-san!
Oh, yeah.
Don't cry, okay?
Aww, are you gonna miss me?
I ain't cryin'.
Hey!
We're gonna interact
from now on, too.
Yeah, we'll play VALORANT.
Will you really?
I will!
We good?
You two are kinda goin' at it.
Hey, you. Get in.
Haato. Play VALORANT with me.
Yeah?
Leaving aside that answer for now,
Good.
please watch next time as well!
Why?!
This has been Akai Haato,
La+ Darknesss,
and Takane Lui!
See you next time!
Farewell.
Farewell!