Kouban!
Wrong!
Houmuru!
Taeru!
Wrong!
Let's see you do better!
She's getting full of herself!
A school where
kanji ability is everything...
Students of hololive Kanji Academy...
Please state your favorite kanji
when we take attendance.
My favorite kanji is
kokoro (heart).
I'm Roboco!
The Underworld's
vampire prodigy, Yozora Mel!
My favorite kanji is...
*smile*
The e from egao (smile).
The e from egao?!
I'm Shishiro Botan.
My favorite kanji is
yasumu, from kyuujitsu (day off).
I like that one too!
I want one of those!
Let's decide on the order for today...
We'll be doing a kanji reading test.
It's a pop quiz!
Wah!
A pop quiz!
The questions range from
about middle school level,
all the way up to Level 1
(most difficult) of the Kanji Kentei test.
I'm sure you can all handle
Level 1 just fine though, right?
Yeah. We can, right?
It's like this segment
was made for me!
I am a prodigy after all.
This'll be a piece of cake.
Piece of cake?
Who wants to start then?
Nobody wants to go first!
What happened to
all that confidence?
I will go first then.
You will?
You have 30 seconds.
Read as many kanji
correctly as you can.
Start the test!
Kyounai.
Wrong.
She got the first one wrong!
K-Kutsui.
Wrong.
Huh?
Tanren.
That's right!
Next!
Tehazu.
Correct.
Next!
Moteasobu.
Correct!
Next, next!
Onbin!
Correct.
Muko!
Correct! Good stuff!
Yay!
Houmuru.
Wrong.
Kankitsu.
Correct.
And that's time!
Jibore!
Unubore!
30 seconds is really short!
That went by so quickly.
And the last one was actually wrong!
So, that was 6 correct answers.
30 seconds really is quite short.
It really is!
It is!
It's so short!
Let's look at the ones you got wrong.
What did you say this was?
How do you read this?
Did you say kutsui?
Yeah. She said kutsui.
This is katajikenai.
Eh?!
That's so hard!
I knew it though, of course.
Oh, you did?
What did you read this as?
Houmuru.
This is minoru.
Minoru?
Minoru!
Oh, so it's minoru!
She probably got houmuru because
the second character is part of houjou?
That makes sense.
Yeah, yeah!
At least someone gets me!♥
So, you got 6 questions right.
That's pretty good!
That's decent, right?
Let's see you do better!
She's getting cocky!
Who's going next?
I might go next.
I'll let you go first then.
Alright then, start the test!
Hanyou.
Correct!
Huh?
Isoku?
Wrong.
Kamaboko.
Correct.
Nisshoku.
Kaki.
Correct.
What's this again?
Ikkin?
That's correct!
Onoono.
Correct.
Kotou.
Wow! Correct!
Omomuku.
Omomuku is correct.
S-Seppan.
Correct!
And that's time!
Well, that was quite...
Oh, Robocosan?
You got that many correct...?
Did I beat her?
That was 9 correct answers!
Yaaay!
You didn't get many wrong,
but let's look over the ones you did.
Me, me!
Is this seku?
That's right! Seku is correct!
Seku!
Seku?
Ah, it was!
Yes, it is.
Now that I've calmed down a bit,
I actually know them.
Yeah. It's hard when the clock's ticking...
Keeping your cool is important, isn't it?
Yeah.
It sure is.
Isn't it pretty amazing
that you knew kamaboko?
Oh yeah, I knew that.
Wow!
Mel, did you know it too?
Err... Of course I did?
And so, it's Mel-san's turn now.
Start the test!
Junshu.
Junshu is correct.
Yay!
Bou...
Bou...bai?
Wrong.
Good work, MelMel!
R-Ronu?
Wrong.
Sabishii.
Correct.
Mohou...
Mohouhin.
Correct.
Huh?
She was surprised it was right.
Kyokusha.
Wrong.
Haijiru.
And that's time!
Mel-san's result is
3 correct answers.
Mel-chan!
I knew you could do it!
Why were you expecting me
to do badly?!
This one is actually age-something.
Age?
Agetamau?
Agetamau? That sounds cute.
It's actually agetsurau.
Have you seen this word before?
What's that?!
No idea!
Never seen it.
It means to debate or denounce something.
I'll start using it!
You're going to start using it?!
So, this one...
I thought you'd say haijiru
so I jumped the gun and said "wrong" early.
This is aku (soup scum).
That's correct!
Really?!
That's right.
As expected of someone who cooks!
Yeah. I've started cooking!
To be honest, I think you all
might need supplementary kanji lessons.
But, Mel + Mel = Roboco
and Mel x Mel = Botan.
And that's what the problem is!
This time, we'd like Botan
to get a double-digit score,
and for the other two
to beat their personal bests.
I'm going for 1st place!
Alright then, start the test!
Kippou.
Correct.
What's this?!
What's this again?
Ah, I don't know... Masu?
Wrong!
What's this again?
Uru-Uruoi?
Ah... Wrong!
That was hard, though.
It was urei! Taki.
Taki is correct.
Hedatari.
Correct.
Zu... Imaru?
That's wrong!
Uh... Natsuin?
Correct.
Tabi.
Correct!
And that's time!
Ketsujo.
Ah, let's include ketsujo
as well then.
Thanks!
So, Botan got 6 answers correct.
That was a total of 6 correct answers.
Thank you!
A little lower than before!
Same as Roboco-chan before.
These supplementary lessons might
actually be more difficult than before.
That looked really hard.
Don't make the
supplementary lessons harder!
So what was this actually?
Isn't it sakana?
It's not sakana!
It's yagura!
Ah, it is yagura!
I've seen this before!
Yeah, I've seen it before too.
And this one, isn't this
actually todomaru?
Todomaru is correct.
I do actually know the answers,
but when the clock's ticking, I panic.
Start the test!
Zo... Zo-ku?
Wrong!
Oh no!
Keep smiling!
Ah... Itamu?
W-Wrong!
You can do it!
Kakyou... I think?
That's correct!
Yukikuzure.
Wrong.
G-Gekkyoku.
T-Tori... Torizoku.
Wrong!
And that's time!
Mel-chan...
Torizoku...
That was...
1 correct answer!
Ah... Only 1...
Good work! You got 1!
Yeah, good job getting 1!
Yeah. It's important to be positive!
Yeah!
I know this one!
What's this one?
Isn't this azamuku?
I don't think so?
One side is different.
It's not.
It's not azamuku.
You were so confident,
but you were wrong!
That's embarrassing!
It's not!
Nageku.
Nageku is correct!
It's nageku.
You said torizoku
for this one, didn't you?
It sounds kind of strong.
I know this one!
If you look here...
Oh, what is it?
Ika (squid).
Yes. It's ika.
This is ika?!
I've seen this before!
That's not even a bird!
The first kanji isn't actually
tori (bird).
It's missing a line here.
True!
So...
You're tricking me again,
aren't you?
I never tricked you!
I've figured out a sure-win strategy.
A sure-win strategy?
You just have to keep on answering.
Ah, you're going
to answer really quickly...?
So, like, "quantity over quality"?
Yeah.
I'm overclocking my memory right now.
I've got this.
Alright then, start the test!
Kouban!
Wrong!
Houmuru!
Taeru!
Wrong!
Kyoutani!
Shouin!
Wrong!
Miko!
That's right!
Kuzu!
Wrong!
Ichibou.
Tateru!
Wrong!
Sohou.
Taimatta!
Wrong!
Kenage!
That's right!
Time's up.
Robocosan,
you got 2 answers correct!
Aah!
That was close...
Weren't you going to win?
This one here...
Houmuru.
It's not.
Habikoru.
That's right! It's habikoru.
I know this one.
You're really good at this, Botan-san!
This is wakimaeru.
Wakimaeru is right!
You kind of seem like
a teacher and students now.
That's not how it's meant to be.
This one is pretty hard.
I might actually know this one.
Ah, you do?
What is it?
I think it's...
Shibashiba?
That's right!
Master!
Apparently, it's a Level 1 question
on the Kanji Kentei test.
Really?
Sorry guys, I made it to Level 1!
Dammit!
Results
So, our top scorer...
Our kanji elite is Shishiro Botan-san!
Congratulations!
Yay!
Congrats!
Congratulations!
But, like, it was pretty fun going over
the ones I actually knew after the test.
And it was pretty fun
discovering new kanji as well.
And our other two students...
I will endeavor to study lots
and not neglect my kanji.
What a good girl!
Roboco will do her best
to study diligently.
I see!
Will you really, though?
If you enjoyed this video,
please like it, and subscribe
to the official hololive channel,
as well as the channels of
everyone here on the show today.
That's it for today.
See you next time!
See you!
Starring
Robocosan
Yozora Mel
Shishiro Botan
hololive Kanji Academy was
brought to you by Robocosan...
...Yozora Mel, and...
...Shishiro Botan.