AyaFubuMi - Hozukibiyori
Lyrics & Composition: Ogura Asuka
All Instruments & Programming: Ogura Asuka
Mix: Masahiro Kawata
Movie: Pokage
The sinking twilight glows on the hills
shizumu akanebi somaru sakamichi
My happiness welling up as the dew falls
tsutau shizuku ni ureshisa nijimu
With the sound of nightfall drawing near
yoru no tobari no chikazuku oto ni
You let a single excited shout out
hashaida kimi no koe hitotsu
To ring through the air
sora ni hibiita
Waiting for you before the fox
inari no mae de machiawase
Passing under the rows of gates
tsuranaru torii kugurinuke
The sweet scent of the lantern fruit
hoozuki no amai kaze
Wafted through my heart
mune o surinuketeku
"Let's dance"
"odorou yo"
Turn, turn, and clap your hands
maware maware te o tataite hora
Do as the others do and join the ring
miyoumimane de wa ni natte
Turn with the stuttering movements
gikochinai furitsuke ni mau
Sleeves fluttering
sode wa hirahira
Dance, dance, and join your hands
odore odore te o toriatte
With cheeks glowing flushed
joukishita hoo botaniro
The sound of the drum ringing in the air
narihibiku taiko no oto ni
My red fruit skipped with the beat
akai kajitsu hajiketa
Perhaps you noticed that it did?
kimi ni kizukareta ka na?
The roar of the crowd, the burning bonfire
hibiku zawameki moyuru kagaribi
I will send my desire with my wavering feelings
yuragu kimochi ni omoi noseyou
As the music of the festival grew distant
matsuri bayashi ga toonoku oto ni
The sight of the Dog Star hiding behind the clouds
tenrou no hoshi no kumogakure
Struck me in the heart
mune o tsutsuita
The moon is hazy tonight
koyoi sora ni wa oborozuki
I hid my heart in the cloud
kasunda kokoro gomakashita
In a fleeting moment's wavering
tamayura ni tayutaite
As it passed through my heart
mune o surinuketara
"Close your eyes"
"me o tojite"
Sleep, sleep, consciousness is transparent
nemure nemure ishiki wa toumei
My desire that grew with each passing night
hitoyo hitoyo ni tsunoru sou
The flowers lit by the moonlight
tsuki akari terasu hanabira
Fall fluttering
chiru wa harahara
Cry, cry, drops falling from above
naite naite nagaruru wa shizuku
An evening shower before the bride-taking
yomeiri mae no sayo shigure
The fickle weather outside the umbrella
kasa no soto kitsune biyori ni
Disguised the shower into my sleeve
sode no shigure kakushita
So that you would not notice
kimi ni kizukarenai youni
The heavenly winds blow the clouds on their path
amatsu kaze kumo no kayoiji
Along with the dreams seen with eyes closed
tozashi miyuru yume no manimani
So long have I longed for this
ikuseisou omoi kogareta
May this moment never end...
kono hitotoki ga taemasen youni...
With a drop, I wished
potsuri negau
Halt, halt, time, come to a halt
tomare tomare jikan yo tomare
Enjoy taking part in this dreamlike moment
yume no kokochi o goshoumiare
I sent with wolf smoke from fox fire
kitsunebi no noroshi ni noseta
My heart wavering
kokoro yurayura
Dance, dance, and join your hands
odore odore te o toriatte
Reflecting like water the cheerful steps
keikaina hochou mizukagami
With such happy processions of oni and spirits
shiawase no hyakkiyakou ni
Come memories such as these
tsuranaru omoidetachi
I wish you happiness tonight
koyoi kimi ni sachi are